Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Next, please.
Next!
Don't fool around
Okay
Did you hear what I said?
I want to document
our trip to America.
Next, please. Next.
How you doing?
Can I see your documents?
What is the purpose of your
visit to the United States?
Two weeks holiday.
Do you have
a return-trip ticket?
Excuse me. No photography
in the F.I.S. area.
Is he travelling with you?
Are you two together?
Yes.
Sir, come on up. Join us.
Is there a problem?
No. If you're together
I want to talk to you together.
-Can I see your documents?
-Sure.
Passport, please.
Are you related?
Yes. He's my friend.
You're a Czech national
and you're a Russian national.
How do you know one another?
We know each other from Prague.
-How long are you staying?
-Two weeks.
I'd like him to answer
for himself.
But he doesn't speak English.
No, sir.
I speakvery good English.
I'm here for movies.
For movies?
I don't understand.
When I was a boy,
I've seen at my school...
movie called
"It's Wonderful Life..."
directed by Frank Capra...
and ever since I just want
to come to United States...
Iand of the free,
home of the brave...
a country where anyone
can be anything.
Bullshit!
"Abandoned baby
in Times Square."
Come on,
it's too fucking soft.
It won't work,
and it won't get the numbers.
Are you suggesting that
we manufacture bad news?
It's what they tune us infor.
We're a tabloid show.
They tune infor rough stuff.
The net work's up
my pretty little ass to change.
Every lobbyist, mom,
and politician...
is screaming about
violence in prime time.
We've got to broaden the format.
Broaden the format.
The story they will run
is the one with the juice.
They want ratings
as much as I do.
If it bleeds, it leads.
What have you got?
Ride-along with Eddie Flemming.
-Fuck, again?!
-Cover of "People."
He is not new.
Eddie's a dear friend,
but we've done him to death.
No, this is good.
The psychiatrist
goes to trial tomorrow.
The ratings'll hit the roof.
What's Eddie doing?
He's staking out
a Jamaican serial killer.
That's good.
I don't want blood and guts!
Broaden the format!
I know they brought you in
to be the journalism cop--
-Excuse me!
-You're killing my show!
Don't forget,
Eddie's always good TV.
Not when he's drunk.
He's got a new cure for that.
-When?
-Tomorrow at lunch.
Ready, set.
Let's go.
Thrill of the hunt.
Look, Times square.
Just like the movies!
Don't speak Russian!
Why do I always have to
Speak to you in Czech?
Because I don't like your
ugly language, okay?
Taxi!
"Fuji colour...
"adjustable shutter speed...
"nightvision, infrared...
"black and white.
"Make your own movies."
Damn!
Watch where you're going!
Where'd that big guy go
with the video?
He stole my camera!
Stop that guy in the cab!
-Go! Go!
-Stop that guy in the cab!
Bryan,we're pulling up now.
This is important.
I need fresh footage for
the piece on Eddie tonight...
so come in fast on my signal
with the camera rolling.
You got it?
So what's Unique?
Not what, who. From Jamaica.
His girlfriend took too long
putting her make-up on.
They were late for a party.
-Stabbed her with a bottle.
-Jesus Christ.
That's unique. Shit.
He still went to the party.
Topfloor, back room.
Eddie, autograph, mon.
Phone number.
Why your picture not on this?
-Bounce.
-All right.
Yo, Unique.
5-0's on the way, bro.
-Cops?
-Let's go.
Love you too, man.
Who does he think Leon was?
It won't matter.
He'll hear the cops are coming
and just get out.
-Come on. Be quiet
-Right.
-Stand by.
-Standing by.
Eddie, are you gonna
be home tonight?
We're running
the Stephen Geller piece.
Again? You ran that fucking
thing a thousand times.
So what?
He's going to court tomorrow.
The psychiatrist's trial
is starting.
Ratings'll be through the roof.
Hey, get out.
Do me a favour.
Cut my interview out.
What for? Jesus Christ.
Are you getting shit
from downtown? Fuck them.
You're the only one
making big cases in this town.
I bring the big cases,
that brings the big news.
That stuff hurts
as much as it helps.
Get real jealous downtown.
Stay behind me.
Hope this fuck don't run.
My knees are killing me.
Be quiet. Get back.
Are you worried about my safety?
I'm touched.
Go! Get away!
Just keep them out of my way.
-You ready?
-Robert,we're ready.
You ready? Let's go.
Go on! Just get out!
Come on,you fucking guys!
Come in rolling!
What's your rush?
You going to a party?
What you chase me for?
You always leave your house
like that?
This not my bloody house!
-You live here?
-Me don't live here!
That sounds like
burglary to me, pal.
Eddie, any chance
we could get that again?
I didn't want to do it
in the first place.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Turn that fucking thing off!
Are you out of your mind?
Where the hell were you?
You two are a waste
of my goddamn life! Fuck!
No, Emil, get the position.
-What?
-First scene of my new movie.
Collecting our share
from the bankjob.
And...action.
Just a moment!
Who's there?
It's Emil.
How are you?
Glad to see you.
Olga said he didn't
know where you were.
If you are trying to hide,
You shouldn't write to her
with your return adress!
Beautiful necklace.
Effects. Video Effects.
It wasn't my fault
you two got caught.
I know.
Please, it's hisfault.
It's really hisfault.
Trying to get
the bank clerk's phone number.
How could I wait?
Hey, you didn't tell us
she was your wife!
That's why I didn't tell you!
Because of what you did!
Let'sforget all this shit!
Hang on. Calm down.
You know what?
Give me my money.
Emil,we spent it.
What?
Look at the way we live.
I'm a plumber.
Nice watch.
You think I'd be working
if I had money?
What's going on?
Just give me my money.
I'll helpyou.
You'll help me?
I get you a job.
A job?
The money is good.
A job as a plumber?
It's easy. It's good.
You think I came
to America to work?
No way.
We started over.
You can, too.
Emil, please.
I'm your friend.
I'm your friend--
Sorry.
It's my fault.
Emil, please--
Emil, put down the knife!
You spent all my money
while I was in prison?
You're telling me to get a job?
As a plumber,
fixing fucking toilets?!
Please, put down the knife!
-You're my friend!
-Yes, I am!
You're my best friend!
Please, put down the knife.
Emil, please.
Shut up!
She saw.
-What are you looking for?
-Her wallet, you idiot.
Daphne Handlova. Six-month visa.
Still here after two years.
She'll call the police.
She will!
She is illegal!
Turn that fucking
sick thing off!
Do as I say!
What are you looking for?
Ah, no!
Bohemian barbecue.
Man,what you got for me?
I don't have time
for this tonight.
Where the fuck you going?
Do yourself a favour
and get the hell outta here.
Gonna make me bust your ass?
I'm not telling you again.
This ain't a smart move.
Give me your fucking money--
You happy now?
Now you're under arrest.
-You the cops?
-Fire Department.
Firemen don't carry
no damn guns.
Guess again.
I'm an arson investigator.
We do everything cops do.
Yo, man, come on!
All right,
we're getting up on three.
One, two, three.
Why don't you
let a brother off, man?
No harm, nofoul.
My bad, dawg.
What's up, man? Come on!
-Put your hand up there.
-What you gonna do?
-Where you going?
-To a fire.
-Hell, no!
-I'll send a cop back!
Oh, hell, mother fucker!
You can't leave me hand cuffed
to no goddamn tree!
Some freak'll come up
in here and stab me, man!
Make sure EMS is standing by.
We'll have to take
the bodies out pretty soon.
Let's get the fourth winches
to the front of the building.
Chief, you first due?
Yeah. I got two roasts
up on the top floor.
You don't have to investigate
because Homicide's here.
Homicide?
Who said they could go up there?
I didn't make this
a crime scene yet.
-It's Eddie Flemming.
-Fuck him.
Jordy, where you been?
We got a celebrity.
I heard.
Who the hell let him up there?
Don't know. Think Eddie'll
give me his autograph?
Maybe he'll give you
a kiss, too.
-Hey, Cap.
-Bobby.
Stairs are soggy.
-Hey, Eddie.
-What?
Looks to me,
from the 69 position...
that they were doing each other.
They must've been
smoking something...
and were so wacked
out of their heads...
that they got careless,
lit up the mattress...
and set themselves onfire.
I don't know.
We got the experts here.
Show them what you found?
Hope you don't mind, guys.
We thought maybe
you needed some help.
Not at all.
Detective? Bobby Korfin.
-How you doing, Bobby?
-My Uncle Tony worked with you.
Detective,you mind
putting that cigar out?
-Trying to pick up a scent.
-Sorry.
I'm glad you guys
got it allfigured out...
but you mind if we go
through our routine?
Give us something to do.
We don't mind.
-No, certainly.
-Appreciate it.
-Be our guest.
-Thanks.
Talk about smoking after sex.
We got a fast-burning fire.
We got some good
low patterns down here.
-Mouth's clean.
-Clean?
So let me get this straight...
you think a couple of crackheads
burned themselves up?
That's what it looks like to me.
While they're burning up...
they're still going down
on one another?
Gotta hand it to them.
I guess some people have
their priorities straight.
I guess they do.
Flammable.
Thank you.
-What's that?
-Evidence.
Of a homicide.
-You know what that is?
-No,what?
Camello,
punch a hole in the corner.
I want to look at the floor.
They have no soot
in their mouths...
which means they weren't
breathing before the fire...
and this little piece
of cloth...
means they were doused
in a flammable liquid...
and then positioned
like this on the bed.
To the untrained eye,
it looks like an accident.
No offence.
What's he looking for?
He's looking for a timer.
Here you go.
Big double homicide.
Good.
Just take some deep breaths.
Did you see the look
on Eddie'sface...
when you handed him
that timer?
Damn, I wish
I had a picture of him.
He knew all along, though.
What?
Why do you think
he was so quiet?
He was testing us.
You think so?
Detective,
does it look like a murder?
We haven't determined
the exact cause of death yet.
There's a lot of answers
we still haven't got.
-How many victims?
-Two bodies.
-Have you identified them?
-Not positively.
Is it drug-related?
We don't know the cause
of the fire or the deaths.
We get them all,
we'll let you know.
What's this in your hand?
Evidence?
This is something
we found on the scene.
Whether it's evidence or not
has yet to be determined.
-Thank you, Detective.
-You're welcome.
See you.
Do you see her?
Who?
There was a woman in the crowd.
She looked scared.
Looked like
she wanted to talk to us.
Shit.
Get a blanket.
Now here you come.
It's about fucking time.
What the hell happened to you?
She stripped me, man.
A bag lady.
Stripped all my clothes off.
Grabbing me in my nuts.
It was disgusting.
Consider yourself lucky.
I won't lock you up.
You're free to go.
Get the hell outta here.
A dog pissed on me, man!
You violated my civil rights.
We got you for robbery one.
Take a walk.
So, before you slept with her...
with your own son's wife...
did you take even a second to
think about the consequences?
I take full responsibility
for sleeping with her.
I had very low self-esteem.
I had to compete with somebody.
It happened to be my son.
You're blaming this
on low self-esteem?
I had a lot of
behavioural disorders.
A behavioural disorder
and low self-esteem...
makes you have sex
with your son's wife?
It's not all hisfault.
No, that's true.
What about your wife?
He's ignored me for months.
I had no one around.
I didn't think that
he loved me anymore.
How could somebody
who loved somebody do that?
That's the lowest thing
you could ever possibly do.
"Self-esteem."
"Low self-esteem."
Turn off the camera.
I'm not filming anything.
Turn off the fucking camera!
I'm watching Milos die.
Turn it off!
Let go.
Don't break it! Don't break it!
How do you erase it?
I'll do it! I'll do it!
Get rid of it!
Don't speak to me in Russian.
You got it?
Erase it! Erase it now!
Just erase it!
Daphne Handlova.
What's this?
"Worldly Escorts."
"Worldly." What is it?
What is it?
I'm serious.
Get on your knees.
Look me in the eyes
and tell me you're sorry.
Let me see if I believe you.
I'm very sorry
for what I've done.
I promise
I'll never do it again.
How come we don't believe you?
Are you looking
for companionship?
Yes. I'm homesick.
I can set you up
with a realfine date.
Do you have Eastern European
girl, Czech girl?
-Of course.
-Askfor Russian girl.
Whatever you want.
As a matter off act...
I have a lovely
Czech girl right here.
Send her. I take her.
What's your address?
-Can you forgive him?
-Give me a hug.
Wait a minute. Hold on.
That's a good start there.
Now that you know Eddie,
maybe he'll put you...
in the next movie about him.
You think so?
You can play his wife.
What's up, Chief?
What the hell is that?
What is that in your hand?
Evidence?
This is something
we found on the scene.
Whether it's evidence or not,
we're not sure.
You gave Eddie Flemming
the evidence?
Who did cause and origin?
Chief,who do you think did?
We did.
Then why didn't you
talk to the reporter?
Because we got more
important things to do...
Iike finding out who did it.
Really?
Don't you guys understand?
It is all about image.
The better we look,
the more money I get to pay you.
Good evening.
I'm Robert Hawkins...
and this is "Top Story."
Tonight we have an exclusive
interview with Stephen Geller...
who horrified the nation
two years ago...
when he murdered three clerks
in a Manhattan shoe store.
But now, Mr Geller's claim...
spoken softly
and articulately...
is that he is the victim.
Hard to believe. Watch.
These people died...
because of the criminal actions
of my psychiatrist.
He didn't insist
that I stay on my medication.
So you feel absolutely
no responsibility...
for killing these people?
It was my finger
that pulled the trigger...
but morally,
I'm not responsible.
My psychiatrist
knew what I was capable of.
How can I know?
I'm not a doctor.
That seems very savvy
for a man who's beenfound...
mentally incompetent
to stand trial.
I'm a victim here, too.
My life has been
permanently disrupted.
Permanently disrupted?
Hasn't this "incident,"
as you call it...
jump-started your career
as an artist?
Isn't there a movie
in the works?
We're in negotiations.
That's correct.
Doesn't the "Son of Sam" Iaw
prohibit convicted criminals...
from profiting
from their crimes?
It doesn't apply to me
because I'm not a criminal.
I wasn't convicted.
I wasfound to be
temporarily insane.
I love America.
No one is responsible
for what they do.
-Get in the bathroom.
-We'll fuck her first.
-Get in.
-Fuck her first, right?
Stay there! Shut up!
I'm Honey
from Worldly Escorts.
You called us?
And how are you tonight?
Where's the Czech girl?
Baby, I'm whatever
you want me to be.
I'm a little schoolgirl,
I'm Mommy, I'm a Czech girl.
Now, I like to get business
out of the way...
before we get down
to pleasure...
so can you put the money
on the dresser?
But I need the Czech girl.
Daphne. You know her?
It's an outcall service
run from a loft.
I don't know the other girls.
Aren't you getting undressed?
Where's the escort service?
That's confidential.
Can you put the money
on the dresser, please?
Yes. Sure.
Thank you.
I'd like to talkwith the person
who runs the service.
Can you give me her address?
Do we have a problem here?
Good. There's no reasonfor us
to have a problem.
I'm gonna make you
feel real good.
Sorry, no smoking.
When I'm through with you...
you won't even remember
the Czech girl.
Listen to me.
I don't want sex.
Just give me the address,
please.
Look, I don't give a shit
if you want sex or not...
but you're paying for my time.
Just listen to me.
Give me the address,
and then you can go.
What are you doing?
Listen to me.
You got to help me!
Just calm down
and listen to me.
Give me the fucking address,
and then you go!
Please,you got to help me.
I need your help!
All right! OK!
It's in my purse. No!
Shit! God!
Help me!
No! Help me!
No! God! Someone!
Please help!
No! Help!
What really stood out
about this girl were her eyes.
She had the most amazing huge
blue eyes you've ever seen.
Just absolutely beautiful.
How long they been
living in your building?
Fouryears.
I'll give you a call as soon
as we know something more.
-What do you got?
-Milos and Tamina Karlova.
They were quiet
and kept to themselves.
Landlord don't know
who your girl is.
OK if I smoke?
It's your crime scene now.
Do whateveryou want.
Did you watch the news?
I must have missed it.
Just so you know...
I gave you guys all the credit.
Well,just so you know...
I don't really care
about that stuff.
Why should you?
I don't even watch TV.
Good. Good.
That's commendable.
You get a report from the M.E.?
Sure did.
I want to ask you something.
You got a problem with me?
If you showed up and found me
stepping on your crime scene...
and remember, it was
my crime scene yesterday...
it might piss you off, too.
What about the report?
You were right.
Both dead before the fire.
The man was stabbed so hard...
the killer broke off the tip
of the knife in his spine.
That usually indicates
something pretty personal.
Super said
he's seen her before...
but she didn't live here.
Prettiest suspect
I've had in a while.
I don't know if she has
anything to do with this.
I saw her outside
after the fire...
and thought maybe
it was a lead.
Thought maybe
she saw something.
Why would they
have taken the trouble...
to position the bodies
like that?
Maybe they're trying
to send somebody a message.
Burial rites are very serious
in Eastern Europe.
Could be to humiliate them.
How do you know all this?
My folks were from Poland.
Where?
You sure it was a knife?
Really?
There was another murder on...
8th Avenue in a hotel.
A stabbing.
Clerk said
a Russian rented the room.
Mind if I go along with you?
This isn't afire.
There's nothing foryou to do.
I'll watch you.
Maybe I'll learn something.
This isn't
homicide school, kid.
But if you want to help,
take that.
What's this?
The matching set
for the murder weapon.
This is our second day
in America.
First day was very exciting...
full of thrills and chills.
Over here is the co-star
of my new movie.
My partner Emil.
Who's this?
That is New York'sfinest.
That's his case.
Is that all you want?
Do you know how much killer
getsfor movie rights?
It says in there
he wants a million.
A million?
You're kidding.
The killer gets million dollars
for television interview?
It pays to be a killer
in this country.
-Just taking a bath.
-Any ID?
-P.D. only.
-He's OK.
We still got
to run some prints.
This kid here from Midtown
caught the case.
How you doing?
Tommy Cullen.
It's a pleasure
tofinally meet you.
This is what we got.
Figure she's a prostitute.
Judging from the defence wounds
on her arms and hands...
she was really fighting
for her life.
The room was registered
to a Frank Capra.
-Who said this guy's Russian?
-The clerk.
Check the switchboard.
See what calls went out.
I'm on it.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
We're waiting on the M.E.
tofind out if she was raped.
We got a shitload
of prints here...
but in this joint,
they could be anybody's.
Anybody take a piss lately?
Check the toilet seat.
Only one guy checked in?
You want to go
to homicide school?
Let me show you something.
The killer was standing
over there, slashing her.
At the point of death,
the heart stops beating...
so you don't bleed anymore.
See these two marks?
Somebody was over here while
the killer was stabbing her.
What kind of knife you think
we're talking about here?
If you look at the marks
on the wall over here...
they're wide,
but notvery deep.
This was not your everyday
kitchen or pocketknife.
What if the tipwas broken off?
Could be. Then we'd probably
find it somewhere.
I thinkwe already found it.
There was only one phone call
made last night.
I dialled it,
and it was an escort service.
-You identify yourself?
-I'm new, not stupid.
Call communications.
Get an address on that number.
-Good work.
-Thanks.
So you gonna head over
to the escort service?
I'll let you know what happens.
Eddie, you the man, bro!
Eddie, this is ridiculous.
If I ride along with you,
we could talk over the case.
Tell you what.
I'll bounce this coin.
If you win,you come with me.
If you don't win,
you don't come with me.
Fair enough?
All right, but I call it.
You call it.
-Tails.
-Heads. You lose.
That's bullshit.
I didn't get to see.
Go ahead. I'll call it.
Heads.
See? You lost twice.
See you around.
Come on.
All right.
That supposed to be funny?
Yeah, come on.
I was just joking.
Thanks for letting me
come along.
No problem. Souvenir.
Two heads.
Better than one.
Police. We just want to
ask you some questions.
Do you have a warrant?
We're not looking
to bust you, ma'am.
It's Detective Eddie Flemming
from Homicide.
Just open the door.
We want to talk.
My God,what an honour.
Rose Hearn.
Please come in.
I just saw you on television.
You look better in real life.
Just give me one second.
So,what can I help
you with, Detective?
We don't have any ID yet...
but we found one of your girls
at the King Edward Hotel.
What?
Did you send anybody over there?
Yeah. Honey.
She's one of my girls.
She's dead?
I'm afraid so.
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
-Do you want some water?
-Please.
Get some water, please.
Do you know
what she was doing there?
She was on a date
with a guy.
He called asking for
a Czechoslovakian girl.
I sent him Honey.
Once they get there,
it doesn't really matter.
Do you have Czech girls
working for you?
No, but he insisted on one.
Does this girl
look familiar to you?
Linda?
What were you saying?
I think I know this girl.
Her name is Daphne.
She's a Czech girl.
I tried to recruit her
and gave her my card.
I never heard backfrom her.
She's very popular suddenly.
Do you have a last name?
No. I just had two guys come in
asking about her.
Who were they?
One guy said he was her cousin
was trying tofind her.
They had a video camera,
and I wanted them out...
so I told them where she worked.
Where's that?
It's a salon
on 63rd and Madison.
-What's the name?
-Ludwig's. She washes hair.
Leon, Ludwig's Hair Salon.
Suspects might be there.
We think
the suspects are there.
-Right away!
-Hurry!
Want a sip?
-I'm on duty.
-So am l.
Hunting for Daphne.
I'll go inside.
You cover the exit.
Of course.
I always wanted to be a cop...
when I was a kid.
I dreamt about
pulling out my gun...
kicking the door in,
yelling "Freeze"!
What did you dream about?
Running into a burning building,
kicking down the door...
rushing through the smoke,
and saving a kid.
Then I guess we're doing it
the right way.
If it was a burning building,
I'd let you gofirst.
Watch out.
Fuck.
The thrill of the hunt.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
I'm looking for Daphne.
I don't know where she went.
Maybe infront.
Thanks.
I've got a temper.
When I lose it,
I lose control.
Get out of here!
I didn't intend to kill Milos.
When I went to prison,
they beat me.
I still didn't tell
he was my partner.
I loved Milos like a brother.
Daphne,will you
be coming back to work?
-In a minute, Ludwig.
-Come!
Thank you.
I don't want to kill you.
But if you talk...
I will.
I thought you'd want it.
This was Tamina's necklace.
Keep it.
Let's get out of here.
Good-bye, my love.
Your name's Daphne, right?
Remember last night at the fire,
you saw me?
Last night,you wanted
to tell me something.
I got it.
I smell smoke across the street.
We just want to talk to you.
We're here to protect you.
No problem.
You speak English?
You speak English, don't you?
Let's go this way.
Did two guys come
and visit you today?
What's that?
Who gave you this?
Across the street,
two guys with a video camera.
Don't look! It's OK.
Let's just box them in.
You stay here with her.
Come on, let's go!
Shit! Go!
Goddamn!
Split up!
Fuck! Go!
Son of a bitch!
Get the fuck out of the road!
Move! Damn!
On the bus!
-Look out!
-Be careful!
Excuse me! Move! I'm a cop!
Look, look!
Watch out! Watch out!
Perfect! Cut! Print! Go!
Bobby,you OK?
I'm all right.
They went towards the park!
-You hit?
-No.
Got my piece.
Did you get him?
Think so.
I'm here, Leon.
I'm having a bad day, man.
You'll be OK.
We've surrounded the park.
They've disappeared.
Detective, can you tell us
what happened?
-I can't talk right now.
-Give me a break.
Excuse me,what's
the Fire Marshal doing here?
I can't give out any statements
right now. I'm sorry.
I understand your partner,
Leon Jackson, is injured.
He was hurt, not seriously.
Do you have a suspect
in custody?
Now's not a good time, OK?
Detective Jackson
was not hurt seriously.
That's all I can tell you.
All right.
Eddie, are you all right?
Not a good time.
All right.
If you'd just be willing
to cooperate...
Let me tell you something.
I want to know who they are
and how you're involved now!
I don't know who they are.
I've never seen them before.
I was there showering,
and Tamina is a friend of mine.
My shower was broken,
so she let me use theirs.
Go on.
That's it.
I saw the killings.
Why are you protecting them?
I'm protecting myself.
From what?
Are you here illegally?
Don't worry about that.
We'll talk to lmmigration.
-Don't talk to lmmigration.
-Why not?
We'll find out
one way or another.
Better that it comes from you.
You understand?
You want to sit down?
Why don't you sit down?
You want a glass of water?
My little sister and I
shared a flat.
I came home one night,
and a man was raping her.
His gun was on the chair,
and I grabbed it...
and when he came at me,
I shot him.
Justifiable homicide.
Yes, but he was a cop.
So you shot him,
and you killed a cop?
I was living in a small town
in Slovakia.
We don't want to hear
your life story.
I got an officer
shot out there.
Just tell us where
we can find these guys.
You're a cop.
I know you won't help me.
You're right.
Not unless you help us.
Eddie, can I talk to you
alone for a second?
For a second.
Even if she is telling
the truth, she's fucked.
Would you mind letting me
talk to her first?
Any leads I get,
they're all yours...
but let me
get first crack at her.
You want to talk to her alone?
She's scared.
You're intimidating her.
Big hotshot celebrity.
I'm a nobody.
Maybe she'll open upwith me.
Maybe she looks
at me different.
What is this?
You're her saviour?
Gonna save her
from the burning building?
I'm being serious here.
I'll give you a head start...
but you get her
to the station house...
and don't let her
out of your sight.
She's the only warm body
we got left.
I'm a professional,
all right?
Women like that have a way...
of turning professionals
into amateurs.
What are you doing?
I've got to light
this scene better.
Make it more dramatic...
just like in the movie,
"Silence of the Sheeps."
Shut up.
Hurts, huh?
Big enough?
Just kidding.
Want to get married?
I love you.
You want to get married?
Sweetheart.
No?
Come on.
I love you.
sweetheart, my love.
I adore you.
I adore you, my Nicolette.
I want you.
I adore you.
She's here.
She's here?
What does that mean?
"Good luck" in Greek.
Good luck in English.
Are you married?
Do you live alone?
I haven't showered
since the killings.
We could stop at your place,
and I could take a shower...
before we have to go back
to custody.
Look, l...
I can't take you
back to my place.
Then somewhere else?
How's it going, dude?
-Eddie, how are you?
-Not too good.
I love you.
You have a funny way
of showing it.
Yeah, me, too.
Why'd you snap at me?
I didn't snap at you.
Yes,you did.
I just wanted a statement.
I just can't answeryou
every time.
I couldn't do it.
Didn't have to embarrass me
infront of my colleagues.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to embarrass you.
You know that.
It's all right.
You OK?
You got blood all over
your watch. Leon's?
Probably. It has to be.
Is he gonna be all right?
He'll be OK.
Last week,you had
that schoolteacher's blood...
on your shoes.
I don't know how you do it.
Speaking of shoes...
you know what I was thinking?
I would like to have...
some shoes next to my shoes.
Wait.
What are you doing, Eddie?
Forget the phone. What?
No, go ahead.
Answer the phone.
Aw, shit.
Look, can I just
call you right back?
You can't call me back.
We can't find Katie.
We want you to anchor right now.
We don't know where she is.
Come down, get in a cab,
and be here in an hour.
Wait a minute.
Now? Right now?
You want your shot?
Get in the cab
and come down here now.
They want me to anchor.
-Great.
-Tonight.
-That's great.
-Oh, my God.
Forget that for a second.
No,when you come back.
You promise?
We'll talk tonight?
Of course I promise.
I'll see you
when you come back...
and we'll do it.
Go ahead.
You'll be great.
I love you, Eddie.
I love you, sweetheart.
I'll see you tonight.
Good luck.
Don't be late.
The video of Milos and Tamina...
I told you to erase it.
I erased everything.
It's all gone.
Don't lie.
I won't be angry.
Why not?
-What is it?
-What does it look like?
It's an address book.
I took it from the black cop.
What's this?
What is it?
"Eddie Flemming."
Why won't you be angry
at me for keeping my movie?
You'll see.
Come. Bring the camera.
Hello.
My name is Frank Capra.
I'm a famous Hollywood director.
There she is!
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
I came to see how
the investigation is going.
I called,
and you're not here.
I waited by the station house,
you never show up.
I beep you,
you don't return my call.
Where the hell have you been?
Ladder 21 was at the rock
for training. All right?
So we stopped there so
she could get cleaned up.
What do you mean cleaned up?
I let her take a shower.
A shower?
And did you take one, too?
Come on, Chief.
She's been through a lot.
I'm trying to help her out.
Really?
That's really nice of you.
You take a homicide witness...
to take a shower after
your partner's been shot.
Are you out of
your fucking mind?
You having that much trouble
get ting dates?
I told him to.
Tommy, get her out of here.
There was the press
all over the place.
I didn't want her face
in the news, so I told him...
to take her someplace quiet
till things calmed down.
-Really?
-It was my decision, not his.
I am
the Deputy Chief Fire Marshal...
and every now and then, I like
to be included in decisions.
I understand.
Infact, once he briefs me...
you guys can take over
the press conference...
and you can take
the lead in the case.
-How's that?
-All right.
I'm ready to be briefed.
-Excuse us.
-Sure.
Are you ready to brief me?
Good.
Wait.
Fellas, can you give us
a few minutes, please?
-You bet.
-Thanks.
Shut that door, too,
when you go out.
Thanks a lot, guys.
Just so you know,
I didn't touch her.
Maybe you should've...
because nobody believes
you didn't, including me.
I know it wasn't
the smartest thing to do...
and you think I'm a fool,
but nothing happened.
It wasn't
the smartest thing to do.
To say the least,
you ought to know better.
She's got the potential
to fucking hang you.
If she even suggests
that you made a pass at her...
it's fucking over.
Deny it all you want.
It won't make a fucking
bit of difference.
You never went
out on a limb for somebody?
"Here's the name of
an immigration lawyer."
That's how you go out on a limb.
If you heard her story,
you'd believe her, too.
You'll jeopardize
your career and your life...
and my case...
and I'll give you
another piece of advice.
Maybe you don't watch TV...
but I'll let you in
on a little secret.
The whole fucking world
watches television.
When you go out there,
they know your face...
and the little fucking
itty bit of fame...
I have in this fucking city
makes my job a lot easier...
and I get a lot more done
because of it.
Why'd you stand up
for me with the chief?
I don't know.
You remind me of a puppy
I used to have...
who pissed all over the carpet,
but I still kept him.
-Let's go.
-Captain!
One at a time, please!
We're looking for two male white
suspects in their thirties.
We believe them to be of
an Eastern-European nationality.
That's another lesson.
You got nothing to say,
don't waste their time or yours.
Let somebody else do that.
What's the plan now?
You're on the team, so I'll
call you when something happens.
Right now I've got to propose
to my girlfriend.
Really? Congratulations.
Don't congratulate me.
She hasn't said yes yet.
I still think
there's something...
I could be doing
to helpfind these guys.
Go home and get some rest.
Sometimes you can try too hard.
Sometimes you have to go away
in order to come back.
Like you did
with that shot today?
That's right.
All right. I get it.
Good, because you don't
look like you get it.
I get it.
-Sure you get it?
-I get it.
-You get it?
-No, I get it.
Trust me. I get it.
Why don't you keep it?
Don't say I never
gave you anything.
Coming.
Hello?
I'm looking for Gayle Cassiopi.
I think it's one flight up.
Thanks.
Action.
Who's she?
None of your fucking business.
Who's Nicky?
Beautiful.
It's OK.
You know what I need?
I need your opinion.
You do? About what?
You see...
they're going to make
a movie about me, too, Eddie...
and write books.
Write books.
Books? What's your fucking
accomplishment?
I kill someone famous.
And I saw you on the page
of "People" magazine.
Eddie, look at me.
Good.
Good. Be tough to the end.
Actor who plays you will
want you to die like a hero.
Tabloids don't have
to do re-enactments.
They're going to have
a real movie this time.
You film killing me,
you'll get away with that?
You're stupider than I thought.
Both out of your fucking minds.
Turn it off!
We are insane.
Who else but crazy men
would film their crimes?
So I kill you,
and if we are caught...
we are sent
to mental hospital...
but once I'm in the hospital,
I say I'm not crazy...
just pretending.
So I would be acquitted.
We see psychiatrists.
They must certify we are sane...
and because of
your double jeopardy law...
we can't be tried
for the same crime twice.
We come out
free, rich, and famous.
This is a fucking great idea.
You think the jury
will buy that bullshit?
You sickfucks.
I'm smarter than Americans.
You watch crybaby talk shows
all day long.
Not only will Americans
believe me, they'll cry for me.
Would you like to say
good-bye to your Nicky?
Maybe you can
propose to her now.
He has nothing to say.
Give me a pillow.
Give me a fucking pillow!
Come here, start the camera.
Cut!
This is my project.
I'm the director,
and I say action.
Shut the fuck up!
Detective Flemming...
was one of the most
decorated NYPD detectives...
in the history of New York.
Among the several thousand
arrests he made...
during his career,
the famed Stephen Geller case.
He was widely loved
by the community he served.
His partner eulogized him.
Eddie was my mentor...
My partner...
Tragedy.
Every great film must have one.
...the word "friend."
I will miss him.
I said, no!
No means no.
Want me to get ugly?
Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
It's a private affair.
-Sorry, no.
-Let me get a drink.
Please hold.
Just stay on. Hold on.
Robert, you've got a call.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Hold on. I'm right here.
Just stay right there.
Don't be ridiculous.
Can't you see I'm busy here?
Trust me. Take this call.
Hang up the phone,
go get yourself a drink.
Take the call.
Give it to me.
I'm sorry.
Who is this?
I made a movie
of Eddie Flemming's murder.
How do I know this is you?
You'll know when you meet me.
-Where?
-Come to 35th and Broadway.
Don't bring the police.
Come alone...
oryou'll be in my next film.
Listen, asshole, I've been
threatened by better than you.
No. I'm the best
that's ever threatened you.
They're gonna get you.
We'll talk about that.
About surrendering?
4.00. It gives you
time to go to bank.
$1 million.
"Top Story,"
are you still there?
I'm here.
It doesn't work that way.
If you don't want my film...
I'll call another show,
and they will show it.
I'll meet you.
I need two things from you--
I want exclusivity,
and you will surrender to me.
Bring cash.
Let's go.
Truck 21 spotted on
the north end of the building...
put the aerial ladder
up to the roof.
Engine company 54
and Engine 9...
took hand lines
up to the second level.
The they cut a hole in the roof
directly over the fire.
-So how was the funeral?
-Not good.
Did the D.A.
video-tape her deposition?
He finished a little while ago.
Swing by her apartment...
pick up her clothes,
and take her straight to INS.
She's their problem now.
Hard to believe. Watch.
What's this?
I don't know.
"Good luck with
all your troubles.
"I'm here if you need me.
Ludwig."
Who's he?
My boss.
Why, are you jealous?
Why don'twe get your stuff?
Look...
you're a witness
to a double homicide.
All right?
I can't get involved with you.
Why don't you go get your bags,
and I'll wait here.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Get back!
That's not mine!
Don't do it!
Come on!
Hurry!
-It's locked.
-Where's the key?
-It's not mine.
-All right.
Get in the bathroom.
1075. 47th and 8th!
All right. We're trapped!
Two alarms on arrival!
Oh, my God.
He's nailed it down.
Baby, don't open the window.
It'll suck the fire towards us.
-They were here.
-Jesus Christ, that's Eddie's.
They were here!
Calm down, Daphne.
Just get in the tub.
-There's gasoline.
-What?
There's gasoline in here.
-What are you doing?
-I'm pouring it out.
-It's not going down.
-Oh, my God.
Give it to me.
Jesus Christ.
It's clogged. God damn it.
Please do something.
We're going to die.
Forget it.
They're all clogged.
Come on, baby.
Just stay low and stay calm.
90% people who die in a fire
die from eating smoke.
Let me introduce you
to my partner...
and the man
who started the fire.
Say something for your fans.
Stand back and get down!
Just get back and stay low.
Stay low!
This'll buy us some time!
Get back!
This is a great film.
We can see fire right now,
and Daphne's in the fire.
Tell him it's OK.
Let's go!
Come on, guys. Let's go.
Get that plug now!
Take care of the boy.
And get her some oxygen!
You all right?
What the hell happened up there?
It was a setup. Somebody
booby-trapped the apartment.
-Who?
-It's gotta be the same guys.
You gotta speak louder.
I can't hearyou.
Jordy, are you hurt?
-I'm all right.
-What?
You have to speak up.
What the hell
are you talking about?
What is it?
We have a disturbance
in the lobby.
-Where's Hawkins?
-He's not on the premises.
Go get that tape
and bring it here right now.
Any request for that
video-tape has to go to--
Woman, I am begging you!
You can't let this happen!
You want that tape,
contact the at torney.
I'll be happy to give you--
You thinkwe're joking?
Listen,you can't do this!
Don't do this to Eddie.
Don't do it to
the people of this city.
You can't show
the man's murder on TV!
You want the tape, there it is!
Stay tuned for a special edition
of "Top Story."
Detective Eddie Flemming's
brutal murder...
has been video-taped,
and we will broadcast it...
after these messages.
Hard to believe. Watch.
Who says you can't be
success in America?
I came here with nothing,
knowing nobody, and now, look.
I am success story.
Why did you say "I"?
-It should be "we."
-Don't be paranoid.
I gave you half of
what they gave me.
Good evening.
I'm Robert Hawkins...
and this is "Top Story."
-Here we are.
-Tonight I present to you...
material of a graphic
and violent nature...
never before seen
on television...
and I do so with a heavy heart.
It would only be normal
to askwhy.
Why are we showing something
so disturbing?
And my answer
is as a journalist...
I am obligated to show it.
I air this tape
in loving memory...
of my friend Eddie Flemming.
Hard to believe.
Watch.
You film killing me,
you're gonna get away with that?
Just turn it off.
Cut! This is my project.
I'm the director,
and I say action.
Shut the [beep] up!
Why did you leave that stuff in
about you being a director?
-Because I am the director.
-What?
Don't you fucking realize
if it wasn't for me...
for my idea, no fucking way
we'd be sitting here right now?
-Your idea?
-My idea.
Is that the guy?
Don't you understand?
This is a greatAmerican movie,
and who made it?
I made it all.
I was the director.
-Who are you?
-Everything.
I am everything.
This is whatAmerica wants--
violence and sex.
Before we hand in
the nextvideo...
I'm gonna put titles on it...
and my credit is going to read,
"Directed by Oleg Razgul."
Yeah, but there is
only one problem.
One credit,
but I don't share credit.
-You got it?
-Share credit?
You think you're a director?
You're just a little,
small, Russian piece of shit.
Let's go!
This is Robert Hawkins
for "Top Story."
We'll be back after this.
All right, I'm here.
Oh,Jesus.
This is the man
I told you about.
This is Bruce Cutler.
Bryan, come get this from here.
I am Emil. I'm insane.
Are you my lawyer?
Not just yet.
I got your money.
Where is it?
Shit,where is it?
Where is it?!
He's got the camera!
He's got the movie!
Let's sit down
and talk a minute.
I need it! Where is it?
Don't move!
Get your hands up
and drop the gun!
Drop the goddamn gun!
What did you hit him for?
He surrendered!
-Go tight on them.
-He's unarmed and hurt!
I'm going with you.
Come on!
I'm coming down there with you.
I'm his lawyer--
Turn the camera off!
Keep going! Keepfilming!
I'm invoking his rights!
What's going on?
I'm going with you.
Fuck!
I'm going down there with you.
What's going on?!
They're taking you downtown.
-Whoa! I'll take him.
-He's mine!
I'm taking him.
Don't argue with me.
-He's my collar!
-He killed my partner!
After he's booked, he's yours,
but I'm walking him in!
All right, kid,
have your 15 minutes.
Tommy, ride with him.
Get in the fucking car.
Don't speak to him!
Put your head in!
Get him in the car, Tommy!
Put your head in,you fool!
I ain't playing with you!
Shit!
You ought to be
ashamed of yourself!
Bullshit, Leon!
Ashamed of what?
I got him off the streets.
Bravo, Mr Hawkins!
You better back off.
You are sick!
I'm fed up with your bullshit!
Let go!
Get outta here!
Where are you going?
You'll lose everybody!
What are you doing, man?
This is not the way
to the station!
Talk to me!
You're losing them!
Answer me, man!
-Answer me!
-Where am l?
-What the hell--
-What's going on?
Hold on. Wait!
Come on!
Where's my lawyer?
Where are they?
God damn it!
What's wrong with you, man?
Shit!
Fuck you!
What's going on?
Jordy, listen!
Wait a minute!
You can't do this, man!
Listen! Wait,Jordy!
Come on.
Listen, man, please!
How'd you know how to rig
that apartment?
My father was a fireman.
He taught me about fire.
Now it's my friend.
-Take a walk.
-You're not thinking straight.
Don't you get it?
He knew he'd get caught.
That's why you video-taped
Eddie's murder!
I want to see
this son of a bitch dead, too--
It's over tonight,
you son of a bitch!
You can't kill him
in cold blood!
Get the hell outta here!
Get in the car!
Listen to me!
I'm not gonna let you do this!
Get in the car! Go!
Now go!
Fuck it, man! Shit!
Something fucking funny?
Refreshing.
You think this is funny?!
Turn around!
You want to be famous?
You want headlines?
Now's your chance.
Put your hands up.
Get your goddamn hands up!
Turn around.
You want to be
a real American, right?
You want to be a tough guy?
Here's Eddie's gun.
You remember him?
Come on.
You want to be famous?
Shoot me.
Want headlines?
Want to make money?
Want to be a celebrity?
Shoot me!
You can't kill me.
You're not a cop.
You're just a fireman
with a gun.
OK...l'll make it easy.
You Americans are pussies
without your missiles and money.
You won't kill me.
You don't have the balls.
Don't do it, brother!
Kill me.
Get up!
You are mine now, sucker!
You are out of control,
you know that?
Here's Eddie's gun.
Where you going?
I lost my shoe.
I want my shoe.
Get him out of here!
Emil Slovak is a victim here.
He is not a culprit.
We all appreciate the tragedy...
of the death
of Detective Flemming.
I represent Mr Slovak.
He was operating under the undue
influence of his partner.
This will all come out
at the trial...
and Emil will be vindicated.
I will see to that.
-Good job.
-Thanks.
How you feeling?
I brought letters.
Fan mail from women.
One wants to buy you a suit...
another one sent money,
and another one wants money.
-Bring me the cigarettes?
-I did.
The perception out there
is very bad, Emil, right now.
And perception is reality.
You may not be crazy...
but I want to get
that message out...
and I want to get it out now.
That's our only defence
in this case.
You have tofocus
on three things--
paranoia,fear, and delusions.
I was all of those.
But you never appreciated
the severity of it until now.
Of course not.
How could I be?
I was paranoid,
fear ful, and deluded.
Now...what about Oleg?
They're looking
all over for him.
Haven't found him.
Maybe he went back to Russia.
I don't know.
He's here.
Let'sforget about him
and focus on you.
You're what's most important.
What about my movie rights?
Book rights?
Foryou?
I have not thought
about that, Emil.
How much do you want?
What's your cut?
I thinkwe could be partners.
50-50.
No way.
I give you 30%, no more.
Don't forget.
We're in it together.
I thought 40%
might be all right.
Oh, my God!
Thirty,
or I call another lawyer.
This is the biggest
case of your life.
Don't try to negotiate.
Say yes or no.
I can live with 30%,
but, Emil, it's important...
you understand
this is not all about money.
What else do you need?
I need to know about you,
what makes you tick.
I need to know
about your background.
I need to know about
your mother,your father...
your brother,your sister,
everything.
That's what I need to know.
My father always degraded me.
He killed my self-esteem.
He hated me from the day
when I was born.
Emil Slovak
will appear in court today.
His lawyer--
Stay focused. Start again.
Emil Slovak
will appear in court today.
His lawyer will argue that
his client is mentally unfit...
This is such bullshit.
In a related matter, Mr Slovak's
attorney Bruce Cutler...
famous for handling
sensational cases...
claims his client is
unfit to stand trial.
Bobby,want to give me
a break already?
Hello?
No, not you, hon.
Hello? No,
we have no comment.
...his partner Oleg Razgul,
who threatened to kill him...
if he didn't follow his orders.
I gotta go!
I'm going back to
the Czech Republic...
toface the charges against me.
I'm innocent.
If she shot a cop
who raped her sister...
in this country,
she'd be a hero.
And I approached him
and asked him...
for some spare change.
Politely, right?
Whereupon he pulls out
his big gun...
pushed me
all up in the tree...
hand cuffs me
like this up here...
and then he takes
my money, right?
Took my money and
left me here like this...
exposed to all the elements.
Un-fucking-believable.
Look at this fucking guy.
Kids, you know,
if you out there...
don't hate your firemen.
Not all Fire Marshals like this.
It's not like this,
so keep the love.
Hard to believe.
You're watching "Top Story."
How could you forget that
you hand cuffed a civilian...
to a fucking tree
in Central Park...
in the middle of the night?!
Tell me that!
Look, all right,
I know I screwed up...
but it's not like this guy
is some innocent civilian.
He'll end your career
and probably mine!
End my career?
What am I talking about?
The press will be all over us!
Get the fuck back to your desks!
Come on, Chief.
Look at my file.
I've never had a civilian
complaint against me before.
-I crack big cases.
-Your record doesn't matter!
It should mean something!
That's past history!
Don't you get it?
Look, I'm sorry.
It's unfortunate...
that I have to make decisions
based on your press coverage...
but that's what I gotta do.
You're suspended, without pay,
pending a department trial.
Not to mention
your criminal charges.
That's not right.
You better get yourself
a damn good lawyer.
...over a million dollars
for the disputed video.
In related news, Emil Slovak
is back in court tomorrow...
where we're expected to learn...
if he is competent
to stand trial.
Meanwhile, the massive manhunt
continuesfor Oleg Razgul...
the alleged mastermind
behind the murder...
of New York City Detective
Eddie Flemming.
"Action News" has learned that
Mr Slovakwon't have to worry...
about how he is going
to pay for his defence.
He has received movie offers...
and has been in conversations
with numerous publishers...
concerning the rights
to his story.
Further developments
are expected today...
in the bizarre Eddie Flemming
murder case.
Judge Stanley Stern
will issue his ruling...
on alleged killer
Emil Slovak's insanity plea.
If the court rules
in his favour today...
Mr Slovakwill be
transferred to the psych ward...
at Rikers lsland
for further testing...
before being remanded
to the custody...
of a permanent institution
for the mentally ill.
Slovak's attorney Bruce Cutler
has maintained...
that an abusive childhood
is to blame...
for the actions of his client.
The Czech national
apparently has a history...
of physical
and emotional trauma...
heaped upon him
by an alcoholic father.
What's ever left over, keep it.
Thanks, buddy.
Keep the Statue of Liberty
in the background, all right?
-How do I look?
-You look beautiful.
Thanks. Fuck you. Roll.
What are you looking at?
Forget about him.
Let's go.
All right. Just roll.
All right. Let's go.
Bruce Cutler,
do you have a statement for us?
It's been a difficult
and long day for us.
Emil has been found
incompetent to stand trial...
and in times
of extreme stress...
as a result of
his delusional thinking...
he could not appreciate
the wrong fulness of his acts...
and therefore he's not
liable for his acts.
This is a victory
for the mentally ill...
and before Emil
is taken on the boat...
to the psychiatric ward
at Rikers lsland...
it should be noted
that what he did...
he was forced to do...
by Oleg Razgul, a dangerous
and demented individual...
who is at liberty right now...
in the streets of New York,
and both Emil and l...
Iook forward to when
he is brought to justice.
What the fuck are you
looking at,you piece of shit?
Officers,you have to watch him.
He's assaulted
my client in the past.
That's it? This scumbag
kills Eddie Flemming...
and now he gets to spend
the rest of his life...
in some country club nuthouse?
What about the victims and
the families and their rights?
Marshal, I understand
you don't agree...
but this is the system,
and this is the law.
Let's go.
I can kill you.
I'm insane.
We need this area cleared.
Move back.
...two-shot
of Cutler and Slovak.
All right.
Give me the boat
in the background.
Do you really believe
that your client is insane?
Emil knew exactly
what he was doing. Watch this.
All right.
Turn it off.
This tape I kept for myself.
In hospital
I say I'm not crazy...
and because of your
double jeopardy law...
we can't be tried for
the same crime twice.
We come out
free, rich, and famous.
Can we deal for this?
It'sfree.
What would you say
to evidence...
that proves your client
is not insane?
"Top Story" has
the truth right here...
from Oleg Razgul himself.
You knew what you were doing.
It's all in here...in my movie.
Officers, do your duty
and arrest this man!
I'm not the killer.
I'm the director. Action!
-Back off!
-Let her go!
Everyone, back away from me!
Hold your fire!
Do not fire your weapons!
Stay back!
Nobody's gonna fire.
-Hold that line!
-Let her go!
Tell him to put his gun down.
-All right.
-Get that shotgun out of here!
-Nobody's gonna fire.
-Stay back!
Everybody, get back!
Do not fire, anyone!
-Lower those weapons!
-Go tighter.
Now! Lower!
Tell him to put his gun down!
-Put your weapon down!
-Let her go!
If he doesn't lower his gun,
I'llfucking kill her!
-Officer, lower that weapon!
-Loweryour gun!
-Remember what he did to Eddie!
-Shut up!
Do not fire that weapon!
I'll surrender
if he lowers his gun.
Don't you let this
piece of shit surrender!
If you don't let me surrender,
I kill her now.
-I don't care!
-I kill her now.
Do not fire that weapon!
-Shut up!
-Take that shot.
God damn it!
You take that fucking shot!
Officer, for the last time,
lower your weapon!
Look, he's lowered the weapon.
Don't shoot her.
You take that shot.
He lowered his weapon.
You don't have to shoot her.
He lowered the weapon,
all right?
You're OK.
Don't look back.
Don't look at him.
Fuck! Did you get that?
Fuck!
Let's get you out of here.
Hey, boss.
He's still alive.
Come on. Let's go.
How was that?
That was great.
Thanks.
I thought you might want that.
Alan, here.
Take this camera.
Marshal.
Marshal,you feel up
to making a statement?
All right. Forget it.
No statement.
Cut the camera.
Listen, I can help you.
Take a lessonfrom Eddie.
The media can be
a powerful ally.
Eddie was my friend.
I'd like to be yours, too.
Good job.
-You OK?
-I'm fine. Fuck him.
Follow him walking away,
and then whip back to me.
We've been talking with
Fire Marshal Jordan Warsaw.
He's understandably
over whelmed...
with what's just
occurred here today--
the tragic end
of two vicious psychopaths...
who attempted to manipulate
the news media...
for their own greed and egos.
We at "Top Story"
will never allow ourselves...
to be used in this way.
Our goal is to bring you
the news in all its complexity.
The truth was
the real hero here today...
and we're proud
to have brought it to you...
exclusively on "Top Story."
This is Robert Hawkins.
Good night.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org