Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
A very long time ago...
...there lived a beautiful princess,
in a mystical land known as...
...India.
She was married to the
handsome Prince Rama...
...who had been banished
to the enchanted forest...
...by his jealous stepmother,
Queen Kaikeyi.
One day...
...Princess Sita saw a wounded deer
in the woods...
...and she begged Rama
to go and help it.
Rama drew a circle in the ground
and said to her:
''This is a magic circle.
So long as you stay inside it...
...no harm can come to you. ''
That night,
the princess heard a horrible cry.
Help me.
Thinking it was her beloved Rama
in danger...
...the princess ran from the circle
to answer the cry.
She soon came across
an old beggar man.
Although she had no money
to give him...
...she could not refuse his plea.
As soon as he had the bracelet...
...he transformed into the
1 0-headed demon, Ravana.
He grabs her and takes her
to his palace...
...to make her his bride.
Did you ever know
a real prince, Maya?
Laki's father.
- I thought he was in the army.
- He was.
And he was my prince.
And I, his princess.
But I mean real princes
and princesses.
All women are princesses.
It is our right.
I shall miss it here.
India is the only place on earth
that stirs the imagination.
I wish we could stay here forever.
I know, sweetheart.
But now that England's at war...
...I must go too.
You understand, don't you?
But why must I go to America?
Because it's safer.
And you'll be going to the school
your mother went to at your age...
- ...in a city called?
- New York.
Papa?
Maya told me that all girls
are princesses.
- Maya is a very wise woman.
- Then it's true?
You can be anything you want to be,
as long as you believe.
- What do you believe?
- I believe that you are...
...and always will be,
my little princess.
I gave this to your mother
on our wedding day.
I want you to have it.
She was so beautiful.
What did you love most about her?
Tough question.
I loved the way her eyes lit up
when she laughed.
Just like yours do.
I loved the sound of her voice when
she sang me the Indian folksong.
But I think,
more than anything else...
...I loved dancing with her!
Hello!
You must be Captain Crewe.
My sister will be down presently.
We were just preparing
the young lady's room.
Your things arrived this morning.
Thank you...?
Heavens, Amelia.
Amelia Minchin.
Captain Crewe.
How delightful to meet you!
And this must be little Sara.
My, what a beautiful child.
- I was telling the Captain--
- Thank you, that'll be all.
Won't you follow me?
Classes begin promptly at 8:00.
We cover all subjects:
literature, math, science...
...and of course, French and Latin.
Oh, Sara speaks fluent--
Luncheon is served at 1 :30.
Then we take our daily walk...
...unless the weather is
extremely inclement.
At 4:00, the girls attend
etiquette classes...
...where they're trained in
the formal graces of society.
Study hall is between 4:30 and 6:30,
followed by a light supper.
Before bedtime,
we read from one of the classics...
...something the children
look forward to with anticipation.
Sunday is a day of rest.
Students may write to their parents.
And of course, we attend church.
Have you any questions?
Come along, dear.
Girls.
Say hello
to our new arrival...
...Miss Sara Crewe.
Hello, Sara.
You must tell them about
your exciting life in India.
No doubt she'll be our most
popular student in no time.
There are certain rules
that should be made clear.
First is the Order Rule...
...which requires the girls keep
their rooms spotless.
These rules are strictly enforced.
But I assure you, the results
are well worth the effort.
Our reputation for sending
the most poised...
...and charming young ladies
into society...
...is one of the highest.
I've no doubt.
Also, I'm afraid jewelry
and such finery are not allowed.
What if I wear it in my room,
during my free time?
If you absolutely insist.
I do.
She'll get in trouble.
This is splendid.
It's our largest suite.
Thank you for all the care
you've taken.
I want Sara to feel at home
while I'm away.
- No expense shall be spared.
- Of course not.
I'll let you say goodbye.
You don't have much time
before your boat leaves.
We'll write to each other
every day.
How do you like your room?
I made sure it was the best,
with corner windows and a fireplace.
And with all your toys
and clothes moved in...
...it's as if you were really...
I think I saw something...
...on that chair over there.
She came all the way from France
to be with you.
Her name is Emily.
Dolls make the very
best friends.
Just because they can't speak
doesn't mean they don't listen.
Did you know, when we leave them alone
in our room, they come to life?
- They do?
- Yes.
Before we walk in, they quickly
return to their places.
Why don't they come to life
in front of us?
Because it's magic.
Magic has to be believed.
That's the only way it's real.
Whenever you're afraid,
or miss me terribly...
...just tell Emily.
She'll get the message to me,
wherever I am.
And I'll send one back right away...
...so when you hug her...
...you'll be getting a hug from me.
It's all right, Papa.
I'm going to be fine.
What are you doing?
Memorizing me by heart?
I already know you by heart.
Goodbye princess.
What was that noise last night?
Somebody was crying for hours.
That's nothing.
You should hear Josephine snore.
I do not!
Who was it? The new girl?
She hasn't come out of her room.
Did you see all her toys?
I want your hair ribbon.
Her father grows crackers.
They're very rich.
They must be.
Everyone I know eats crackers.
Her father's British. I hear he's
best friends with the king and queen.
I hear he was thrown out of India...
...because people died
from eating his poisoned crackers.
Poisoned crackers?
My aunt died from eating poisoned
string beans.
- Who cares about her?
- Yeah, who cares?
But before we catch them, they return
to their places, quick as lightning.
Gosh, she's fast.
Mama.
Sara?
We don't delay breakfast
for one student.
I'm sorry, but I--
Remember, you're not the only
child here.
Yes, good morning.
You remember our newest pupil
from our visit yesterday.
This is Monsieur Dufarge.
You begin French lessons today.
Do I have to?
You most certainly do.
Apologize to Monsieur
for your rudeness.
- But I didn't mean to be rude.
- Now!
This child doesn't need to learn French.
She practically is French!
She learned from her father.
I understood what she said.
I'm sorry. We tried to tell you.
She can tutor the younger children...
...and help you
with your pronunciation, Miss Minchin.
Are those sausages I smell?
Thank you.
There's no talking at the table.
Doesn't seem natural.
I won't say it again.
Seven times five is 35.
Seven times six is 42.
Seven times seven is 49.
Seven times eight is...
...58.
No, wait. 54?
55?
Or 72? Or 93? Or 1 2?
I'm sorry, Miss Minchin.
I studied for hours last night.
I find that hard to believe.
I imagine your father will as well.
Please don't tell him.
I promise I'll do better.
Please.
Lavinia, you may continue.
Seven times eight is 56.
Seven times nine...
...is 63.
Dear Papa:
I miss you already.
Things are fine.
Except I never imagined there
would be so many rules at school.
I guess they're there for a purpose...
...and I'm trying hard to obey them.
But I get the feeling
I'm doing something wrong.
Goodbye, Father.
Bye, son.
I hope when you read this...
...it kindles your heart and puts
a smile on your face.
I'm so proud of you.
I think about you every moment.
And I love you forever.
Your Sara.
Lottie, you mustn't get so excited.
Lottie? Precious?
Please, Lottie dear!
Please stop screaming!
How about a cookie?
Would you like that?
I'll get a cookie.
It's hard to study with you
carrying on like this.
I want my mama!
You'll see her soon.
I won't. She's dead,
and I won't ever see her again!
I don't have a mother either.
You don't?
Where is she?
In heaven with my baby sister.
That doesn't mean
I can't talk to her.
I tell her everything,
and I know she hears me.
How?
Because that's what angels do.
- Your mama's an angel?
- Of course.
And so is yours.
With beautiful wings of silk...
...and a crown of rosebuds.
And they all live together
in a castle.
Do you know what it's made of?
Sunflowers...
...hundreds of them, so bright
they shine like gold.
When the angels
want to go someplace...
...they just whistle, like this.
And a cloud floats to the castle
and picks them up.
As the angels fly through the sky...
...riding the cloud
like a magic carpet...
...under the moon
and through the stars...
...until they're hovering
above us.
That's how they can look down
and see if we're all right.
And sometimes they even
send messages to us.
You can't hear them if you're
kicking and screaming as you were.
But they always try again,
in case we've missed it.
Hey, wait!
That's Becky.
She's not allowed to talk to us.
Why not?
She's a servant girl,
and she has dark skin.
So?
Well, doesn't that mean something?
I'm sorry, I--
Is there anything
I can do for you, miss?
I just came up here
to change my shoes.
No, there's nothing.
Begging your pardon, but we'll
both be in trouble if you stay.
All right, girls, pair up.
Pair up.
''Sir Edward saw the sorrow
in his daughter's eyes...
...but he knew
that family honor must prevail.
Nobility was not to be trifled with.
'I beg of you, Charlotte,' he said.
'Marry Sir John in the spring,
as he has asked.' ''
Thank you, Lavinia.
Sara, you may take your turn.
''Charlotte said to her father,
'Father, you are right.
I must put away my foolish fancies
and childhood wishes.' ''
But I simply won't do it.
I'm sorry, Father.
When I marry, it'll be for love.
And with that,
Charlotte ran from the house.
Waiting outside was
the handsome stable boy, Pierre...
...whom Charlotte secretly adored.
Together they escaped to the coast
and quickly set sail for Tahiti.
When they were halfway there,
their ship was attacked by pirates!
Rather than be eaten alive...
...they threw
themselves into the sea.
As they began to drown...
...they held each other close,
and swore undying love.
Then, when all seemed lost,
a group of mermaids appeared--
Stop!
What are you doing?
I couldn't bear to see her marry him,
so I imagined another ending.
lmagined it?
Don't you ever do that, miss?
Believe in something,
just to make it seem real?
That's easy for a child
who has everything.
There will be no more make-believe
at this school...
...during reading
or any other time.
- Is that understood?
- Yes, Miss Minchin.
All of you, go to your bed.
I never heard a story like that
in my life.
I bet you know lots of them,
don't you, Sara?
I want silence up there!
We have to do something about this
communication rule.
After Minchin goes to bed...
...we'll sneak into your room, and you
can show us a real story.
How about it, Sara?
Only if it's just you three.
Come on, come on.
The evil Ravana locked the princess
up in his tower.
There she stayed for many weeks...
...just staring out her window...
...missing her Prince Rama terribly.
Perfect.
You look just like Emily.
My father hates dolls.
And he hates coming here.
Says he doesn't belong.
Then why does he send you?
Because he wants me to belong.
My little girl. She spoke French!
She really spoke French.
Your mother and I
are very proud of you.
I caught you, Nellie!
Papa!
Randolph...John!
Rama approached the thorny palace...
...unaware that Ravana
was waiting for him.
That's it!
I can't take it anymore!
I don't care what you say
about Sara's stories.
They have to be more fun than
watching your hair being combed!
If anyone else feels the same way,
she should leave too.
But Ravana was not through yet.
He took a bow that could
hold, not one, but 1 0 arrows...
...each filled with poison.
The arrows sped through the air...
...heading straight for Rama.
The arrows hit the ground...
...and released their poison,
giant clouds of thick, yello w smoke.
- I want a big piece!
- Hush up, Lottie.
''Princess'' Sara will give
everyone a fair share.
Right, Princess?
I told her that's what you were.
Well, not just me.
All girls are princesses.
Even snotty, two-faced bullies
like you, Lavinia.
Here, Lavinia,
you get a big piece.
Yes, may I help you?
I'm Mr. Barrow.
Captain Crewe's solicitor.
Oh, yes, do come in.
- We're celebrating Sara's birthday.
- May I speak to you in private?
Yes, of course.
Right this way.
May I just say that Sara is quite
the favorite around here.
We went to great lengths to make
this a special day for her.
I'm afraid your check to us this month
will be rather large.
There will be no check,
Miss Minchin.
Excuse me?
The party is over! Everyone
go to their rooms, this instant!
But we--
Sara, you will stay behind.
I have something to tell you.
Move!
Amelia, go to Sara's room
and find a simple black dress.
If nothing is suitable, borrow one.
- But, sister--
- Do as I say.
Why would I need a black dress,
Miss Minchin?
I'm afraid I have some bad news, Sara.
Your father has...
Your father--
It's been discovered that
your father has died.
He was killed in battle
several weeks ago.
I'm sorry.
That's the situation, and
there's nothing we can do to change it.
The British government has seized
control of his company and assets...
...leaving you penniless,
without any money.
Since you've no relations,
this puts me in a terrible position.
What are you staring at?
Don't you understand
what I'm saying?
You are alone in the world...
...unless I decide to keep you here...
...out of charity.
Because of the expenses you've
incurred, all you own is mine...
...your clothes, your toys, everything.
It'll hardly make up for
the financial losses I've suffered.
From now on, you must earn
your room and board.
You'll move to the attic
and work as a servant.
If you fail to meet our standards...
...or if you don 't obey,
you'll be thrown out.
And the streets of this city
are not kind to homeless beggars.
Report to Mabel in the kitchen
promptly at 5 a.m.
You could be arrested
for taking this.
You're lucky I let you keep
that doll.
You may have the book.
But another incident like this...
...and I will call the authorities.
I expect you to remember,
Sara Crewe...
...you're not a princess any longer.
Papa.
Papa, please.
Sara, what happened?
You're to serve the girls
without conversation, understand?
Sara will be working here
as a servant from now on.
There will be no communication.
Is that clear?
Yes, Miss Minchin.
Seven times five is 35.
Seven times six is 42.
Let go!
Great God!
It can't be!
It's my son, John!
Dear God, no.
Not John.
It's John, Ram Dass!
It's John. Help me.
- Come inside.
- Help.
I thought you'd be sleeping.
I never got a chance
to give you your birthday present.
It's a picture of where you
used to live.
See the blue threads?
That's the river.
These are the mountains
you always talk about.
Thank you, Becky.
It's beautiful.
Why don't you tell stories anymore?
They're just make-believe.
They don't mean anything.
They've always meant something to me.
Some days I thought I'd die, until
I heard you talk about the magic.
There is no magic, Becky.
Papa...
...can you hear me?
I'm so scared.
Are you still a princess?
You better get back in line
or we'll both be in trouble.
Are you?
Girls, get in line.
Don't touch that!
It's for Mr. Randolph.
The poor man. His son is
missing in action in Europe.
You mean John?
He's such a nice boy.
Here, little girl.
I told you
not to give your money away.
Excuse me.
You see?
You never get rid of them.
May I help you?
Would you like to buy a flower?
- Would you?
- Not today.
Would you like to buy a flower?
Would you?
Pardon me.
Give her a flower.
Wait!
For the princess.
What is it, little mouse?
Are you a prisoner too?
Is it ever this cold
where you come from?
No.
Tell me about it, Sara.
Tell me again about India.
India.
Tell me.
Well...
...the air is so hot there...
...you can almost taste it.
I bet it tastes like coconuts.
It's more like spices, really.
Curry and saffron.
What else?
Tigers sleep under trees...
...and elephants cool themselves
in the lakes.
The warm wind blows
through the fields...
...and the spirits ride it...
...singing as they look down on us.
Their voices echo
through the mountains...
...and the sky...
...is all different colors...
...like a peacock's tail.
Soot all over the place,
you clumsy fool!
Get out!
Get out of my house!
And you can forget
being paid this week!
Ungrateful little wretch.
No, you don't!
I won't tolerate
any soot in this house!
There, just look at my boot!
It's filthy!
Out!
Out! And take this
ridiculous-looking thing with you!
Where might Miss Amelia be
this morning?
Good morning, Frances.
You're here early this morning.
A working man gets up early if he
wants to have an effect on the world.
How true.
And what a powerful effect you have,
Frances.
Where have you been?
I've been chilled for half an hour.
Hurry up and light a fire.
And don't touch anything
else with your dirty hands.
This is my room now,
and I won't have you messing it up.
What is that awful smell?
When did you last have a bath?
What are you doing?
I don't believe in this!
So you can just stop it!
Stop it, I said!
What did you just do?
Just a little curse I learned
from a witch in India.
Curse?
- What kind of curse?
- You'll see.
But I wouldn't brush my hair as much
if I were you.
It's all right.
I saved it especially for you.
Go on. Take it.
Is this where you live?
You shouldn't be here.
It's too dangerous.
Why don't you like me anymore?
Did I do something wrong?
No, of course not.
I didn't think you'd
want me for a friend...
...now that things are different.
I'm sure you could do fine without
me for a friend...
...but I couldn't get along
without you.
I'm sorry.
I should've known...
...you wouldn't be like the others.
- What's that?
- One knock means ''I'm here. ''
Two knocks means ''All is well. ''
Three means
''The coast is clear. ''
- ''The demon Minchinweed is asleep. ''
- It all sounds so adventurous!
Look, Becky. We have a visitor.
Hello, Becky.
Oh, Sara, I miss your stories so much.
Won't you tell us what happened
to Rama and the princess?
The smoke from Ravana 's arrows...
...finally began to lift.
Rama lay dead on the ground.
Oh, no!
But then
a wonderful thing happened.
The gazelle laid down next to Rama,
giving him his own life.
He's suffering from amnesia...
...one of the rare side effects
of poison gas.
His eyes will heal in time.
His memory...who can say?
He's not my son.
I'm sorry, Mr. Randolph.
He was in severe shock...
...with no coat, no identification.
Since your son was the only name
unaccounted for...
...they assumed this was John.
I am sorry.
All the hoping.
You must think me a fool.
Is it your wish to be wise, sahib?
I don't know.
I suppose a wise man
wouldn't have come here at all.
But if he had...
...he would have looked
closely upon the soldier's face.
What would he have seen?
Pain, sahib.
He needs to be cared for.
He's not my responsibility.
A wise man would remember
that this man was in John's regiment.
If his memory returns, he might
tell what happened to his son.
Perhaps sahib will learn
that John is in British hospital...
...wishing that a kind man would
take him home, away from his pain.
If the plumber comes,
show him the problem.
And don't babble with him.
He's paid by the hour.
And correct the Latin tests
by the time I get back.
Yes, sister.
Hello, Miss Minchin.
Goodbye, Miss Minchin.
Oh, no, not again!
Lottie, not again.
Let's find the locket.
All right...
...it's okay. It's all right.
Come quick!
I think Lottie's possessed.
I got it.
Will you please get that child
under control?
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
What is it?
I thought I saw a mouse.
Hello.
I swear, that child has
a pact with Satan to destroy me.
I'm not cut out for this job.
I have no patience.
And teaching!
All those facts to remember.
I don't like it at all.
You like Frances, don't you?
What?
Of course not. How dare you.
I think he likes you too.
You do?
Really?
I think you should run away
and get married.
It'd be terribly romantic.
What an extraordinary thing to say.
Well, anyway, my sister would be
furious if she found out.
You'd be long gone by then.
Living in some exotic paradise...
...with that dashing young milkman.
I'd better get to the market.
You're doing well, young man.
You're almost home.
You must trust my eyes, sahib.
What's going on?
It's a surprise.
- What are you doing here?
- We brought you something.
Princess Sara, we present you with
something we rescued.
In a dangerous adventure.
- Our very own crusade.
- Risking all our lives.
And mine too.
I don't know what to say.
You are the best friends
anyone could ever ask for.
It's all right.
It's just my little monkey friend,
Hanuman.
Where did he come from?
Right next door. Look.
He likes to visit me.
Can you really talk to him, Sara?
Hanuman, say hello to all my friends.
After Rama came back to life...
...he raced towards the monster's
palace to rescue Sita.
Suddenly...
...Ravana appeared!
I think we better save
the rest for later.
What's going on here?
It's not their fault.
I asked them to come.
You five go downstairs.
I'll deal with you later.
Becky...
...you'll remain locked in your room
tomorrow without meals.
Go!
And you will perform her chores
in addition to your own...
...without breakfast, lunch or dinner.
It's time you learned...
...that real life has nothing to do
with your fantasy games.
It's a cruel,
nasty world out there...
...and it's our duty
to make the best of it.
Not to indulge in ridiculous dreams,
but to be productive and useful.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
But I don't believe in it.
Don't tell me you still
fancy yourself a princess.
Good God, child, look around you!
Or better yet, look in the mirror.
I am a princess.
All girls are.
Even if they live
in tiny old attics.
Even if they dress in rags.
Even if they aren't pretty
or smart or young.
They're still princesses.
All of us.
Didn't your father ever tell you that?
Didn't he?
If I find you up here
with the girls again...
...I'll throw you out
into the street!
What're we going to do?
A whole day with nothing to eat.
Don't cry, Becky.
I'm scared.
If Minchin throws me out,
I've got no place to go.
That's not true.
I'm here with you. I've always
thought of us as sisters.
You have?
Let's make a promise
to always look out for each other.
It's a promise.
Now, what are we going to do
about food?
Starve, I guess.
No, there's only one thing to do.
We'll eat a great feast
before we go to sleep...
...and that will
keep us full tomorrow.
Feast? What feast?
Just look around.
See that table there?
It's covered with a beautiful cloth...
...and candles...
...and trays
of good things to eat.
Come on, Becky.
Tell me what kind of food there is.
But I don't see any food.
Try, Becky.
Just make-believe it.
Remember what you told me?
About the magic?
- Muffins?
- Good! What kind?
All kinds.
Every kind of muffin God ever made,
and all of them hot.
Good!
But we're not dressed right
for such an elegant banquet.
I'm wearing a long velvet cape
with fur on the collar.
And you?
Well,
I always liked diamonds myself.
Rings and bracelets,
and a whole dress covered with them.
Smell those sausages!
I love sausages.
Oh, my Lord!
I think you went
a little too far this time.
It wasn't me.
Go ahead.
I feel like I've been
touched by an angel.
Look!
Just what we ordered.
I'm a little scared about this.
Me too.
Do you think we shouldn't eat it?
I'm not that scared.
Thank you for your kindness.
I'm sorry to inconvenience you.
It is nothing, sahib.
That word...
It sounds so familiar...
...yet I don't know what it means.
It is not English.
We use it where I am from.
In India.
India...
You know it?
No.
Everything's just a blur.
Maybe someday I'll sort it out.
You will, sahib.
You will.
Yoo-hoo?
One minute.
Oh, my God.
Where is it?
Where's the locket?
Give it to me!
What is all this?
Where'd it come from?
I don't know.
I just woke up and it was here.
You stole it,
like you stole this locket!
You're nothing but a dirty
little thief.
It's my responsibility to protect
the children from animals like you.
You'll be leaving
with the police very shortly!
No, Miss Minchin!
I didn't do it.
Miss Minchin, please!
Miss Minchin, I didn't do it!
You heard me.
I want her picked up immediately!
You've removed the bandages.
There wasn't much point.
I can see all right.
Come on in, have a brandy.
Don't worry.
I'm sure they'll believe you.
I have to get out.
But how? My room's locked too.
The police, they're here!
Let's go, boys.
Step lively now.
Quick, help me with this board!
- Right this way.
- Yes, madam.
You'll fall!
I can do it.
I'll come back for you.
I promise.
What is she doing?
Get back in here!
- The little beast is running away!
- We're trying, miss.
Good God!
Don't just stand there!
Go and find her!
Take this one while you're at it.
I heard you calling
in your sleep last night.
Sometimes when I dream,
I sense a part of me that's missing.
It's strange, having your heart
remember what your mind can't.
She jumped like a little animal.
Who's that at this hour?
Let us in, man.
A child from the school
is in your house.
What's going on?
I'm sorry, but there's a child
hiding in your house.
- What?
- Search upstairs.
Oh, not now!
Ram Dass, get some candles!
- Start with the attic.
- Let's go.
Quickly!
Who's there?
Make sure you check the closets
and under the beds!
What is it?
Why are you crying?
Please tell me.
I won't hurt you.
Won't you tell me your name?
That's such a pretty name.
Papa.
What did you say?
- I'm sorry.
- Papa, it's me, Sara.
Do you know me?
Don't you remember me?
Please...
...you've got to know me.
It's Sara. Remember?
Remember India and Maya?
Remember the Ramayana...
...and Emily?
The locket with Mama's picture?
Oh, Papa, please!
Papa, please!
Do you know this man?
Tell them!
This child has no father.
Take her away!
Papa!
I'm so sorry.
Sara!
Papa, don't ever leave me!
- I missed you.
- I love you.
Well, well, well.
I hardly recognized you.
I'm glad you straightened
everything out.
They released all my property.
I came to say goodbye...
...and to thank you
for everything you've done for us.
No more than you tried to do for my son.
- Take care, Mr. Randolph.
- And you too.
You must be glad
to be going home.
Thank you.
I have a surprise for you all.
Whenever you think of me, tell Emily,
and she'll get the message to me.
And when you hug her, you'll really
be getting a hug from me.
Then we'll hug her every day.
That's the first time
anyone's hugged Lavinia.
Bye, Becky.
Come on.
Yeah, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Get over here.
I've been looking for you, Minchin.
- Pick up the bucket.
- When do I get my break?
Follow me!
What do you put in here, rocks?
Bye, Ram Dass!
- Bye, Hanuman!
- Cheerio!
Professional Translation Services
www.gts-translation.com