Have much fun,
by: ErikB.NL
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Wow,
look at that big blue ocean.
How does it feel, Dave,
to see the Pacific Ocean
for the first time?
When did you
get this tattoo?
It's your last chance
to play the truth game.
You know what we should do?
Play the truth game
tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
Do you promise that you will?
- Oh, I promise.
Dave?
Why do you always leave me
in the dark, alone?
I'm sorry, baby,
I was just taking a photo.
Come here, I'm scared. Okay,
I'm here now, it's okay.
Don't do that.
I won't.
Ugh, ew, gross.
I don't like bugs.
I don't know why you
have to put on boots
every single time
you see a spider.
It's day two
of our California vacation.
And today we're going to
tell each other three truths,
that we've never
told each other before.
I'm not doing it.
Come on, you promised,
I'll go first.
Dave...
I hate the New York Knicks.
- What?
No, you don't.
I do.
Years, we've been watching
Knicks games together
and suddenly
now you tell me...
It's your turn.
I don't like that butterfly
tattoo on your ass.
You are such a jerk!
You've kissed it
a million times.
By accident.
That is not fair,
I was 17 and drunk.
You've done lots of stupid things,
you just...
don't have a mark
on your ass to prove it.
See, this is dangerous!
No, no.
No what?
No more.
What do you mean
no more... why?
Because you've
eaten that entire bag.
Here, I'll split half of this
chocolate bar with you.
So you're doing me a favor
by eating half of it?
Remember that, remember that,
for when we get married...
By keeping the chips
that I did want.
Fat husband, kind wife.
That is a very large knife
that you are holding.
The guy at the store said
it was the largest knife
you could fold up
and put in your pocket.
I'll just
hold on to it.
You ready for number two?
Sure.
I don't like that
you don't ever stick up for me
in front of your friends.
What are you
talking about?
You don't, come on.
Yes, I do.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do. And I
always stick up for you.
My turn.
I don't think that you think
I'm good at what I do.
What?
I think you're
very good at what you do.
I think you can
try harder
but I think you're good at what
you do.
That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
Christy.
We're not
gonna be late.
We're not gonna be late,
Christy.
See that?
You're sister's right.
That's me sticking up for
you. Thank you, thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's nice.
Yep, okay, bye.
We made it through
one and two.
Give me three.
Come on. Hmm, I don't wanna
play this game anymore.
Please?
We still have to get through
dinner with your sister.
What's wrong?
Something
just hit me.
What?
Fuck, fuck.
911,
what's your emergency?
Me and my girlfriend
are being abducted.
I'm escaping right now.
What is your name, sir?
Dave Roberts
and Jessica Marino.
Where is your location,
starting with
your street name?
I don't have a street name,
I'm on a trail.
Can you track me? Are
you in immediate danger?
Yes, just get to
Mount Hollywood,
that's where they got my
girlfriend right now.
Sir, sir, hello?
I think I just heard them,
I have to go.
I'm still on the trail,
can you track me or not?
Can you track me or not
... hello?
Sir, hello?
Have you located me yet?
Yes, now we have you.
You're on the south side
of the mountain.
Keep heading
towards the Observatory.
I'm dispatching
a patrol car.
Okay.
Keep this line open.
Stop, stop, help me!
Dave?
Dave, is that you?
Who are you?
Can you say something?
You all right?
Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
What did you see?
Um, I just remember getting
shot and I woke up here.
What happened to you?
The same.
Dave, who would
do this to us?
I don't know,
I have no idea.
I'm scared, I'm really
scared. I know, I know.
But at least we're
together. Yeah.
It's me and you.
Hello!
No...
No, please.
It's okay.
It's okay,
we're just gonna take
this one breath at
a time, okay?
Just one
breath at a time.
Okay, okay.
Breathing's good.
I'm gonna go walk around
and see what's here.
You stay put, okay?
I wanna know where
you're at, at all times.
Okay.
I just bumped
into something.
It's a toilet.
This feels
like a bench.
It's bolted down,
it won't move.
Fuck, this is a...
this is a mattress.
A sink.
A light switch.
We're in some
kind of prison cell.
It's my fucking father.
You don't know that.
Come on,
my father's position.
Hold on to me
tight, Jess.
Something's got me!
Don't breathe.
Don't breathe, Jess.
Oh, my God.
Dave, Dave... Dave!
Dave, wake up, look,
our hands are free, look.
Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
What grabbed you?
I don't know,
it was like a...
metal vice grip.
What's going on?
Who are you?
It's food.
That's why there's
this gap here.
So they can slide this
under like we're in a cage.
What are we,
lab rats?
It could be poison.
Why go to the trouble
of poisoning us
if they
could just kill us?
It's probably...
cement up there.
There's a security camera.
What does that mean?
What do you want
from us, who are you?
If this is about Jessica's
father, she hates him.
Come out!
Dave, Dave,
are you okay?
Are you okay, what happened?
What happened...
are you okay?
Oh, my God,
it's our clothes.
My phone.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Oh my God,
I've got full power.
Oh, please, please, please,
please.
Please, come on,
come on, come on.
I have full reception.
Phones yes, but...
knife, no.
That figures.
Why would they
give us our phones
if our phones actually
worked?
They gave me my watch.
All my apps
are wiped out too.
And a chocolate bar.
I don't even have date
and time on the screen.
And one stick of gum.
And my nail polish.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Here we are, at the beginning
of our vacation,
abducted in LA.
We don't know
why we're here.
And we don't know
who abducted us.
And this could be
the last proclamation
of what's happening to us.
We were kidnapped right
out of Griffith Park,
and just
placed in this cell
and our only contact has been
with someone
who uses these
metal pincers to grab us
like we're fucking
wild animals.
And there's
this weird wheezing sound
every time they come around.
They gave us
our phones back
and there's no reception...
it's fucking creepy.
And they're watching our every
move on a security camera.
I'm scared shitless.
Where are you going?
I'm going to flash them.
Dave?
Dave?!
It's day two
and Dave is gone.
I've been passed out
for 12 hours
and, uh,
I'm officially freaking out.
There's this thing on the top
of my spine.
I'm gonna use
the camera to record it now.
I feel stuffed but I haven't
eaten anything.
I want Dave.
Please come back, Dave,
please come back, Dave.
Come on, come on.
Fuck!
It's day four.
There's still no Dave.
That fucking light is going to
drive me insane.
I just... I don't...
I don't understand how
kidnapping me and Dave
is going to
change the world.
Yeah, yeah?
Something's happening
inside my body.
Like my hormones are changing.
Maybe it's getting off
the pill, I don't know.
Come on, just give me
something.
Dave.
Hello?
Are you okay?
Oh, no!
Ahh, get off of me!
Get off of me!
Get off!
Please!
Please,
I don't wanna die!
Jessica?
Are you okay? I woke
up in a hospital room.
There was a-- there was a dead
abductor on the ground.
I tried to escape.
I saw--
I saw a news webpage,
and there were pictures,
our pictures were next
to pictures
of my dad
in Afghanistan.
It has to be the Taliban.
Fuck, you were right.
Oh my God.
It's day five.
It is the Taliban.
I escaped and I saw
a news headline
and Dave
found an ear.
So that backs it up.
It's probably some sort of
sleeper cell
that's been in
the U.S. for a while.
And I found
this little kid.
They kidnapped a kid.
She was 10,
12 years old.
It's so creepy.
A kid?
And Dave has that same wound
on the back of his neck.
We both have needle marks
on our arms, it's fucked.
I tried a protein bar.
You ate
the rat pellets?
That or starve.
They turned the lights on.
Yeah, now we can see what
a shithole we're in.
Do you hear that breathing?
Hello?
Who the fuck are you?
Please don't hurt us.
Who are you?
I'm Justin.
Summer.
Who kidnapped you?
I-- I don't... know.
My name's Dave.
This is my girlfriend,
Jessica.
We we're kidnapped
in Griffith Park.
Summer,
this is my fault.
We knew four people were
already missing from the park
and-- and we walked right
by the poster,
and now we're here.
I'm so sorry,
I'm sorry.
Four people?
Posters?
What did the posters say?
We... we didn't
look at it.
I read online that
the police were using
blood hounds in the park,
and all they ended up finding
was a Flip cam.
My Flip camera.
That means the cops
must have a good lead.
There wasn't any
talk about hostages,
or... or... or ransom notes
from the Taliban?
No.
Did you see them?
Here.
Here, put this on, wrap it
around like a skirt.
It'll make
you feel better.
The rest of your clothes
should come soon...
part of their procedure
to strip you down, and make
you huddle in the dark.
How old are you two?
18.
When were you
guys kidnapped?
Saturday,
around 7:00 p.m.
What time is it now?
Um, I think by
our calculations
it should probably be about
Sunday morning.
We've been joined
by two new victims,
Justin and Summer,
who also have no idea why
they've been abducted.
Do you two have
any military connections?
What?
Any reason why
the Taliban would kidnap you?
No.
Justin...
it's your mom and dad.
Hey, okay, is this
like a boot camp,
like... like
some kind of intervention?
I don't think so.
'Cause they found
some pot in Justin's room
and they threatened to
send him away.
I mean...
it's gotta be it.
Believe me,
this is not a boot camp.
Are either of your
parents rich?
Justin's father
is Jerry Weiner,
you know, the big movie
producer?
Maybe this is
about ransoms?
Yeah, we found this
little girl.
I mean, maybe
she's being held, too.
Okay, Justin...
Dave?
Hello?
Summer?
Oh, fuck.
Where is Dave?
What are you doing?
No!
No, no, no!
Fuck you, no!
No, no, no,
no, no, no!
Are you okay?
Hey, what happened?
What is that?
Don't-- don't touch.
What is it?
Don't touch it.
Can I look?
It hurts.
Oh, my God.
What did they do?
What, did they
take out your kidney?
What is that?
Fuck!
Just take our
fucking body parts one by one,
sell it off to the highest
bidder?
They look like fucking
metal staples.
Jesus.
It's okay, you're fine,
you're okay, you're okay.
Wow... the first ones.
What?
Your 9-1-1 call got a lot of
people down to Griffith Park
hoping to be
the chosen ones.
What the fuck are you
talking about?
We wanted to get abducted.
Why?
You don't know
who abducted you?
No, do you?
They're aliens.
They're not
fucking aliens.
You got a scar?
Yeah.
Aliens.
I got mine a couple
of days ago!
They entered
your body, right?
I can feel a worm, crawling
around inside me.
I don't feel anything inside me,
so I don't buy it.
Hello, I'm Elliot.
That's Maria,
she's totally freaked out.
She's writing her dissertation
on alien abductions.
But now that it's happened,
she's comatose.
They're abducting couples
to repopulate Earth
with human aliens.
I guess we should be
rejoicing, huh, Dave?
I mean, if it's gonna be between
aliens and the Taliban,
I'd take
aliens any day.
You guys are insane.
I'm a Harvard
PhD'er with degrees
in Physics and Philosophy
with an IQ rated
in the top percentile
of the human population.
Maria believes that's
why the nabbed us,
and, we're not
even a couple.
That doesn't
make any sense.
I mean, why take
Jessica and me?
We're regular people.
Males
are the chosen ones.
Females are
the egg farm.
Got it.
Did the aliens send you
to put out their message,
to be the Messiah?
I don't believe in
any of this alien crap.
Have as many as you want.
They're running experiments
to determine our
body status for future use,
controlling exactly what we eat,
so I say eat.
In the blue room
I saw something
that said Nevada five,
Jeff Miller, RIP, 2009.
Yep, Miller,
he's on our list.
The count was up to nine
in Nevada,
12 in Boston,
six in New York.
In that same room
I found an ear.
Seems to be a bit
more of a ransom move.
Think that Getty kid back
in the '70s.
They're running transfusions
through our kidneys.
Think about it.
Elliot,
you're full of shit!
Where's the proof?
Not once have I seen
one alien gadget
that can't be bought here on
"off the shelf" planet earth.
Here's why, if the FBI ever
captures one,
there won't be
anything to positively
identify them as alien,
no smoking ray-guns.
That's your proof?
No proof
is your proof?
Are you saying that we're
like Adam and Eve?
That's exactly
what he's saying,
they're rounding up
a new herd,
taking us two-by-two,
walking us up the plank to
the alien fucking ark.
Aliens, no need to gas us,
we're on your side.
One time we're gonna
get gassed and not wake up.
If we die,
I just don't
wanna die alone.
That's why you got me.
Let's get married...
right now.
It's too sad.
No, it's not.
I'll record it...
and we can still
have a wedding video.
So...
in case we miss our
future wedding,
do you, Jessica Marino,
take me, Dave Roberts,
to be your lawfully wedded
husband?
I do.
Do you, Dave Roberts...
take Jessica Marino
to be your
lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
By the power vested in me,
in the middle
of this cell,
I now pronounce us...
husband and wife.
You may kiss
the bride.
Day seven.
I read a book
on prison once
by the French writer
Albert Camus.
And he goes through
the four stages of how to
break down a prisoner.
One, you strip
them of everything.
Two, you make them grovel
for the most basic
human fucking needs.
Three, you confuse
the ever-living
fuck out of them
by unexplainable changes
in their routine,
shuffling
prisoners in and out.
And then you follow that up
with long, long, long lonely
periods of isolation.
Well, you fucking
forgot one thing, Camus,
the fucking, freaking,
goddamned red light!
That helps!
That fucking helps!
Come out!
Come the fuck out!
Come on!
Is this funny for you?
Fucking laugh at!
Come on, I'll tear this
whole fucking place apart!
Come on!
It's gas,
cover your mouth.
Cover your mouth!
Get ready to run.
Run!
Get the light!
Let's go.
Fuck.
There's a kid!
No!
Fuck!
Who the hell are you?
We're getting
out of here.
Shit yeah, come on,
Tiffany, get your stuff.
Oh, my God!
Get back, get back!
Stop it!
Please, stop,
you're going to kill him!
Stop it!
You okay?
What up?
You all right, man?
What the fuck?
Buzz, it's Dave,
from Griffith Park 8.
There's eight
of us now?
He has no idea
what's going on.
Shut up, Tiffany,
the guy's hurting.
Look, Buzz,
he has the same scar as you.
Watch it, watch it.
Fucker Tased me
right in the wound.
It's Dave and Jessica,
right?
What do you know?
Hey, man, shh,
they're watching.
Yeah.
Is it the Taliban?
Listen, I can get
on the Internet,
not now,
sometimes late at night.
What?
Our phones don't work.
Your phone sucks.
This thing
is the shit.
They don't seem to care that
I can get on the Internet.
I mean, what
difference does it make?
It's not like I can tell anyone
where we are, can I?
Can the cops
trace your signal?
Scrambled.
This place is
high-tech, man.
Haven't you guys noticed that
your phones never go down?
Tesla's dream,
no wires, no cords.
Secret government mojo.
They've been stealing
people off the street
for some secret,
genetic mission.
They're creating
a super-human.
Oh, Christ,
not this shit again.
Dude, it's all on
the Internet.
Those protein bars
you've been eating,
full of hormones, doing
weird shit to us.
Like stopping your hair
and nails from growing,
never taking a shit,
turning your pee pink.
It's freaky shit,
man.
My beard hasn't
grown in at all.
Yeah, right there,
Griffith Park 8.
There's no mention
of a little girl?
No.
Just young couples
in our prime.
If they don't care that
he's making connections
to the outside world,
then they don't give a shit
about being caught.
Yeah, problem is,
everyone thinks
my Facebook
updates are a hoax.
The abductors broke
my phone camera
so I can't send pictures.
They know exactly
what they're doing.
Well, let me log
into my Facebook.
No.
If we both say the same thing
our our status,
the outside world
might believe it.
All right, fine.
Okay, here's
what I'm gonna say.
You say
the same thing.
Oh, shit, come on!
What's going on here?!
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop!
Get back!
No, get off!
Buzz, Buzz,
are you okay?
Fuck, that hurt.
It's gone.
- What?
They took my phone.
Now we're screwed.
You fuck!
This is your
fucking fault.
How?
You are officially
persona non grata, ass-wipe.
Give me one of
your phones.
Fuck you.
Yeah, get
the fuck over there.
I don't wanna see your
ugly face. Stop it!
Please go, please.
Somebody's
gonna find us.
Don't cross this line!
Have a little faith.
This is my cell,
my domain!
You hear me?
There is no room
for anyone else!
Okay.
This will
keep us going.
Describe walking into your
favorite place.
I'll go first.
Getting off the G,
we're walking past
over to the diner,
and smelling
all that greasy food.
And then walking up
to that dirty door
that you hate touching,
and running
up the steps...
... and unlocking the door
to our apartment.
And Felix is meowing.
Aw, poor Felix.
Yeah.
Poor Felix.
Sitting in
my brothers place,
getting fatter...
and fatter
by the minute.
You little bastard.
Give me one of your phones,
goddamn it.
Buzz,
what are you doing?
Get over there!
Give it to me
or I'll fucking kill you.
This'll take care
of your ass.
Get off of him!
Give me the phone!
Get off!
Get off, get off!
Are you all right?
So they're
only jacking couples,
which means that
that little girl
isn't a hostage,
she has to
be their kid.
Well, if it's not the Taliban
and it's not kidnappers,
sure as shit
ain't the government.
We don't know that.
I mean, think about
what the government did
to unsuspecting citizens
in the '50s.
They gave them LSD,
they did nuclear tests.
Yeah.
What was your
third truth?
I don't remember.
Wasn't anything
too revealing.
I was not trying to
make you any more mad
than the first two truths
made you.
Fine.
I have one since.
Since we've been here?
When we were abducted,
I woke up,
and I looked for you--
we were still on the peak.
And I went running down
the mountainside,
towards the Observatory.
I thought
I'd made it.
I was flagging down
this van.
You just left me?
No.
I was... I was
trying to get us help.
I was on the phone
with 911.
I was trying to
get us rescued.
Why didn't
you tell me earlier?
When would've been a good time
to tell you that, Jessica?
You're so guilty.
When?
Jessica hasn't spoken
to me in hours...
and I'm starting to lose it.
Jess, I need you
to talk to me, please.
Jess, where are you?
Tell me
where you are.
Dammit, this is not
the fucking time
to be mad
at me, where are you?
(lock latching)
Who's there?
Maria?
Where's Elliot?
I don't know.
Jessica?
Jessica.
We only have each other
right now, please.
You just left me.
You're a coward.
It wasn't the bravest
thing I've done.
I've never been
in a fight before...
... except for in
the third grade, and I lost.
I probably wouldn't
have married you
if you wore wife-beaters.
I love you.
Okay, Morris, it's time to
jump through the hoop. Come on.
Come on, Morris.
Come on.
Jump through the hoop,
Morris.
Da-da
Come on, Morris.
Come on,
I feel it.
It's coming, here it is,
here it is.
Oh, come on, you tiny
little alien bug. Yes, yes.
You did it!
Hey!
Ahh, Morris,
you're a champ.
You two are
really losing it.
That's the first thing
you've said in ten hours.
We're losing it?
I'm studying
UFOs at UCLA.
You can study
UFOs at UCLA?
I saw my first UFO
when I was ten,
March 13, 1997,
Phoenix, Arizona,
thousands of people saw it.
For 20 minutes a spaceship
hovered over downtown.
You can look
it up on YouTube.
I can't, actually.
Don't you get it?
We're on a spaceship.
We're not
on a spaceship.
Why do you think they
wear oxygen masks
when they come in here?
Gassing's been around
since World War I.
Armies going in and gassing
the shit out of the enemies,
using gas masks to protect
themselves.
Which is why
they don't touch us.
Why they use pincers.
To avoid contact
with human viruses.
It's the same thing that
killed off the Aztecs.
The avatar's
are here, among us.
That's a really, really...
nice theory, Maria,
but unfortunately,
I don't think it's anything
nearly as fun
as that.
I can't find my kidney.
They're harvesting
organs, okay.
Do you know how much
money can be made in that?
Goodbye, Morris.
This is one small
step for bug
and one giant
leap for "bugkind."
Go out that way.
Go.
It was good
meeting you.
Don't forget to write.
Maria... wake up.
It's completed.
Come on!
Where is she, huh?
You hear me
down here?
You better not hurt her!
You better not
hurt her!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God-- ow.
It's food,
it's real food.
It's lots and lots of
real food... oh, my God.
Mmm, oh my God,
look at this.
Look at...
oh my God.
Oh my God...
it's so good.
It could be poison.
They don't
need us anymore.
They've got plenty
of our eggs.
I mean, how many
Jessicas do they need?
I don't know.
I don't
really think about it.
Well, I'm not
touching that stuff.
I'll wait to see
if you croak.
Okay,
I'll be your guinea pig.
Oh, Morris,
you're going to be a star.
Your name up in lights.
(Jessica) Come on,
come through the hoop.
Come on.
He's doing it.
Okay, come on.
Come on,
give me something.
Please, God,
Fucking shit.
Please, please, please,
please, please.
Oh my God.
Oh, oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God.
I have bars-- oh my God--
come on.
Come on.
Please...
Hi, you've
reached the Marino residence.
Thank you for your kind
messages.
All our thoughts are
with Jessica and Dave,
and we pray they are safe
and will return soon.
Hi, Mommy.
It's me, um,
it's... it's Jessica.
Uh, hi, I'm okay, um...
If you can... if you can trace
this phone call
then maybe you can find us,
we don't know who has us.
But I'm okay,
I'm okay, sort of.
Please.
Fuck, fuck!
Come on, Christy.
Give me something.
Oh my God,
come on, Christy.
Please answer,
please answer.
Jessica?
Oh my God.
Jessica is that...
- Christy, can you hear me?
Oh my God, Jessica,
hello, are you there?
Hi, yeah, it's me,
can you hear me?
Jess, hello,
I can barely hear you, hello?
Christy, don't hang up,
please don't hang up.
Hi, hi.
Can you hear me now?
Hello, please--
fuck, I need help.
Please.
I just had my sister
on the phone.
What are you doing?
Call 911!
Oh my God, oh my God.
Fuck, they shut
off my phone.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Oh my God.
Jesus.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Oh my...
please don't be Dave.
Oh my God, oh.
Oh, Summer,
I'm so sorry.
Oh, oh...
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Maria, Maria, come on.
Come on, look at me,
wake up.
Come on,
we're breaking out, get up.
Maria, we're breaking
out, get up.
Come on, get up.
Come on.
Oh my God!
It's been weeks...
and still
no Jessica.
I've completely lost
track of time.
And I'm going fucking crazy.
And I thought that they
abandoned us here to die,
and then they shove more
goddamned protein bars
under the door.
There's Justin.
He's been here...
... a while.
He just got back
from surgery.
And he hasn't seen
Summer in forever either.
Okay, Justin, go ahead.
Take a look.
Man...
This greenish puss,
is it... gangrene?
I feel something
inside of me, moving.
We need to
get out of here.
Have you noticed that
they've been shorthanded
the last couple weeks?
It's the only reason you
and I are in here together.
They wait until
we fall asleep.
They send the short,
limping one
in here to
collect our bandages.
He's very weak.
He's deteriorating.
He stinks.
We take two cloths,
we're going to wet them,
lay down as if we are
going to sleep,
and when they
come in here to gas us,
I want you to take that cloth
and put it over your mouth.
What makes you
think that that will work?
They are human.
We can kill them.
Oh, gross.
The only reason
they come in here
is to keep it sanitary.
We get him when he comes
over here to pick these up.
I'll keep my foot
on your arm,
I'll tap you when
he walks through the door
to make sure you're
still awake.
Just like that.
Justin, get the light!
Get the light, Justin!
He's human.
He's got some
fucking disease.
Let's go.
Let's go find
Jessica and Summer.
No, no, no!
Fuck!
They must've put this in since
the last time we escaped.
He probably has keys.
I'm gonna run back
and I'm gonna see
if he has
any keys on him, okay?
I want you to stay here
and keep a lookout.
If you see anyone, I want
you to scream to me, okay?
Don't... don't... don't
leave me alone here, Dave.
Justin, stay right here
and yell as loud as you
can if you see anyone.
My buck knife.
I got them!
Dave?
Are you okay?
The lights are out!
I can't see anything.
Dave!
Somebody's coming!
Come back!
I'm hit.
Dave!
I've been hit!
I'm coming, I'm coming.
No, I'm not
letting you in.
No, I'm not letting
you in here.
I'm here, Justin,
hang in there, hold on.
No!
Justin, you okay?
Fuck!
Jessica?
Is Jessica in here?
Dude, you're still alive?
We need to go, Elliot.
They experimented on Maria.
They implanted a chip
in the back of her neck.
She came back, puked
for hours
right in front
of me, and died.
I'm sorry.
But right now we need
to get out of here.
This is your last chance,
Elliot!
They tried to turn her
into a human-alien hybrid,
that's what
the abductors are.
Jessica?
You check this door.
What the fuck?
Buzz?
What's happened to you?
Elliot, come on,
wake up.
Come on.
Jessica?
Tiffany, wake up.
Wake up.
Tiffany, Tiffany.
Jessica?
Jessica.
Wake up.
Jess, Jess, wake up.
Jessica, Jessica.
Come on, come on.
Wake up, wake up,
you okay?
We have to
get out of here, okay?
Up right now.
We gotta go,
we gotta go.
You can put me down.
You all right, are
you okay? I'm okay.
Can you run?
All right.
We never left L.A.
Oh my God.
We're free!
Oh, I can't believe it!
What happened?
I don't know.
How long
has this been?
I don't know,
it's less than a month.
It looks like it's three
months, it's huge.
It's one of them.
Go to the fire escape,
right over here, go.
They've got guns!
Dave, Dave!
Oh my God.
Hold me!
I love you.
Okay?
Okay.
I love you.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org