Because the world is round
It turns me on
Because the world
Is round
Ah
Because the wind is high
It blows my mind
Because the wind
Is high
Ah
Love is old, love is new
Love is all, love is you
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I was really involved
at the beginning
because I nurtured a dream
about a project with George.
For him, this project was
not only doing a show,
but it was also an opportunity to maybe
have the Beatles members left alive
working together
on a creative project again.
(McCartney) I was introduced
originally to the Cirque by my daughter
when she took me to a show
in the Albert Hall in London.
And then George and Olivia
took me to see "O"
in Las Vegas.
George, because he was friends,
I think, with Guy,
started talking about a collaboration
between the Cirque and the Beatles.
There was the possibility
that Cirque
wanted to use Cirque's interpretation
of Beatles music
with possibly musicians on stage
just like, you know, normal Cirque shows.
And I said,
"No, it's got to be the Beatles' music."
The brief that I was given was:
"You've got to have
90 minutes of music
and you create that from anything you
recorded with the Beatles since 1962."
(drum intro)
(Starr) George knew
where all the bodies were.
"That bass line that wasn't used,
we can put that there. There's a drum..."
There was talk of,
like, some new, hip guy,
which sounds all very nice
for a minute.
But, you know, suddenly the new, hip guy
is... There's another new, hip guy.
So we got George Martin,
who's always been hip.
Baby, you can drive my car
And maybe I'll love you
(George Martin) I've lived with
these songs for 40-odd years.
It's great to listen to.
(man) I started, with my father,
started working on this
two years ago.
I suppose when I started doing it, I was
full of fear, loathing and dread, thinking:
"God, I've been given a Beatles tape
and they want me to do something to it
and people are going to
hate me for this."
It's a good retrospective song.
(George Martin) We've been
running around in circles.
OK. All I've got...
I've got nothing left.
Oh
Oh, yeah
(man) I felt like un imposteur.
How do you say? The syndrome of the...
- (man) Impostor.
- Impostor.
Who am I to be there,
sitting in studio 2
with George Martin
and dreaming of which tracks,
which music
we would play with?
(George Martin) But also we're
changing the actual tracks themselves.
And this is a tightrope of taste
that we're walking
because once you start
tampering with Beatle material,
you're tampering with
the Holy Grail.
It's like, sort of,
if I went in
and we overlaid guitars
to make things sound more rocky,
people would go
completely bonkers.
I'd find out my house
had been burnt down.
(Champagne) Like yesterday,
visiting all of those places
and signs of that mythology...
We went to Liverpool yesterday.
Some other guy, now
Is taking my love away from me,
oh, now...
- (Champagne) I feel like a pilgrim.
- (George Martin) You're Scousers now.
(Champagne) So I feel
really excited, actually.
Delighted, excited,
honored and panicked.
I was told in the very beginning
that this was going to be,
or this was already,
an impossible show.
And this is what I deal with
from day one.
Get back
to where you once belonged
Get back, Jo
(Champagne) Honestly,
I was very, very nervous,
thinking that,
from the time that they broke up,
the world is hoping
for a comeback.
Oh, get back
Get back
to where you once belonged
(Champagne) You've got to go
straight to your final destination, OK?
Don't do the whole path.
OK, number two, go.
(man) I play Sergeant Pepper.
Sergeant Pepper is the band leader.
At this stage of the creation,
I would say
he's more on paper.
I guess I'm a mix, maybe,
of George Martin, in a certain way,
and Dominic told me also
that Sergeant Pepper, for him,
represents the father
of Paul McCartney
because he played
the trumpet in a band.
(shouts)
Instead of just dully telling
the Beatles' story:
"It started here and ended there,
and that was this, this and that,"
I tried to touch
the main emotions
that went throughout
their experience,
building this show
as a rock-'n'-roll poem.
("Eleanor Rigby"
by the Beatles)
It is cold!
I'm from Johannesburg.
I'm from the east side of Johannesburg,
which is called Katlehong.
They chose me
for one of the characters,
you know,
for the Beatles' music.
And at that time I didn't even
know about the Beatles and all that.
Like, "I don't know about those people,
so I'll know everything when I get here."
He just arrived just now.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome. We were worried.
We were not hoping anymore, actually.
I'm really glad you're here.
So it's going to be a cultural shock
for you, but welcome aboard.
We're going to take care of you.
Thank you for being here.
Evelyne, you play with Hassan.
Hassan, tu fais un geste
et tu stoppes.
Crab a locker fishwife,
pornographic priestess
Boy, you've been a naughty girl,
you let your knickers down
I am the eggman
They are the eggmen
I am the walrus,
goo goo g'joob
(Champagne) OK, stop.
Now, can I have everyone sing:
"Oompah, oompah,
everybody's got one,
oompah, oompah,
stick it up your jumper"?
OK, so, stand by.
Three, four...
(all chant) Oompah, oompah,
everybody's got one.
Oompah, oompah, stick it up your jumper.
Oompah...
("I Am the Walrus")
(Champagne) And keep,
keep, keep, keep...
OK, give your upper body
a little bit more...
Can you imagine?
We're the first company
that, in 35 years, has been able to make
a deal - a business deal - with the Beatles.
We're partners with the Beatles.
This is big.
The Beatles,
with the name they have,
and us, who never give away
creative control, it was...
How could you find,
you know, creative consensus?
Well, partnerships are difficult. If you've
ever been married, you know that.
But partnerships where there's more than
two people are even more complicated.
Exponentially.
Cirque has a done a lot of business
with our company, MGM Mirage,
and it's been
a two-part partnership.
LOVE is unique
because we have a third partner,
which is the Apple Group
that represents, of course, the Beatles.
One of the things about the Beatles
and the shareholders now,
it's sort of like
an inverted democracy, right?
That if one person doesn't want
to do something, we don't do it.
It's not like
three can overrule one.
Thank you.
This is something George wanted
to happen from the minute he met Guy.
So, for me, this is really
emotional and important.
And I know that he's on one of those
bungee wires up there somewhere.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I just want to thank George
because he's the one
who discovered you for us.
And thank you
for doing this, Olivia.
We lost George and George's input
into the show, and that's a...
that's a great loss.
It made people more determined
to see the project through,
you know,
and make it work and, uh...
We would have done that anyway
if George had been alive.
It just made us all
more determined to do it for George.
I think so.
It did me, anyway.
Here comes the sun
and I say
It's all right
Little darling
It's been a long cold
lonely winter
Little darling
It feels like years
since it's been here
Here comes the sun
(Starr) I've always loved Cirque.
God knows -
it's 10, 12 years I've seen it,
when it was in a tent
in Santa Monica in LA.
So I had no problem with
the Cirque du Soleil attitude,
'cause it's like this fantasy world,
which I loved.
Found my coat
and grabbed my hat
Made the bus
in seconds flat
Found my way upstairs
and had a smoke
Somebody spoke
and I went into a dream
Ah
We've always liked to associate ourselves
with slightly crazy people
'cause we're slightly crazy.
Artists are slightly crazy, you know.
So to work with the Cirque,
we're drawing on
that same attraction.
("Back in the USSR")
Flew in from Miami Beach BOAC
Didn't get to bed last night
On the way
the paper bag was on my knee
Man, I had a dreadful flight
I'm back in the USSR
I met Dominic, actually,
from the inception of this idea,
and I thought he understood
John's songs, especially, very well.
("I Am the Walrus")
It's not so much that
John's character's personified -
I don't think that they're doing that so
much as to really express the songs well.
Help me get my feet
back on the ground
Won't you please,
please help me?
Help me, help me, ooh
Eleanor Rigby
Picks up the rice in the church
where a wedding has been
Lives in a dream
(Olivia Harrison) When I went to watch,
to have a visual imagination
was really difficult for me
'cause I kept thinking, "That doesn't look
right. What are they gonna do there?"
And they'd say, "No. That's not going
to be there. The stage is going to come up
and they'll be gone
and that will be dark."
So that was actually
a whole new experience for me.
And also, you know,
you have your concept about a song.
"Eleanor Rigby" to you might be
something and it might be different to me.
And that's the beauty of music.
You know, the vision of it is in your head.
("While My Guitar Gently Weeps")
I look at you all
See the love there
that's sleeping
While my guitar
Gently weeps
I feel strongly about the two characters
from the beginning of the show,
that, you know,
we have to let go of that at some point.
These characters will be emotionally
very charged at this point of the show.
- Can I speak freely?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I don't particularly
like those characters.
- And I don't know if it's, you know...
- You know what?
I'll tell you what. In the beginning he was
in it too much, if you know what I mean.
(PA) This is a short pause.
If we count
all the titles that we have,
we have 14 John, 13 Paul,
four George and one Ringo.
- But you know what?
- So?
What I'm saying is we're concerned about
trying to respect a balance in between...
Yeah, but, you know, you use John
for the early-day ones, and here comes...
This is the time
that they were the best, and so...
And, anyway, it's not just about that.
It's about what makes you feel the best.
Hey, Jude
Don't make it bad
Take a sad song
And make it better
Remember
to let her into your heart
Then you can start
To make it better
Uh...
I would say first
that I was given a lot of freedom
to write and direct this show
by the Beatles.
And I really appreciated that,
knowing that
the balance in between them
is a very fragile one.
If you have a school photograph
and everybody's clustering around,
the first thing is, "Where am I?" You don't
look for your friend, you look for yourself.
So that if Paul
is listening to a mix of a song,
he's going to listen to himself.
And the same with Ringo.
And Olivia and Yoko
do the same thing.
They are, in a way, looking after their
own territory, perhaps with more care.
Of course they're looking at
the broad elements too.
But you have to juggle with that and sort
of make sure that everybody is satisfied,
that we have
a consensus of approval.
Hey, Jude
Na na na
Na na na na
Hey, Jude
Na na na
Na na na na
(cheering and applause)
My background is theater.
In England, I'm an actor.
You come to
an environment like this,
which is incredibly challenging
for an artist
because of the nature of the company
and the shows it does.
It's very much
like a factory as well.
I'm not used to big productions.
I'm used to, like, people that I know,
people that I understand
and doing the same things and all that,
you know, so it's quite...
It is hard because you're trying to
work through not just interpreters,
but coaches as well
and assistant directors.
You're at the bottom of the food chain,
trying to get through so many people
to articulate what you're trying to say
or your concepts.
Also, in the show itself, there's a director
and eight or nine different coaches...
See you in Vegas. Forget the snow.
It's over. Forget the snow. It's over.
The devil lives here
for a South African.
- Take care of yourself. Have a safe trip.
- God bless.
You'd think that you couldn't go wrong
with Cirque and the Beatles,
and I hope that's true.
But risk in the entertainment business
is just about as scary
as risk in a poker game -
there are no sure bets.
The aggregated investment
in the Beatles show is...
approaches $180 million.
As long as it's empty, it costs me about
$5 million a month, so I'm incentivized
to get the show room
up and running.
Everything was on fast-track - to do all the
negotiations with Cirque, Mirage, Apple,
and do the storyboards
and build the theater.
All that was happening at the same time,
so it was pretty frenetic at times.
Still is, actually.
(Hudson) My reaction was, "I know
where we are now and the world we're in."
And that's
the most important thing to me.
For the first time, it went, "Oh,
it'll be nice to come to work tomorrow."
"It'll be nice to come in and say,
'I see what you want. That makes sense."'
Because we've had five months of
not knowing how to navigate through this.
I think we're going to be able to see
all the characters
and we're going to sense the emotion
on stage because it's very intimate.
So I think
this is a very good thing.
(Champagne) Welcome to the casino.
I'm very happy about
the intimacy of the theater.
It's a room
good for actors and characters,
much more than other,
let's say, big, impressive scenery,
but where the human being
is, like, very small
or part of a machine.
And that leads me to what I think
should be one of your challenges
and state of mind
for this creation -
what we would call
"showmanship."
OK. Sometimes it happens, OK?
The trap is open,
but we need the stage to be closed
and it's not working
and you're all alone on stage.
I want you not to leave, not to escape,
but to stay there
and to make this show
as good as it was one minute ago
up until the light turns green.
- Did you ever stop "O"?
- (man) Many times.
- Many times?
- You have to go on stage and improvise.
Sometimes it takes time,
like 10 minutes or 15 minutes.
You're doing, and suddenly there's
a green light and the show continues.
- OK, you go on stage and you improvise.
- (Hudson) That's the best way, I think.
(Champagne) "OK, let's play with it."
That's the first reaction you have to have,
so this is why I insist on that.
"We're panicking now.
Let's have fun. Let's play with that."
"We have nothing to lose somehow."
Yeah, OK.
So save the show.
I don't think he's like that,
as piggy as that.
I think he has to save...
- He has to keep some control. Exactly.
- Right. OK.
It's... I don't know, because now
we're working with professional people
who have learnt things
from the school and all that.
Because with me and what you call
pantsula and gumboots dance,
I've never been to school for that.
I learnt it from the streets -
from the streets of South Africa,
from Johannesburg.
So I'm learning from them as well
and there's small things
that I can pick up
and then make use of them.
(Champagne) OK, so how many times...
We have 10 minutes?
Well, we could work on
"Lady Madonna". No?
Just show me. I just want to see you
performing together, face to face.
("Lady Madonna")
(Moloi) Working with Natasha,
it's a different thing
because I've only
worked with guys.
And I was even... The first time,
I was even scared to touch her
because I'm not used to
working with ladies.
I'm not just dancing because I know
the style, the routine, but I'm giving.
I want to make people happy,
at the end of the day.
I want to sit down here and know
that people are happy, you know.
Baby at your breast
Wonder how you manage
to feed the rest
("Lady Madonna" continues)
Tuesday afternoon
is never ending
Wednesday morning
papers didn't come
(George Martin) Listening sessions have
been important for analyzing the theater,
which, let's face it,
isn't an ideal place
for putting out music.
We're used to working in a studio
where everything
is geared to a good sound.
Now, here we have an auditorium
which is very, very large
and it's oval - almost circular.
And above what you can see,
there is as much space
as there is below it.
(Baldwin) We did allow for the most
sophisticated audio system ever devised.
They had to have speakers everywhere.
I had to pay for the speakers, too.
They were in the seats and in the seat in
front, and behind your right and left ear.
And they ended up with
several thousands of speakers.
And they felt like,
"We have to give them the music
as if the Beatles
were in the room performing."
Get back
to where you once belonged
(Proteau) I think it's something
like a historic moment to do this show.
All the characters and all the people
in the show, we realize that.
But as a stage performer,
the way that I will play, the way that
I will approach my character, is the same.
Dominic says, "I remember
that your father is a policeman
and I see you
being Sergeant Pepper."
And, strangely, when I tried the uniform,
it was like the photo of my father.
So it was very special. And also
because my father is now in a hospital
because he has
Alzheimer's disease.
He doesn't remember me. He cannot say
who I am and that I am his son.
So it touched me greatly.
("Sgt Pepper's
Lonely Hearts Club Band")
(Giles Martin) I'm of a different generation.
I was born in late '69, when they broke up.
Since I was about 17 or 16,
I started working
in studios with him.
And I learnt a lot through the fact
that his hearing was failing,
and so he needed
another set of ears.
And that was my training,
and a fantastic honor.
I mean, despite him being my dad,
he is George Martin.
Wednesday morning
and five o'clock
As the day begins
Silently closing...
(Giles Martin) It's funny, the studio
he's chairman of has been sold
and he said to me,
"I might take early retirement."
You know,
he's much younger mentally
than a lot of other people
in the music industry,
much more keen on innovation,
and this appeals to him, this show.
He may not have the ears he had
and he's old,
but he still has the brain.
He never accepts second best.
I think that's the best thing for me
with him on this project,
'cause I've had to do lot of chopping
around and a lot of changes.
And...
I know that if he thinks it's good,
then it's good.
(musicians tune up)
- (George Martin) Nice to see you again.
- It's nice to see you.
I know.
I never thought I'd be here again.
We wanted to use George Harrison's
song, "While My Guitar Gently Weeps".
And the version
that everybody knows,
which is on the albums,
was going to be used
in the show.
But then Dominic, who has been trawling
through the Anthology all the time,
listened to one of the tracks
where George virtually made a demo,
and he liked this very much.
And I did agree with him. It had a wistful
quality that the master didn't have.
(Olivia Harrison) There was a version
that everyone wanted to use except me.
It's really beautiful and intimate,
and I was worried that, um...
it would not sustain
in a big theater.
And it was really Dhani that said,
"No, no, no. They have to use it."
(Giles Martin) So everyone said, "What
can we do?" You know, mixing tracks.
And there was nothing that you could take
from another Beatles song.
- Hello, Olivia.
- Hello.
Nice to see you.
Come in.
Actually,
I was really quite nervous about it
because this song
is such a tender song for George
and George isn't with us anymore.
And my responsibility in adding music
to this, it weighed very heavily on me.
("While My Guitar Gently Weeps")
While my guitar
Gently weeps
With every mistake
We must surely be learning
(Olivia Harrison) I don't think you can
put into words what was George like.
You know, he says in some of his songs,
"beware of sadness,"
"all things must pass, " "life goes on
within you and without you."
And that's sort of practical advice
that I have to apply in my life.
He's not here.
("While My Guitar Gently Weeps"
continues)
Ah, lovely.
That was great.
The string players,
they realized the significance of...
- It'll be your last string session.
- Yeah, absolutely.
And playing, you know,
a Beatles string session.
And at the end of it,
they gave you a big bouquet of flowers.
They gave me two dozen red roses,
the musicians.
Normally they hand out invoices,
so there's a...
(George Martin) No,
I was knocked out by that.
(Champagne in French)
How long was this, Armand?
Was it 45 seconds?
("Being for the Benefit of Mr. Kite!")
(Champagne) A crash
with the machine?
(PA) Stand by, please, same place.
We had an automation crash.
(Champagne) Armand, tell us
when you're ready to bring them down.
OK, so we have a couple of events
I would say that we need to prepare for.
On Saturday, as you know,
we have also some visitors from Apple.
Paul McCartney will be here. We're going
to do the listening of music with him.
So they will have
a lot of people around this week,
so we just need to get focused
at the same place.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- Not yet.
Because I'm sure it would be enormously
helpful if you could show Paul
as much of the show visually
as is possible.
Because he hasn't seen it and
he's terribly, intensely curious about it.
The thing is that with the machine,
with the state of the process now,
if we launch ourselves
in a complicated act,
it might stop for an hour and a half.
This is where we're at.
Like this afternoon, we worked four hours
and then we were ready to run through,
and we waited 45 minutes because
everything was turned upside down.
(Champagne in French)
(Lalibert)
(Champagne)
We stick on the plan. This is what we do.
We're on a work time frame here.
There's no way we're going back there.
This is staging.
It's not true that we'll expose ourselves
to things that are unfinished
that will create another debate
for two hours and long letters.
Excuse me, but we're past that.
("While My Guitar Gently Weeps")
(man) They're outside.
They just arrived.
- (George Martin) Oh, there's Paul.
- (man) Here he is.
- Mon ami.
- Bonjour! Bonsoir!
Bon afternoon.
Hi. All right.
- You know Dominic.
- Welcome. How are you?
- (McCartney) Good, good.
- We're thrilled to have you here.
Everyone has butterflies
in their stomach.
(McCartney) Good.
I like to keep everyone
in a state of tension.
My only problem was
nobody knew what we were gonna do.
I'd say, "Well, what is the show?"
(French accent) "Don't worry.
It's OK. It's OK."
"The Cirque will be good.
The Cirque and the Beatles, very good."
I'm going, "No. No, no."
Then finally they came up with this idea
that the show is based on,
with the ladders,
bringing up the building,
World War II
and Eleanor Rigby coming through.
So, you know, I felt,
"Oh, that's enough. It's all I needed."
Just, "What are you
going to hang the show on?"
(Champagne) Stop. Stop it.
("Get Back")
- (Champagne) Stop.
- (woman) We're going to have to stop.
(Champagne in French)
What's new?
It's much taller
than I thought it would be.
I'd like to have a speaker like this. Doing
a concert, you wouldn't have it up there.
- No. That's true.
- So...
- But then we wouldn't be in the round.
- That's right.
(cheering)
(McCartney) The only time
we ever were in the round
was our first American gig,
in Washington.
And they stuck us there
and kept asking Ringo to move his kit.
He had to physically move them each
time. I remember, poor Ringo was facing...
We'd never seen the likes of it. They're
saying, "But you've got to do this."
We said, "No!"
They said, "Yeah, there's audience there."
We said, "Well, they'll just see our backs."
"No, you've got to move."
So we're moving. Poor old Ringo
picking up his bloody drum kit
and repositioning it
between numbers.
- And then, to make it worse, jelly babies!
- (George Martin) Yeah.
- (McCartney) The stage...
- They were thrown at you.
We'd said that our favorite sweet
was jelly babies,
so all the Americans threw them at us -
Bassett's jelly babies.
And the whole bloody floor
was like glue.
("I Want to Hold Your Hand")
Oh, yeah, I'll
Tell you something
(Starr) I just loved
the front line of that band.
You know,
John, Paul and George were that band.
And in Liverpool, if they were playing,
it'd be, like, a band I would go and see
if I wasn't playing
in the band I was with.
And then, by chance, there was a knock
on the door at 12 o'clock in the afternoon
and Brian Epstein said, "Would you
play with the Beatles just for today?"
And I did,
and that's how we became friends.
We were just a couple of kids
walking around town in black
with a guitar over our backs,
walking down the streets like that.
So I remember that -
the very beginnings -
or just going to John's house
and learning chords and playing things.
Then it would be, like, in hotel rooms,
and saying, "OK, I've got a bit of an idea."
So you'd fire off each other.
And it nearly always took us
about three hours, top.
We never took
any longer than three hours.
And every day we did it,
every single time
we came to do it,
we did it.
We finished a song.
We had a knack for it.
We understood what we were trying to do.
Eleanor Rigby
Died in the church
and was buried along with her name
Nobody came
Father McKenzie
Wiping the dirt from his hands
as he walks from the grave
No one was saved
All the lonely people
Where do they all come from?
Where do they all belong?
It's strange, isn't it?
But for me,
what's really strange about this is, um...
remembering writing these things,
you know, which was so little -
little guitar, little old piano, bit of paper
and a pencil, the back of an envelope.
You know,
"Sergeant Pepper" or something.
So it was such a little process,
and look what's happened to it.
(George Martin) It is amazing.
(George Martin) It's very difficult
to escape this heritage that we have.
I've been having memories brought back
every day of my life.
There will be a little knot of Beatle fans
somewhere who says:
"They shouldn't do that. They should
leave the masters as we know them."
But we're embarking on
a new direction here.
- (Lennon) I'm sorry. I feel useless.
- (Champagne) No noise up there.
It's critical.
No noise there. It'll alter the sound.
- (man) We're not going to...
- (Champagne) But McCartney is there.
- (McCartney) Ringo!
- Beep, beep
- (Lennon) Phew! OK, let's go.
- (McCartney) Don't, John. Don't...
(Harrison) Sorry. OK?
- (McCartney) I love that sequence.
- (Champagne) You liked it?
I was playing it safe.
I'm glad I came
and said don't be nervous.
It's something to not be nervous about.
It's great.
But I can play you some more
and have your opinion on that.
I'm sorry for the rest.
It's like...
It's great. Man, come on.
Hey, come on, man, we understand.
We've been at this a long time too.
So a piano will appear...
(Lennon) Are you ready, Ring?
What should I do now?
- (McCartney) Swing it, man.
- (Lennon) Swing it.
- (McCartney) Let's go.
- (engineer) Take four.
- (McCartney) Hey, Jude, don't...
- (Lennon) Paul, it's very hard to sing this.
- (Starr) Do I love you?
- (McCartney) Ringo, stop.
- (Harrison) We'll get that other one.
- (McCartney) Un, deux, trois, quatre.
I love the talking,
'cause it put us in that environment,
you know, in the studio,
and the fun we used to have
before we made these records,
which was always
about the music.
But the chatter I loved.
I thought it made it...
It seemed like it could be now,
in a way.
I thought they could have
made me a bit taller.
That's the only thing I thought,
"My God, can't I be taller now?"
"Seeing as I'm a shadow."
How did the guys
get together to do a tune right?
You were always
on top of one another like this.
I think that's a good thing. It shows the
humor of recording. We always said...
How could you
put up with them?
I'll tell you.
This is what I was going to say.
Because he did Peter Sellers, the Goons...
He did all the comedy records.
My favorite memory of you lot
is when we were doing "Kite"
and I had to do the harmonium.
I became the artist
and you four were the producers.
And you were saying,
"Yeah, another take, please, George."
And I was pumping my guts out.
And they were doing it deliberately,
keeping me going.
"Just try one more, George.
It's not quite right."
George Martin was like
the grown-up in the group.
George was...
We were like the kids.
In fact, they used to call us "the boys."
That was the working title
of this show, wasn't it?
And we always used to joke,
but we were, like...
In the later years, we were, like, 28
and we were still being called "the boys."
We were, like, married with kids
and stuff, "the boys."
But, um...
So George Martin was fantastic.
He could do so much.
He could guide us,
he could understand what we were doing,
he could encourage us,
and he could also pick up the
experimental ideas that we threw at him.
I mean, all I had was a bit of tape
and a pair of brass scissors.
And now it's incredible
what the computer power is,
and stretching sounds
and bending them,
putting them in different keys.
It's amazing what you can do.
(McCartney) You work
how you're told to work.
You work with
what technology you have.
Now, of course, everyone's got
so much technology, they take forever.
We were told to make four songs a day,
so we did.
Not just ready to mix
some other time,
mixed, finished, ch-ching,
put it up on the shelf. There's "Michelle".
Right, let's do "Nowhere Man".
Ch-ching. Put that up on the shelf.
So that meant at the end of the week
you'd done 20 songs.
So, you know,
the early albums, we only did...
It took us, like...
The first album was a day.
- (Giles Martin) I'm pleased he's happy.
- (Champagne) I'm relieved.
I'm relieved.
I'm not sure what I'd do
if he wanted to change the music.
It would rather bugger everyone up,
wouldn't it?
- Now the ball is on my camp.
- (Ste-Croix) You think he will like it?
- You think he will like it?
- Ringo? Of course he will.
Because he's only coming
the day before the premiere.
He cannot come to a session like this.
So to have you...
He'll love it. He's heard this music.
It's just a cool idea.
The way you put the sound
is beautiful.
He's never sounded so good.
They mixed 15 minutes
of the music first
and we went to hear it
and I was blown away.
And I just kept saying,
"Make it crazier."
You know, you can...
you can go broader,
as far as I was concerned.
Not for broad's sake,
but just because it was so cool.
Well, I had to... Once I opened out
the drums, I had to open out the vocals.
Oh, right.
Is this the cool fight?
(man) Yeah, yeah.
("Lady Madonna")
- It's in process.
- No, it's good.
(applause stops)
(laughter)
(Champagne) We trained for that.
Yeah, what to say?
We just watched a little bit of it.
We think it's fantastic, very exciting.
I think you're great acrobats,
great performers.
And I think it's going to be a fantastic
show. Really fantastic. So thank you.
- But I want you to work harder!
- (laughter)
Harder! Much harder!
That's it!
(men sing African song)
("Octopus's Garden")
(Champagne in French)
Every morning, before I get out of bed, I
put the Beatles on and order room service.
No, I don't. I don't.
You know, if it's on, it's on.
Sometimes, I'll play a Beatles record
and say, "Wow, look."
"Listen to that on that track."
Any combination,
it seems that Beatles tracks work
because the tracks
are strong enough.
That's the deal.
("Octopus's Garden")
(Giles Martin) Ringo loves
the fact that his...
He's a great drummer. I mean,
I've learnt how good a drummer he is
because I had the ability to remove him
from a song and put him back on
so the song becomes... He plays the song
unlike any other drummer.
He doesn't play necessarily a fixed, "This
is my drum part," he'll play the song.
He really is a song-playing drummer.
But he has a groove that's his own.
So if I can take him playing one song
and stick it in another,
he loves it because it's like,
"It's me, but it's more me."
("Drive My Car")
Asked a girl
what she wanted to be
She said,
"Baby, can't you see?"
(Starr) My dream at 13
was to play drums.
I started in hospital.
I was in hospital
with tuberculosis for a year,
and so to keep us busy...
I learned to knit.
So they'd give you, like, things to do
'cause we couldn't do a lot.
So then,
every couple of weeks,
a music teacher would come in
with little drums, tambourines, maracas.
I fell in love with the drum. I wouldn't be in
the hospital band unless I got a drum.
Then I came out of hospital and made
my own snare drum out of a biscuit tin
and pieces of firewood as sticks.
I couldn't play, but I could hit.
You know,
and that's how it started.
Now they give me a drum set a week,
you know, if I want one.
It's so hard.
You got nothing, you get nothing.
You got everything,
they'll give you anything.
("A Day in the Life")
I read the news today,
oh, boy
About a lucky man
who made the grade
Well, I think that the show has to have
some gritty or sad moments too,
because that was life.
That is life, you know?
And it can't just be happy-go-lucky
from the beginning to end.
I remember when I went to the Dakota
building and Yoko Ono's apartment
to present
the concept of the show.
And I remember the moment
of John Lennon's murder.
And when I came up there,
I was really, like... (sighs)
I was really shaken
by just being there.
And she offered me a cup of tea.
She told me, "Welcome into this."
Then I just felt more comfortable,
and simply I expressed
what I thought the show should be,
and I left the meeting with
great encouragement and strength.
I read the news today, oh, boy
Julia is the character of a song
on the White Album,
but she is also John Lennon's mother
who was killed by a policeman
driving a car when he was a teenager.
And as you can hear him singing
"Julia" or "Mother" in his solo career,
you can appreciate
how sensitive he was about her.
Then, is it too sensitive to be there
with the blessing of the Beatles?
(Ono) I'm very glad that "Julia"
is something that they're working on.
John had an incredible, incredible
love for his mother.
He was very, very saddened
that his mother never saw him
become so famous.
And that was one thing
that he regretted all the time.
("Julia")
(George Martin) People say,
"What's your favorite song?"
I say, "I don't know -
there were so many of them."
But if I had to pick one of John's it would
probably be "Strawberry Fields Forever".
It's such an extraordinary song.
And the first time I heard it,
we'd been...
Up to that point, we'd been making
albums which we had to rush,
until they made the decision,
wisely and rightly,
not to do any more touring
but to concentrate on recording.
And the very first song
we recorded after that decision
was John's "Strawberry Fields".
As usual, I perched myself
on a high chair, like a bar stool,
and John stood in front of me with his
acoustic guitar and started singing.
No one, I think, is in my tree
And I was knocked out.
I thought, "What an extraordinary song."
"What a beautiful song."
He was a marvelous man,
but he was never really satisfied
with anything he did.
In the year before he died
I spent a night with him,
and we talked about old times.
We had a lovely evening.
Then out of the blue, he said to me:
"You know, George, if I could,
I'd record everything we did again."
I said, "You can't be serious, John.
We did some great stuff."
"What are you on about?"
He said, "We could have done it better."
I said, "What about 'Strawberry Fields'?"
And he looked at me over his glasses and
he said, "Especially 'Strawberry Fields'."
And I thought, "Gosh," you know.
I practically bled for that song.
Nothing is real
And nothing to get hung about
(Giles Martin) After we did it
using the different versions,
Yoko said it was nothing
to do with the music at all,
it was that he didn't like his voice on it,
he didn't like his singing on it.
He had a great voice and yet he was
always asking me to distort it:
"Put more tape echo on it.
I can't bear that."
I think that also John had this vision
in his mind which was a fantastic sound
and he wanted it to be realized.
But he was never very practical.
He would talk to me in
terms of colors and so on, and dreams.
And I had to pin him down, saying,
"OK, what instrument do you use?"
"How do we get this off the ground?"
He didn't want
to be bothered with that.
He wanted to create something
that would just flow.
("Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds")
(man) Le prochain.
Regarde ta boule.
Somebody calls you,
you answer quite slowly
A girl with kaleidoscope eyes
(George Martin) I want you to fix me up
so that I can do one of those things.
- You mean hang with harnesses?
- I could join her up there.
- Well, no problem.
- (both laugh)
(cheering and applause)
So today with your presence,
we do the traditional "Lion Den."
It's the first time we run it with the public.
So you are our lion,
and we hope that you don't eat us.
Well, we try to run it, as much
as possible, smoothly for you guys,
and enjoy everything with love.
(cheering and applause)
("Gnik Nus")
Something in the way she moves
Attracts me like no other lover
Something in the way she woos me
I don't want to leave her now
You know I believe, and how
(Champagne) Go, go, go!
They're all late. They're all late.
("Within You Without You"/
"Tomorrow Never Knows")
We were talking
(woman) Guys, pull north.
Pull north.
And the people
Who hide themselves
Behind a wall
Sitting on a cornflake
Waiting for the van to come
(Champagne in French)
Man, you've been a naughty boy
(Champagne) His gas mask?
Where his gas mask is?
I am the eggman
They are the eggmen
I am the walrus
Goo, goo, g'joob
Here come old flat top
(Champagne) Video, no?
They're late.
This looks bad.
He got hair down to his knee
Got to be a joker,
he just do what he please
- I want to talk to him.
- Well, he's going to come. Guy's...
- Why don't we just go to that table?
- Sure, sure.
I mean, what is it? It's sleazy.
This "Come Together"
is not a sleazy song.
- It's a song of political coming together.
- I see what you mean.
(Ono) You're not inspired
with John's songs?
- (Champagne) I am, honestly.
- Great.
Tell me what you were inspired about,
and the words.
He's singing so well and I feel so sorry
for him because nothing's going on.
It's just making it like...
Oh, "atmospheric" is the word.
But it's not atmospheric.
Beatles' thing is power. Also...
I have, you know, a lot of respect
for him, for having done this much.
And of course we're all still saying, "Well,
could you just..." et cetera, et cetera.
Olivia is going there and I'm going there
because we are very protective
of our husbands' songs, you know.
So he's got a lot to deal with, really.
(Champagne in French)
- (they laugh)
- Oh, la, la, la, la.
(woman over PA) OK.
("All You Need is Love")
- All you need is love
- All together now.
- Everybody.
All you need is love, love
Love is all you need
(cheering and applause)
- See you later.
- See you.
(Olivia Harrison) OK, see you later.
- You like it?
- When the pictures come up...
- The smile?
- The smile, it just kills me.
And, you know, Dhani is just like him,
so to see exactly...
- It's amazing.
- It's like twins.
Oh! No, you can take that after.
Very cold ice.
My feet are going to shatter.
- (man) If only you could feel them.
- Exactly.
Do you think this is a departure,
this is a change for Cirque?
The dancing, the staging,
the way it's presented?
Yeah, it is. This is more a musical
than a Cirque show.
- You could have told us!
- Huh?
Yeah, you know, 'cause I think
people are gonna be surprised.
- In terms of not having many acrobatics?
- I hope they're not disappointed.
- Yeah, that type...
- Well...
I don't think they expect...
People will come for the music,
the encounter of the Cirque du Soleil
and the Beatles.
Now it's a question of tidying up things
and clarifying things.
That's why it's important to get... That's
what I like about the opinion of Yoko.
This is what we need,
because we were not there with them.
You know, especially with Yoko and you,
we were not there.
With George I didn't have time
to go into detail of each of the songs.
I want to make sure
the details are addressed.
Like I said, at the end
we have to make a decision
because we can't do a show
in a community way.
As long as there is something...
each one has something going,
- and there's some focus.
- But it's the same thing.
That's what I always bring back
to the people I work with.
I said, "It's not about
who has the best idea."
"It's what is the best idea,
who will prevail."
Of course, everybody has
his personality, his pride
and his ego,
and I totally understand that.
But at the end, we're all there
to serve one thing -
- the show for the public.
- The show.
They will decide who will live or die
with what we do.
(Proteau) In Montreal, I have a family.
I have three sons.
May we present the Beatles?
So this is a kind of sacrifice
that maybe I do.
The last time I saw them was at the end
of March because my father died.
When I open the show, I just feel that...
that I'm doing that for my father.
I bring a message from Apple,
my boss Neil Aspinall,
and from Paul and Ringo
and Yoko and Olivia
to wish you the very best for tonight,
and express their profound respect for
your skill, your energy, your courage.
One day, this will all seem
like a long time ago,
so savor the moment,
and you have my best wishes.
(Champagne) We all know we worked
really hard. It was not an easy one.
All the Beatles themselves - Paul, Ringo,
Yoko and Olivia and their family,
tonight we have the honor to have also
Cynthia Lennon, first wife of John Lennon,
is going to be here with Julian Lennon
and Sean, and Dhani Harrison.
And all those people gathered around
with what you've done,
with what we've all done together.
I think it's great that...
You know, bodies go.
George Harrison is dead, but we can
really say that his spirit is with us.
And we gave a body
to that spirit all together.
- Peace and love. I love you.
- (applause)
(hums to himself)
You told me once that you had
le symptme de I'imposteur.
- Yeah.
- How's that now?
Well...
It's hard to answer that, you know?
I'm happy that we...
I've been a lot... very nostalgic of the '60s,
you know?
All those years of freedom and revolution.
And I felt I was having my 20s
more in a decade of cynicism.
And I've been pretty cynical myself.
And I feel like today I'm back to the roots,
you know,
of dreaming that we can take a sad song
and make it better, as the man said.
("Because")
Because the world is round
It turns me on
Ah
(Giles Martin) It was a great experience.
I've tried to get away from
the George Martin mantle, you know?
"George's son, in he comes."
But it's been a huge learning curve for me.
And it's your dad, you know?
You spend time going through his stuff.
In a way, a father and son team,
you know, in years to come,
I'll probably remember this more
than I'll remember the show.
Ah
Love is old, love is new
I guess I'm used
to all these celebrities and stuff.
Even in South Africa, I've been
performing for big people,
like even the president of South
Africa, which is Nelson Mandela.
I've performed for him. So it's not
a big deal. It's not a big issue.
I'm just going to do what I do best.
You know what I'm saying?
("Get Back")
(cheering and applause)
Jo Jo was a man
who thought he was a loner
But he knew it couldn't last
Jo Jo left his home in Tucson, Arizona
For some California grass
Get back, get back
Get back to where you once belonged
Get back, Jo Jo
(Starr) If you hear that music,
there's four people.
It doesn't matter that only Paul and I
are here, there's still four people.
There are only two of us now,
but in spirit there's four of us, you know?
("Being for the Benefit of Mr. Kite!")
The band begins at ten to six
When Mr. K performs his tricks
without a sound
And Mr. H will demonstrate
Ten somersets he'll undertake
on solid ground
Having been some days in preparation
A splendid time is guaranteed for all
And tonight Mr. Kite is topping the bill
(cheering and applause)
("Drive My Car")
Asked a girl what she wanted to be
She said, "Baby, can't you see?"
I wanna be famous, a star of the screen
But you can do something in between
Baby, you can drive my car
I was sitting next to Ringo,
so it was great because
I just kept saying to him:
"What a fucking great band we were."
I should be more modest. I should say, "It
was good" and, "Thank you very much. "
But I don't care now.
The Beatles is over. It's a body of work.
And I can now stand back and say,
"That was great."
("Octopus's Garden")
I'd ask my friends to come and see
An octopus's garden with me
I'd like to be under the sea
In an octopus's garden in the shade
We would be warm
Below the storm
(Starr) You think, "Oh, you know,
it was a long time ago."
And what's interesting is that now
we are these people
but the music still carries on.
It's not our personalities, it's the music.
("A Day in the Life")
I read the news today, oh, boy
Four thousand holes
in Blackburn, Lancashire
And though the holes were rather small
They had to count them all
Now they know how many holes
it takes to fill the Albert Hall
I'd love to turn you on
(applause)
(Lennon) Just keep going, then.
(Starr) Just keep going.
(Harrison) Keep going.
(McCartney) Keep going.
- (Harrison) Peace.
- (Lennon) Peace.
I look at you all
See the love there that's sleeping
While my guitar gently weeps
I look at the floor
And I see it needs sweeping
Every time I heard George's voice
or saw the image,
you just want to pull them off the...
You want to pull them right there
because it's so close
and the voices are so intimate
and so familiar,
the way that they just resonate
in your ear
in a vibration that nobody else has.
How to unfold your love
Dhani said it was hard for him. It made
him very sad because it's so close,
and yet, you know...
physically unsatisfying.
But, spiritually, very satisfying.
("Within You Without You"/
"Tomorrow Never Knows")
Try to realize it's all within yourself
No one else can make you change
And to see you're really only very small
And life flows on within you
and without you
(cheering and applause)
(Lennon) Come on, George.
You ready, Ring?
- (Starr) I think.
- What shall I do now?
- (McCartney) Swing it, man.
- Swing it, swing it.
- (McCartney) Right, let's go.
- (engineer) Take four.
(strums)
- Ringo.
- Do it again.
One, two, three, four.
("Strawberry Fields Forever")
No one, I think, is in my tree
I mean, it must be high or low
That is, you can't, you know,
tune in, but it's all right
(Ono) It's the light that is not here
anymore, you know?
It's that one, isn't it?
John was there.
But it's very different from listening to his
songs and seeing a show of it, you know?
It always makes me feel a little bit...
Well, sad is not the word.
Well, it is, you know.
I feel sad that he's just a voice now.
He rollercoaster
He got early warning
He got muddy water
He one mojo filter
He say one and one and one is three
Got to be good-looking
'cause he's so hard to see
Come together
Right now
Over me
(Starr) John had a huge heart, you know.
He was a good man.
He was very sharp
and, you know, had this quick wit.
And George in the band
was my best friend.
Paul is incredible.
An incredible man.
He's still the most melodic bass player
out there today.
You know, it was
a really, really great band.
("Back in the USSR")
Show me round the snow-peaked
mountains way down south
Take me to your daddy's farm
Let me hear your balalaikas ringing out
Come and keep your comrade warm
I'm back in the USSR
You don't know how lucky you are, boy
Back in the USSR
Let me tell you, honey
I'm back, I'm back in the USSR
It's so good to be
Well
Back in the USSR
("Sgt Pepper's Lonely Hearts
Club Band (Reprise)")
We're Sgt Pepper's
Lonely Hearts Club Band
We hope you have enjoyed the show
Sgt Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band
We're sorry but it's time to go
Sgt Pepper's Lonely,
Sgt Pepper's Lonely
Sgt Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band
(McCartney) I'm very proud, of course,
of the music we made with the Beatles.
I can hardly believe it.
It's a slightly strange feeling.
It's like, I wake up some mornings
and think, "I was in the Beatles?"
There's only four people who could say
that in the world, in the universe,
and I'm one of them.
So it's a slightly sort of strange feeling,
but an amazing one.
("All You Need is Love")
Love, love, love
There's nothing you can do
that can't be done
Nothing you can sing
that can't be sung
Nothing you can say
but you can learn how to play the game
It's easy
Nothing you can make
that can't be made
(Starr) You can't help but feel
with the chat, with the songs,
that we're all still there.
It's a bit like when we did
"Free As A Bird", when John had left us.
We all had to pretend that he was making
a cup of tea in the kitchen or something.
You have to get over it, you know?
Because we were this incredibly
close-knit four-man band.
All you need is love
Everybody.
All you need is love, love
Love is all you need
(George Martin) Each generation,
as it grows up,
finds the Beatles for themselves.
And now... My children found it
for themselves
and my grandchildren have found it
for themselves. And it will go on.
It really will.
Love is all you need
(cheering and applause)
Just one special round of applause
for John and George!
(loud cheering and applause)
(McCartney) All right,
fade it there, Charlie.
(Harrison) Take seven.
OK, put the red light off.
(Lennon) This is Johnny Rhythm
saying good night to yous all,
and God bless yous.
(laughter)
(The Beatles:
"Can You Take Me Back")
Can you take me back
where I came from?
Brother, can you take me back?
Can you take me back?
Nobody was very sure
how this was going to work.
It was the first show that Cirque had
that didn't have live musicians.
We were thinking about
perhaps using live musicians
for which I would score,
together with tape.
What we didn't want to do is
to do what everybody else had done
for the last 35 years
since their separation,
which is a replica
of The Beatles on stage
playing imitation of The Beatles' music.
So we thought, "We've got to do
something different,
not just play one Beatles song after the
other. We have to offer something new."
We have the technology to do something
different, so we thought we'd give it a go.
("The Word")
It's so fine
It's sunshine
It's the word, love
Beep-beep, beep-beep, yeah!
(man) Because of the nature of the project,
we felt we had to do it with computers.
So obviously the next stage with that
is that all the tapes have to be digitized -
put into a format that then George and
Giles could manipulate and play with.
(Giles) We took all the Beatles
catalog on tape -
original Beatles four-tracks,
eight-tracks and two-tracks.
So, in layman's terms, what we're doing
is deconstructing what's happened
and putting it back together
so it works in a surround format.
(Hicks) Even though
the rhythm track is on one track,
another tape has the bass,
the drums and the guitars separated.
So they have a way where they can lock
that tape up to the master tape,
then just have all your separate elements
to work with and play with.
So that was just really sort of
delving back, dissecting history, really.
(Ringo Starr) Not just a mix of the music,
not just the same track remixed.
It's the track reworked.
So it's like it's new, you know?
And how difficult is that
when most of it was on four-track?
'Cause that's how we worked when
we started - four-track to eight-track.
We never got to the 72s,
like they have now. So it was great.
(Paul McCartney) We'd said to them,
"Be as experimental as you can."
And so they gave us
this little demo playback.
And suddenly they'd taken
"Within You Without You"
and put the "Tomorrow Never Knows"
drums on it,
and then started to bring in a guitar
from here and a thing from there.
And we went, "That's it exactly.
That's what we're talking about."
And I think we were all amazed
at how well it worked.
I'll bring in the song gradually.
("Tomorrow Never Knows" intro)
(segues into "Within You Without You")
If I take down "Tomorrow" now...
(Yoko Ono) George Martin and Giles
Martin did justice to The Beatles' music.
And not only that,
but I think they went a step further.
This is showing
that the music is so strong,
an incredible artistic power that it has,
that it can be used in a different way.
(Giles) You're playing with what
everyone holds so precious and dear.
They heard it and loved it. They loved
the idea of not doing something ordinary.
And The Beatles never, never did
anything ordinary.
(George) "Tomorrow Never Knows"
has got a great rhythm sound to it.
Ringo's drums are very hypnotic.
And, of course, "Within You Without You"
is a well-known George song.
It was a matter of fitting, really,
because there are moments when
you have to stop it, then start again.
You have to work with the original rhythm
and tabla sound, and so on.
I think George's love of those sounds
of Indian instruments was so prescient.
They're timeless instruments
and he always knew that.
That's why he loved them
and he loved to use them.
But it's amazing that today they actually
add some kind of edge to the music.
(Giles) The Beatles recorded in a very...
My father was economical - he always
says this - with how things were done.
People go,
"You could use the drums from Help!"
You go, "No, I can't. They're with the
guitars and the bass." That's a challenge.
People go, "Why didn't you use this?"
But they're tied together.
Turn off your mind, relax
and float downstream
It is not dying
There's so much space in what they did.
Suddenly the tablas had more importance
and the different instruments
just flying around the room.
I think that was the one
that really sold everybody on it.
Life flows on
within you and without you...
Ringo and Paul were constantly saying,
"Go as far as you can."
"We will stop you. Go as far as you can."
But there's only so far you can go before
you start completely losing your mind.
And "Octopus's Garden"...
I had an idea to put Ringo on his own,
you know, because it's such a...
To leave his vocal kind of bare.
(George) We wanted to use
one of Ringo's tracks,
and the show director was very keen
on using "Octopus's Garden".
We started off with a very orchestral
and dreamy beginning,
and most people who listened to it
said, "Where did that come from?"
"That doesn't sound like Beatles to me."
Well, of course, it was Beatles
and it was something I had scored.
And we cut up Ringo's voice,
so that instead of singing the track as it is,
he does it quite slowly and leisurely
to begin with.
(Ringo) I'd like to be
Under the sea
In an octopus's garden
In the shade
- He'd let us in
- ("Yellow Submarine" starts)
Knows where we've been
In his octopus's garden
In the shade
I'd ask my friends to come and see...
(Giles) Ringo was dead interested in this.
He'd come in, and I worked in order,
so "Octopus's Garden" hadn't been done.
He kept saying, "How about
'Octopus's Garden'? You done it yet?"
He'd come in, and I'd go, "No."
And so there was this pressure
mounting up. "You go mad on it. Go mad."
"Don't, you know... Don't skimp
on my song!" It was one of those things.
And I'm thinking, "Oh, OK."
So originally I tried
the end of "Glass Onion".
I put that with his vocal and
actually it sounded too dark and eerie.
I wanted him on his own - Ringo on
his own - 'cause he's such a character.
Then I took the strings from "Good Night",
put them up a tone
and changed the key slightly.
And, it's funny, it just fitted.
And I did the whole of "Good Night",
and my dad came in and goes:
"What are you doing?" I said, "Well,
I thought this might be kind of cool."
He goes, "Oh, my God!"
He goes - and this was good direction -
he goes, "But you should
just chop the first verse back in again."
"Don't play the whole thing."
So there's a bit of a clash going on.
- The rhythm track to "Octopus's Garden".
- ("Octopus's Garden" plays)
- It's just very light. And so...
- That's the original?
That's the original.
So we combined "Lovely Rita".
(drumbeat)
Yeah.
And it's the same groove
'cause it's just Ringo.
We didn't sample or move anything.
And he's exactly right, too.
It has to be right on the nose.
(Ringo) I'd like to be
Under the sea...
(Giles) Because you wanted
the double time in this section here,
in comes "Polythene Pam".
(percussion on "Polythene Pam")
(segues into "Helter Skelter")
The end goes into "Helter Skelter" - the
guitars and rhythm are "Helter Skelter".
So I really threw in the kitchen sink.
It finished off with "Sun King".
I threw everything at that song,
to make Ringo happy.
I was so nervous when he came.
He knocked on the door
and opened the door to my studio -
a lot like this one at Abbey Road.
I played it and I stood in the corner.
First of all, I thought he had
my voice a little too loud.
I always tried to hide it a bit.
But it works 'cause it's very pure.
(Ringo) I'd like to be
Under the sea...
When he heard the strings of
"Good Night", his face dropped -
he's not that keen on his vocal
on "Good Night" apparently,
so he was delighted
that it didn't happen, and he loved it.
In an octopus's garden with you
(intro of "Lady Madonna")
(Giles) The Beatles did
a lot of amazing psychedelic stuff,
really heartfelt stuff
and a lot of rock stuff.
But "Lady Madonna" is slightly more,
I suppose, funky in a way.
So we got the track up
and I listened to it on four-track.
What we do is listen to each four-track.
They bounced, so we put them together.
The first track you hear
when you get it out is this.
(piano solo on "Lady Madonna")
- Yeah.
- Which is...
- I think it's almost boogie-woogie.
- Yeah. It's great.
And then on top of that, they put this:
(drum and bass play
on a different channel)
Obviously listening to themselves
in the cans.
- If you put them both together...
- (complete version)
On "Lady Madonna" we departed
from our normal procedure,
because normally we would lay down
a rhythm track and overdub things on it.
But this song was piano-driven, really -
Paul on his piano, working away.
The bass and other things
were added later,
which was not what we normally did.
See how they run
Lady Madonna,
baby at your breast...
You know, when The Beatles started,
none of them played keyboards at all.
And when they were successful, I think
Paul got himself a piano first, John later.
And yet in a very short space of time Paul
became extremely good at playing piano.
And on "Lady Madonna"
he plays a brilliant piano.
Lady Madonna,
children at your feet,
Wonder how you manage
to make ends meet...
(Giles) I didn't realize that
Paul wrote "Lady Madonna",
then John wrote "Hey Bulldog"
to compete with it.
I had no idea
there was this thing going on.
They're both great piano parts and
it's funny how they just work together.
So "Bulldog" on its own, which is:
(instrumental section of "Hey Bulldog")
I always wanted to get "Hey Bulldog"
in the show 'cause it's such a fantastic riff.
So put some other tracks in.
I got it to work in the solo section, and
I thought what would work over the top
and found that Eric Clapton's guitar solo
from "While My Guitar Gently Weeps"
complemented it nicely and it just worked.
It took a while to get it all to work.
I used the organ from "I Want You
(She's So Heavy)" to glue it together.
(guitar solo
together with "Hey Bulldog")
- And you hear it sped up.
- (fast-paced guitar)
Billy Preston was very good but...
There's the "Lady Madonna" vocals...
and the guitar coming in.
And then back into "Lady Madonna".
(George) Yeah. It's mixed together nicely.
(McCartney) You finally hear Ronnie Scott.
The sax player in the middle is Ronnie.
I knew Ronnie, so I said to him, "Would
you work on this record we're making?"
"We just need a nice wild... (imitates sax)
Sax solo. You can do that, Ronnie."
He said, "Yeah, mate, I'll do that."
So he came along to the session,
played it great, but in the mix we buried it.
I met up with him weeks later after and
he'd heard it on the radio or somewhere.
He said, "What did you do to my solo?"
I said, "Sorry, Ronnie. It's pop."
"This isn't jazz. It's a different thing.
It still sounds good, Ron, great."
But he was always a bit pissed at...
you know. "What are you doing?"
So now finally in the show,
at the end of "Lady Madonna",
you suddenly hear... (imitates sax)
So he's not with us anymore,
but he would have been pleased
to finally be revealed in all his glory.
(sax solo)
(applause and cheering)
("Strawberry Fields")
Let me take you down
'cause I'm going to...
(George) "Strawberry Fields",
I thought, would be difficult to handle
because it's one of my favorite tracks
and it's also a kind of icon too.
It's something which
many people would say:
"Don't ever touch it.
That is sacrosanct."
No one I think is in my tree...
(Giles) Yoko had some tapes from home,
from John's house,
with him doing early versions of
"Strawberry Fields".
(George) No one had heard this bit.
So this is him at home.
(Lennon) No one I think is in my tree...
(Giles) So what we did is we took
all of the versions we could find
and tried to combine them
in one long, expansive song
that just starts off at home
and finishes in the studio.
That is I think it's not too bad...
And while I swanned around,
you tuned all of the...
You pitch-shifted on the tape machine,
like in the old days, all the versions
so they're all in the same key.
(George) It was near enough, but not
near enough for what we were doing.
Living is easy with eyes closed
Misunderstanding all you see...
(Yoko) This show has to be something -
especially John's songs -
had to be something
that John would be proud of.
That was my concern, in the sense that
the spirit of the songs will come out well.
Nothing is real
And nothing to get hung about
Strawberry fields forever...
So now this is the final version -
the final four-track that was done.
I think I know I mean yes,
but it's all wrong
(George) Which is like the master, so...
(end of "Strawberry Fields")
(Giles) So we used this drumbeat
as a foundation
'cause the song was faded in and out,
and we still used everything that's there.
They faded in and out because, of course,
in those days we had no click tracks
to keep us in synch.
And, in fact, the rhythm went
completely haywire at one point.
But there was a bit after it
I wanted to include.
I couldn't edit them together,
so the only thing I did on the mix
was to dip them down to nothing,
with the bit that was wobbly,
then bring them back again.
So everybody said, "Great idea -
fading, then coming back."
I didn't tell them the reason,
but now we don't need to do that.
(instrumental section
of "Strawberry Fields")
We should run through
the separate elements,
and the first thing we hear
is "Hey Bulldog", very quietly.
- And "In My Life".
- (piano solo on "In My Life")
- And "Penny Lane".
- (trumpet solo on "Penny Lane")
All happening with the...
And "Piggies" comes in.
Meanwhile, we have the whole rhythm
from "Strawberry Fields" at the end.
And "Hello Goodbye".
Hela, heba, helloa...
I think, because The Beatles
had so many musical ideas,
that often they work together.
They're so sort of melodic
in what they did, that it's amazing how...
It's the same brain,
it's just wedged together.
(Yoko) There's no other Beatles
in the world. It's one and only.
The Beatles were like
acrobatics of the mind,
and Cirque du Soleil
is the acrobatics of the body.
And so when it comes together,
it makes a kind of... something
that's whole. I like that, yeah.
("Baby, You Can Drive My Car")
Asked a girl
what she wanted to be
She said, baby, can't you see...
(Giles) No one has done this before.
No one has gone to their own library
and used themselves.
It's great The Beatles have done this first.
Others will do it,
and I hope people like the results
that have come from it.
(McCartney) There will be people who are
purist and want to hear it as it was.
And you know what? It exists as it was.
So, you know, just play your vinyl.
And I think that's great.
That is how it was.
But obviously,
by allowing it to happen,
we don't have a problem
with the remix aspect.
(George) We're talking about probably
the most important popular music
of the 20th century,
and it's historic what we're dealing with.
Of course, over a period of 90 minutes
we can get in a lot of songs
which are icons,
which are wonderful.
And when you hear them in a big room
with what we've been able to do with them
in surround sound,
I think you'll have a few shivers
going down your spine.
("Being For The Benefit Of Mr. Kite")
Yeah, it's great.
I think that Lennon's voice all over,
- it sounds very good.
- (George) You're happy with it?
Yeah. What about you?
I'd like to be able to hear the voice nearer,
without being louder.
We can certainly play with that,
see if we can, without increasing the level,
bring it closer by using the center
speakers on the back of the chair.
When we did the 5.1, I think
we put a slight slap on him as well,
and that may just make him boom
a bit more.
He doesn't sound like he's a ringmaster.
I fear, with the experience, people thinking
The Beatles are selling out to Las Vegas.
I think Las Vegas...
There's a lot of money in Las Vegas!
You can do things in Las Vegas
you can't do anywhere else in the world.
Even The Beatles couldn't build
a $100m theater
to put their music into
which has 6,000 speakers inside.
- So each section has its own sound?
- Its own sound, yeah.
You get a little spill from...
The idea of working with The Beatles'
music is something that is unbelievable.
It's unbelievable because I grew up...
That generation was my generation,
and I know The Beatles' music inside out.
So the idea of working with
The Beatles' music is just fantastic.
("La Marseillaise" opening
of "All You Need Is Love")
Love, love, love
Love, love, love...
(Deans) We started as a proscenium
theater, then it went to a 360 theater.
So now the whole auditorium
was around the stage,
which for me, as a sound designer,
it's like: Where do you put the speakers?
(Giles) There's left and right,
as you have at home - The Beatles stereo.
Then we have a speaker in the seat -
we can have this voice up close.
We have a speaker 80 feet away.
You can have strings or you can have...
We have speakers in the ears -
they're three inches away.
So my idea is to almost feel like you're
dropping someone into a Beatles studio
where they're
surrounding you completely.
- So I'll hear these two and this?
- Plus you'll hear...
The subs for these are in the ceiling.
And then you have what's behind, like
what we saw downstairs, what's behind,
what's in front and then the main PA
as well. And then we can move sound...
- I can't hear a word, mate! Sorry.
- ("Hey Jude" plays loudly)
(all laugh as McCartney mouths words)
(Deans) The kind of work I do,
I like for the audience to be enveloped.
I like for the audience
to be a part of the show.
And I'm not trying to do it so people go,
"Oh, there's sound around me."
It should just belong. It should be
as one unified joint production.
("Hey Jude" carries on playing)
- I know this song. Yeah.
- Takes a little time, but...
- Good singer. Who's this?
- We're trying to find out.
- French guy?
- Yeah!
Thought so.
OK, let's move on.
("La Marseillaise" opening
of "All You Need Is Love")
Here we go!
Love, love, love...
(Giles) I've seen a lot of shows in Vegas
and they sound very good,
but they don't sound... English!
I don't mean that in a nasty way at all -
it's great -
but I think The Beatles
should sound like The Beatles.
Me and Paul are pretty good
at getting that done.
Paul Hicks is... Funnily enough,
he's Tony Hicks' son from The Hollies.
There was a band called The Hollies.
I've only worked with "son-ofs" - that's the
most important thing: "Who's your dad?"
He's been at Abbey Road for a long time,
so we'll be here mixing in the theater.
- I was going backwards and forwards.
- There's too much sub going on.
(George) Cirque du Soleil
has never had a show
where the music has been
entirely on tape or on recording.
They've always had live musicians.
And they were scared, because
what happens if something goes wrong?
You know, if a guy hurts himself
and we have to fill in time.
So we've had to make our music
continuous,
but, at the same time,
we've had to have flexibility within it.
There are a lot of places where
you can stretch the music a little bit.
Or, if it comes to really dire straits,
then the operator will be able to loop
a particular section and keep it going.
("Help!" comes to an end)
(man) On normal Cirque shows -
other Cirque shows -
the music is written
in the creative process of the show itself.
And so that way the music
is also eligible to be changed
over the course of the show
from minute to minute.
Here, once a song starts
that the whole audience knows,
you don't want to mess with it,
and we don't want to mess with it either.
("Here Comes The Sun")
Little darling
It's been a long, cold, lonely winter
Little darling...
(George) We're playing back
in 5.1 surround,
which is quite a different experience
to stereo or mono.
I love it. I think it's great.
And it gives you another dimension
to the music.
Hela, heba, helloa...
(Whiteley) Because so many
of the songs stay the same,
projections are heavily synchronized
to the music.
Lighting punches
happen at the exact same time,
so, from here, we're spitting out numbers
those departments can synchronize too.
We've done a lot of preparation.
There's no other Cirque show
with so many elements so tied together
because they've never had
the music established
40 years before the show was created,
like this one.
- (George) They'll have a playback?
- (man) That's the first time for them
- to hear the real thing.
- I hope they like it.
Because in the rehearsal room
we have commercial versions.
And even then they haven't heard it
like you and I have heard it.
We'll play you the opening of the show.
To explain what we've done
with the music is,
all of the music for the show is basically
chopped Beatles stuff from all their tapes
that my dad, who's here now,
recorded from 1962 to '69 onwards.
(cheering)
(George) We're embarking on
a new direction here.
The sounds we are getting are not
the sounds you would get in a studio.
It's a different thing altogether.
It's sounds that are designed to enhance
the visuals and make the show exciting.
("Get Back" starts up/audience cheers)
Jojo was a man
who thought he was a loner
But he knew it couldn't last
Jojo left his home
in Tucson, Arizona
For some California grass
Get back
to where you once belonged
Get back...
When I heard the show in Las Vegas
and heard the sound quality,
I was blown away,
'cause I'm listening and thinking,
"Wow, that snare drum!
I can't believe it!"
It's just so clear, it's so original.
You just don't hear snare drums like that.
("Glass Onion")
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah!
("La Marseillaise" opening
of "All You Need Is Love")
(man) I remember clearly when
we decided with Dominic Champagne
to work in 360 degrees.
For me it was impossible to see the show
in an Italian way of seeing a show -
I mean, from being outside the frame
of the theater.
It's very difficult.
It's a nightmare to work like that.
For the light, for the video, for the stage,
for the artists, it's very, very tough.
All the exits of the stage
are inside the audience.
Also, even the video projections
are in the audience.
And it's very important because it means
the audience can have the feeling
that they are inside the show
and can live an experience.
(man #2) The challenge is
to use those screens
as something who places you not outside
of the scene, but inside the stage.
My approach is more working with
optical effect, natural effect.
It's always better
if I can shoot what I have to do,
and then, of course, I put filters,
I composite and everything.
But my first material, the roots are
always better if I do it like a handcrafter.
And I'm sure of that.
- It must be all right.
- OK, let's go.
- Don't, John.
- Sorry.
- (McCartney) OK?
- (Lennon) Yes.
(McCartney) Now!
- (Lennon) Yes, sir, that's my baby!
- (McCartney) Straight away.
- (Lennon) We'll do this again.
- OK. Go!
(Lennon) Sorry. I feel less than useless...
Apple Corps gave to Cirque all those
recording sessions between '63 and '69,
during which The Beatles
were recording their songs,
with which I could make a montage.
(McCartney) Are we still
recording even now?
(Lennon) No, I don't think so.
You're not being funny, are you?
- I can hear voices talking.
- (Ringo) Nobody was listening.
(moaning)
(Lennon) I get something in me head and
all the walls of Rome couldn't stop me.
They had a great sense of humor. That's
what I tried to show with this montage.
- (Lennon) Paul, it's very hard to sing this.
- (Ringo) Do I love you!
Ringo, stop!
Of course, I had to sign so many papers
to promise I won't sell it over the net!
But for a year and a half
it was such a terrific experience.
- Let's get this show on the road.
- (Lennon) OK, George. Go ahead.
This is the greatest band in the world
and you can hear them work together.
And it's clear as if it was now.
(man, in French)
I think their effect was universal.
Their arrival turned the world upside
down, seduced it and revolutionized it,
and it was the same everywhere.
("Revolution")
You say you want a revolution
Well, you know...
I started making costumes
at the age of eight.
I like to give the impression
that the character
comes from an unknown world
but, by the details in the costume,
by the manner in which
he or she moves,
give the impression that that world exists
and the character is a part of it.
(woman) So this is all costumes
from the presentation.
(applause)
There are references to
absolutely loads of names,
like Michelle, Polythene Pam,
Sugarplum Fairy,
Father McKenzie, Lady Madonna.
There's an entire universe,
an entire population of people, really,
who exist most probably in
the imaginations of thousands of people,
because there were thousands of people
worldwide who listened to The Beatles.
So we had an enormous responsibility in
portraying these characters in the show.
All the lonely people
Where do they all belong?
(woman) I have two favorite props.
The first one is Eleanor Rigby's train
because it's really made from junk parts.
So it's really made from antiques,
so it has a real life. It's not newly made.
This one carries a lot of...
I remember each part of this train,
where I buy it.
The other one is Sgt Pepper's bundle
'cause I think it's so...
Because it's a sphere, it's like
he's carrying the world on his back.
It's very poetic, I think, this image.
Dominic is a prop-consuming guy.
I heard in previous Cirque shows a lot of
things were sent to the Cirque warehouse.
But on this show, I think I have two or
three major props who were cut. That's it.
And there are more than 600 props
on this show.
And every day he's asking for more -
he's still asking for more.
I'll continue to feed him because I like
that my work is so integrated in this show.
Dominic is a guy
who puts a lot of stuff on stage.
We are both big hockey fans,
so we have a kind of a language.
We have one puck, OK?
So where's the puck now?
I have to put the audience
to help them to focus, to follow the story.
Sometimes we have two pucks, but we try
to keep the game at one puck on the ice!
But it's a big, big challenge.
And after that, I have to express myself
artistically, you know,
with colors, with emotion
in relation to the music,
with rhythm, with beat,
with counter beat,
with a big "Whoo!"
And I like to, you know...
"Lucy In The Sky",
it's a song that I like visually
because I put a lot of hours on that,
but with some other songs I'm more
laid-back and just install a nice ambiance.
That means that
we recreate a place, a space.
Woke up, got out of bed
Dragged a comb across my head...
Those tracks have been recorded
40 years ago,
and everything that I discover with
the lyrics and the way they were writing
and the sense of humor they had...
They were four guys, you know?
That's what I'd like people to remember
when they come and see the show.
("Glass Onion")
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah...
(man) The first time I get inside
the Abbey Road Studio
I was thinking about all the archives
that I was supposed to check.
So many pictures.
I spent a week, ten hours a day,
watching The Beatles.
And finally, I had this flash.
I was like, "We don't want to be
documentary with our concept."
"We want to bring the people
inside their universe."
"So why don't we use all the pictures
to create one picture?"
Finally it's a little movie,
so you have thousands of movies
inside the image,
like a kaleidoscope of their life.
("All You Need Is Love")
(refrain) Love is all you need...
(McCartney) Right, fade it there, Charlie.
OK, put the red light off.
(Lennon) This is Johnny Rhythm saying
good night to yous and God bless yous.
(applause and laughter)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org