Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Oh, you're so good.
Oh, yes.
I am the best, baby.
- Oh, yeah!
- Oh, that was a tit.
That is a tit! Yes!
Oh, you're so big!
Oh, yeah.
That's right, baby.
Doggie wants
to hide his bone.
I'm bone smugglin', baby.
Man, would you shut up!
Hey, Jimmy.
Just wanted to say sweet dreams.
Sweet dreams.
Good night, Mom.
Kiss good night.
- Something wrong with the reception?
- Yeah. Yeah.
There's this nature show
that I'm trying to watch.
And the birds are
all scrambled and I can't even...
Do me! Yes!
Baby! Ride me like a pony!
The thing must be broken
or I sat on the remote or something.
- Getting ready for bed, son?
- I'm all set, Dad.
No, I think he's tried
to watch some illegal channels.
- lllegal channels?
- This is just bad reception, honey.
- Spank my hairy ass!
- What's that?
Oh, baby!
You know what?
Just give me this, please...
- Oh, my God!
- And let's get this...
Okay, okay. What the hell's
the matter with this thing?
Yes!
lllegal channels? Shit!
If there's any channel that should be
illegal, it's that all-woman's channel.
Lifetime supply
of pantihose or some shit.
Did you see The Little Mermaid
on TV the other night?
- Ariel, man, she's so hot!
- She's a mermaid, dude.
Yeah, Oz. But not when she's on land.
Come on, Vicky, it's Stifler's party.
We got to go. It'll be great.
All that happens at Stifler's parties
is people get drunk and do it.
Come on, Kevin. Open it.
It's a big, thick envelope,
Vicky. You got in.
If you think so,
just open it.
Fine.
"Dear Miss Latham: We're sorry but
after keeping you on the waiting list...
for the past couple of months, we've
decided that you are now rejected. "
- Shut up!
- You got in.
Yes! I love you!
You think I should wear
this shirt to Stifler's party?
You've worn that shirt for
three days in a row, man!
Guys, she said it.
- Said what?
- She said she loves me.
Holy shit, dude! The "L" word?
Cornell's not
that far from "U" of"M."
It's only, like, seven hours.
And you get to drive across Canada.
Beautiful country.
Whatever. It's doable.
What we should do today, in band...
instead of playing our instruments
regularly, we should play backwards.
- That'd be so funny!
- Yeah.
You're talking about a post-high school
long-distance relationship.
-And you and Kevin haven't even done it.
-That's not why we're going out.
What do you expect him to drive
to Cornell for? Milk and cookies?
We're gonna have sex
when he's ready and I'm ready.
It's got to be
completely perfect.
I want the right time,
the right moment, the right place...
Vicky, it's not
a space shuttle launch. It's sex.
- Finch.
- Here's the man we are looking for.
- What's goin' on, buddy?
- Same ol'...
Finch.
You got the Latin homework?
It means, "My dog ate it. "
It's Latin.
- It's a Latin joke.
- Latin. Just drink your coffee.
- No, Jim, it's mochaccino.
- What?
It's mochaccino.
It's not coffee.
'Nova!
- What's up, dude?
- Comin' to the party, you fuckface?
Depends if my date
wants to stop by.
- I'm workin' on somethin' new.
- I got an idea about something new.
How about you guys
actually locate your dicks...
remove the shrink-wrap
and fucking use them!
Dude, it's gonna happen.
She's a college chick.
Oh, right.
I'll see you guys tonight.
I'll look for you
in the no-fucking section.
I'm shooting for a 9:00 E.T.A.
Beer in hand by five after.
Breath check.
- I wish you wouldn't do that.
- You got something up your sleeve?
This is a foolproof plan,
my friend.
I have a serious question
to ask you guys.
You know Nadia the Czechoslovakian
chick? She might be there tonight.
Do you think she would prefer...
laid-back Jim, or...
cool, hip Jim?
I don't think it really matters
with that shirt you're wearing.
You're the one with the girlfriend,
and you're still stranded on third base.
Hey, at least I know
what third base feels like.
- You're still just a batboy.
- Batboy. What are you talking about?
Guys, uh...
What exactly does
third base feel like?
You wanna
take this one?
Like warm apple pie.
Apple pie, huh?
McDonald's or home-made?
Gentlemen, destiny awaits.
That's number five and six
for the Stif-meister!
Holy!
Nadia! Buenos dias.
Glad you could make it.
I'll be back for you later.
- Another party sultan!
- How ya doin'?
Welcome to Stifler's
Palace of Love, fellas.
The keg's back there! Enjoy!
Vicky, Jessica! Great to see you.
Glad you could make it.
Bitches!
- Sherman!
- Hey!
What the fuck
are you doin' here?
Fellas! What's goin' on?
Sherman. Not much.
Just scopin' the babes.
Indeed!
Some fine ladies here, boys.
Confidence is high.
Repeat. Confidence is high.
Sherman is movin'
to DEFCON 2.
Full strategic arsenal
ready for deployment.
You have somethin'
goin' tonight, Sherman?
You see that
Central chick, Bernette?
She's around.
Seems she's taken a liking to me.
It's time she experienced
the Shermanator.
Yeah, okay, Sherman.
Whatever.
I'm a sophisticated sex robot
sent back through time...
to change the future
for one lucky lady.
- Go get 'em, tiger.
- I'll be back!
- Hopeless.
- Completely.
- Hi.
- Hey, Vic.
Oh, shit.
Guys... Guys...
There's Nadia
and she just looked at me.
- She just looked at me.
- Why don't you go talk to her?
You're right, Kev.
I should just go talk to her.
I could do that.
Sure.
That's great!
See ya later.
We're here for the party.
What party? There's no party.
Weird.
Try the house down the street.
So, what's your major?
Post-modern feminist thought.
Oh, cool.
Great night, isn't it?
Sure.
Yeah, it's just somethin' about the
springtime that's just cool, you know?
Like the smell
of fresh rain or somethin'.
- Suck me, beautiful.
- What did you just say?
Suck me, beautiful.
My friends call me "'Nova,"
as in Casanova.
That's pathetic.
Jeez, you don't
have to laugh at me.
There's just some things
you need to learn.
- Like what?
- Well, you've got to tone it down.
You don't need to come
to a place like Lookout Point...
and spout off cheeseball lines
to be romantic.
- Okay.
- You have to pay attention to a girl.
Be sensitive to her feelings.
Relationships are reciprocal.
Come on, Casanova.
I'll take you back to your friends.
Vicky, think it's time to take
the next step in our relationship?
- Tonight?
- Yeah, it's such a perfect evening.
I mean, it's how you've
always pictured it, isn't it?
Damn, my farts fuckin' stink!
Dude, you gotta take a shit!
You smell like a Yeti!
Or not.
Just relax.
You actually said that?
Shut up!
You did a hell of a lot better
than I did with Nadia.
Oh, thanks, Jim, that's great.
That's really reassuring.
Hey, no problem, 'Nova.
Hey, don't call me 'Nova any more.
I'm a fraud.
You guys are pathetic.
I'm gonna find myself
a little hottie.
"Suck me, beautiful"!
- Let me know.
- Okay.
Keep going.
I should be able
to talk to girls.
I'm articulate.
You know, I got a 720
on my S.A.T. verbal.
Bullshit.
There's no way.
I kid you not, man.
Look. Listen.
Copious.
Verisimilitude.
Oh, now.
Suck me, beautiful!
- Damn it, Stifler.
- Checkout time!
Please, vacate the room.
You are such a jerk.
God, I can't believe how many
cool people are at this party.
And you got a keg too!
- Wow!
- Indeed.
Oh, wait.
I left my beer downstairs.
No. No.
Here, babe!
Thanks.
You're really beautiful. Oh...
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
You know what? I don't know
if I want to be doing this.
Doing what?
You know, if we hook up tonight...
tomorrow I'll just be some girl
you go telling your friends about.
No way!
Steve, you could at least look at me
when you say that!
Look.
Sarah, I wouldn't go telling stories
or anything about you.
I promise.
So, just relax.
Take it slow,
and let the good times roll.
- Okay.
- All right.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Xenophobic.
- Regurgitation.
- I know that one.
- Kevin likes it.
- He likes getting head.
Gee, what a total shocker.
What about you, Vicky?
I mean, have you just
never had one with Kevin...
or have you never
had one, period?
I've had one.
- I think.
- Okay.
That's a no. No wonder
you're not psyched about sex.
You never even had one manually?
-I've never tried it.
-You've never double-clicked your mouse?
Nice!
Jesus! How much did you drink?
Hey, Stifler?
- How's the pale ale?
- Fuck you!
- That's Stifler's mom?
- Yup.
Shit. I cannot believe a fine woman
like this produced a guy like Stifler.
- Dude, that chick's a "MILF."
- What the hell is that?
M-I-L-F... Mom I'd like to fuck.
Yeah, dude!
Oh, yeah!
- Yeah! MILF!
- Hey, guys.
- Come here.
- Sherman, what's goin' on?
Don't you think you fellas
could try a little tact?
I got company,
if you know what I mean?
She's hot!
If Sherman has sex before I do,
I'm gonna be really pissed.
The Shermanator?
Come on, man.
MILF! MILF!
MILF! MILF! Hey, dude.
What are you doin' to her, dude?
Oh, my God, bro, dude.
Enough of this blow job bullshit.
I gotta get laid already.
That's nice.
Really, really nice.
- Can I have a ride?
- Sure.
- Vicky, wait.
- Not for you.
Yeti! I am the Yeti!
- Good morning, gentlemen.
- Finch, where were you last night?
What happened to that
foolproof plan of yours?
I was going for a fashionably late
entrance, and I was too late.
So, no ladies left.
It was a very
special night, very special.
Guys. Guys.
- I'll never forget this.
- I'll never forget it, either.
Thank you.
Fellas, say goodbye
to Chuck Sherman, the boy.
I am now a man.
I highly recommend
you join the club.
We were doin' the wild thing
all night.
I'm exhausted.
I don't get it.
How the hell did you do that?
It was just my time.
Best of luck to you boys.
- I cannot believe this.
- Come on, guys.
We should be happy
for Sherman.
No, we shouldn't be.
You know, I put in months
of quality time with Vicky.
Sherman meets a chick
for one night and scores.
- This is just wrong.
- No shit.
How the hell am I supposed
to become Mr Sensitive Man?
We're all gonna go to college
as virgins. You realize this, right?
They probably have special dorms
for people like us.
All right. I got an idea.
But it's got to stay between us.
It's really simple. We just
got to make an agreement.
It's more than an agreement.
- A bet?
- A pact.
No money involved.
More important than any bet.
Here's the deal.
We all get laid before we graduate.
Dude, it's not like I haven't
been trying to get laid.
Think about when you work out, Oz.
You gotta have someone to spot you.
Someone to keep you motivated.
That's what we can do for each other.
We'll be there
to keep each other on track.
Separately we are flawed
and vulnerable, but together...
we are the masters
of our sexual destiny.
Their tiger-style kung fu is strong,
but our dragon-style will defeat it.
Guys!
The Shaolin masters from
East and West must unite!
- Fight, and find out who is number one.
- Guys!
Come on. You're ruining my moment here.
This is our very manhood at stake.
We must make a stand,
here and now.
No longer will our penises
remain flaccid and unused!
We will fight for every man out there
who isn't getting laid and should be.
This is our day.
This is our time.
And, by God, we will not stand by and
watch history condemn us into celibacy.
- Amen.
- I like that.
- We will make a stand. We will succeed.
- 'Bout time!
We will get laid!
The sex.
It's got to be valid,
consensual sex.
No prostitutes.
That's what you're thinkin', Finch.
Busted.
So, basically,
prom is our last chance.
- Dude, prom sucks.
- I know.
But you gotta think
about it this way.
I mean, all the parties afterwards?
The chicks are going to want to do it.
He's right. It's like
tradition or something.
- Like the Rose Bowl.
- So, that gives us...
Exactly three weeks to the day.
- We're gonna do this.
- To the next step!
Next step!
Well, did you get the flowers?
You'll get her back soon enough.
- You think so?
- She likes you.
- I like her too.
- Do you love her?
You know what?
You can't really ask me that.
If you want to get her in the sack,
just tell her you love her.
- That's how I was duped.
- Look, Jessica.
I don't want
to dupe her.
All right. What you need to do
is learn how to press a girl's buttons.
You have to give her
what she's never had.
- What's that?
- Let me give you a hint.
Comprende?
- You mean an orgasm.
You got it, stud.
Well, I'm pretty sure
that I've given her a...
- No, you haven't.
- Well, there was one time...
- No.
- Oh, man.
Look, kid, it's up to you.
The big "L" or the big "O."
Dickhead!
You gotta see this.
Do you believe in magic
In a young girl's heart
How the music can free her
whenever it starts
And it's magic if the music is groovy
It makes you feel...
What did you cocks do to him?
I'll tell you about the magic
It'll free your soul
But it's like tryin'to tell
a stranger 'bout rock 'n'roll
Great.
See you next time.
Hey, guys.
Came to watch me in action?
- I think you sounded pretty good.
- Yeah, man.
I think you need
your balls reattached.
- Hey, keep it down, dude.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
This place
is an untapped resource.
I mean, check it out.
These vocal jazz girls are hot.
Why the hell is he joining
jazz choir so late?
Maybe he's preparing for
another senior year at East?
You guys,
we don't even know him.
You dipshit!
You're expecting to score with some
goody-goody choirgirl priss?
These chicks don't know me. I can work
the sensitive angle here, fellas!
You know, it's just like
that college chick told me.
All that you gotta do
is just ask 'em questions...
and listen to what
they have to say and shit.
I don't know, man.
That sounds like a lot of work!
Just a second!
Come in. Come in.
Oh, Jim, you're here.
I was just walking
by your room and...
And, you know, I was thinking, "Boy,
it's been a long time since we've had...
a little father-son chat. "
Oh! I almost forgot.
I bought some magazines.
Do you just want to flip
to the centre section?
Well, this is the...
this is the female form.
And they have
focused on the breasts...
which are used primarily
to feed young infants...
and also in foreplay.
Right.
This is...
This is Hustler.
And this is a much
more exotic magazine.
Now, they have decided to focus
more on the pubic region...
- Right.
- The whole groin area.
Look at the expression on her face.
You see that? See what's she's doing?
She's kind of looking
right into your eyes saying...
"Hey, big boy.
Hey, how ya doin'?"
- You see?
- Right.
Shaved is a magazine
I'm not too familiar with...
but, again,
if you flip to the centre...
section...
Well, you see the detail that
they go into in this picture here.
It almost looks like a tropical plant
or something, underwater thing.
- Do you know what a clitoris is?
- Oh, my God.
- Don't say, "Oh... "
- I know what a clitoris is.
You've been there and back.
You know everything.
I've learned about it in Sex Ed.
I don't need you to talk about clitoris.
You know what?
I'm sorry, okay?
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have got hot there.
You know what I'm going to do, Jim?
I'm going to just
leave these books here...
for you to peruse at your...
at your leisure.
Wait!
Well, safer than a tube sock.
- Okay, that was good.
- Yeah.
- See you at dinner.
- Yeah. I'll see you at dinner.
So, Finch, this is your plan?
You know, I don't think girls are
into the whole mini-golf thing.
Kevin, I'm sure
that they're not.
Actually, there is one small matter that
I need to ask for your cooperation in...
- in the spirit of this pact.
- What do you need?
Whatever you hear about me, you agree.
And tell all the boys the same thing.
Look, I gotta go.
Sixteen minutes round-trip.
You know, Finch,
it's senior year.
Don't you think it's time you learned
how to take a dump at school?
When was the last time you looked
at the facilities in this school?
Excuse me.
That's Paul Finch, right?
You've seen him
in the locker room, right?
My friends, they want
to know: Is it true?
You know, that he's equipped.
I have no idea. Finch showers
with his bathing suit on.
I mean...
As a matter of fact, it is true.
The guy's huge!
- Does he have a date for the prom yet?
- No, definitely not.
All right. Thanks.
Oh, man!
So I was thinking maybe you could give
me some advice, brother to brother.
I thought you might know a trick
or somethin'to make her...
Orgasm?
- Yeah.
- What's good here?
- Try the spicy tuna hand roll.
- What?
How do you do that?
Never mind that.
Pay attention.
Is that all that you're interested in,
tryin' to get your girl into bed?
It'd be good to be able to,
you know, return the favour.
Be nice to know she enjoys
things as much as I do.
Good. That's what I wanted to hear.
Now you qualify.
- Qualify for what?
- You've just inherited the Bible.
It originally started
as a sex manual...
this book that some guys
brought back from Amsterdam.
Each year it got passed on
to one East student who was worthy.
Now, it's full of all sorts of stuff
that guys have added over the years.
But you have to keep it a secret
and return it at the end of the year.
So now you know. Good luck.
- If you believe in magic
- Magic
Don't you bother to choose
If it's jug band music
or rhythm and blues
Just go and listen
It will start with a smile
That won't wipe off your face
no matter how hard you try
Your feet start tappin'
And you can't seem to find
How you got there
Do you believe in magic
Yeah, magic
What was that?
- Sorry.
- No, it was good.
Well, it...
It came from the heart.
Keep it coming.
All right, people, good work.
Don't forget. The state competition's
a couple of weeks away, so keep on it.
- Not bad, Chris.
- Really?
Thanks.
Heather, right?
You've got this sort of
Frank Sinatra thing going on.
Right. I feel like I've discovered
this whole new side of me.
I mean, music is so expressive.
Okay, I agree, but aren't
you supposed to be out...
trying to decapitate someone
with your lacrosse stick or something?
Oh, sure, sure. You know,
I know what people think.
It's like, "Oz, he's just this
kick-ass lacrosse player. "
I also play football, by the way,
but that's not all that I am, you know?
Of course, I didn't...
It really bothers me when people
try to pigeonhole me like that.
You? You think
I don't get that?
God, it's like just because I don't
get drunk and barf every weekend...
that people say, "Look, there's this
Goody Two-Shoes choirgirl priss. "
Yeah. So, like,
what else do you do?
Well, the same things you do...
like hang out
with friends and stuff.
Why? What do you think I do?
I just realized that I don't know
anything about you. I was interested.
What do you want to know?
You know, stuff about you.
All right.
Mom, I'm home!
Oh, yeah.
It's not what it looks like.
Well, we'll just tell
your mother that...
that we ate it all.
Goal by number eight,
Chris Ostreicher.
- Nice game.
- Good game.
Hey, what are
you doin' here?
Just enjoying my first exhilarating
lacrosse experience.
- You kicked butt.
- Oh, thanks.
- Chris...
- You can call me Oz.
- Do I have to?
- You can call me Ostreicher.
- What's your middle name?
- Forget it.
- I won't tell anyone.
- Well, neither will I.
So, I had this thought and...
It may seem like
it's way out of left field.
I don't know if you can...
but since I'm not going with
anybody, I thought that maybe...
Those guys sucked ass!
Choir chick, what the hell
are you doing here?
Well, I was asking
Chris to prom.
So, do you want to go?
Oh, yeah!
That would be great.
Just don't expect Oz
to pay for the limo!
Stifler, fuck!
I mean...
Why do you got to be
so insensitive all the time?
What?
Whatever. Look, don't forget.
My cottage after prom.
On Lake Michigan.
Wait up, you pussies!
Well, I gotta hit
the showers now...
but I think this is gonna
be really, really good.
Yeah. Me too.
All right.
- Happenin' Oz!
- Working with the choir chick?
What d'ya say, fellas? I just dig
those cute little sweaters she wears.
Nuts you do, you little horn dog.
Yeah!
Yeah, baby!
Spank me!
Hit that high "C"!
What's goin' on?
I was being selfish
and majorly insensitive.
I'm a total idiot.
I mean, a fool, a buffoon.
I think shithead
really says it.
You're right. I'm a shithead,
and I want to make it up to you.
Oh, yeah? How?
Vicky, shh.
Your parents are downstairs.
- Kevin, don't stop!
-Just a second.
Hon, can you tell Vic
to come on down for supper?
Holy shit!
Shh. You know there's
no lock on your door?
I'm coming!
- Oh, Jim!
- Dad.
I was just looking at
the old family portrait out here.
Well, that was
a fun day wasn't it?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
Jim, I want to talk
about masturbation.
I just want you to know that
it's a perfectly normal thing.
And I have to admit,
you know...
I did a fair bit of masturbating
when I was a little younger.
I used to call it
"stroking the salami. "
You know,
"pounding the ol' pud. "
I never did it with baked goods.
But you know your Uncle Mort?
He "pinched the one-eyed snake"
six times a day.
See, it's like practise
for the big game.
You see?
It's like... It's like...
banging a tennis ball
against a brick wall.
Which can be fun.
It can be fun, but it's not a game.
- Right.
- It's not a game.
What you want is you want
a partner to return the ball.
- Do you want a partner?
- Yeah, I want a partner.
- You do?
- I want a partner.
Want a partner.
Good. Good.
So, once Hal becomes king,
he has to take on...
the responsibilities of leadership
and turn his back...
on his old,
drunken friend, Falstaff.
You see, Hal is going through a rite
of passage, much like you all are.
So make most of the time you've got
left together. You'll miss it later.
So, does your tongue cramp up?
Nah. You get kind of dizzy, though.
Wow. That's amazing. She's probably
gonna want to do it soon.
All right. Class dismissed.
Still questing after
the Holy Grail, huh, guys?
- Hey, where's Finch?
- He went home to take a shit.
I don't get it. How does a guy like that
get this sudden reputation?
- What reputation?
- Observe.
Excuse me.
Do you know who Paul Finch is?
Yeah! He's the guy
with the tattoo, right?
You know, the eagle and the
blazing fire and that stuff.
If you guys see him later,
will you tell him Courtney says hi?
Bye.
Okay. Explain.
I can't. I don't know
how he's doing it.
I guess that just
leaves Jim trailing.
-Jimbo!
- Better sack up, buddy!
Yeah, I know.
I'm working on it.
James? You are very good
in the world history class, yes?
Me? Yes. No...
Yes, I am.
Perhaps you could help me
with my studies.
Yeah. Absolutely.
That would be great sometime.
- How about tomorrow?
- Well, I have ballet practise.
Perhaps I could come
by your house afterwards?
I could change clothes
at your place.
Yeah. I suppose
that would be okay.
Sure.
Nice car!
- I'm glad you think so.
- You don't like it?
No, I like the car.
By the way, though, about prom?
That was a bad idea.
I'm sorry I invited you.
- What are you talkin' about?
- Please.
I asked you because I thought
you might actually be worth going with.
But you are just a jock.
No, wait. You're a jerk.
Wait! I don't understand.
I saw you making fun of me
with your lacrosse buddies.
I wasn't makin' fun of you.
Give me a break.
You're so full of it.
Fuck me! There's gonna be an Eastern
European chick naked in your house.
And you're not gonna
do anything about that?
What am I gonna do, huh?
Broadcast her over the Internet?
- Yeah.
- You can do that?
No. I cannot do that to her.
Jim, get some fuckin' balls.
If you don't have the guts
to photograph a naked chick...
how you gonna sleep with one?
I don't like the kid,
but he's got a point.
See, even Shit-break
knows you should do it.
All you gotta do is set up some sort of
private link or whatever on the 'Net...
and tell me the address.
You can send me
the address too.
I'll save you a seat.
How sweet it is
to be loved by you, by you
I needed the shelter
of someone's arms
Someone's arms
- There you were
- You were
I needed someone
who understands my ups and downs
There you were
Okay, that was good,
but I want to thicken up that solo.
Michigan State is this Saturday,
and I want that part to smoke.
Yeah, I know,
my timing's off.
It's not that. I think it'll work better
as a duet with a tenor part.
I'll do it.
- Dick.
- I'll do it.
Great. See you tomorrow.
- Why are you doing this?
- 'Cause I want to.
Yeah? Well,
you can't fake this.
You better practise.
Come in.
Jim? There's a...
a young lady here to see you.
- Hey, Nadia.
- Hi, James. Ready to study?
He's always ready to study.
He's a real bookworm.
Dad.
He's not one of those
nerdy guys...
Dad!
Well, I'll let you two
hit the books.
You want a beer?
- Oh, there we go.
- Come on, move!
Steve! It's my computer,
and I wanna use it!
Shut up!
You need to change, right?
- Uh, do you mind?
- No, not at all.
Please, you know.
Just go ahead and get changed.
I'll go downstairs
and start studying up.
There he goes.
Now we're in business.
- Back in a sec.
-Jimmy, honey...
Here she is.
- Did I miss anything?
- No. You are just in time.
- Oh. Oh!
- This is incredible.
Oh, my God!
This is too much.
Oh, did you see?
Oh, there that goes. Oh, Jeez.
God bless the Internet.
- Do it. Take it off.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, thank you, God,
for this wonderful, wonderful day.
She takes her vitamins.
Stop hyperventilating.
This is, like,
the coolest thing I've ever seen.
I know.
This is definitely one
of Stifler's best ideas ever.
What is she...
She's touching my stuff.
- Why is she touching my stuff?
- Let her touch.
- She's going through my stuff!
- Nadia can touch anything she wants.
- No, no.
- Nice collection there.
She's gonna leave.
She's definitely gonna...
She's getting comfortable.
She's not gonna leave.
She reads the articles.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/34u2
Help other users to choose the best subtitles