Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Stella?
- Stella.
- No!
Look at them sugar warehouses
blowing up like
blasted paper bags.
Young madam.
It's all right, luv.
Come on. That's it.
Don't cry. You be a
good girl for your mum.
Shh, shh, shh. Don't worry.
Your father's gone.
Oh, no. Shh, shh.
Look. Pretty pearls.
Be a good girl, now.
It's all right. It's all right.
You be a good girl now,
and I'll be back soon.
Stella!
Stella, don't worry, luv.
You're all right.
Now, take deep breaths, Stella.
Stella, breathe deeply.
That's it.
Don't worry. You're all right.
How... now...
brown... cow.
How now, brown cow.
I didn't know it was
called Dramatic Art.
Hoo-er.
Oh, yes. It is.
I thought she was just
learning to speak properly.
Well, that's it, that's it.
Oh. Well, I hope she's not in
for another disappointment.
Well, if she is,
I've told her
this time she'll end up
behind the counter
in Woolworths, my girl.
Or Boots.
And she'll be damn lucky
to get that and all.
Damn lucky. Oh, yes.
Hello, Mother?
It's Auntie Lily
and Uncle Vernon.
They ask too much of me.
Hello? Hello?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a trunk call.
She's practicing acting
as if into a telephone
for her interview.
Oh? Oh.
Well, fancy that.
Mrs. Fairfield's out.
Can I take a message?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a trunk call.
Should she walk
when on the phone?
Mrs. Fairfield's out.
Shall I take a message?
Mrs. Fairfield speaking.
Good Lord!
Sidney, don't say Good Lord.
No, that's not right.
How now, brown cow.
Won't do, young lady.
I'm expected.
Rose Lipman is known to me
which is how you've come
by this interview.
Audition! Have you
settled up with the taxi?
Yes. Here, here.
I'd rather die than tip him!
I think it degrades the giver
every bit as much
as the receiver.
Chuck it through the window
and hook it, then!
I'll go on the tram.
You'll arrive bedraggled.
She'll be soaked!
She'll ruin her hair!
Mrs. Fairfield says...
Sidney, I believe
the telephone is going--
Not a play that springs
immediately to mind, is it?
Off.
Hello? Hello?
Everybody is always out
when you need them most.
There's no need for that, Bunny.
Hello? Hello?
I think it's tea time.
Don't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
It-- it's a trunk call.
Not my fault.
Hello?
The thing is...
I think she's a genius.
Don't you, Bunny?
Your promiscuity is humiliating.
# Even when the darkest clouds #
# Are in the sky #
# You mustn't sigh #
# And you must not cry #
# Just spread a little happiness #
# As you go by #
I must keep my coat on.
Thank you.
But you're drenched. Huh?
That is not important.
Auntie Lily said time enough
for a new dress
when I get the job.
Yes.
I think I'm falling in love
with him, Mother.
I could've been afraid of him
but for his nicotine-stained fingers.
I know a man who
can't close his eyes.
He burned... in a bomb.
How interesting.
He was to be married
but his fiancée was afraid
that it would pass on
to the children
and threw him over.
It's all right.
But the worst thing, he says,
is people thinking
he looks fierce
when most days
he weeps.
Inside.
Oh, hell.
Well, I look forward to meeting
you again, Miss Bradshaw.
Congratulations.
Oh?
Bunny here is our stage manager.
I think he ought to
take care of--
There's a taxi.
- No, I-- I--
- Taxi!
I have shopping to do,
thank you.
Uncle Vernon
never travels by cab
'cause he finds tipping degrading.
Isn't that foolish of him?
But you haven't seen me act,
Mr. Potter.
Oh, I rather think I have, what?
Stella?
Good evening.
My name is Stella Bradshaw.
I don't expect you'll
ever want to love me.
What you are is dog's bodies.
Assistant stage managers
they have to pay.
You're students.
So they don't have to pay you.
When you've been nine days
in an open boat
I expect you look on that
sort of thing with contempt.
George was in an open boat.
Oh.
For nine days.
Weren't you, George?
It's not as deep as all that.
Eh? What?
The stage, George.
It's not as deep as I expected.
I thought you meant the organ.
Too deep for me to see.
Here.
Keep your nice clothes clean.
Thank you.
It's not that I'm bored by
what you all did in the war.
But everybody has,
like, stories to tell
and bits of them to show
where they were hurt.
Oh, they will have.
Who's that?
That's P.L. O'Hara.
"Richard II" before the war.
I keep that notice
because it mentions me.
Not by name. The set.
He sent me that postcard
during the war.
Don't know why.
He was on the "Andrew,"
commanding a corvette.
Best Captain Hook we've had
in this theatre, the same.
Set for "Richard II"
on which I solved
the problem of the dungeon.
Ladies, gentlemen,
and others assorted
please find a seat.
It is rather fine.
But then, I love
beautiful things, don't you?
- Yes.
- Wait.
Morning, darling.
- Hello!
- How old is she, exactly?
Absolutely none of your business.
It's my fault.
I was trying to be pleasant.
She drinks.
Have I got time for a cup?
No. You're here to work,
young man, sit down.
Get some fags, will you?
What's your name?
Her name's Stella.
And she won't, Mr. Fairchild,
unless Bunny lets her.
Time hurries.
So, does everybody
know everybody?
This side.
Well, if you don't, you will.
And you all know me
or what they say about me.
And all of that is true.
So speak now if you don't
because we do "Dangerous Corner."
Two weeks' rehearsal,
play for two weeks
while we rehearse
"Caesar and Cleo."
Playing for two weeks,
while we rehearse "Peter Pan."
So, the thing is,
it's a very heavy season
and you're all going to have
to work very, very hard.
But you're all the very
best people we could find
the length and breadth
of the profession.
Aww!
For the money.
Welcome.
I think you're all very good.
I mean...
wonderful.
You wanted to know the truth
and here it is!
Some of it.
She's been in love
with you for ages.
Wives are always
aware of these things, you know.
I'll tell you what I have longed
to tell you for some time
that I think you're a fool
for not having responded to it.
For not having done something
about it before now.
Sorry.
Doesn't matter. Go on, go on!
When somebody loves you
like that
for God's sake,
make the most of it
before it's too late.
Leave it!
Stop fussing
like an old queen, Bunny!
Stella.
Ten minutes.
Darling, I'd like you to take
some notes for me.
Care for a snifter, squire?
Do you know where
the general post office is?
Of course. I live here.
Of course you do.
I think that's charming.
Now, I want you
to run all the way
and don't change a word.
There you are.
Ten bob.
That's two and six change.
Bunny! Where's Bunny?
Bunny!
Meredith, old boy,
when are we gonna
get onto the stage?
The old green, huh?
I'm having a bit of trouble
finding my character.
Mmm. So I'd noticed.
A cup of tea, please.
One of those, thanks.
There's a man next to you
whose toes can be seen
through his boots.
Oh, my God, I can smell it.
There's no need to be so loud.
People have feelings.
A minute longer
and you'd be scratching.
"Darling Hilary stop.
In hell stop."
"You must ring stop."
"Reverse charges."
"I love you. Meredith."
Oh!
What's this about Hilary?
I phoned twice
this morning, Bunny.
I mean...
not a dicky bird.
Well, perhaps the bill
hasn't been paid.
It has. I paid it.
Of course, that girl is
in love with you, too
if that's any comfort.
Stella by Starlight?
"Don't bother to telephone stop."
"Will not accept
reverse charges stop."
"Yours, Meredith."
Thank you.
If I could,
I'd take you away from all this.
I'm sorry.
You're afraid of dirt.
Better than lurking in corridors
for Meredith Potter
with a copy of Shakespeare
at hand in case he notices you.
What about you, then?
Got a pash on him?
He's not here anyway.
In London with the designer,
I'm told.
I know.
Why don't you like George?
I do.
He has native intelligence.
- He's not a nigger.
- What?
He went straight from St. Aloysius'
to the Royal Court as a stagehand.
If he slopped glue
he was hit on the head
with the brush.
If he made a noise,
he was fined sixpence.
They all were.
Then he came here as a day man.
They were all something.
At sea. Over Germany.
In the desert.
Well, Mother, I might as well
get it over with
s-so that when the moment
comes to be p-penetrated
by Mr. Potter,
I shall not put him off
scream... or anything.
I don't like the feel of it.
Thank you very much, Geoffrey.
It's not that
I don't like old George.
It's just that he stinks.
I'll put these on the boiler.
Leave it! Leave it!
You'll have us all
blown to eternity!
I can do it!
Oh, can you? Can you?
Look at you!
Blow us all to buggery.
At the theatre
I have a lot to do with gas.
It's one of my jobs is gas.
Oh, is it?
I hope you know what
you're doing there all hours.
All kinds of hours.
What do you know of life?
The way that life
can bowl you over?
Bowl you over!
But not here it won't.
You put that on the door.
Unless you want all and sundry
catching you in your vest.
Uncle Vernon?
I know you want
what's best for me.
A-and...
fear for me, don't you?
But it's all right.
I want it to happen.
And...
Really,
I-- I think the world of you.
I've cleaned the tidemark
and put the loofah
back under the stairs.
Night-night.
Nighty-night. God bless.
Do I do the right thing?
If the school
won't have her back...
Not won't. Not won't.
Well, they don't think
she'd benefit.
She's got the brains.
Candles. But not...
Oh, yes. Anything else?
...the application.
Toilet rolls.
Quantity two dozen.
Afraid I can only manage...
She's burgeoning, you know.
Is she?
- Is your daughter?
- What?
Burgeoning, as it were, yet?
I don't know.
I haven't looked.
No, no, no!
It's the one on the left!
The left, dear!
She's deaf as a post.
Yes, well, it's your right.
Thank you.
Now, Geoffrey,
move stage left.
Stage left.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, no. Number 8?
- No, thank you.
- Shall I move stage left?
Geoffrey, is that where
I asked you to stand?
I was trying--
Please stand where
I asked you to stand!
- Sorry.
- Number 10?
Footlights.
That takes me back.
No. Number 11.
Now, that's very close.
Thank you.
The play's awfully good,
isn't it, Mr. Potter?
Why this wasn't sorted out
yesterday is beyond me.
I'm coming in!
What do you think it's about,
Stella?
Now, there are two ways
of doing this...
Love?
Uh, love.
Is it?
People loving people
who love other people?
No, no. Thank you.
I, um...
I think it's about time.
I think we're all mourners
at a funeral procession
and that some of us
have simply dropped behind
to tie a shoelace.
So contact with the beloved
is suspended.
But the dead--
the dead are still there.
So, too,
those we think we love.
Just around
the dangerous corner,
if you like...
waiting to be, um...
Hilary!
Bunny. How long?
Weeks at this rate.
Caught up with--
waiting to be caught up with.
I-- I hadn't thought of it
like that.
No.
Stella. Stella!
Call beginners, please.
Don't you think they're good,
Stella's notes?
I mean, I wish
I could spell like that.
Mourners at a "funral,"
is my favourite bit.
It's cold now!
I hate cold bacon.
We haven't all got
shoes with laces.
All beginners, please!
Beginners, please!
- Fetch Bunny.
- What's that noise?
Not a word.
Why can't we start?!
Th-there's a spot of bother.
Huh? Speak up. What is wrong?
I've been forbidden to divulge.
How long?!
Leave her!
He's such a shit!
Cheer up, Stella.
It might never happen.
There are priests out there.
Only for rehearsals.
It's a sin otherwise.
His Nibs is a convert.
Mr. Potter's Catholic?
Well, they all are. Actors.
Desmond Fairchild, he's not.
What is he?
Hold it under there,
like that.
Deep breaths, Miss Allenby.
Remember your training.
Stand by, Mr. Fairchild, please.
House lights.
Going up.
You have just
been listening to a play
in eight scenes
written for broadcasting
by Mr. Humphrey Stoat,
called "The Sleeping Dog."
Hello, Mother.
I'm becoming a Catholic.
You'd like the play.
At the end,
they dance to that tune
"My Foolish Heart."
# When I take my sugar to tea #
# All the boys are jealous of me #
# 'Cause I never take her
where the gang goes #
# When I take my sugar to tea #
# I'm a rowdy dowdy, that's me #
# She's a high hat baby,
that's she #
# So I never take her
where the gang goes #
# When I take my sugar to tea #
# Every Sunday afternoon #
# We forget about our cares #
# Rubbing elbows at the Ritz #
Ah, Dotty's over there.
Shall we join them?
Oh, let's not.
Oh, poor Dicky.
What a cross he has to bear.
Drunk as
a fiddler's bitch she was.
Is. Will be. Ha ha ha!
Some people like being burdened.
Gives them an interest.
Obsession?
Obsession is hell!
It devours.
Oh, I haven't forgotten
the misery of it.
Him! P.L. O'Hara.
Though everybody warned me.
I mean, he chased
everything in a skirt.
Dicky isn't like that.
No, but Dawn is. Trousers.
Poor Dicky.
Poor Dicky and his trousers.
Oh, P.L., P.L.!
I thought
I could help him forget.
About what?
What he did.
Got a local girl in trouble
and scarpered.
Is Mr. Potter's friend
o-obsessed with him?
Bunny?
Hilary.
Do you know, treasure,
I don't know.
Is she pretty? Is she elegant?
She'd have to be special.
Any lady friend of Meredith's
would have to be
something special.
How very true.
What about Desmond Fairchild?
What's your estimation of him?
He's a cunt.
Belated afternoon to you girls.
I shall give her a part.
Of course, he is.
She shall play...
She shall play
Ptolemy, the boy king, hmm?
Save getting an amateur in.
Trouble is, Fairchild is
a local councilor's nephew.
Is he?
Maybe you should
talk to her, then, Bunny.
Wash her mouth out with soap.
Stella...
Can't stop or
it won't stretch, George says.
It's been
brought to my notice
that you called
a member of the company a...
Is that how you spell it?
This is a theatre,
George told me he was.
Isn't it something to do
with betting, like favourite?
Spend less time
in the prop room.
Ptolemy. The boy king.
Son of the flute-blower.
He's only in Act II.
Geoffrey, don't stand about.
You'll turn to stone.
You're a bit lucky.
Luck doesn't come into it.
Mr. Potter wouldn't ask me if
he didn't think I could do it.
I'm being interviewed by
the "Manchester Daily News."
I'm at the Reparatory Theatre.
I play the boy king.
S'all right for some.
Son of the flute-blower?
Didn't he want
his welsh rarebit?
I'm 16 years old.
I've got a diploma from
the Manchester
Academy of Dramatic Art.
I can also do American dialects
from the Deep South.
I was trained by Mrs. Ackerley.
She plumped out me vowels.
I tend to have flat ones.
I'll wait for you
after the show.
Take you for a drink.
Oh! Good girl! Ohh!
How do you get V.D.?
All the newspapers.
Even Manchester.
There'll be many's
the write-up for our Stella
but this'll be
the important one, now.
On the doorstep of my digs
this morning
with a bloody great bunch
of half-dead daffodils.
- Who?
- Dawn Allenby, who do you think?
I had to let her in.
She started picking up my socks.
Ohh! She drinks.
- We know.
Why does Richard St. Ives
put a red dot
in the corner of each eye?
To make him look younger.
How dare you?!
How dare he?
All right, Stella?
Good luck.
House lights, Joe.
Ah! By Apis, Persian,
thy gods are good to thee.
Try yet again, Captain.
Double or quits.
No, I am not in the vein.
Stand! Who goes there?
Good night, old boy!
T-there's this man.
A boy--
Been given my bloody notice.
Not wanted after
"Caesar and Cleopatra."
Oh, dear.
Swine. What a swine.
Tells me there's nothing for me.
Looking at me
through that bloody monocle.
Bloody swine.
Swine Meredith bloody Potter.
What about bloody Wendy?
Mr. Potter's not to blame!
It was Dicky St. Ives
said it was you or him.
Come on, then! Be a good--
No! Stay away!
Ha! I only drink
because our house
took a direct hit in Ealing.
I'm not like that!
I'm sorry.
For two days,
I was buried alive
nursing my mother's vase.
Oh, dear.
What are we to do?
When they pulled me out
the vase was without so much
as a single crack.
The thing is...
Then the bloody rescue man
stumbled.
I have a gulp in my throat
won't go away.
As if I'm waiting for something.
What are you doing here,
young lady?
N-nothing, Miss Lipman.
These new shoes are killing me.
They're gone, Vernon and Lily.
It's not them. It's a young man.
A reporter.
He pursues me
and awaits me in the shadows.
I've ordered a taxi.
Silly girl.
What'll become of her, Bunny?
What will become of you?
If you're lucky,
you'll end up like me.
At least me...
I was as silly as you
in a lot of ways. Still am.
A sickness, my girl,
being something else.
See you don't get lost
while you are something else.
Came to the right place for it,
I'll say that.
Listening to every word we say.
Look...
And this stuck in her sock.
I find it comforting.
You're never a Catholic.
Vernon Bradshaw
wouldn't let you near--
Uncle Vernon
does not rule my life.
Not this nor in the next.
I'm thinking about going over.
To the Romans.
While you think, wear
a smaller one round your neck.
Don't tell Uncle Vernon.
All right, but behave yourself.
I do rule your life while
you're in this theatre, my girl.
Be what you like.
Don't tell the whole of
Liverpool I said you could.
While you're on the cross
there's a boil coming in
on your wrist should be lanced.
Anything else?
No.
Right. Left foot forward.
Thank you.
Stella?
Go down to the kitchen
and ask the waiter
with a dent in his forehead
to send up
a bucket full of ice cubes
and two or three napkins.
And then get lots of
black coffee and some aspirin.
Last night
he thought he could fly
from a window at The Commercial.
Fortunately at
the bar parlour window.
I've got a part in this one.
As I live and breathe,
Peter Pan!
- Slightly!
- Very same.
Scala Theatre, 1922.
'Course I've-- I've
grown somewhat since then.
Oh, yes! Mmm!
Oh, who's Hook this time?
- Dicky St. Ives.
- Oh, bugger.
Morning, Dicky.
How are you, squire?
Very, very well.
Geoffrey!
Get me 20 Players, will you?
What did
your last servant die of?
Do as you're told, Geoffrey.
Hoity-toity this morning,
aren't we?
Thank you, Stella.
And there's your torch.
Remember what I told you?
I can't.
Not shine a torch and
ring a bell at the same time.
Weren't you
in the Girl Guides, dear?
No. They wouldn't have me.
And I have an aversion
to flickering lights.
Something in me past.
Little candle flames
make me shiver.
I cannot go into it here.
Sufficient to say,
it is the stuff of nightmares.
You-- None of you know--
I don't know.
I'm not qualified
to say whether the grief
his mother felt in the death
of his elder brother had an
adverse effect on Mr. Barrie's
emotional development
because...
I have pains of my own.
Me. Not you.
Or you or you or anyone.
I-- Me!
I... I... have them.
"Peter Pan"
is pure make-believe.
I don't want any truck
with anything else
so, children,
and poor people
if you can't see the truth,
give me make-believe.
I prefer it.
So don't give me any symbolic...
Ohh!
Shambolic more like, what?
What are you miserable about?
Nothing.
Is it because I've got a part
and you've only
a torch and a bell?
Tinkerbell's very important.
In this precarious profession
it doesn't do to get too big
for one's boots.
So, what were you doing the other night
swearing at Meredith
and running down the stairs
like a looney?
What were you doing spying?
I was coping with Dawn.
Poor woman.
She was two days under rubble.
They all were.
It-- It's Mr. Potter.
He hardly knows I'm there.
He can't feel anything of me...
here.
He should be able to.
He's got other things
to think about.
Thank you, Jimmy.
Oh, dear, dear.
The last thing we need.
"Dearest Swine,
"no money, no job, no friends.
"Hope you and that ghastly
Liverpool girl are satisfied.
"Use this in memory of me.
Yours, Dawn Allenby."
"Manchester Daily News,
November 9th."
Up and out, please!
That means you, too,
Miss Bradshaw.
A marvellous man this Caesar.
When think you he will come?
He was settling
the Jewish problem when I left.
"In other roles,
a promising debut was made
"by young local actress
Stella Bradshaw.
"In the part of Ptolemy,
she was always convincing..."
See, my ship is waiting.
The time for Caesar's farewell
to Egypt has arrived.
Caesar comes!
Attention there!
Here comes Caesar!
What the--
Aah! Oh, no!
All right, squire?
That bloody woman! Ohh!
Thank you.
This has never happened before,
not even for miscarriages.
What's wrong with
Desmond Fairchild?
Why could he not go on?
Says he hasn't the legs
for Caesar.
He would be a laughing-stock.
So what about Captain Hook?
Says he's suited
with the part of Smee...
Thank you very much.
Oh, for God's sake, are you sure
Dicky can't stand up?
Meredith, the poor man has
broken his leg in two places.
Yes, that's £1,10 shillings.
Enjoy the--
Oh, what am I saying?
What about that actor always
sending me photographs?
His wife phoned to ask
for them back. He's dead.
- What about Cyril?
- Who's Cyril?
Oh, yes, Cyril What's-his-name
I did know at Derby.
And he later lost both his legs
at the first Battle of Alamein.
I mean, try, Bunny!
O'Hara.
- No.
- Why not?
The thing is, Rose,
I don't-- I don't--
If he's free,
he'll come for me.
The thing is,
I don't think he's right for it.
Do you, Bunny?
Fiddlesticks!
He is the best Captain Hook
there has ever been.
Haven't changed.
Still hankering
after the past, I see.
Bloody motorbike at your age.
What is it,
next week "Lawrence of Arabia"?
Mind you don't fall off.
Six-week run. Two matinees
a week from Tuesday.
All right with Potter
after last time?
Funny bugger.
Spent too much money
on two big productions,
one after the other
and now we won't break even.
Well, we might.
With "Peter Pan." With you.
I don't do that
with everyone, so mind.
Welcome home.
I know this is
your old dressing room.
George told me.
I'm Stella. A student.
Should be A.S.M.
as George says
but they won't pay us.
You have to kick the pipes to
get the water out of the taps.
I expect you didn't know.
Do you know Mary Deare,
Peter Pan?
I think she's very good,
don't you?
How strange it is.
You and me. Together.
I mean, here.
After all these years.
Did you ever
get my Christmas cards?
I never forgot.
But then you never were one
to dwell on the past, were you?
I'm not called.
I just came in to see you.
They're all very nice.
Miss Bird is very nice.
So's Miss Blundell.
Very nice, too.
Uh, Sibyl, a brew?
Mr. Fairchild is...
Hmm?
I do know other words
but nobody usually likes
the sound of them.
I know her.
Stella? Oh, hardly, darling.
First job. Never been
further than Blackpool.
I know him.
Now is the hour
when children
in their homes are abed.
Their lips bright-browned
with the good-night chocolate.
And their tongues drowsily
searching for belated crumbs
housed insecurely
on their shining cheeks.
Compare with them
the children on this boat
about to walk the plank.
Split my infinitives
but 'tis my hour of triumph!
Yo-ho, yo-ho,
The frisky captain
walks along and so...
And yet
some disky spirit
compels me now
to make my dying speech.
Lest when dying
there may be...
"No time for it."
Should one pause there?
Yes.
No, no, I mean
should we pause there?
Good time to break. Mary?
I-- I thought...
Mr. O'Hara,
can I get you a cup of tea?
Yes. Thanks.
Bunny?
Mr. Potter doesn't ask me
to do notes anymore.
Have I upset him, Bunny?
I shouldn't think so, dear.
Not you.
Did you come back for me,
P.L., or something else?
You. I owe you a great deal.
What you been looking for?
You can't do anything
I don't hear about
on that motorbike.
You won't find her. Not now.
I might.
Or I might find him.
How will you know?
I'll know.
A little chap
that stands like me.
How's that?
Heroical. Twice nightly.
Leave it.
Disley?
Disley!
Do you want the nursery set
stage left or stage right?
- Stella!
- Are you sure?
Because
it's got to be even numbers.
Cup of tea, dear.
- George?
- Uh-huh?
I want the nursery set
in next, please.
Hey!
Good of you to join us,
Geoffrey.
Right! Let's hang the cloths!
Careful.
Let's take it up.
Easy! Right!
Fly it! Stella, I'll do it.
Gently!
Steady, steady, steady!
That's it, that's it.
That's it. Yes, good!
Oh, Disley, it's beautiful.
Do you like it?
Wait till it's lit.
Yes, well done, Disley.
It's beautiful.
Wait till it's lit.
No, thanks.
I've had more than enough
for one morning.
Well... Ahem!
It's, um...
Not far enough upstage...
by two foot.
Well, it can't go
any further back.
It's already
on the last set of lines.
Well, it's too far downstage.
What do you
propose I do about it?
I don't know.
Hang it from below the bridge
and tumble it.
You do know how to tumble
a cloth, don't you, Bunny?
Oh, dear, Bunny doesn't know how
to tumble a cloth.
George, can you help?
Now we'll have
to re-hang everything!
Well, you should've got it right
the first time.
I need depth.
Every inch you can give me.
Eh, George?
Well, you have the wish
to come with me, Geoff-wey
or do you want to stay here
with Mr. Potter?
Oh? Oh? Geoff-wey!
Well, Geoffrey?
Sorry. What does he call you?
Your new friend?
Geoff-wey? Go on, Geoff-wey!
Get up them stairs.
You might learn something.
"Bring me out that doodle-doo!"
Morning.
Launched me pirate ship yet?
Not quite, no.
Perhaps
you ought to show us how
being a jolly jack tar,
and all, hmm?
Or a matelot, and all.
Tiddly drop of thickers, George.
I think he makes
a very good Captain Hook
don't you, Stella? Hmm?
How still the night is.
Nothing sounds alive.
Now is the hour
when children
in their homes are abed
their lips bright-browned
with the good-night chocolate.
And their tongues
drowsily searching
for belated crumbs
housed insecurely
on their shining cheeks.
Compare with them
the children on this boat
about to walk the plank.
Split my infinitives
but 'tis my hour of triumph!
And yet...
some disky spirit
compels me now
to make my dying speech
lest when dying...
there may be no time for it.
As usual, a child being sick
during my quiet scene.
Well done, Shirley.
Oh, thank you.
There's a Christmas party.
You were very good
with the torch.
Un triomphe!
Over there.
You sit down there.
All right.
John!
I can't go on like this.
We have to talk.
Oh, I think
everyone ought to talk.
I think you ought to dance,
as well.
He's thinking about
leaving the theatre.
We've saved you
a seat here, darling.
Come on.
Look at her hair. What a colour.
I know! Isn't it tedious?
Thank you, darling.
Everybody
looked at someone else
even while
they were talking to somebody.
It's not easy to do.
I thought you understood.
Don't let it get you down,
Geoff-wey.
What's going on there?
Meredith.
He's up to his usual nonsense.
You're ruining my life.
You can't force him
to give you better parts.
You mind your own business.
You know nothing about it.
Would you like to dance?
I-- I'm no good at it.
Keep the hands up.
Yes.
Huh?
Where's Meredith?
Went to midnight mass.
With Bunny.
They've just gone.
Shall I give you a lift home?
Y-yes.
Stop! Stop, please!
Here'll do.
I want to phone me mother.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Damp.
Turpentine.
I had a friend who painted.
You look at me as if
I might fly up the chimney.
It shouldn't be
quite like that, you know?
There are things come first.
Lots of things.
For instance, you have
to take your knickers off.
Or shall I?
If you like.
Stella...
Stella Maris...
Who's Stella Maris?
I knew someone called that.
"Star of the sea."
Stella Maris.
That's nice.
It's not a real name.
It's something she made up.
Dotty bought me this.
'Cause she was
worried about me growth.
If you need some water,
there's only the sink.
No, thank you.
I had a bath last night.
I expect there's a knack to it.
It's very intimate, isn't it?
Hello, Mother?
I've got something--
It's Stella.
I've got something to tell you.
Uncle Vernon?
I'm in.
I'm looking for Mr. Potter
from the-- the theatre.
Sorry to intrude,
but I'm impelled to speak.
Oh. My name is Bradshaw.
Oh, my God.
You're Uncle Vernon.
Delighted!
Someone was splashing out
at Woolworths.
Quiet, please!
Stella's very young
and very impressionable.
Well under
the age of carnal consent.
I-- I can't be everywhere.
It'd look very odd, that-- that.
The thing is,
she gets very upset.
Do you get very upset?
Ohh. I served in North Africa.
I didn't.
I was in the catering corps.
Were you very brave?
Stella!
Coming back?
No.
Why not?
I just don't want to.
Uncle Vernon wouldn't like it.
It strikes me clear as day,
she's gone, Lily.
What have I--
What have we led her in for, eh?
No tea for me.
It'll warm you up.
No, it doesn't.
You ought to get a proper coat.
Auntie Lily bought me a coat.
I'd rather die.
It's too big
and it's got a fur collar.
It sounds glamorous.
You have to paint your face
if you wear fur.
Cheap goods should be wrapped
in plain brown paper.
Who gave you the pearls?
My mother.
I'm sorry.
I can see they weren't
bought in Woolworths.
They probably were.
Which is why she left them
on me pillow...
twined around a single red rose.
What a lovely thing to do.
I'm in love with someone else!
Do you do this with him?
What's that got to do with it?
Put your legs closer together.
That feels different.
Put them-- There's--
Meredith.
She won't wear the vest
wardrobe has made for her.
I bleed for her.
Bunny's watching.
Here, put those--
The crocodile!
Stella,
this is very dangerous.
I told you.
No real flowers on the stage.
This has nothing to do with me.
And you, Mr. O'Hara,
should know better.
They're made for each other.
Wendy,
you are wrong about mothers!
I thought like you
about the window
so I stayed away
for moons and moons...
Is Stella bronchial,
by any chance?
Are you crying?
It's-- it's to do with
the low notes in the male voice.
I noticed it first in the army
when music was compulsory.
Oh, I know.
No. She's got
such a nasty cough.
Bunny's had to put cough drops
in the prompt corner.
We've had her X-rayed.
She's sound as a bell.
I shall let you have
the 3 ha'pence for the sweets.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- Was it more?
No, no. No,
the reason I'm here is
we're playing football against
the "Treasure Island" cast
on New Year's Day.
My footy days are over.
Heh. I haven't the wind.
No, no, Uncle Vernon.
I wanted you both
to come and watch.
You know, support us,
meet some of
Stella's new friends.
I'm beginning to get
the hang of fucking.
Yes.
It's no different from learning
to play the ukulele.
You just need practice.
Don't you love me just a bit?
No.
I love another.
# Oh, I do like to be
beside the sea #
# Oh, I do like to stroll along
the prom, prom, prom #
# Where the brass bands play #
Oh! Sorry.
That's perfectly all right.
# Beside the seaside #
Is he one of our pirates
or one of theirs?
One of theirs.
I mean, I think their pirates
are much better
than our pirates,
don't you, Bunny?
Can't you find anywhere to sit?
Bunch up, Bunny.
Geoff-wey can sit between us.
Oh, no, he can't.
He's too chubby.
We need someone slimmer.
John! John Harbour!
You come and sit between us and
Geoff-wey can have your seat.
I'll stand, thank you, Meredith.
I am the wefewee, Geoff-wey,
so just you be careful.
# Oh, I do like to be
beside the seaside #
Where's that pirate?
# Oh, I do like to be
beside the sea #
# Oh, I do like to stroll along
the prom, prom, prom #
# Where the brass bands play #
# Tiddley-om-pom-pom #
# So just let me be
beside the seaside #
# I'll be beside myself
with glee #
Got it!
Come on, The Playhouse!
Come on, The Rep!
- Hey, you're not trying.
- I'm trying very hard.
No, you're not.
- Yay!
- Go, Rep!
Yeah! Good one!
Thank you.
I'll let you get away with that.
What?
Come on, Geoffrey!
- Yeah!
- That's it! Go on!
- Yay!
- You've done it!
Good goal, son!
Offside.
Surely that was offside.
Offside. Offside.
Back here.
- What?!
- Offside?!
How could
that have been offside?!
The first thing
an actor must learn
is humility, Geoffrey.
Remember?
Thank you, John.
I might have missed it.
- Boo! Boo!
- Get some spectacles, Potter!
- Leave it!
- Get off me!
Geoffrey, leave it!
Yes?
Oh, my God!
Geoffrey!
Come on.
Breathe. You'll feel better.
Just breathe deeply.
My bloody scarf!
He was wearing
my bloody scarf
and he wouldn't even look at me!
You all right?
- I fainted, I think.
- Oh, good God.
I fainted
because the pain was
very excruciating,
so I did the best thing
I could think of and I fainted.
Get me my coat, Bunny.
Geoffrey's got to go.
Get me my coat, Bunny!
- Mr. Potter.
- Uncle Vernon.
There, there. Shh.
Poor boy.
Desmond!
All right, all right.
Now, look here,
we were wondering--
we were all wondering
if you might not have
a word with Potter.
Geoffrey
shouldn't have hit him
but it does seem
a cry for help.
That's right! We all think
it's a cry for help.
Cry for help, squire-- skipper.
Ah, yes, I see.
I'll tell the bugger!
No, Babs.
He'll be awful to you.
Cry for help, old boy.
Yes, yes.
Leave it with you, then.
You were in the navy.
Meredith,
you all right, squire?
No, I don't think one should be
too hard on the lad.
Geoffrey-- he has been
working very hard.
you are one
of nature's gentlemen.
That's very nice of you,
Uncle Vernon.
I like these days.
Hint of frost.
Touch of sunlight.
Mmm! Invigorating, isn't it?
I always think
on a day like this
a man can stand up
and face the--
Oh, Christ!
...world.
- Oh, God, I--
- Pirates!
Where's our Stella?
I'm all right.
Where's Stella?
Aah! God!
Good of you to bother.
Could have waited.
It's to do with
that boy Geoffrey...
You know...
he is a boy.
Hardly more than a child,
really.
Have you seduced him?
Does he think he loves you?
Are you playing games with him?
I think you are.
I think you're doing
what you did in Windsor.
A much older man, I grant you.
A much sadder man.
Don't need to remind you
that he later hanged himself
in a police cell, do I?
Ohh...
Nothing to do with you.
Perhaps.
Look, just drop it.
Leave the boy alone.
The play's about innocence.
Not seduction or exploitation.
I mean, look at the play, man.
This is awkward for me.
Yes. Isn't it?
I'm not a narrow man
and, God knows,
I'm no saint, but you...
you...
Aren't you going to be off
if you don't hurry?
Here.
Just before you go down
to the nursery, Mr. Darling
don't you think
you ought to remember
that it's also
a criminal offense
to consort with a minor?
You know...
assault a child?
- Mr. O'Hara!
- You wouldn't.
God, I'm off!
Aah!
"Potter, my concern
is for a young man
"whose life may well be ruined
by your attentions.
"If the situ--"
He's boasting about it
in the prop room!
Stagehand --that one with
the glass eye-- egging him on!
- Who?
- Geoffrey!
Why hasn't he been given
the sack?
- Geoffrey has his reasons.
- He's unbalanced!
Don't talk rot.
Mr. Potter's a wronged man!
Mr. Potter has spent his life
harming people like Geoffrey
and causing pain to people
like Bunny who really love him.
Hilary Melville was only 18
when Potter picked him
up at the BBC.
Hilary is a him?
Believe it or not.
Doesn't much matter--
him or her, old or young,
to Meredith.
What he wants is hearts.
You're jealous of him!
Oh.
I'm going
and I'm not coming back.
Not ever.
Oh, for God's sake.
Look, please--
Kind of you to come.
I am ashamed.
I'm at a disadvantage.
It's not broken!
Sprained.
It was me own fault.
I went down
not watching where I was--
It's Mr. Potter
I feel sorry for.
I hear he's from a good family,
the lad who butted him.
So I believe. Is Stella here?
He's not gonna sack the boy?
He too was bothered
about me injury.
You just missed him.
What did Potter have to say?
He's helping us with Stella,
keeping an eye on her.
She, of course,
tells us nothing.
She keeps things locked in,
you know, Stella.
That's why
I got her on the stage
to help get them out.
We're all she's got.
What about her mother?
She talks to her mother
on the phone.
Did you hear that, Lily?
The little madam.
She can't ring her mother.
She doesn't know where
her mother is.
None of us do.
America, we think.
What I am about to tell you
may put us in a bad light.
We threw her out,
Stella's mother.
Our Renée.
Not at first
when she came back
from London. Not then.
Going out...
staying out all night on more
than one occasion-- occasion.
She was young, Vernon.
She wanted a bit of life.
It was-- it was
before the war, of course.
She came back when the baby
was born-- our Stella.
But she went off again.
Got herself
a room in a house
around the corner
in Percy Street.
Artists and suchlike.
She got herself a job.
A telephonist at the GPO.
Quite successful.
Successful.
But she-- she couldn't stop it.
Dollin' herself up
and going out.
The neighbours told us.
They told us.
There she was, little Stella...
left alone in that basement...
in a cot...
with a row of nightlights
along the floor.
A baby.
And our Renée? Not sure.
She left a rose on her pillow.
Withered, of course.
Place stank of turps.
Could have been a conflagration.
There have been times...
there were times
I was close to death.
I knew it. Felt it.
And what I thought was...
I have a son...
and it will not be
the end of me.
But it is.
I may not face it as well
as I did death.
Stella!
Stella Maris!
Aah!
Now is the hour
when children
in their homes are abed.
Their lips bright-browned
with the good-night chocolate
and their tongues
drowsily searching
for belated crumbs
housed insecurely
on their shining cheeks.
Compare with them
the children
on this boat
about to walk the plank!
Split my infinitives
but 'tis my hour of triumph!
All right.
Right.
"Potter,
it may be that you think
"my association
with a certain person
"will prevent me from doing
anything about Geoffrey,
"but if this is so,
you are mistaken.
"My concern
is for a young man
"whose life may well
be ruined by your..."
Excuse me, sir.
Are you the stage manager?
Yes. I am.
Our Stella's been a brick.
She cradled me head, you know.
But she's been telling
her fibs again.
Like mother, like daughter.
Renée wasn't all bad.
She won that competition
to be the speaking clock
out of the whole of England.
"The girl
with the golden voice."
No, I'm out of 'em.
Will you take a substitute?
There is no substitute
for the real thing.
Tink! Dear Tink!
Are you dying?!
Captain Hook's drowned himself.
What do you mean?
Her light grows faint
and if that goes out,
it means she is dead!
Her voice is so low
I can scarcely hear
what she is saying!
He's dead.
Drowned himself, yes.
She says...
She says she thinks
she could get well again
if children believe in fairies!
Do you believe in fairies?
Say it quick! That you believe!
If you believe in fairies,
clap your hands!
Oh, children, clap your hands
and Tinkerbell will live!
If you believe in fairies,
children, clap your hands!
Louder! Louder!
Oh, clap your hands
and Tinkerbell will live!
Be a good girl, now.
It's all right. It's all right.
You be a good girl
and I'll be back soon.
I'll be just a minute.
Don't worry.
The thing is...
I don't suppose
we can keep it
out of the papers, Rose.
I could, but I won't.
God forgive me,
but it'll be good for business.
It's been awful.
I haven't dared phone you.
There was
this man who seduced me.
It wasn't my fault.
"At the third stroke...
"the time will be
10:47 and 20 seconds."
I'm learning, Mother.
I'm just...
bending down to tie a shoe lace.
"...10:47 and 30 seconds."
And everyone is waiting
round the corner.
"...the time will be
10:47 and 40 seconds."
"At the third stroke...
"the time will be
10:47 and 50 seconds."
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/54ety
Help other users to choose the best subtitles