Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Hey, Timmy, get me a hot dog.
Hey, Dave.
I like your Dukes of Hazzard T-shirt.
Thanks, Sara.
I like your CHiPs T-shirt.
-Thanks.
-Fun party, huh?
Yeah. Except for Arnie Shankman being here.
Wedgie! Wedgie! Wedgie!
You know, I kinda feel bad for him
with his sister losing her mind and all.
Whatever.
You know what we should do?
Play Truth or Dare.
-You want to?
-Sure.
Okay, I'll go first.
Truth or dare?
Truth.
Have you ever kissed a girl before?
-Well, I--
-Family doesn't count.
-Maybe I'll take dare.
-Okay.
I dare you to kiss me.
Right here?
Yeah. I want everyone to see
that your first kiss is with me.
Got any mustard for that
cocktail frank, butt-lick?
-David Buznik.
-I just landed in St. Louis.
-I hope you wrote my speech.
-I did, sir. I pulled an all nighter.
I look forward to this, Mr. Head.
Never been to St. Louis.
Thank you for allowing me
to come on this trip--
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, that sounds great.
If we finish our work,
I'd love to go to a jazz club.
Terrific.
-He hung up on you again, didn't he?
-Yes. Yes, he did.
He's a jerk. You came up with the idea
for the Husky Cat clothing line.
He didn't say thank you.
He should give you a promotion.
There's a creative executive position
that just opened up, so...
Bring that up on the trip.
You gotta stick up for yourself.
I know. I'll figure something out.
I gotta go. Sorry.
I'm gonna miss you.
That guy's looking at us.
You know I don't like it when
people watch me kiss.
I'm sorry.
Take care.
Okay. Bye.
Dave...
-Have a good flight.
-Okay.
I'm sorry.
I think you're in my seat.
Come on, pal. I'm already settled in
here. Can't you sit somewhere else?
You're supposed to sit in the seat
they assigned you.
Nobody cares. Just sit in the seat
I'm supposed to sit in.
Excuse me. This seat's available.
Okay. Thank you.
You're very welcome.
No air.
That's too bad, huh?
You're on my side of the armrest.
We're not gonna have problems,
are we?
No.
I'm wetting my Jockeys here.
You gotta get a load of this, keed.
I mean, you like comedies?
I just haven't been sleeping a lot
lately so I was trying to catch some...
Look at this actress here.
What is your position
on breast implants?
This guy.
I can just watch the movie with you.
Excuse me.
-Could I get a headset?
-Certainly.
Thank you.
Probably make out
with my next boyfriend.
Oh, my God, it was disgusting.
Miss?
I'll be right there, sir.
Where's your headset?
She's busy right now,
but it's coming.
For crying out loud. You're missing
important plot points.
Ma'am?
Could you give me a second, sir?
Excuse me.
Could I maybe get that headset,
please?
-Do not raise your voice to me, sir.
-I wasn't raising my voice.
Just calm down.
I am calm.
I just want my headset.
Our country is going through
a difficult time now.
If you won't cooperate--
I don't know where a headset
ties into patriotism.
Is there a problem here, sir?
I don't think so.
Can you come to the back with me
so we can have a talk?
A talk about what?
There's not a problem.
-The stewardess just keeps--
-Flight attendant.
The flight attendant keeps
ignoring me when--
Calm down.
I am calm.
What is it with you people?
"You people"?
Now wait a minute.
I don't mean you people.
I mean you people.
I will not tolerate any racist
behavior on the plane.
This is a difficult time
for our country.
I'm not a racist.
I just want to watch the movie.
I'm only going to say this
one more time, sir. Calm down.
I'm calm!
All rise.
-What do you think?
-Not guilty. It's a no-brainer.
Mr. Buznik. In case 723, assault and
battery against a flight attendant...
...I find you guilty.
I'm ordering you to pay a fine
of $3500.
Thank God you're okay.
In addition, to prevent
further acts of rage...
...this court orders you to undergo 20
hours of anger management therapy.
Anger management?
Oh, my goodness. Bobby Knight.
-You're in this group?
-Oh, yeah. This is my first day.
-It's my first day also.
-I hope this class cures me.
Working on the anger problem?
Anger? Isn't this
Sexaholics Anonymous?
No. I think that's down the hall.
Well, the hell with this!
I'm going home!
Dr. Rydell?
You don't remember me, do you?
-I sat next to you on the plane.
-Oh, yeah, the headset guy.
-Good to see you again.
-Good to see you too.
That was a crazy flight.
They actually sentenced me
to anger management for that.
Really?
Wow.
This is incredible.
You could sign this for me...
...and tell them I don't have
an anger problem if you want.
I can't just sign your papers.
I didn't do anything wrong.
You know that.
All right.
How's this?
Just hang for one session...
...so I can at least say
I gave you a proper analysis.
-Then I'll sign your papers.
-Okay.
-Shall we?
-Oh, yes. Yes.
So my boss, he was talking to me
about how many sick days I've taken.
And I was like, you know,
"Don't go there."
But he kept on about wanting to see
a doctor's note or something.
And I said, "Look, I'm seriously
serious. You don't want to go there."
But he kept talking and talking,
being such a nag...
...and then I just blacked out.
I blacked out.
And when I woke up, I was standing
over him and I was screaming:
"I told you not to go there!
I told you not to go there!"
How do you feel you
handled that situation?
Not as well as I could've.
Remember, Lou, temper's the one
thing you can't get rid of by losing it.
Now, Fury Fighters,
let's say hello to someone...
...who's joining our quest to get
the anger monkeys off our backs:
-Dave.
-Hi, Dave.
Hi.
Good news, I fed my anger monkey
a banana this morning...
...and he's feeling much better.
More good news, you won't have to
listen to those lame jokes...
...because I'm only here
for one session.
Dave assaulted a female
flight attendant in midair.
-Nice.
-I bet you beat her good.
I didn't beat anybody.
I touched a woman.
Liar. Bullshitter.
You're a woman beater.
You can't admit it because
you're a piece of garbage.
I don't know about all that, but
now I understand why you're here.
I'm here because I was verbally
attacked by my neighbor.
And I took a dump on his porch.
I guess you're better than me.
That's why you can't cop to your rage.
You're superior. He's superior.
-Maybe Dave's not ready yet, Chuck.
-You're not ready. Hear what he said?
Let's introduce Dave
to some of the rest of us.
Girls, why don't you tell Dave
what brought you here.
I'm sure he'd love to listen
to what you guys have to say.
We always do.
-Come on, Dave. Join us.
-Okay.
Okay. Well, we're
in the adult film industry.
And we're lovers.
One day, Gina was having sex
with this Filipino guy Melo...
-...which was cool, it was in the script.
-Sure.
And then I asked Melo
back to the house with us...
...which is cool, because,
well, we like a little variety.
Variety's good.
So anyway, in the middle
of our session...
...I look up and I see Gina
kissing Melo on the mouth...
...which is not cool because it
violates our threesome code of ethics.
-Stacy bit my toe off.
-Then Melo freaks out...
-...and calls me a crazy skank.
-Nobody talks to my bitch that way.
-So I stapled his lips shut.
-Here we are.
Well, we've all been there.
-I like him.
-Yeah, he's funny.
Not as funny as you.
I like that.
-All right, girls.
-Let it go. Let it go a little bit longer.
Walk it off.
Nate. Didn't we decide that you
shouldn't listen to the ball game?
Don't worry, Dr. B, it's just a
regular season game. Not important.
He missed the lay-up!
See? Iverson just missed a lay-up
at the buzzer, Sixers lose.
Who gives a crap, huh?
I mean, it's just a silly game,
anyways.
The anger sharks are swimming
in my head.
You gotta dunk that shit!
Listen to me. Stay with me, Nate.
Now, repeat after me, Nate:
Goosfraba.
Goos blah blah.
Not "blah blah," Nate.
Goosfraba.
That's good. Slower.
How do you feel?
Better.
Good job, Nate.
That sound is a derivation
of an old Eskimo word...
...that mothers used to calm
their children.
-I see.
-Eskimos seem nice.
-They do.
-I think Eskimos are smug.
Hold that thought, Chuck.
So, Dave...
...tell us about yourself.
Who are you?
Well, I am an executive assistant...
...at a major pet products company.
I don't want you to tell us what you do.
I want you to tell us who you are.
All right.
I'm a pretty good guy.
I like playing tennis on occasion...
Also, not your hobbies, Dave,
just simple:
Tell us who you are.
I just...
Maybe you could give me an example
of what a good answer would be.
What did you say?
You want Lou to tell you who you are?
No, I just...
I'm a nice, easygoing man.
I might be a little bit
indecisive at times.
Dave, you're describing
your personality.
I want to know...
-...who you are.
-What the hell do you want me to say?
I mean, I'm sorry. I just...
I want to answer your question.
I'm just not doing it right, I guess.
I think we're getting a picture, Dave.
-Let's move on.
-Dr. Rydell, I'd like to know something.
Why is it that Chuck
thinks he can smoke?
I do whatever I want when I want,
you little Spanish fruit topping.
Honey, at least I didn't
make my aunt pregnant.
What are you laughing at, Dave?
Just laughing. I don't know.
I'm not laughing at you.
Were you laughing with me?
Because I'm not laughing.
Am I out of line,
or is this guy pushing me?
Well, how do you feel, Chuck?
I went from happy to angry, skipped
sad. Now I feel like kicking his ass.
Then we'll see who's laughing.
What? Think you're better than me
because you've got both your nuts?
All right, man. All right. Come on.
Come on, big boy. Pretty boy.
All right. Is it worth going back
to the penitentiary, Chuck?
-So he's laughing at you.
-I'm not laughing at him.
Goosfraba.
-Goosfraba.
-Okay.
Good job, Chuck.
That was really good.
Where's the coffee cake?
I was looking forward to it.
I haven't been to the Actors Studio
in quite some time.
-I'm sure your audition will go well.
-Thanks. I hope so.
-Good night.
-All right.
-Thanks, Buddy.
-Bye-bye.
That was a little bit insane.
If I had to do 20 hours of that,
I'd end up killing myself.
Here you go.
Twenty hours in my class
would be pointless for you.
I agree.
I think I'm going to recommend
to the court that we double your time.
What do you mean?
Let me explain something.
There are two kinds of angry people:
explosive and implosive.
Explosive is the kind of individual that
you see screaming at the cashier...
...for not taking their coupons.
Implosive is the cashier
who remains quiet, day after day...
...and finally shoots everyone
in the store.
You're the cashier.
No. I'm the guy hiding in the frozen
food section dialing 911, I swear.
I'm going to assign you an anger ally...
...to help calm you down
when you're losing it.
Chuck.
Not Chuck. Give me Bobby Knight,
or the porno girls.
Heard we're partnering up, huh?
-Yes.
-Here's my number.
Great. "You're going to die, bitch."
Oops, that's a letter I'm writing
to Geraldo Rivera.
-I see.
-My bad. Here.
That's the number. Good. Thank you.
Dave and Chuck...
...working together as a team.
-It's a win-win situation.
-Yeah, feels it.
Dave's particulars.
I'll see you soon.
The Yanks are great this season.
Dave thinks they could beat
Seattle's win record.
Remember at Brown when we
saw Ron Guidry win his 20th?
Oh, man.
He was on fire that year.
We could've been too.
Andrew, don't start or I can't
hang out with you anymore.
Sorry, it's just hard. I'll never
meet anyone as good as you.
You will.
She'll be a very lucky lady.
Thanks for being my best friend.
Linda.
-Hey, Dave.
-Andrew.
Good to see you guys hugging.
How was the doctor?
Psychotic.
Well, did you get any good
promotion news from Mr. Head?
I wasn't able to talk to him
about that yet, but I will.
Not that crowded here.
You'd think it would be packed.
I rented the place. I figured it'd be
more fun if it was just Brown alumni.
Where'd you go to college again?
Trenton Community College.
You had a hard day.
Let me buy you a milk shake.
Later, Andrew.
--once you cast your line in,
so during retrieval...
...it'll help you to create
a realistic and a erratic...
Hey, Dave.
-Hey. Andrew, what's up?
-Not much.
You always try to simulate live bait.
Okay, they got fishing while you
go to the bathroom. That's nice.
Yep. Bass fishing.
Hey, he caught one.
Be aware of your presentation...
...and make sure that,
as you work it along...
Oh, yeah.
Congratulations.
Now that is a big one, folks.
Always a blast being with your friends.
It was a great night.
Yankees winning, beer and hot dogs.
Yeah, you like those foot-long
hot dogs, don't you?
So I saw your boy Andrew
at the urinal.
Saw his...
-...thing.
-You were looking?
Yeah, unfortunately.
So, now, did this guy grow up near
a nuclear power plant or something?
What are you talking about?
Never really seen nothing like that
before. Didn't it used to scare you?
I never saw it.
You never saw it?
No, I told you, I never slept
with him. Why, is it huge?
No. No. No. No.
It's actually quite petite.
I felt bad for him.
It looked like it belonged on
a baby and it had a funny color.
I bet he got a lot of snickers
in the locker room.
Like, "What the hell's that thing?"
When you're in a locker room,
you must feel good about yourself.
I do. If there are 20 naked guys
in there, I'm usually in the top 18.
-Which isn't bad.
-You're doing really good.
Thanks.
-Who's that?
-I don't know. Let me get rid of them.
-Hello?
-Dave, it's me, Chuck.
-Who's Chuck?
-Your anger ally.
I'm in a mood, Dave. A bad mood.
A very bad mood.
I was fired from my ice-cream truck job
today. No more Fudgeicles.
-What's an anger ally?
-Who's that?
She making fun of me?
No. That's my girlfriend.
You tell her to put a sock in it because
I need to talk to you right now!
We're a little busy right now.
You're busy? We're all busy, okay?
You come down here before
a black wolf swallows my brain!
After I got kicked out of the Army,
I went through a real bad time:
Hookers, booze, shooting holes in the
ceiling, screaming myself to sleep.
Finally, my parents said I
had to move out.
I'm guessing that's when you
decided to shack up with your aunt.
Don't get cute, wiseass!
But, yes.
What's with the watch, huh?
Am I boring you?
We ordered the drinks 15 minutes ago
and I kind of gotta get back.
Miss? Excuse me, miss?
Is this
Slow And Stupid Waitress Day?
I'm sorry. I be right with you.
Damn, man, reminds me
of these chicks back in the war.
Would give you the old licky-licky,
then fry your banana.
Settle.
I have seen some shit, man.
I kid you not, I have seen some shit.
Wake up to the sound
of kids screaming.
Explosions everywhere.
Never know when your number's up.
Vietnam, huh?
-Grenada, man.
-Grenada?
Wasn't that like 12 hours long?
Did you see that?
-See what?
-That guy. He just gave me a look.
He didn't give you a look.
And I'm pretty sure I heard him mutter
some kind of anti-Semitic remark.
Are you Jewish?
I could be. But, no. Half Irish,
half Italian, half Mexican.
Let's go give those guys some tsuris.
Well, the guy on the left
is blind, Chuck.
I hear you.
He's yours.
No. That's not what I was saying.
-Hey.
-What the hell?
Got something against guys
with hair?
What's going on?
Don't! Stop it! Stop!
Stop! Goosfraba!
You piece of shit!
Stop it! Stop it!
Welcome back, Mr. Buznik.
I see you've managed to brutalize
a cocktail waitress this time.
I guess beating up stewardesses
can get old after a while.
Flight attendant, Your Honor.
I didn't hit her on purpose,
Your Honor.
I was being attacked by someone...
...and while I was
trying to take away his...
His...
Trying to take away my cane,
Your Honor.
You cracked a waitress in the face...
...while attempting to steal
a blind man's cane?
Your Honor, we're not even sure
how blind this man really is.
Okay. My bad. Moving on.
Happy now, ass-wipe?
Mr. Buznik, I don't know
why you hate women.
Maybe you don't know either...
...but I'll let you think about it while
you spend one year in a state prison.
-Isn't that a bit harsh, Your Honor?
-No!
Okay.
-May I approach, Your Honor?
-By all means, Dr. Rydell.
Thank you.
-It's been a while.
-Yes, it has.
-You look marvelous, Brenda.
-Thank you.
-And how are the boys?
-Fantastic.
James made the basketball team,
Raheem landed the lead...
...in Fiddler on the Roof.
Raheem will make
a breathtaking Tevye, I'm sure.
So do you have a take
on this Buznik guy?
Is this good or bad?
Well, it's bad that he's
talking to her...
...but it's good that...
No, it's bad. It's all bad.
-You think you can help him?
-I think so, Your Honor.
If I can't, I'll tear him apart
with my bare hands.
Mr. Buznik...
...because of the enormous respect
I have for Dr. Rydell...
...I'm placing you in his intensive
anger management program...
...for 30 days.
But if you fail to strictly adhere
to the rules of his program...
...you will spend the next year
in state prison.
-Buddy?
-Good evening. Ready to get it on?
Get what on?
What are you doing here?
Well, well, well.
The lair of the rage rhino.
I smell the effluvium
of pain and frustration.
-Where should we put my stuff?
-What stuff?
We've got 30 days
to control your anger.
My approach dictates
intense observation.
What better vantage point
than bunkmates?
Put that there, Dan,
thank you very much.
No. No. I'm sorry. Guys, I don't think
you should be moving in with me.
Sit down, Dave.
Let's be perfectly clear about this.
You've been deemed
a threat to society.
I believe that radical,
round-the-clock therapy...
...is the only way to effect
a meaningful and positive change...
...in your behavior.
Now we can do it here
or Rikers Island.
-Anything else, Dr. B?
-No thanks, Dan.
We'll install the wiretaps
tomorrow.
Wiretaps?
-Is this your CD collection?
-Yes.
Oh, my.
What are you doing?
I don't want you listening
to any angry music.
The Carpenters are angry?
I mean...
Don't be naive, Dave.
"Close to You."
"We've Only Just Begun."
Songs of madness and obsession.
Who's going to pay for that?
Retard your anger level a few notches
and listen to me. Can you do that?
Yeah. It's retarded. I'm retarded.
Good.
Now then, we need to go over
some ground rules.
My girlfriend got me that.
You're to refrain from violent acts
including verbal assault...
...and vulgar hand gestures.
You may not use rage-enhancing
substances...
...such as caffeine, nicotine, alcohol,
crack cocaine...
...Slippy-Flippies, Jelly Stingers,
Trick Sticks...
...Bing Bangs or Flying Willards.
-How about Fiddle Faddles?
-Under my supervision.
Also, if you are unable
to stop masturbating...
...please do so without the use
of any pornographic images...
...depicting quote-unquote
"angry sex."
That having been said,
I'm a pretty good guy...
...and I think you'll be
pleasantly surprised...
...at how much fun we can have.
Jeez, without Slippy-Flippies or angry
masturbating? How is that possible?
Sarcasm is anger's ugly cousin.
From now on, unacceptable.
Dave, I got this for you.
It's a wonderfully therapeutic tool.
Record your thoughts on this
whenever you feel angry.
I'm feeling very angry right now...
...because I only have one bed
and no couch.
Not a problem.
In Europe, it's not considered unusual
for three or four men to share a bed.
Yeah, well, that's why I'm
proud to be an American.
By the way...
I like to sleep in the nude.
You hear that frog?
Nope.
What do you want?
I'm just recording your demeanor
upon awakening.
Good to see you got your
underwear back on.
6:30?
I don't gotta be up till 7.
You've got to make my breakfast.
Dave, cooking is very relaxing
and therapeutic.
I want two eggs,
over easy and unfertilized...
...wheat toast, dry, and please...
...tell me you've got ketchup.
There's a Denny's down the street.
Not only do they have ketchup...
...but they got the angriest
waitresses I've seen.
You could have a blast with
the goosfraba thing down there.
Lame-o.
Your eggs.
-Holy shit!
-I said over easy!!
Now, why did I do that?
Because I refused to spoon with you
last night?
The angry man opens his mouth
and shuts his eyes.
Alpha-Bits.
No matter how old I get,
always a culinary delight.
No explanation for the egg throwing.
He's a psycho.
Don't sulk, Dave. Eat. Sit down.
We'll be off to work in a jiffy.
"We'll be off to work." Now, by "we'll,"
I assume you mean just me, right?
Well, I have to join you at work.
Full contact.
That will make me look nuts, Buddy,
bringing a shrink to work...
...you whipping eggs at people.
I don't know.
You must never be ashamed that you
sought help for yourself, Dave.
It's not a weakness.
I mean, I gotta be there by 9:00.
I don't think we'll make it on time.
You're not even dressed.
The Talmud says:
"Wherever you look...
...there's something to be seen."
Look, Dave.
-What exactly was that all about?
-What?
You just ran through a red light.
Are you trying to get us both killed?
I'm a little flustered right now.
I have to be to work in eight minutes.
Flustered?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa, man!
-Holy shit! What are you doing?
-I need you to unfluster.
My boss is going to go nuts on me
if we're late, so please?
We will proceed when you
are centered.
I'm centered, I'm centered.
There's 10,000 people behind us.
Let's go, crazy man.
What is that? Is that good?
We're going to sing a song.
No. I don't want to sing a song.
I want to go to... I've gotta go.
Here we go.
The magic of Leonard Bernstein
and Stephen Sondheim's...
...West Side Story.
"I Feel Pretty."
Get this moving.
What the hell's your problem?
Shut your pie-hole!
We're working here!
Wow. Sorry.
# I feel pretty, #
# Oh, so pretty, #
# I feel pretty and witty and gay! #
# And I pity #
# Any girl who isn't me today. #
# I feel charming, #
# Oh, so charming #
# It's alarming how charming I feel! #
Move your ass, dipshit!
# And so pretty #
# That I hardly can believe I'm real #
Burn in hell!
# See the pretty girl in that mirror there?
What mirror? Where? #
# Who can that attractive girl be?
Wich one? Where? #
# Such a pretty face,
Such a pretty dress, #
# Such a pretty smile,
Such a pretty me! #
# - I feel stunning #
- I feel stunning
# - And entrancing #
- And entrancing
# Feel like running and dancing for joy, #
# For I'm loved #
# By a pretty wonderful boy! #
You're late.
Yes. There was a little bit
of a tie up on the bridge.
I didn't ask for a traffic report.
You're always late.
Now is the first time I've been late.
But you're right. I'm sorry.
May I interject?
You were about to say something else
before you said, "I'm sorry."
We mustn't absorb and repress.
-Who's this?
-I'm his anger management therapist.
You're in anger management?
Temporarily, yeah.
Do you remember the flight
to St. Louis...
...that I was on when they had to
turn the plane around?
Yeah, yeah. Because of that unruly
passenger in coach.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
He doesn't like people
touching his clubs.
Well, that unruly passenger was me.
I got arrested at Kennedy. That's why
I didn't make the next flight.
You said your apartment caught fire.
Dissembling is a common tool
of the anger junkie.
Might I have your first name,
Mr. Head? And tell me it isn't Dick.
-It's Frank.
-Fran.
Isn't that normally a girl's name?
What went on on that flight?
To be honest with you,
it was a mix-up. I...
Jibber jabber. Jibber jabbering.
Mumbo jumbo.
Denial. Key, key, key, key, key, key.
Fran, your assistant beat the bejesus
out of a flight attendant.
-I didn't.
-You broke her nose.
I broke the cocktail waitress's nose.
I mean, I accidentally did that.
Dave, you have a disease.
Would you apologize if you
were a diabetic? Of course not.
Why do you feel you have to apologize
because you're suffering from T.A.S.?
T.A.S.?
Toxic Anger Syndrome.
I don't have T.A.S.
He's angry. It's a sickness,
not a crime, Fran.
His name is Frank!
No. I'm sorry.
Clothes for cats
isn't really a new idea...
...but there was never really a line
made for overweight cats...
...who might feel a little
self-conscious...
...about how they look
in certain outfits.
That's why I got the baggy sweater
on him, to cover up his gut.
And the beret to take attention
off his plump head.
Oh, little Meatball.
You tie this up tight...
...and away goes the chin.
I'm so handsome.
-Hey, Dave. This is your office?
-Andrew.
-What are you doing here?
-I played golf with Frank.
He's friends with my dad. We're
members of the same country club.
Really? I've been wanting to
play golf with him a long time.
-Is it awesome there?
-It's nice.
So, anyway, Dave, how's
anger management going?
Who told you about that?
Linda's my best friend.
There's no secrets between us.
For the love of Mike!
This guy's your girl's best friend?
No. I mean, I like to consider
myself her best friend...
...but Andrew is her best friend friend,
if that makes any sense.
You ought to golf yourself.
You look a little stressed out.
I gotta go. Bye.
Well, well, well.
This guy's got quite a basket on him.
Really? I didn't notice that.
Do you really want the love of your life
hanging around with a guy...
...who looks as though he could
satisfy a blue whale?
Well, it's...
I'm doing okay myself, pal.
Maybe it's the way his pants fit him.
What's up?
-This is your young lady?
-That's my Linda.
My, oh, my.
I was toying with the notion
that you were gay...
...because of the kitty-cat
clothes, so forth.
What does she do?
She teaches poetry. Poetry teacher.
I love poetry.
Oh, my, my, my. It's...
Yes, it's a good picture of her.
Well, apparently Dr. Rydell has a
history of unorthodox techniques.
He's got a dozen lawsuits pending.
So it's not just me.
This guy is nuts, isn't he?
Or a genius.
But if you could prove that he's nuts:
audiotape, video, picture, whatever...
...I'll arrange a hearing.
I gotta go. I think he's coming.
Hi, Nancy.
What are you doing
in the ladies' room?
Sorry. I just heard you guys
got cleaner seats than us.
Not after I get through with them.
I don't care for the way you've
ironed my shirts, Dave. Try it again.
-I've been very patient with you.
-Beware the fury of the patient man.
-I'm serious!
-Too serious.
Get undressed.
What did you say?
Take off your clothes.
I've got a stress-reduction
technique to show you.
-It'll be good for you.
-Take off my clothes?
Do you want to see me naked, Buddy?
Are you a homophobe, Dave?
No, I'm a pulling-my-penis-out-
in-front-of-you-a-phobe.
Let's take a walk on the wild side.
-What's up, baby?
-Why are we here?
I'm not a homophobe.
My lawyer's gay.
His boyfriend is gay.
And are they all aware
that you despise them?
Looking for company, baby?
No. We're not. Thank you.
It's worth 50 bucks...
...if you get in the back seat with
my friend here and have a little chat.
My pleasure, Mr. Eyebrows.
Oh, boy, here we go.
-Hello.
-Hey. Good to see you.
-What's your name, baby?
-Melvin.
His name is David. Don't dissemble.
I'm not dissembling.
That's my Hebrew name.
I'm Galaxia. That's my German name.
Great.
Where are you from originally,
Hebrew Melvin?
Brooklyn.
What part of Germany
do you hail from?
I'm from a little Bavarian village
called Lickin Zee Dickin.
Care to visit?
Actually, I like to spend
most of my time...
...in Girls Without Wieners-ville.
I'm more comfortable there.
He's just not used to male intimacy.
Well, that's okay,
because I'm a lady.
Oops, no, I'm not.
Whoa! There it is.
I feel like dancing. Dancing.
Oh, my God.
What does this have to do
with anger management?
-Oh, are you an angry boy?
-No.
Do you need some discipline?
No, thank you very--
Oh! Hey! Hey, watch that shit!
Listen, ladies!
Gentleman! Lentleman!
I'm not having sex with a she-male!
Relax!
Galaxia, you may
get out of the car now.
Your services are no longer required.
You know what?
You guys are freaks.
Give me the tape recorder.
Come on.
Patient number 135, David Buznik...
...has learned the difference between
unhealthy anger and righteous anger.
Thus he has advanced
to the second level of my program.
Great. Can I go throw up now?
I'm a lady. Oops, no, I'm not.
-Whoa, there it is.
-I feel like dancing.
Wasn't that sick?
She looked like Olivia Newton-John...
...if she was really ugly
and had huge balls.
But Buddy didn't order you
to have sex.
I'm getting a call.
Please hang on.
-Hello?
-Is Buddy there?
No, he's in the shower right now.
This is Becky, his assistant.
Just tell him his mom called
from Boston.
She said she's having
some minor surgery.
It's not serious, but she'll be at Boston
County Hospital for the next two days.
Miracles of modern science.
I am stimulating my hair follicles...
...and brushing my teeth
at the same time.
It looks really good.
What's the matter?
Your mom. They took her
to the hospital, Buddy.
What's wrong with my mother?
She's having surgery.
I'm sorry.
-Is it serious?
-When is surgery not serious?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
Maybe I better get up to Boston...
...see what's going on up there.
Yeah. Yeah.
Why don't you just go up there.
Spend some quality time.
I'll stay here.
It'll be good for you guys.
Oh, God.
You're all I got, Mom.
Please don't leave me.
No more clam chowder.
Buddy...
...it was a joke.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to cry anymore.
-A joke?
-Yeah.
Oh, boy.
A joke. A jo-- I...
I can't believe that
I fell for that one.
I really thought my mother
was having surgery.
I'm going to get you
back for that one.
Just so you know,
she really is having surgery.
I thought you said you were joking.
No, the serious part was the joke.
She's having surgery,
but just minor surgery.
Maybe I better get up to Boston...
...see what's really going on up there.
Why don't you--? You just
shoot up there. I'll be here.
What?
-I can't believe he's making me go.
-How come you guys aren't flying?
Because Dr. Cocoa Puff said legally
I'm not allowed to get on a plane.
Meanwhile, I've got Head up my ass
about that catalog.
I've got to get it done with
nut-boy in Boston.
Why can't Head write his own catalog?
Because I've got to earn
that promotion.
You've been doing his job for years.
You should be his--
I'm sorry. I know this is really
stressing you out.
I'm sure that it's going to be over
before you know it.
Yeah, if I don't get caught
popping any Jelly Stingers.
Well, that's going to be tough!
Oh, God. There he is.
-That's him?
-Yes.
What? Oh. Okay, I'll hold that.
My--
The quiet warmth
Smoldering beneath the rituals
Of hope for familiarity
A coursing underground river
Pregnant with the chance currents
Of knowledge and love
-What?
-That's my poem! I wrote that.
I know.
That is your poem.
I love that poem.
I found it crumpled up
behind the sports pages...
...on the floor of David's bedroom.
-Shades of early Emily Dickinson.
-Who was great on Police Woman.
Thank you. And thank you
for rescuing it from the floor.
I think I better get going.
I'll miss you, big guy,
so take good care.
-How about a kiss?
-I'd love a kiss.
I think she's talking to me.
I think I can handle it.
So why don't you back up
an inch or two.
Got it.
Thank you. And, take care.
Have a great trip, you guys.
Oh, we will.
Bye.
What?
Some mindless nitwit
is parked behind me.
Good. Then we can't go.
No, I can get out.
-Get in.
-I don't know how you'll get out.
Try to wiggle out, you're going to get
a ding. But you know everything.
What's he doing?
Well, you're batting a thousand...
...in craziness.
Now we're bumping into cars.
I'm just making a little room
to back up.
If I had lost my temper...
...would I have had
the presence of mind...
...to leave my card
and my insurance information?
Whatever, Mr. Insane-Vein-Popping-
A-Little-Too-Far-Out-Of-His-Head-...
...While-Swinging-The-Bat Guy.
I think you've got room to back up.
Why haven't you taken Linda
off the market?
Think you can do better?
I'm going to ask her to marry me
when I'm ready.
Nobody wants to settle down
with a 35-year-old secretary.
Procrastination, Dave.
I'm not procrastinating.
I even think about how I'm
going to pop the question.
Husky down jacket.
Husky Eskimo look.
What's your plan,
ask her at a Yankee game?
Actually, yes. How did you know?
I said the corniest thing
I could think of.
If you knew Linda, you'd know
how uncorny it would be to her.
Putting up a "Marry me, please"
on the scoreboard...
...proclaiming my love for her
in front of thousands of strangers.
As you seem to have noticed, I'm a little
bit jumpy with public affection.
You seemed to be lovey-dovey
back there.
Glad you think that's funny.
I gotta work.
A five-hour trip to find out Mommy
had a jelly bean...
...removed from her nose.
I'm glad I missed work.
Can we eat now?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/35mqg
Help other users to choose the best subtitles