Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
October is inventory time.
So right now, Statler Toyota
is making the best deals of the year...
on all 1985 model Toyotas.
You won't find a better car...
At a better price with better service
anywhere in Hill Valley.
That's Statler Toyota
in downtown Hill Valley.
But hurry. These prices
are only good till the end of...
The Senate
is expected to vote on this today.
In other news, officials at
the Pacific Nuclear research facility...
have denied the rumor that
a case of missing plutonium...
was in fact stolen
from their vault two weeks ago.
A Libyan terrorist group had claimed
responsibility for the alleged theft.
However, officials now
attribute the discrepancy...
to a simple clerical error.
The F.B.I., which is investigating
the matter, had no comment.
Twelve wooden crates filled
with cocaine washed ashore near
Boca Raton, Florida, yesterday.
Hey, Doc?
Doc?
Hello. Anybody home?
Einstein, come here, boy.
What's goin' on?
Oh, God.
Oh, Jesus!
That is disgusting.
What the hell is it with him?
Whoa.
Rock 'n' roll.
- Yo. Hey.
- Marty, is that you?
Hey, Doc.
Where are you?
I've found you. Can you meet me
at Twin Pines Mall tonight at 1:15?
I made a major breakthrough.
I'll need your assistance.
- 1:15 in the morning?
Doc, what's goin' on?
- Yeah.
- Where you been all week?
- Workin'.
- Is Einstein with you?
- Yeah, he's right here.
You left your equipment
on all week.
My equipment.
That reminds me, Marty.
Do not hook up to the amplifier. There's
a slight possibility of overload.
Yeah.
I'll keep that in mind.
Good. I'll see you tonight.
Don't forget now.
- 1:15 a.m., Twin Pines Mall.
- Right.
- Are those my clocks I hear?
- Yeah, it's 8:00.
Perfect!
My experiment worked!
They're all exactly
25 minutes slow!
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you telling me
that's it's 8:25?
- Precisely.
- Damn!
I'm late for school.
# The power of love
is a curious thing #
# Make one man weep
Make another man sing #
# Change your heart
to a little white dove #
# More than a feelin'
That's the power of love #
# You don't need money
Don't take fame #
# Don't need no credit card
to ride this train #
# It's strong and it's sudden
and it's cruel sometimes #
# But it might
just save your life #
# That's the power of love #
# Can you feel it #
- Yo, Jennifer.
- Marty, don't go this way.
Strickland's looking for you.
If you get caught,
it'll be four tardies in a row.
All right, come on.
I think we're safe.
This time wasn't my fault. The doc
set all his clocks 25 minutes slow.
The doc? Am I to understand
you're still hanging around
with Dr. Emmett Brown, McFly?
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Tardy slip for you, Miss Parker.
And one for you, McFly.
I believe that makes four in a row.
Let me give you a nickel's worth
of free advice, young man.
This so-called Dr. Brown is dangerous.
He's a real nutcase.
Hang around with him,
you'll end up in big trouble.
Oh, yes, sir.
You got a real attitude problem.
You're a slacker.
You remind me of your father when
he went here. He was a slacker too.
Can I go now,
Mr. Strickland?
I notice your band is on the roster
for the dance auditions.
Why even bother, McFly?
You don't have a chance.
You're too much
like your old man.
No McFly ever amounted to anything
in the history of Hill Valley.
Yeah, well,
history is gonna change.
Next, please.
All right.
We're the, uh...
We're the Pinheads.
One, two, three...
Okay, that's enough.
Thank you, fellas.
Hold it.
Hold it, fellas.
I'm afraid you're
just too darn loud.
Next, please.
Next group, please.
Reelect Mayor Goldie Wilson.
Progress is his middle name.
Too loud. I can't believe it.
We'll never get a chance
to play in front of anybody.
Marty, one rejection
isn't the end of the world.
I just don't think
I'm cut out for music.
But you're good, Marty. You're really
good, and your audition tape is great.
You've gotta send it in
to the record company.
- It's like Doc's always saying.
- I know.
If you put your mind to it,
you can accomplish anything.
That's good advice, Marty.
All right. What if I send in
the tape and they don't like it?
What if they say
I'm no good?
What if they say,
"You got no future"?
I don't think I can take
that kind of rejection.
Jesus. I'm starting
to sound like my old man.
- He's not that bad.
- Save the clock tower.
He's letting you borrow
the car tomorrow night.
Check out that 4x4.
- That is hot.
- Back her up.
Someday, Jennifer.
Someday.
Wouldn't it be great to take
that truck up to the lake?
Throw a couple of sleeping bags
in the back.
Lie out underneath the stars.
- Stop it.
- What?
Does your mom know?
About tomorrow night?
Nah, get outta town. My mom thinks
I'm goin' campin' with the guys.
My mother would freak out if she knew
I was goin' up there with you.
I'd get
the standard lecture...
about how she never did
that stuff when she was a kid.
I mean, look,
I think the woman was born a nun.
She's just trying
to keep you respectable.
She's not doin'
a very good job.
- Terrible.
- Save the clock tower.
Save the clock tower.
Mayor Wilson is sponsoring
an initiative to replace that clock.
Thirty years ago,
lightning struck that clock tower...
and the clock
hasn't run since.
We at the Hill Valley
Preservation Society...
think it should be preserved
exactly the way it is...
as part of our history
and heritage.
- There's a quarter.
- Thank you.
- Don't forget to take a flyer.
- Right.
Save the clock tower!
- Where were we?
- Right about here.
Jennifer!
It's my dad. I've gotta go.
- I'll call you tonight.
- I'll be at my grandma's.
Here, let me
give you the number.
Bye.
# That's the power of love #
# First time you feel it
it might make you sad #
# Next time you feel it
it might make you mad #
# But you'll be glad, baby
when you've found #
# That's the power
makes the world go round #
# And it don't take money #
# Don't take fame #
# Don't need no credit card
to ride this train #
# It's strong and it's sudden
It can be cruel sometimes #
# But it might
just save your life ##
California, Bravo, Tango, Delta 6-2-9.
Tow for impoundment.
Any unit, please respond.
Perfect. Just perfect.
I can't believe
you'd loan me your car...
without tellin' me
it had a blind spot.
I could've been killed.
Now, Biff,
I never noticed...
that the car had any blind spot
before when I would drive it.
Hi, son.
Are you blind, McFly? It's there.
How else do you explain
that wreck out there?
Now, Biff, can I...
can I assume...
that your, uh, insurance
is gonna pay for the damage?
My insurance?
It's your car.
Your insurance should pay for it.
I wanna know who's gonna pay for this.
I spilled beer when I was smashed into.
Who's gonna pay my cleaning bill?
-  Uh...
- And where's my reports?
I haven't finished those up yet, but I
figured since they weren't due till...
Hello? Hello?
Anybody home? Huh?
Think, McFly. Think!
I gotta have time
to get 'em retyped.
Do you realize what would happen if I
hand in my reports in your handwriting?
I'll get fired.
You wouldn't want that
to happen, would ya?
- Would ya?
- Of course not, Biff.
I wouldn't
want that to happen.
Now, look. I'll finish
those reports tonight...
and I'll run 'em on over
first thing tomorrow.
Not too early.
I sleep in Saturday.
Your shoe's untied.
Don't be so gullible, McFly.
Got the place fixed up nice.
I have your car towed
all the way to your house...
and all you got for me
is light beer?
What are you lookin' at,
butthead?
Say hi to your mom
for me.
I know what you're gonna say,
son, and you're right.
You're right.
But, uh, Biff just happens
to be my supervisor...
and I'm afraid I'm just not
very good at... confrontations.
But the car, Dad.
I mean, he wrecked it.
He totaled it.
I needed that car
tomorrow night, Dad.
Do you have any idea
how important this was to me?
I know, and all
I can say is I'm...
I'm sorry.
Believe me, Marty,
you're better off...
without having to worry
about all the aggravation...
and headaches
of playing at that dance.
He's absolutely right.
The last thing you need
is headaches.
Kids, we're gonna have to eat
this cake by ourselves.
Your Uncle Joey
didn't make parole again.
It would be nice if you
all dropped him a line.
- Uncle Jailbird Joey?
- He's your brother, Mom.
Yeah. It's a major embarrassment,
having an uncle in prison.
We all make mistakes
in life, children.
- Goddamn it. I'm late.
- David, watch your mouth!
You come here and kiss your mother
before you go.
Come on, Mom. Make it fast.
I'll miss my bus.
See you later, Pop.
Whoo! Time to change
that oil.
Oh. Ha-ha-ha.
Hey, Marty. I'm not
your answering service.
While you were outside
pouting over the car...
Jennifer Parker
called you twice.
I don't like her. Any girl who calls
up a boy is just asking for trouble.
Oh, Mom. There's nothing wrong
with calling a boy.
I think it's terrible.
Girls chasing boys.
When I was your age,
I never chased a boy or called a boy...
or sat in a parked car
with a boy.
Then how am I ever
supposed to meet anybody?
Well, it'll just happen.
Like the way
I met your father.
That was so stupid.
Grandpa hit him with the car.
It was meant to be.
Anyway...
if Grandpa hadn't hit him,
then none of you would have been born.
Yeah, well.
I still don't understand what Dad
was doin' in the middle of the street.
What was it, George?
Bird-watching?
What, Lorraine? What?
Anyway, your Grandpa
hit him with the car...
and brought him
into the house.
He seemed so helpless.
Like a little lost puppy,
and my heart just went out to him.
Yeah, Mom, we know. You've told us
this story a million times.
You felt sorry for him.
So you decided to go with him
to the "Fish Under The Sea" dance.
No. It was
the "Enchantment Under The Sea" dance.
Our first date.
I'll never forget it.
It was the night of that
terrible thunderstorm, remember, George?
Your father kissed me for
the very first time on that dance floor.
It was then
that I realized...
that I was gonna spend
the rest of my life with him.
Oh, no! Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
# #
Hello.
Marty, you didn't fall asleep, did you?
Ah, Doc. Uh, no.
No, don't be silly.
Listen, this is very important.
I forgot my video camera.
Can you pick it up at my place
on your way to the mall?
Uh, yeah.
I'm on my way.
- Einstein! Hey, Einstein,
where's the doc, boy?
Doc!
- Marty! You made it!
- Yeah.
Welcome to
my latest experiment.
This is the one I've been
waiting for all my life.
- Uh, well, it's a DeLorean.
- Bear with me.
All your questions will be answered.
Roll tape, and we'll proceed.
- Is that a Devo suit?
- Never mind that now.
- Not now.
- I'm ready.
Good evening.
I'm Dr. Emmett Brown.
I'm in the parking lot
of Twin Pines Mall.
It's Saturday morning,
October 26, 1985, 1:18 a.m.
This is temporal experiment
number one.
Come on, Einie.
Get in there.
Attaboy. In you go. Sit down.
Put your seat belt on.
Whoa, whoa. Okay.
Please note
that Einstein's clock...
is in precise synchronization
with my control watch.
- Got it? Good.
- Right. Check, Doc.
Have a good trip, Einstein.
Watch your head.
You got that thing
hooked up to the... car?
- Watch this.
- Yeah. Okay.
Got it.
Jesus!
Not me! The car!
If my calculations
are correct...
when this baby hits
88 miles per hour...
you're gonna see
some serious shit.
Watch this! Watch this!
Ah! What did I tell you?
Eighty-eight miles
per hour!
The temporal displacement occurred
exactly 1:20 a.m. And zero seconds!
Ah, Jesus Christ!
Jesus Christ, Doc!
You disintegrated Einstein!
Calm down. I didn't
disintegrate anything.
The molecular structure of both Einstein
and the car are completely intact.
- Then where the hell are they?
- The appropriate question is,
"When the hell are they?"
You see, Einstein has just become
the world's first time traveler!
I sent him
into the future!
One minute into the future,
to be exact.
At precisely 1:21 a.m.
And zero seconds...
we shall catch up with him
and the time machine.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, Doc. Uh...
Are you telling me that you
built a time machine...
out of a DeLorean?
If you're gonna build
a time machine into a car,
why not do it with some style?
Besides, the stainless steel
construction made the flux dispersal...
Look out!
- What? What? Is it hot?
- It's cold.
Damn cold.
Ah, ha-ha!
Einstein, you little devil!
Einstein's clock is exactly one minute
behind mine and still ticking!
- He's all right.
- He's fine.
He's completely unaware
that anything happened.
As far as he's concerned,
the trip was instantaneous.
That's why his watch
is exactly one minute behind mine.
He skipped over that minute to instantly
arrive at this moment in time.
Come here.
I'll show you how it works.
First, you turn
the time circuits on.
This readout tells you
where you're going...
this one tells you where you are,
this one tells you where you were.
You input your destination time
on this keypad.
Say you wanna see the signing of
the Declaration of Independence.
Or witness
the birth of Christ.
Here's a red-letter date
in the history of science.
November 5, 1955.
Yes, of course.
What happened?
That was the day
I invented time travel.
I remember it vividly. I was standing
on my toilet hanging a clock.
The porcelain was wet.
I slipped, hit my head on the sink.
When I came to,
I had a revelation.
A vision. A picture in my head.
A picture of this.
This is what makes
time travel possible.
The flux capacitor.
- Flux capacitor?
- It's taken almost 30 years
and my family fortune...
to realize
the vision of that day.
My God, has it been that long?
Things have certainly changed
around here.
I remember when this was all farmland
as far as the eye could see.
Old man Peabody
owned all of this.
He had this crazy idea
about breeding pine trees.
This is, uh...
This is heavy-duty, Doc.
This is great. Does it run on
regular unleaded gasoline?
Unfortunately, no. It requires something
with a little more kick. Plutonium.
Uh, plutonium.
Wait a minute. Are you...
Are you tellin' me
that this sucker is nuclear?
Hey, hey, hey.
Keep rolling there.
No, this sucker's electrical, but I need
a nuclear reaction to generate...
the 1.21 gigawatts
of electricity I need.
You don't just walk into a store
and buy plutonium.
Did you rip that off?
Of course. From a group
of Libyan nationalists.
They wanted me
to build them a bomb.
So I took their plutonium and
gave them a bomb casing full of
used pinball machine parts.
- Come on!
Let's get you a radiation suit.
- Jesus!
It's safe now.
Everything's lead-lined.
Don't you lose
those tapes now.
I need that as a record.
Let's put this back here.
There we go.
Whoop! Almost forgot
my luggage.
Who knows if they've got
cotton underwear in the future.
- I'm allergic to all synthetics.
- The future.
- That's where you're goin'.
- That's right.
Twenty-five years
into the future.
I've always dreamed of seeing
the future, looking beyond my years...
seeing the progress
of mankind.
- Why not?
- I'll also be able to see who wins...
the next 25 World Series.
- Uh, Doc. Uh, look me up
when you get there.
- Huh?
Indeed I will.
Roll 'em.
Ahem!
I, Dr. Emmett Brown...
am about to embark
on an historic journey.
What am I thinking of?
I almost forgot to bring
extra plutonium.
How do I expect to get back?
One pellet, one trip.
I must be out of my mind.
What is it, Einie?
Oh, my God. They found me.
I don't know how, but they found me.
- Run for it, Marty!
- Who? Who?
Who do you think?
The Libyans!
Holy shit!
I'll draw their fire!
Doc, wait!
No!
You bastard!
Go!
Come on! Move!
Damn it!
Jesus!
Holy shit!
Let's see if you bastards
can do 90.
Lord, what is it? What is it, Pa?
Looks like an airplane...
without wings.
That ain't no airplane.
Look.
- Don't look!
- Listen... Whoa!
Hello?
Uh, excuse me.
Sorry about your barn.
It's already mutated
into human form! Shoot it!
Take that,
you mutated son of a bitch!
- It's getting away!
- Hold it!
Shoot it, Pa!
My pine! Why, you...
You space bastard! You killed my pine!
Okay, McFly. Get a grip on yourself.
It's all a dream.
Just a very intense dream.
Whoa! Listen,
you gotta help me.
Don't stop, Wilbur! Drive!
Can't be.
This is nuts.
Oh, come on.
Perfect.
# Mr. Sandman #
# Bring me a dream #
# Make her complexion
like peaches and cream #
- # Give her two lips
like roses in clover#
# And tell me that
my lonesome nights are over#
# Sandman #
# I'm so alone #
# Don't have nobody
to call my own #
# Please turn on
your magic beam #
# Mr. Sandman
bring me a dream #
# Make her the cutest
that I've ever seen ##
Remember, fellow citizens,
the future is in your hands.
If you believe in progress,
reelect Mayor Red Thomas.
Progress is his middle name.
Mayor Red Thomas's
progress platform...
means more jobs,
better education...
bigger civic improvements
and lower taxes.
On election day,
cast your vote for a proven leader.
Reelect Mayor Red Thomas.
This has gotta be a dream.
# Raised in the woods
so's he knew every tree #
# Kilt him a b'ar
when he was only three #
# Davy ##
Hey, kid.
What'd you do, jump ship?
- What?
- What's with the life preserver?
I just wanna
use the phone.
Yeah, it's in the back.
"Brown."
Great. You're alive.
Come on.
Do you know where
1640 Riverside...
Are you gonna order
somethin', kid?
Uh, yeah.
Gimme... Gimme a Tab.
Tab? I can't give you a tab
unless you order somethin'.
Right.
Give me a Pepsi Free.
If you want a Pepsi, pal,
you're gonna pay for it.
Just give me something
without any sugar in it, okay?
Somethin' without sugar.
Hey, McFly.
What do you
think you're doin'?
- Biff.
- I'm talkin' to you,
McFly, you Irish bug!
- Oh, hey, Biff. Hey, guys.
How are you doin'?
- You got my homework finished?
Well, actually, I figured since
it wasn't due till Monday...
Hello? Hello? Anybody home?
Hey, think, McFly.
Think. I gotta have time
to recopy it.
You realize what would happen if I
hand in my homework in your handwriting?
I'll get kicked
outta school.
You wouldn't want that
to happen, would ya?
- Would ya? No.
- Of course not.
I wouldn't want
that to happen.
What are you lookin' at,
butthead?
Get a load of this guy's life preserver.
Dork thinks he's gonna drown.
How 'bout my homework,
McFly?
Uh, okay, Biff.
Well, I'll, uh...
I'll finish that on up tonight...
and then I'll bring it over
first thing tomorrow morning.
Not too early. I sleep in Sundays.
Your shoe's untied!
Don't be so gullible, McFly.
- I don't wanna see you in here again.
- Okay. All right. Bye-bye.
- What?
- You're George McFly!
Yeah. Who are you?
What do you let those boys
push you around like that for?
- They're bigger than me.
- Stand tall, boy!
Have some respect
for yourself.
Don't you know if you
let people walk over you now...
they'll walk over you
for the rest of your life.
Look at me. You think I'm gonna
spend my life in this slop house?
- Watch it, Goldie.
- No, sir!
I'm gonna make somethin'of myself.
I'm goin'to night school.
- One day, I'm gonna be somebody.
- That's right. He's gonna be mayor.
Yeah, I'm...
Mayor! Now that's
a good idea!
I could run for mayor.
- A colored mayor. That'll be the day.
- Wait and see, Mr. Carruthers.
I will be mayor. I'll be the most
powerful man in Hill Valley...
and I'm gonna
clean up this town.
Good. You can start
by sweeping the floor.
Mayor Goldie Wilson.
I like the sound of that.
Hey, Dad! George!
Hey, you on the bike!
He's a Peeping Tom!
Dad!
Hey, wait... Wait a minute.
Who are you?
Stella! Another one of these damn kids
jumped in front of my car!
Come out here!
Help me take him in the house!
Mom?
That you?
There, there, now.
Just relax.
You've been asleep
for almost nine hours now.
I had a...
horrible nightmare.
I dreamed that
I went back in time.
It was terrible.
Well, you're safe
and sound now...
back in good old 1955.
1955?
You're my mo...
My name is Lorraine.
- Lorraine Baines?
- Yeah.
But you're, uh...
You're so, uh...
You're so...
thin!
Just relax, Calvin.
You got a big bruise on your head.
Ah! Where are my pants?
Over there...
on my hope chest.
I've never seen
purple underwear before, Calvin.
Calvin? Why... Why do you
keep calling me Calvin?
That is your name, isn't it?
Calvin Klein.
It's written all over your underwear.
I guess they
call you Cal, huh?
No, actually, people...
call me Marty.
Oh.
Pleased to meet you,
Calvin...
Marty...
Klein.
- Do you mind if I sit here?
- No.
Fine. No. Good.
Fine. Good.
- That's a big bruise you have there.
- Ahh!
Lorraine, are you up there?
Oh, my God!
It's my mother!
Quick!
Put your pants back on!
Tell me, Marty,
how long have you been in port?
- Excuse me?
- I guessed you're a sailor.
That's why you wear
that life preserver.
Uh, Coast Guard.
Sam, here's the young man you hit with
your car. He's all right. Thank God.
What were you doin'
in the middle of the street?
Don't pay attention to him.
He's in one of his moods.
Quit fiddling with that thing.
Come in here to dinner.
You already know Lorraine.
This is Milton,
this is Sally...
that's Toby, and over there in
the playpen is little baby Joey.
So you're my Uncle Joey.
Better get used to these bars, kid.
Yes. Joey just loves
being in his playpen.
He cries whenever we take him out,
so we leave him in there all the time.
Well, Marty,
I hope you like meat loaf.
Well, listen,
I really oughta...
Sit here, Marty.
Sam, stop fiddling with that thing
and come in here and eat your dinner.
Oh, ho, ho! Look at it roll.
Now we can watch
Jackie Gleason while we eat.
Bang! Zoom!
Our first television set.
Dad just picked it up today.
Do you have a television?
Well, yeah, ya know,
we have... two of'em.
Wow! You must be rich.
Oh, honey, he's teasing you.
Nobody has two television sets.
Hey... Hey, I've seen this one.
This is a classic.
This is where Ralph dresses up
as a man from space.
What do you mean you've seen this?
It's brand new.
Yeah, well,
I saw it on a... rerun.
- What's a rerun?
- You'll find out.
You know, Marty,
you look so familiar to me.
Do I know your mother?
Yeah, I think maybe you do.
Then I wanna give her a call.
I don't want her to worry about you.
You can't. Uh...
That is, uh, nobody,
uh, nobody's home.
- Oh.
- Yet.
Oh.
Uh, listen. Do you know
where Riverside Drive is?
It's on the other end of town.
A block past Maple.
East end of town.
That's John F. Kennedy Drive.
Who the hell
is John F. Kennedy?
Mother?
With Marty's parents
out of town...
don't you think
he oughta spend the night?
After all, Dad almost
killed him with the car.
That's true, Marty.
I think you should spend the night.
I think you're our responsibility.
- Well, gee, I don't know.
- And he can sleep in my room.
I gotta go! I gotta go.
Thanks very much.
It was wonderful. You were all great.
See you all later.
Much later.
He's a very strange
young man.
He's an idiot.
Comes from upbringing.
His parents are probably idiots too.
Lorraine, you ever have a kid
who acts that way, I'll disown you.
Doc?
- Don't say a word.
- Doc!
I don't wanna know
anything about you.
- Listen, Doc... Doc...
- Quiet!
- Don't tell me anything. Quiet.
- You gotta help...
I'm gonna read your thoughts.
Let's see now.
You come here
from a great distance?
- Yeah. Exactly.
- Don't tell me!
You want me to buy a subscription
to The Saturday Evening Post?
- No!
- Not a word! Not a word now!
Quiet.
Uh... donations.
You want me
to make a donation...
to the Coast Guard
Youth Auxiliary.
Doc...
I'm from the future.
I came here in a time machine
that you invented.
Now, I need your help
to get back to the year...
1985.
By God!
Do you know
what this means?
It means that this damn thing
doesn't work at all!
Doc, you gotta help me.
You are the only one who knows
how your time machine works.
Time machine?
I haven't invented
any time machine.
Okay. All right.
I'll prove it to you.
Look at my driver's license.
Expires 1987.
Look at my birthday.
I haven't even been born yet.
And look at this picture.
It's my brother,
my sister and me.
Look at her sweatshirt, Doc.
"Class of 1984"?
Pretty mediocre photographic fakery.
They cut off your brother's hair.
I'm tellin' the truth.
You gotta believe me.
Then tell me, "future boy,"
who's president
of the United States in 1985?
- Ronald Reagan.
- Ronald Reagan? The actor? Ha!
Then who's vice president?
Jerry Lewis?
I suppose Jane Wyman
is the First Lady.
- Wait, Doc!
- And Jack Benny
is secretary of the treasury!
- Doc, you gotta listen to me!
- I've had enough practical
jokes for one evening.
- Good night, future boy!
- No, wait, Doc. Doc!
Th-The bruise on your head.
I know how that happened.
You told me the whole story.
You were standing on
your toilet hanging a clock...
and you fell and hit your head
on the sink...
and that's when you came up
with the idea for the flux capacitor...
which is what makes
time travel possible.
There's something wrong with
the starter, so I hid it... here.
After I fell
off my toilet...
I drew this.
The flux capacitor.
It works!
I finally invent something
that works!
You bet your ass
it works.
Somehow we've gotta sneak this
back to my laboratory.
We've gotta get you home!
Here, Doc.
This is it.
Never mind that.
Never mind that now.
Why, that's me!
Look at me!
- I'm an old man!
- I'm Dr. Emmett Brown.
I'm in the parking lot
of Twin Pines Mall.
Thank God,
I've still got my hair.
What's this thing
I'm wearing?
This is a radiation suit.
Radiation suit?
Of course. Because of all
the fallout from the atomic wars.
This... is truly amazing.
A portable television studio.
No wonder your president
has to be an actor.
He's got to look good on television.
Whoa. This is the part
comin' up, Doc.
No, no, no, no.
This sucker's electrical...
but I need a nuclear reaction
to generate the 1.21 gigawatts...
What did I just say?
...this sucker's electrical,
but I need a nuclear reaction...
to generate the 1.21 gigawatts
of electricity...
1.21 gigawatts!
1.21 gigawatts.
Great Scott!
What...
What the hell
is a gigawatt?
How could I have been
so careless?
1.21 gigawatts!
Tom, how am I gonna generate that kind
of power? It can't be done, can it?
Doc, look. All we need
is a little plutonium.
Oh! I'm sure
that in 1985...
plutonium is available
in every corner drugstore...
but in 1955,
it's a little hard to come by.
Marty, I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid you're stuck here.
Whoa, Doc, stuck here?
I can't be stuck here.
I got a life in 1985.
- I got a girl.
- Is she pretty?
Doc, she's beautiful.
She...
She's crazy about me.
Look at this.
Look what she
wrote here, Doc.
I mean,
that says it all.
Doc, you're my only hope.
Marty, I'm sorry, but the only
power source capable of generating...
1.21 gigawatts of electricity
is a bolt of lightning.
- What did you say?
- A bolt of lightning.
Unfortunately, you never know when
or where it's ever gonna strike.
We do now.
This is it!
This is the answer.
It says here
that a bolt of lightning...
is gonna strike the clock tower
at 10:04 p.m. Next Saturday night!
If we could somehow harness
this lightning...
channel it into
the flux capacitor...
it just might work.
Next Saturday night...
we're sending you
back to the future!
All right. Saturday's good.
Saturday's good.
I can spend a week in 1955.
I can hang out. You can show me around.
That is completely out of the question.
You must not leave this house.
You must not see anybody
or talk to anybody.
Anything you do can have serious
repercussions on future events.
Do you understand?
Yeah. Sure. Okay.
Have you interacted with
anybody else today besides me?
I'm... Yeah, well, I might've
sort of bumped into my parents.
Great Scott!
Let me see that photograph again
of your brother.
Just as I thought. This proves
my theory. Look at your brother.
His head's gone.
It's like it's been erased.
Erased from existence.
Whoa! They really cleaned this place up.
Looks brand new.
Remember, according to
my theory, you interfered with
your parents' first meeting.
If they don't meet, they won't
fall in love, get married and have kids.
That's why your older brother's
disappearing from that photograph.
Your sister will follow, and unless
you repair the damage, you'll be next.
- Sounds pretty heavy.
- Weight has nothing to do with it.
Which one's your pop?
That's him.
Okay. Okay, you guys.
Ha, ha, ha, ha. Very funny.
You guys are being real mature.
Maybe you were adopted.
Okay, real mature, guys.
- Okay, pick up my books.
- McFly.
That's Strickland.
Jesus, didn't that guy ever have hair?
Shape up, man.
You're a slacker.
- Do you wanna be a slacker
for the rest of your life?
- No.
- What did your mother
ever see in that kid?
- I don't know.
I guess she felt sorry for him
'cause her dad hit him with the car.
He hit me
with the car.
That's the
"Florence Nightingale effect."
It happens in hospitals when nurses
fall in love with their patients.
Go to it, kid.
Hey, George, buddy.
I have been lookin'
all over for you.
You remember me, the guy who
saved your life the other day?
Oh. Yeah.
Good. There's somebody
I'd like you to meet.
Lorraine?
Calvin!
I'd like you to meet
my good friend George McFly.
Hi. It's really
a pleasure to meet you.
- How's your head?
- Uh, good. Fine.
I've been so worried about you
ever since you ran off the other night.
A-Are you okay?
- Come on. We're tardy! Come on!
- Sorry. I have to go.
Isn't he a dreamboat?
- She didn't even look at him.
- This is more serious than I thought.
Apparently, your mother
is amorously infatuated with you...
instead of your father.
Whoa. Wait a minute, Doc.
Are you trying to tell me...
that my mother...
has got the hots for me?
- Precisely.
- Whoa. This is heavy.
Heavy.
Why are things so heavy in the future?
- Is there a problem with
the Earth's gravitational pull?
- What?
The only way we're gonna get those two
to mate is if they are alone together.
So you've gotta get your father
and mother to interact...
in some sort of social...
What, you mean like a date?
- Right!
- What kind of date?
What do kids do in the '50s?
They're your parents.
You must know them.
What are their common interests?
What do they like to do together?
Well, nothing.
Look! There's a rhythmic
ceremonial ritual coming up.
Of course!
The Enchantment Under The Sea dance!
They're supposed to go to this. That's
where they kiss for the first time.
All right, kid. You stick
to your father like glue...
and make sure he takes her
to that dance.
George, buddy.
Remember that girl
I introduced you to? Lorraine?
What are you writing?
Uh, stories.
Science fiction stories
about visitors...
coming down to Earth
from other planets.
Get outta town! I didn't know
you did anything creative.
- Let me read some.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
I never... I never let
anybody read my stories.
Why not?
Well, what if they
didn't like them?
What if they told me
I was no good?
I guess that would be pretty hard
for somebody to understand.
Uh, no.
No, not hard at all.
So anyway, George,
about Lorraine...
she really likes you.
She told me to tell you
that she wants you to ask her...
- to the Enchantment Under The Sea dance.
- Really?
Oh, yeah. All you gotta do
is go over there and ask her.
What, right here, right now in
the cafeteria? What if she said no?
I don't know if I could take
that kind of a rejection.
Besides, I think she'd
rather go with somebody else.
Uh, who?
Biff.
- Little kiss. Come on.
- Come on. Leave.
You want it. You know you want it.
You know you want me
to give it to you.
- Shut your filthy mouth.
I'm not that kind of girl.
- Ooh.
Maybe you are and you
just don't know it yet.
Get your meat hooks off of me.
You heard her.
She said get your meat hooks...
off.
Uh, please.
So what's it to you,
butthead?
You know, you been
lookin' for a...
Fight, fight, fight.
Since you're new here, uh,
I'm gonna cut you a break...
today.
So why don't you
make like a tree...
and get outta here.
George!
Why do you keep
following me around?
Look, George.
I'm telling you, George...
if you do not ask Lorraine
to that dance...
- I'm gonna regret it
for the rest of my life.
- But I can't go to the dance.
I'll miss my favorite television
program, Science Fiction Theater.
Yeah, but, George,
Lorraine wants to go with you.
- Give her a break.
- Look, I'm just not ready...
to ask Lorraine
out to the dance.
And not you or anybody else
on this planet...
is gonna make me
change my mind.
Science Fiction Theater.
Who are you?
Silence, Earthling.
My name is Darth Vader.
I am an extraterrestrial
from the planet Vulcan.
Marty!
- Marty! Marty!
- Hey, George, buddy.
You weren't at school.
What have you been doing all day?
I overslept.
Look, I need your help.
I have to ask Lorraine out,
but I don't know how to do it.
All right, listen. Keep your pants on.
She's over in the cafe.
God! How do you...
What made you change
your mind, George?
Last night, Darth Vader
came down from planet Vulcan...
and told me that if I didn't take
Lorraine out, that he'd melt my brain.
Yeah, well, let's just keep this
brain-melting stuff to ourselves, okay?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- All right, okay. There she is, George.
- Now just go in there and invite her.
- Okay.
- But I don't know what to say.
- Just say anything, George.
Say whatever's natural, the first thing
that comes into your mind.
Nothing's coming to my mind.
Jesus, George.
It's a wonder I was even born.
- What? What?
- Nothing, nothing. Nothing.
Look. Tell her destiny
brought you together.
Tell her that she is
the most beautiful girl...
you have ever seen
in the world.
Girls like that stuff.
What are you doing, George?
I'm writing this down.
This is good stuff.
- Yeah. Okay, let's go.
Can you take care of that?
- Oh, right.
Lou, give me a milk.
Chocolate.
And a cherry Coke.
Lorraine? My density...
has popped me to you.
- What?
- Oh.
What I meant to say was...
Wait a minute.
Don't I know you from somewhere?
Yes. Yes.
I'm George.
George McFly.
I'm your density.
I mean...
Your destiny.
Oh.
Hey, McFly!
Oh, gee...
I thought I told you
never to come in here.
Well, it's gonna cost you.
How much money you got on you?
Well, how much
do you want, Biff?
All right, punk.
- Now I'm gonna...
- Whoa, whoa, Biff. What's that?
That's Calvin Klein.
Oh, my God, he's a dream.
Whoa! Kid! Kid, stop!
Stop, stop. Stop!
- Stop.
- Hey!
I'll get it back to you,
all right?
You broke it!
Come back here!
Wow! Look at him go!
Get him!
To the car! Go!
- What's that thing he's on?
- It's a board with wheels.
He's an absolute dream.
- Come on, come on!
- Look out for the car!
I'm gonna ram him.
Shit!
Whoo!
Thanks a lot, kid.
I'm gonna get
that son of a bitch.
- Where does he come from?
- Yeah, where does he live?
I don't know...
but I'm gonna find out.
Oh, my God. They found me.
I don't know how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Oh, my God.
They found me.
I don't know how, but they found me.
Run for it, Marty!
Doc?
Oh, hi, Marty.
I didn't hear you come in.
Fascinating device,
this video unit.
Listen, Doc.
There's something I haven't told you
about the night we made that tape.
Please, Marty, don't tell me.
No man should know too much
about his own destiny.
- You don't understand.
- I do understand.
If I know too much about my future,
I could endanger my existence...
just as you have
endangered yours.
You... You're right.
Now, let me show you my plan
for sending you home.
Please excuse the crudity
of this model.
I didn't have time to
build it to scale or to paint it.
- It's good.
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Okay, now, we run some
industrial-strength electrical cable...
from the top
of the clock tower, down...
suspending it over the street
between these two lampposts.
Meanwhile, we've outfitted
the time vehicle...
with this big pole
and hook...
which runs directly
into the flux capacitor.
At the calculated moment...
you start off
from down the street...
driving directly toward the cable,
accelerating to 88 miles per hour.
According to the flyer,
at precisely 10:04 p. M...
this Saturday night, lightning
will strike the clock tower...
electrifying the cable...
just as the connecting hook
makes contact...
thereby sending 1.21 gigawatts
into the flux capacitor...
and sending you back to 1985.
All right, now.
Watch this.
You wind up the car
and release it.
I'll simulate the lightning.
Ready.
Set.
Release.
You're instilling me
with a lot of confidence, Doc.
Don't worry. I'll take care of ideas.
You take care of your pop.
By the way, what happened today?
Did he ask her out?
- I think so.
- What did she say?
It's your mom!
She's tracked you down!
Quick! Let's cover
the time machine.
Hi, Mar... Cal... Marty.
Mom... Lorraine.
Uh, how did you know
I was here?
I followed you.
Oh, uh, this is my,
uh, Doc... My uncle...
Doc... Brown.
- Hi.
Uh...
Marty, this may seem
a little forward...
but I was kind of
wondering if...
I-if you'd ask me to the...
Enchantment Under The Sea dance
on Saturday?
Uh, you mean...
You mean nobody's asked you?
No.
Not yet.
- What about... What about George?
- George McFly?
Oh, he... He's kind of cute and all,
but, uh, not...
Well...
I think a man
should be strong...
so he can
stand up for himself...
and protect
the woman he loves.
Don't you?
Yeah.
I still don't understand.
How am I supposed to go
to the dance with her...
if she's already going
to the dance with you?
Well, because, George,
she wants to go with you.
She just doesn't
know it yet.
That's why we gotta show her that you,
George McFly, are a fighter.
You're somebody who's gonna
stand up for yourself...
somebody who's
gonna protect her.
Yeah, but I've never
picked a fight in my entire life.
Look, you're not gonna be
picking a fight, Dad...
dad-dad-daddio.
You're coming
to her rescue, right?
Okay, let's go over the plan again.
8:55, where you gonna be?
- I'm gonna be at the dance.
- Right. And where am I gonna be?
You're gonna be
in the car with her.
Right, so around 9:00,
she's gonna get very angry with me.
Why is she gonna
get angry with you?
Well, because, George,
nice girls get angry...
when guys
take advantage of them.
Oh! You mean you're gonna
go touch her on her...
No. No, George, look.
It's just an act, right?
Okay. So, 9:00, you're strolling
through the parking lot.
You see us, uh,
struggling in the car.
You walk up, you open
the door and you say...
Your line, George.
Oh! Uh...
Hey, you, get your
damn hands off her!
- You really think I oughta swear?
- Yes, definitely.
Goddamn it, George, swear.
Okay. So now you come up.
You punch me in the stomach.
I'm out for the count,
right?
And you and Lorraine
live happily ever after.
Oh, you make it sound
so easy.
I just...
I wish I wasn't so scared.
George, there's nothing
to be scared of.
All it takes is a little
self-confidence.
You know, if you
put your mind to it...
you can accomplish anything.
Hill Valley
area weather this Saturday night.
Mostly clear,
with some scattered clouds.
Lows tonight
in the upper 40s...
Are you sure
about this storm?
Since when can weathermen predict
the weather, let alone the future?
You know, Marty, I'm gonna
be very sad to see you go.
You've really made
a difference in my life.
You've given me
something to shoot for.
Just knowing that I'm gonna
be around to see 1985...
that I'm gonna succeed
in this...
that I'm gonna have a chance
to travel through time!
It's gonna be really hard waiting
30 years before I can talk to you...
about everything that's happened
in the past few days.
I'm really gonna
miss you, Marty.
I'm really gonna miss you.
- Doc, about the future...
- No!
Marty, we've already agreed that
having information about the future...
can be extremely dangerous.
Even if your intentions are good,
it can backfire drastically.
Whatever you've got
to tell me...
I'll find out through
the natural course of time.
"Dear Dr. Brown...
on the night that
I go back in time...
you will be...
shot by terrorists.
Please take whatever
precautions are necessary...
to prevent
this terrible disaster.
Your friend...
Marty."
Evening, Dr. Brown.
What's with the wire?
Oh, just a little
weather experiment.
- Whatcha got under here?
- No, no! Don't touch that!
Some new, specialized
weather-sensing equipment.
You, uh, got a permit for that?
Of course I do.
Just a second. Let me see if
I can find it here.
Do you mind if we...
park... for a while?
- That's a great idea. I'd love to park.
- Huh?
Marty, I'm almost
18 years old.
It's not like I've never
parked before.
What?
Marty, you seem so nervous.
Is something wrong?
No.
Lorraine, Lorraine,
what are you doin'?
I swiped it from
the old lady's liquor cabinet.
Yeah, well,
you shouldn't drink.
- Why not?
- Because you...
You might regret it
later in life.
Marty, don't be such a square.
Everybody who's anybody drinks.
Geez, you smoke too?
Marty, you're beginning
to sound just like my mother.
We're gonna take a little break,
but we'll be back in a while...
so, uh, don't nobody go nowhere.
Marty?
Why are you so nervous?
Lorraine...
have you ever...
uh, been in a situation where you
knew you had to act a certain way...
but when you got there, you didn't
know if you could go through with it?
Oh, you mean like how you're
supposed to act on a first date?
Oh, uh, sort of.
- I... I think I know
exactly what you mean.
- Y-You do?
You know what I do
in those situations?
- What?
- I don't worry.
This is all wrong.
I don't... I don't know
what it is...
but when I kiss you,
it's like I'm kissing...
my brother.
I guess that doesn't make
any sense, does it?
Believe me.
It makes perfect sense.
Somebody's coming.
You caused 300 bucks' damage to my car,
you son of a bitch...
and I'm gonna take it
outta your ass.
Hold him.
Let him go, Biff.
You're drunk.
Well, lookee
what we have here.
No, no! Stay right here with me.
Come on, Lorraine.
- Let me go!
- Leave her alone, you bastard!
You guys, take him in back.
I'll be right there.
Just admit that you want it.
Come on. Well, go on.
This ain't no peep show.
- Hey, let's put him in there.
- Yeah!
That's for messing up my hair.
What the hell
are you doing to my car?
Hey, beat it, spook.
This don't concern you.
Who you callin' "spook,"
peckerwood?
Hey, hey, listen, guys.
Look, I don't wanna mess
with no reefer addicts, okay?
Get home to your mama, boy.
Biff! Biff! Hurry, Biff!
Let me outta here!
Yo!
Reginald, where are your keys?
The keys are in the trunk.
- Say that again?
- I said the keys are in here.
Let me go!
Come on!
Hey, you,
get your damn hands off...
Oh.
I think you got
the wrong car, McFly.
George, help me! Please!
Just turn around, McFly,
and walk away.
- Please, George.
- Are you deaf, McFly?
Close the door and beat it.
No, Biff.
You leave her alone.
All right, McFly.
You're asking for it...
and now you're gonna get it.
Stop it!
Biff, you'll break his arm!
Biff, no!
Gimme a hand here, Reginald.
Ow! Damn it, man!
I sliced my hand!
- Whose are these?
- Mine.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
You're gonna break his arm!
Biff! Biff, leave him alone!
Let him go! Let him go!
Are you okay?
Who is that guy?
That's George McFly.
- That's George McFly?
- Excuse me.
The storm.
Hey, guys, you gotta get back
in there and finish the dance.
Hey, man,
look at Marvin's hand.
He can't play with this hand like that,
and we can't play without him.
Yeah, well, look, Marvin,
you gotta play.
See, that's where they kiss for
the first time on the dance floor...
and if there's no music,
they can't dance.
And if they can't dance,
they can't kiss.
If they can't kiss, they can't
fall in love, and I'm history.
The dance is over, unless you know
somebody else that can play the guitar.
This is for
all you lovers out there.
# Earth Angel
Earth Angel #
# Will you be mine #
# My darling dear
Love you...#
George, aren't you
gonna kiss me?
I... I don't know.
Scram, McFly.
I'm cuttin' in.
# Earth Angel
Earth Angel #
# The one I adore #
Hey, boy,
you all right?
I can't play.
George!
George?
Excuse me.
# The vision of your happiness
Whoa-oh-oh-oh #
# Earth Angel
Earth Angel #
# Please be mine #
# My darling dear#
# Love you for all time #
# I'm just a fool #
# A fool in love #
# With you # #
Yeah. Yeah, man, that was good.
Let's do another one.
Oh, no. I gotta go.
Come on, man. Let's do
something that really cooks.
Something that... that cooks.
- All right.
- All right!
All right...
All right, this is, uh,
this is an oldie but, uh...
Well, it... it's an oldie
where I come from.
All right, guys, listen.
This is a blues riff in "B."
Watch me for the changes,
and try and keep up, okay?
# Way down in Louisiana
down in New Orleans #
# Way back up in the woods
among the evergreens #
# There stood a log cabin
made of earth and wood #
# Where lived a country boy
name of Johnny B. Goode #
# He never ever learned
to read or write so well #
# He could play the guitar
just like he's ringin' a bell #
# Go, go
Go, Johnny, go, go #
# Go, Johnny
Go, go, go #
# Go, Johnny, go, go #
George, I heard you laid out Biff.
Nice goin'.
George, you ever think of
running for class president?
# Johnny B. Goode #
# Go, Johnny, go, go #
# Go, Johnny, go, go, go #
# Johnny B. Goode # #
Chuck! Chuck, it's Marvin.
Your cousin, Marvin Berry?
You know that new sound
you lookin' for?
Well, listen to this!
I guess you guys aren't
ready for that yet.
But your kids
are gonna love it.
Lorraine.
Marty, that was
very interesting music.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, I hope you don't mind, but George
asked if he could take me home.
Great! Good.
Good, Lorraine.
I had a feeling
about you two.
I have a feeling too.
Listen, I gotta go,
but, uh...
I wanted to tell you
that it's been...
educational.
Marty, will we ever
see you again?
I guarantee it.
Well, Marty, I want to thank you
for all your good advice.
I'll never forget it.
Right, George.
Well, uh...
good luck, you guys.
Oh. One other thing.
If you guys
ever have kids...
and one of them,
when he's eight years old...
accidentally sets fire
to the living-room rug...
go easy on him.
Okay.
"Marty."
Such a nice name.
Damn! Where is that kid?
Damn!
Damn! Damn!
You're late!
Do you have no concept of time?
Hey, come on!
I had to change.
Do you think I'm going back
in that... that zoot suit?
The old man really came through.
It worked.
He laid out Biff in one punch.
I didn't know he had it in him.
He's never stood up
to Biff in his life.
- Never?
- No. Why? What's the matter?
All right!
Let's set your destination time.
This is the exact time you left.
Let's send you back
at exactly the same time.
It'll be like you never left.
Now, I painted a white line
on the street...
way over there.
That's where
you'll start from.
I've calculated
the precise distance...
taking into account the acceleration
speed and wind resistance...
retroactive from the moment
the lightning strikes...
which will be in exactly
7 minutes and 22 seconds.
When this alarm goes off,
you hit the gas.
Right.
Well, I guess
that's everything.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
See you in about 30 years.
I hope so.
Don't worry!
As long as you
hit that wire...
with the connecting hook
at precisely 88 miles an hour...
the instant the lightning
strikes the tower...
everything will be fine.
All right.
- What's the meaning of this?
- You'll find out in 30 years.
It's about the future,
isn't it?
- It's information about the future!
- Wait a minute!
I warned you
about this, kid.
The consequences
could be disastrous!
Doc, that's a risk
you're gonna have to take.
- Your life depends on it!
- No!
I refuse to accept
the responsibility.
- In that case,
I'll tell you straight out!
Great Scott!
You get the cable!
I'll throw the rope down to you!
Right! I got it!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Doc!
- Come on, come on. Let's go!
- All right! Take it up!
Go!
- Doc!
- Huh?
I have to tell you
about the future!
- What?
- I have to tell you about the future!
What?
On the night I go
back in time, you get...
Oh!
Doc!
Go!
- No, Doc!
- Look at the time!
You've got less than
four minutes.
Please, hurry!
Yeah!
Damn it, Doc! Why did you
have to tear up that letter?
If I only had more time.
Wait a minute.
I got all the time I want.
I got a time machine.
I can just go back early and warn him.
Okay. Ten minutes
ought to do it.
- Okay. Time circuit's on.
- Fluxing.
Engine running.
All right.
No. No, no, no, no.
Come on. Come on.
Not this time.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Here we go. Here we go.
This time. Come on.
Please. Please.
Come on!
Doc.
Yeah! Ha-ha!
# We searched
all through the night # #
Crazy drunk driver.
Whoo!
All right. Oh, Red.
You look great.
Everything looks great.
1:24.
I still got time.
I'm comin', Doc!
No! No, not again!
Come on! Come on!
Hey!
Libyans.
No! You bastard!
Go!
Doc! Doc!
Oh, no!
You're alive.
Bulletproof vest?
How did you know?
L- I never got a chance
to tell you.
What about all that talk
about screwing up future events?
The space-time continuum?
Well, I figured,
what the hell.
So how far ahead
are you going?
About 30 years.
It's a nice round number.
Look me up when you get there,
all right?
Guess I'll be about 47.
I will.
- Take care.
- You too.
Right. Bye-bye, Einie.
Oh, and watch that reentry.
- It's a little bumpy.
- You bet.
# Take me away #
# I don't mind #
# Just better promise me
I'll be back in time #
# Gotta get back in time #
# Get me back in time # #
What a nightmare.
If Paul calls me, tell him I'm
working at the boutique late tonight.
Linda, first of all,
I'm not your answering service.
Second of all,
somebody named Greg or Craig
called you just a little while ago.
- Which one was it, Greg or Craig?
- I don't know.
- I can't keep up
with all of your boyfriends.
- Hey.
- What the hell is this?
- Breakfast.
What, did you sleep
in your clothes again?
Yeah. L...
Yeah. What are...
What are you wearing, Dave?
Marty, I always wear
a suit to the office.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I think we need a rematch, George.
- A rematch? Why? Were you cheating?
- No.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
Mom! Dad!
- Wh... Did you hit your head?
- Marty, are you all right?
You guys... You guys look great.
Mom, you look so thin.
Why, thank you, Marty.
George!
Good morning, sleepyhead.
- Good morning, Dave. Linda.
- Good morning, Mom.
Marty, I almost forgot.
Jennifer Parker called.
I sure like her, Marty.
She is such a sweet girl.
Isn't tonight
the night of the big date?
What? What, Ma?
Aren't you going up to the lake?
You've been planning it for two weeks.
Mom, we talked about this.
How can I go to the lake?
The car's wrecked.
- Wrecked?
- What happened?
- When did this happen?
- I'm sure the car is fine.
- Why am I always the last one
to know about these things?
See? There's Biff out there
waxing it right now.
Biff, I want to make sure we get two
coats of wax this time, not just one.
I'm just finishing up
the second coat now.
Now, Biff, don't con me.
I'm... I'm sorry,
Mr. McFly.
I meant I was just starting
on the second coat.
Ah, Biff.
What a character.
Always trying to get away
with something.
I've had to stay on top of Biff
ever since high school.
Although,
if it wasn't for him...
- We never would have fallen in love.
- That's right.
Mr. McFly! Mr. McFly,
this just arrived.
Oh, hi, Marty.
I think it's your new book.
Oh, honey!
Your first novel.
Like I've always told you,
you put your mind to it...
- you can accomplish anything.
- Oh, Marty, here's your keys.
You're all waxed up,
ready for tonight.
Keys?
How about a ride, mister?
Jennifer! Oh, are you
a sight for sore eyes.
Let me look at you.
Marty, you're acting like
you haven't seen me in a week.
I haven't.
You okay?
Is everything all right?
Oh, yeah.
Everything is great.
Marty! You've gotta
come back with me!
- Where?
- Back to the future.
Wait a minute.
What are you doin', Doc?
I need fuel.
Go ahead. Quick!
Get in the car.
No, no. I just got here,
okay? Jennifer's here.
We're gonna take the new truck
for a spin.
Well, bring her along.
This concerns her too.
What are you talking about?
What happens to us in the future?
- Do we become assholes or something?
- No, no, no, no, Marty.
Both you and Jennifer turn out fine.
It's your kids, Marty.
Something has gotta be done
about your kids.
Hey, Doc, we better back up. We don't
have enough road to get up to 88.
Roads? Where we're going,
we don't need roads.
# Tell me, Doctor#
# Where are we goin'this time #
# Is this the '50s #
# Or 1999 #
# All I wanted to do #
# Was play my guitar and sing #
# So take me away #
# I don't mind #
# But you better promise me
I'll be back in time #
# I gotta get back in time #
# Don't bet your future #
# On one roll of the dice #
# And better remember#
# Lightning never strikes twice #
# Please don't drive 88 #
# Don't wanna be late again #
# So take me away #
# I don't mind #
# But you better promise me
I'll be back in time #
# Gotta get back in time #
# Get back, get back ##
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/364vc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles