Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Keep that horn going.
Ten fathoms by the mark, sir.
Hoist your pilot signal lights.
Haul down your jibs.
By the deep eight and a sandy bottom, sir.
- Stand by the anchor.
- Aye, sir. Standing by.
Right ahead, sir.
- I see it. Right over there.
- We're here, boys!
Ahoy!
Be quiet down there.
- Who are you?
- The Flying Cloud.
220 days out of New York...
...and 15 days trying to find
your blasted harbor.
Nobody asked you to come.
You got anything
in this hog-end of the world except fog?
Sure! We've got gold, mountains of gold!
What are our chances?
You're just in time. We're all humpbacked
carrying nuggets around.
- Where are you going, Jerry?
- To the promised land!
Man overboard!
Pilot boat, ahoy!
Man overboard! Please pick him up!
There they are at last, Miss Rutledge.
The will-o'-the-wisp lights of fortune.
San Francisco,
the latest newborn of a great republic.
I see a lot of fog and a few lights.
I like it when life's hidden.
It gives you a chance to imagine nice things.
Nicer than they are.
Listen to them.
Men like to yell, don't they?
They imagine they're millionaires already.
More than that.
They've all left lives behind they didn't like.
They all dream of being reborn
in the new land.
Do they? Or do they dream of gold?
No, Miss Rutledge.
Behind that fog lies
not only sand filled with gold...
...but a new empire for men of vision.
Men of vision! I love the fine names
men give each other...
...to hide their greed
and lust for adventure.
I am amazed at your idealism, Col. Cobb.
Newspaper men are either drunkards
or idealists, Miss Rutledge.
I'm afraid I'm both.
However soiled his hands...
...the journalist goes staggering
through life with the beacon raised.
Beg pardon, but there's not much time
to pay for your clearance papers.
Nobody will be allowed off ship
until they do.
- How much is it?
- $45.
Tell the purser I'll settle
before the ship leaves the port.
Sorry, but there'll be no going ashore
unless it's paid.
Here, young man, you get our luggage
and a boat to take us ashore.
Yes, sir, thank you.
Thank you, Colonel, I...
A paltry sum to unlock the golden gates of
that new empire that lies behind the fog.
Miss Rutledge, you'll pardon an old man
for interfering, but I'd like to help you.
San Francisco is no place
for so fair a flower as yourself.
Thank you for your offer of protection,
Col. Cobb...
...but I don't think I shall need it.
- Are you ready with the anchor?
- Aye, sir.
- Let her go!
- Aye, sir!
We're in, Colonel.
Boat's alongside, sir. This way.
Will you step aside please
and let the lady get in here?
Sufferin' snakes! A white woman!
How much to take us ashore?
- $50 apiece, in advance.
- $50? Why that's outrageous!
This is New Year's Eve, folks,
and them's New Year's Eve prices.
- I know, but...
- Colonel, it'll be paid when we get ashore.
Jumpin' Jehoshaphat! A white woman!
What is the matter, my man, tired?
Tired? Say, I could row from here to China
and back again without even puffin'.
- Then why the delay?
- It's after 10:00 p.m.
I don't get the significance of your remark.
After 10:00, the rates go up.
A blackmailer at the gates of El Dorado.
Why, it's preposterous.
Pay or get out.
And the proposition goes for you too, miss.
- We are hardly in a position to walk.
- Try swimming.
But I haven't that much money!
Over you go then, both of you.
Business is business.
- You wouldn't dare!
- I wouldn't dare?
You don't think they call me
"Old Atrocity" for nothin', do you?
If I was to tell you the atrocities
I've committed in my time...
...you'd keel over.
Another thing,
there's a price on my head in every state...
...except in the Californy,
and it ain't organized yet.
Upsy-daisy, over you go, no foolin'.
Wait. Does it mean anything to you
that I came here to marry Dan Morgan?
- Marry Dan Morgan?
- Yes.
The man that made the Homestead Gully strike?
Yes.
Moses in the mountain.
Here comes one.
- Who you got there?
- A new white woman.
You're lyin'!
No, I ain't. She's a New York white
woman. Whiter than a hen's egg.
Be careful with her.
Give her room boys,
she ain't gonna disappear.
- Welcome to San Francisco, miss.
- Thank you, sir.
Happy New Year
to the gentlemen of San Francisco.
On behalf of the assembled multitude,
allow me to wish you likewise.
That's right and many of them.
Thank you. Would someone
please help Col. Cobb up?
I'd swim with my hands tied if you ask it.
Up you come to San Francisco, partner.
Col. Marcus Aurelius Cobb is the name,
gentlemen.
That's fine. Anything we can do for you?
- If you're chilly, have my coat.
- Mine's newer.
- Are you hungry?
- You can have me roasted, boiled or fried.
- Find something better than monkey meat.
- Bella Donna serves the best steaks.
Thank you, gentlemen,
but I came here to meet Mr. Dan Morgan.
Does anyone know where he is?
She's Dan Morgan's fiancée.
You came all the way from New York
to marry Dan Morgan?
There seems to be some mystery, gentlemen.
Mr. Morgan wrote me
that if he couldn't meet me...
...somebody'd take me to the Homestead Gully.
I'd like to go there if it isn't too far.
Does anyone know where it is?
You see, miss, Homestead Gully
has been taken off the map.
Would you like a little drink, miss?
Could you tell me where
I could find Mr. Morgan?
Well...
Go on, Jed.
You've been doing all the talking.
I hate to be the first
to break the news, miss, but...
...Mr. Morgan has been
taken off the map likewise.
- He's dead?
- He's deader than a doornail.
- Shut up, you varmint.
- Here, drink this.
How did it happen?
You see, the red come up
13 times straight in a row...
...and the gold mine changed hands.
After which unfortunate incident,
Mr. Morgan sort of...
...had a misunderstanding.
I'm afraid he was a bad loser, miss.
San Francisco is no place for a bad loser...
...especially if you're not so quick
on the draw.
Which he wasn't.
I never seen a man take so long
to pull a gun.
- He got drilled right clean through...
- Shut up or I'II...
Then there's nothing, no...
Miss Rutledge.
Allow me to offer my heartfelt sympathy.
I don't know why I'm crying, Col. Cobb...
...but that's what men expect of women,
isn't it?
- That they should cry?
- You poor child.
It seems my first claim
hasn't panned out so well.
You don't fool me, my dear.
You're hurt. Can't I be of some assistance?
You don't understand, Col. Cobb.
I never loved Dan Morgan.
- But you were going to marry him.
- Yes.
He must have meant something to you.
He meant a million dollars.
Miss Rutledge, I'm shocked!
Why? Because, I'm not pretending
an emotion I don't feel?
You poor dear.
Let me take you back to the ship.
No.
I'm not running away.
I came here to get something
and I'm going to get it.
Yes, but San Francisco
is no place for a woman.
Why not? I'm not afraid.
I like the fog.
I like this new world.
I like the noise of something happening.
No, San Francisco is no place
for a bad loser, man or woman.
Dan Morgan was a bad loser.
I'm not. I'm staying.
I'm tired of dreaming, Col. Cobb.
I'm staying.
I'm staying and holding out
my hands for gold.
Bright yellow gold.
Gentlemen, who got Dan Morgan's money?
I'd forget about that money if I were you,
'cause you ain't ever going to get it back.
Who got the money?
It's in the hands of the worst fiend
in San Francisco.
- What's his name?
- His name's Louis Chamalis.
He owns the biggest gambling parlor
in California.
The Bella Donna,
the one we was telling you about.
- Gentlemen, I'm hungry.
- Of course you are.
I should like to have supper
at the Bella Donna.
Let's go down there.
- The streets ain't paved yet.
- I see.
Make way for a lady.
That's opium you smell, miss.
Opium and Chinamen
sure perfume up the street.
Make way for a lady.
Don't worry, miss, we'll soon be there.
Look out, here come some more Chinamen.
He's just having some fun, miss.
He's going to cut off their pigtails.
- Why?
- If you cut off a Chinaman's pigtail...
...he can't go to Heaven in their religion.
- That's the reason they're carrying on so.
- It's outrageous, gentlemen.
Surely you would not allow persecution
of this sort...
...to raise its ugly head in this new land.
Look out there, partner.
The Chinese are the oldest civilization
in the world.
We must not be intolerant.
We must respect their beliefs.
We must...
We must get me out of here!
Couple more minutes and he'd been in China.
Lucky you wasn't on Sacramento Ave.
They lost a burro there last week
and ain't found hair of him yet!
- Shall we go on to the Bella Donna?
- Yes!
I hope this doesn't give you
a wrong impression of our city.
Rome wasn't built in a day, gentlemen.
The paths of empire have always started
in the mud and ended in glory.
I shall make that the subject
of my first editorial.
A white woman.
I've got one of the biggest mines
out here, miss.
- I'd be mighty honored if...
- I gotta bigger mine than his, miss.
I was thinkin'
if you might consider marriage.
I'd like to meet the little lady, too!
- This is Jack Holt.
- Speakin' about marriage, miss...
We sure hope you're going
to like it out here.
I'm mighty serious about that marriage,
indeed I am.
- Get back to work.
- Sure.
We're taking out more than 100 ounces
of gold and that's more than...
Ain't somebody going to introduce me?
My name is Louis Chamalis.
I'm very glad to know you, sir.
Thank you.
I'd like that seat.
Well, miss...
...how do you like San Francisco?
I think I'm going to like it very much.
That's fine. I own it.
What's your pleasure, gentlemen?
This is on the house.
I drink nothin' but rye.
Knuckles, bring some wine.
I hear...
...you come out here to marry Dan Morgan.
Yes.
There's no accountin' for taste.
You'd have been throwing yourself
away on him.
You'd have been throwing yourself away.
You ain't told me your name yet.
My name is Mary Rutledge.
Nice name.
I am Col. Marcus Aurelius Cobb, sir.
I'm glad to know you.
- Miss Rutledge is not staying here, sir.
- Is that true?
- Depends on how much I like your town.
- Miss Rutledge, I beg you to reconsider.
Good night, Mr. Cobb.
Hope we'll see you around here often.
Good night, Col. Cobb and thank you.
Ready?
Happy New Year!
- Happy New Year.
- I didn't hear you knock, sir.
- I guess that's because I didn't knock.
How do you feel?
I feel like New Year's morning, Mr. Chamalis.
I kinda thought you might,
so I brought you something.
Go on, take it.
We call this a prairie oyster.
It'll make you feel better.
Thank you.
Have you made up your mind
about what I told you last night?
Let me see. It was something about...
...marriage, wasn't it?
No, that wasn't me.
Have you something better to offer?
Let's you and me understand each other.
You ain't stayin' in San Francisco
to go into society, are you?
You're staying here for gold.
And you didn't bring a pick
and shovel with you, either.
You seem to have everything all figured out.
You're quite right. I'm staying for gold.
Then, you'll be glad to hear
that you've found it.
- I take it that you're a journey's end.
- Yeah.
That's me. Say, now look here.
You had a lot of the boys last night laying
bags of gold at them little feet of yours.
Them bags of gold is mine.
Only I don't have to dig
and sweat to get them.
I see. They shovel it out of the ground...
...and they hand it to you across the table
with the wheel on it.
You're high-falutin',
but you're smart, ain't you?
Yes, I'm smart.
You got a pretty way of holdin' your head.
What's your proposition, Mr. Chamalis?
All right. You work at the table, see?
You're worth a lot to me as an attraction.
They'll come swarming in here
like flies around a pot of honey.
How would you like to get part of
all the gold that's dug up around here?
Suppose I lose?
You lose only when you wanna
and you win when you wanna.
That's the kind of a little wheel it is.
Is that the wheel Dan Morgan played?
The very same one.
Head feel better?
Very much better, thank you.
Then it's a bargain?
Yes.
Good.
Like a swan, ain't it?
That's what you're like.
Soft and slick.
A swan.
One thing more, Mr. Chamalis.
I suggest you get used to knocking on doors.
All right, Swan.
San Francisco is getting
to be more like a city.
I've been in cities where they chased me
off the streets like a mad dog.
Shut up, before I start doing
some more chasing.
Looks like they'll have to build
a couple of more stores here pretty soon.
- Do you like this, Swan?
- It's very nice, sir.
It'd look right pretty on you.
I don't like that.
She can be the orneriest critter!
Shut up. I like her when she talks like that.
If it ain't the Mayor
of this thriving metropolis.
- Louis!
- Good morning, Mr. Mayor.
I want you to meet a friend of mine.
Miss Rutledge.
I'm sorry, sir, but I'm with my wife.
Come, my dear.
Why, the ungrateful coyote.
The two-faced hyena.
I made him mayor of this town
and I'll stop him being mayor!
- I wouldn't do that.
- Why I...
- I wouldn't do that!
- But he insulted me!
No, he didn't.
He just insulted me, that's all.
- I don't like that either!
- You'll get used to it and so will I.
- Now, then...
- I have one gown...
I'll show him and that horse-face
he calls his wife.
Buzzard meat. That's what she is. Gimme that.
- Which one, sir?
- The one she's got her paws on.
- Go on, take it. It's mine. I bought it.
- Sorry, miss, this belongs to Mr. Chamalis.
I'm buying that, too. It's mine, put it back.
- What?
- You heard what I said.
I don't approve of your behavior.
- You don't?
- No, sir.
It's my behavior,
and it's good enough in this town.
I'll show you some real behavior.
I'm buying this and that.
I'm buying all this, understand?
It's mine. I don't want anyone touching it.
I'm buying everything.
Do you want the fish, too?
No. Throw the fish to the Mayor's wife.
She looks hungry.
Make your plays, gentlemen.
22, even, black. You lose, sir.
I've never seen anything like it.
The black's come up six times in a row.
The red's bound to come up soon.
Sawbuck McTavish is me name
and I'm the luckiest man in the world.
I'm sure you are, sir.
Make your plays, gentlemen.
- Make your play, sir.
- Place them on the red, Sandy.
Go slow, Sawbuck.
We worked for that for a whole year.
I'm tired of bendin' over,
liftin' gold out of the ground.
I wanna pick up off the table,
standing up, let 'er go.
- How much is that?
- Weigh it when the gentleman wins.
- How about bettin' just half, Sawbuck?
- The play is made.
- All of it, sir?
- All of it, miss.
- You're daft, man.
- Daft, am I? Who found Bonanza Creek?
I'm the luckiest man in the world.
I never lose.
11, black.
- Sawbuck.
- Pull in your whiskers, Sandy.
- I want to talk to you.
- I don't want to hear no scolding.
- It isn't that, it's...
- Lost to the prettiest blue eyes I ever seen.
- Make your bet, sir, or get out.
- You were nicer to me a little while ago.
You'd better skedaddle,
while you've still got your shirt.
Sawbuck McTavish
never skedaddled from a lady yet.
Come on, let's go somewhere and celebrate.
You're drunk, sir.
I wasn't too drunk for gamblin'
and I'm no too drunk for love.
He asked for it, gentlemen.
I guess he didn't read the sign.
Go on, pick him up and take him out.
Go on, take him out.
You've no heard the last of this.
Make your plays, gentlemen.
See what he's up to.
Wait a minute, partner, where you going?
I saw the way she ran that wheel.
- How?
- Crooked!
And I'm going to tell the whole town.
I'm gonna tell 'em all.
There's your man, Sheriff.
- No Chinamen allowed in here.
- He's with us. Go ahead.
Knuckles, I'm sorry...
- What's on your mind?
- Nothing serious, Louis, I...
We'll do the talking, Sheriff.
Sandy Ferguson was murdered last night.
- Shot in the back.
- You know murder is a pretty big word.
Never mind, Joe.
All right, he was murdered. What about it?
We've sworn out a warrant
for the man that did it.
Before we're through,
he'll tell us who ordered it done.
Got a warrant?
- All printed out and everything.
- Serve it, Sheriff.
- Simply a matter of routine.
- Come on, serve it and take him along.
Not so fast, boys.
Where do you think you're taking Knuckles?
He's going to stand trial for murder.
You don't have to take him anywhere for that.
You want a trial?
All right.
Judge.
What is it? How dare you... My dear Louis.
I'm afraid it's rather late
so I think I'll go home.
- You're not going home.
- But I have things to do.
Steady, Judge.
Got a little work for you.
For me?
Seems that fellow named Ferguson
has just been killed.
Who?
- Ferguson, ain't it?
- Yeah.
- What's the matter with him?
- He's just been killed.
Ain't it a shame?
- It's appalling. Who did it?
- He's your man.
- Which one?
- Him.
Knuckles.
We've got a warrant. We're going to
put him in jail until court opens.
- Court's open now. Go ahead, Judge.
- But my dear Louis...
- This ain't no court, it's a saloon.
- It's whatever he says it is.
- But, my dear Louis...
- Go ahead, Judge, the court's open.
Hear ye.
This honorable court is now in session.
Gentlemen, I must insist upon
absolute silence. Pardon me.
And will you kindly remove your hats.
Gentlemen, Knuckles is accused of homicide.
- Who seen him do it?
- That fellow was there!
- This is the man.
- Come, gentlemen.
You can't expect me
to take the word of a Chinaman.
- Did any American witness this homicide?
- There ain't any question who did it, Judge.
Come on, get going.
Hold your horses.
This court is not going to be hurried.
Will you please stop the music
during the trial?
I can't concentrate.
- Give the Judge a drink.
- Thank you.
Fred, quiet on that noise.
That's better.
Mr. Slocum, are you prepared to
swear that these statements are true?
Sure.
You are.
Let me put it to you,
that if Knuckles did commit this crime...
...that he must have had some reason.
Of course he had a reason.
- Here you are, Judge.
- Thanks.
This man Ferguson passed a remark
about Miss Rutledge.
He was vulgar.
What? He insulted a lady?
Gentlemen, do you hear that?
He insulted a lady. A woman.
That sensitive vessel,
which from our childhood...
- Come on, hurry up.
- Yes. Of course.
- Under the evidence...
- Hurry up, Judge.
The case is dismissed. Good day, gentlemen.
Have another drink, Judge.
There's your trial.
I hate to see you fellows
make mistakes like this.
Might go bad with you sometime.
We'll be back, Chamalis.
Don't come around here
wasting my time anymore.
Get out of here. Come on, get out.
Ah Wing.
Knuckles.
I'm just going to cut your pigtail off.
What are you yelling about,
there's nothing to wash in Heaven.
What do you want to go there for? Let him go.
I'm afraid, my dear Louis,
I really must be going.
And so, I shall bid you good day, sir.
- Good day, your Honor.
- Thank you.
All right, Tim.
Easy, Mr. Peebles. Don't strain her, sir.
There she goes.
She starts, she moves.
She seems to feel the thrill
of life along her keel.
All right, that's enough.
There she is, Mr. Wigham.
The last word in human ingenuity,
the modern printing press.
She worked fine. Let's look at her insides.
- Welcome. Glad to see you all.
- We want to talk to you.
You all know Mr. Joseph Wigham?
You're just in time
to help christen our new printing press.
The beacon that is to guide
the destiny of our city.
Glad to hear you say that,
because we want your help.
Gentlemen, I'm at your service.
Go on, tell him, Jed.
We want you to write about Louis Chamalis.
- Criticizin' him.
- For being a murderer.
And running this town like a jungle.
We want to know if you have the courage
to print in your newspaper...
...exactly what's wrong with San Francisco.
That's right.
I've waited a long time for this.
She's oiled, inked and we're both ready.
The Clarion is at your service
in any cause...
...that will make San Francisco
a better city to live in.
That's fine, that's great.
If you'll just sit down,
I'll listen to your story.
All right, shut her off.
The first issue of the Clarion, Mr. Wigham.
Look at that make-up. Look at that type.
Looks mighty neat.
This is something I've dreamed of.
I'm a new man, Mr. Wigham.
Forgiven for my journalistic sins.
Restored to my profession.
There is nothing that can touch it.
One of you stay here.
What's the meaning of this?
- That your newspaper?
- Yes.
Lemme see it.
You want law and order? I'm the law
around here and I give the orders.
Why are you buttin' in for?
Did I ever do you any hurt?
This is not a personal matter,
it's much more than that.
Listen.
Everybody gets along in this town
who minds his own business.
You're trying to spoil San Francisco
by printing this kind of stuff.
- Is that the machine this was printed on?
- Get Mr. Slocum in a hurry.
You stay where you are. Knuckles.
What are you going to do?
You just watch and you'll see.
Smash that machine.
You can't do that.
I can't? Smash it till there
ain't a word left on it.
- I won't allow it.
- After you finish, burn the building.
- You can't do that!
- This is outrageous! He's an old man.
He ain't going to get much older acting the
he way he does. Break it up.
You can't do that. You mustn't do that.
Wait a minute.
Louis.
- I don't want you to do this.
- Get out, this is business.
Then it's my business, too.
- Get out. Let me handle this my own way.
- I don't like your way.
I've never said anything
but now I'm saying it.
All right, have your say and get out.
You've done enough things I haven't liked.
I want him to have his paper.
- Now listen, Swan...
- I said let him have his paper.
Tell Knuckles to get out.
Go on, get out, will you?
You heard what she said, go on, get out.
- Do you still want your paper?
- If you destroy my press, you destroy me.
More than that, you destroy
the soul of San Francisco, a city...
Cut out the high-soundin' talk
and answer me...
- Do you want your paper?
- Yes.
Then, run it the way you should run it.
- What way is that?
- My way.
Next time you do anything,
write anything or think anything...
...just ask yourself,
"How would Louis Chamalis like it?"
Understand?
Is that what makes the writing on the paper?
Yes.
I don't want anybody readin'
this kind of stuff.
There you are.
You still got your little plaything.
- Come on, Swan.
- I'll come in a moment.
Thank you, Miss Rutledge.
I couldn't have stood it if they'd broken it.
It isn't much use this way though, is it?
A poor shamed thing that mustn't speak.
It can speak, Colonel.
Let it speak the language of the town.
Lies, hypocrisy, and more lies.
The beacon of the new empire.
Mr. Chamalis' empire.
Is this true about Sandy Ferguson?
You should know better than I, Miss Rutledge.
Louis, I want to talk to you.
This is true, isn't it?
Sure.
- Why did you kill Sandy Ferguson?
- For business reasons.
Our bargains included lots of things.
But this wasn't one of them.
I don't like it.
Listen, Swan, I'm running this town
and there's only one way to run it.
My way.
I'm beginning to learn that...
...and it isn't a pleasant lesson.
Come on, Swan, have a drink.
I'm one up on you.
You haven't thanked me yet
for lettin' the Colonel have his paper.
Thank you.
You seemed almost human for a moment.
How about you being human for a change?
I'd like another drink, please.
Why don't you ever kiss me
of your own accord?
Why don't you ever put your arms
around me and kiss me?
Wait till I have my drink.
I don't want that kind of love.
I'm sick of you talking to me like that.
I'm sick of you looking at me
like I was a snake in a gold skin.
Stop it, you're drunk.
I told you I'd wait, didn't I?
I've waited long enough.
You're going to love me or you're through!
You're going to say you love me and mean it.
I don't want any woman
looking at me like you do.
You're going to say you love me or get out.
I heard you. Don't keep repeating it.
- Is that all you got to say?
- Just that I'm going.
You're going, are you? Where?
There isn't a man who would
speak to you if you went out of here.
Because they know I'll kill 'em.
I'll kill the first man you talk to.
What do you want me to do, lie?
Lie and pretend I have a heart?
Do you think I'm still Mary Rutledge,
that I'm still a white woman?
Shut up.
Look at me, Louis.
Look in my eyes. What do you see?
It isn't pretty, is it?
I'm just what you see there.
Take what you can get, Louis,
and let it go at that.
Let's enjoy our mud puddle.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going riding.
I want the wind and the air on me.
- Yes, but it's going to rain.
- I like the rain, too.
Swan.
I want to talk to you about last night.
Forget it, Louis. I'm trying to.
I'll be back in time to run the table.
I'm sorry to break in on you like this,
mister, but...
...it's getting pretty wet out there.
What's the matter?
I can't get over it.
- Over what?
- How beautiful a woman is.
I'd almost forgotten, so help me.
Did you ever read about Balboa when he
first caught sight of the Pacific Ocean?
- What are you talking about?
- He fainted with pure joy.
You're the most peculiar desert rat
I've seen yet.
Would you mind very much if I
looked at you, if I promise not to faint?
You're pretty wet, ma'am.
Don't you think you ought to hang those
clothes of yours in front of the fire to dry?
Well...
I'm afraid there's only this one room, but...
I'll either have to go outside or I could use
my willpower and turn my back.
- Turn around, mister.
- Yes, ma'am.
I apologize for this place.
I found it myself a few minutes ago.
That's how I happened to join the gold rush.
It was a case of going to work for my
father or finding the Golden Fleece.
I'm afraid I'm gabbin' my head off, but...
...I haven't talked to anybody for two years,
except my two burros.
I reckon you met them outside.
What did you talk to them about?
About cakes of soap.
Whether I'd shave or not.
Lamb kidneys in wine sauce
for breakfast we used to have at home.
- You're from New York, aren't you?
- 14 Gramercy Park.
Gramercy Park!
I used to play there when I was a little girl.
You weren't that little brat
with the Shetland pony?
No, I don't think you know me.
I was raised under a bell jar
with forget-me-nots in my hair.
Clothes dry yet?
I'll see.
Yes. I guess they're about cooked now, ma'am.
I'm afraid I'll have to use
my willpower again.
Pardon my curiosity, ma'am, but...
...I'm amazed to find anyone like you
blooming away in this arid land of gold.
You live in San Francisco?
No, I'm just visiting here.
Alone?
No. My family is with me, naturally.
Prospecting?
No, we're just visiting someone
who owns a ranch.
You can turn around now.
Would you mind my asking you
who you are, ma'am?
My name is Mary Rutledge.
Pleased to meet you, Miss Rutledge.
My name's James Carmichael.
I've never seen you before, have I?
In San Francisco?
No, I've never been there, only to get off
the boat and now to get on it again.
- You're leaving the West?
- Yes.
Shipping out like Sindbad with his loot.
Here it is.
I've been poking around
for this stuff for about two years.
I keep expecting it to vanish
like the figments of a dream.
It's safe now, that is, if I can get by
the harpies at San Francisco.
- The harpies?
- Yes, ma'am.
Although some people call them
by other names.
- Can I help you button that?
- Thank you.
Remember how Ulysses
had to stuff cotton in his ears...
...to keep from hearing
the song of the Siren?
They're going to have
to sing awfully loud for me.
What does a harpy look like?
They've got snakes in their hair and
cats' eyes and no hearts at all.
You can always tell them easy.
This is more fun than digging gold.
If you weren't a lady from Gramercy Park
and I weren't a poetical half-wit...
...full of the most idiotic respect
for beauty and grace and gentility, I'd...
- You'd what, Mr. Carmichael?
- I'd act a lot different than I'd been acting.
You've been very charming.
That's the trouble with being
a poet at heart.
You always have to be charming
at the wrong time.
You don't mind this loose talk I hope, ma'am?
There.
I guess you're buttoned now and forever.
It seems to have stopped raining.
I think we'd better go.
I had an idea we were never
going to leave here, but...
...I guess that's impractical.
I'm afraid it is.
How am I going to write to you
if I don't know where you live?
I write awfully well, something like
Shelley when I'm in the mood.
- I'll read you something he wrote.
- You haven't time, Mr. Carmichael.
This is my road, and that's yours,
to the boat...
...and the lamb chops in wine sauce.
Lamb kidneys, ma'am.
Only they don't seem so important now.
- Can't I see you home?
- You'll miss the boat.
Aren't I ever going to see you again?
I'd like to remember it just like this.
The rain, the fog...
...and a poet from Gramercy Park
with his bags of gold.
Let's leave it that way.
It's awfully hard to live poetry.
Goodbye, Mr. Carmichael.
Will you take this as a present, then,
and read it yourself?
And pretend I wrote it?
Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Hey!
You don't want a couple of jackasses
to remember me by?
No, thank you. Goodbye.
Kind of foggy, ain't it, Josephine?
Maybe that old boat won't sail after all.
Where have you been?
I've been worried about you.
I've been riding, Louis, in Gramercy Park.
What are you talking about?
There ain't no Gramercy Park around here.
I guess you're right.
Is something the matter? Did anything happen?
A lot happened.
- What?
- I got caught in the rain.
Got soaked.
Rode back a thousand miles and here I am.
That's all that matters, isn't it?
That's all that matters.
I guess I'd better change my things.
I beg your pardon, gentlemen.
Is this the way to the boat?
- Passenger?
- Yes.
There's no use
your going aboard tonight, sir.
That is, unless you want to.
We ain't sailin' till this fog lifts.
- How soon do you expect that?
- A day or two.
I'll be seein' you on deck, sir.
- That's mighty discouragin', stranger.
- Yes, it is.
- You hit it rich and homeward bound?
- Yes.
You don't figure on standin' here
until the fog lifts?
I don't know.
Reason tells that's the smartest
thing to do. To stand right here.
But I've been too reasonable all day.
Something I left up in the air
that I'd like to attend to.
- How about a nice home-cooked meal first?
- Lead on, sir.
Lucky you met up with me, I can
protect you from the perils of the city.
Yes.
Yes siree. They had me hemmed in,
so I pulled my gun...
...and I clipped one down there
and one man...
- Take it easy, you might hurt somebody.
- Don't be afraid, son, it ain't loaded.
It's not loaded?
No, I don't depend on firearms
for protection...
...it's my muscles that scares them away.
If you were to know things
I've done with my bare...
Here's a nice homey place for a stranger,
the Bella Donna.
Yes. I've heard of it.
Maybe you'd like me to help you carry
that gold. You're apt to strain yourself.
No. Thanks just the same.
It's a shame not to take advantage of
my strength, but have it your own way.
Some folks are suspicious for no reason.
I never saw more grand larceny
behind one pair of whiskers.
- You ain't foolin', son?
- No.
You know most folks
don't seem to realize how bad I am.
Let's sit here and I'll fetch a garsin.
What's a garsin?
That's what we call waiters in San Francisco.
"Garsin".
That's a kind of stylish nickname.
Garsin, come.
Quit yer hollerin'. What do you want?
Don't get fresh with me.
I'll shove you off the earth.
Start shovin'.
He's always foolin'.
Give us a minute
and get us a couple more drinks.
You'd better make it a bottle,
tootie-sweetie.
That's French. Let's wet the whistle.
I think I'll have...
Makes me look a little more ferocious.
If you can't make out what that says,
Number 3 is the best meal.
- What's she doing here?
- Who?
Her? Told you this was a nice homey
place. That's the lady known as Swan.
- Swan?
- Yep.
How long has she been here?
Brought her in myself,
right off the Flyin' Cloud.
Here's your bottle.
- She come alone?
- Yeah.
But Mr. Chamalis wanted her services
exclusive for the Bella Donna.
- Did she ever live on a ranch?
- Her? A ranch?
- The joke's on me.
- If you're lookin' for fun, there it is.
Win or lose, it's a pleasure
just to stand beside her at the table.
Can you see from here
whether she has snakes in her hair?
Son, go easy on that liquor.
Brought you another admirer, Swan.
All quiverin' to try his luck agin' ya.
10, black, even.
Old man, advise me.
Are those snakes in her hair
or forget-me-nots?
It's all right.
He's a little young and been drinkin'.
No, they're not snakes. They're diamonds.
She's got lovely cats' eyes.
What's the delay, Swan. Come on, spin her.
Make your plays, gentlemen.
Quiet. I want to hear the song of the Siren.
- That ain't no way to talk to a lady.
- I most humbly apologize.
I forgot she was raised under a bell jar
with a sprig of forget-me-nots in her hair.
21, red. Waiter.
I'll take that.
Let's drink together, ma'am.
To me, James Carmichael.
The dumbest jackass that ever came
hee-hawing into San Francisco.
- Put your money up or get out.
- Come on, put up your money.
Come on, spin that wheel. Let's get going.
All right, here goes.
- Gramercy Park versus the hallucination.
- You'd better get it weighed first, son.
We'll weigh it for the gentleman
when he wins.
On the black, the color of women's hearts.
Easy. You ain't gonna get no place
with them sentiments.
- A little less fancy talk, stranger.
- Sorry to give offense.
7 and red.
You lose this one time, son.
If at first you don't succeed, try again.
That's my motto since a child.
- Is that it?
- Yes, sir.
Knuckles.
Give him this.
Here you are, stranger. On the house.
Thank you. Hospitable of you.
Make your bets, gentlemen.
Had enough, you?
Not so fast there.
- You ain't bettin' it all at once, are you?
- On the black.
- Does it all go?
- Go on, roll your hoop.
Round and round the old willow tree.
Come on, old man of the sea.
Drink to the little ball.
27. And it's red.
- Who won?
- The red. Yes, sir, the red come up again.
Not my color.
You lost! Just like I did!
You lost like Sawbuck McTavish.
Cover up your back
or they'll shoot you like they did Sandy.
- Get out!
- I seen it.
To Madam Swan and to Galahad.
The pure in heart
and the expert dress cottoner.
One day, the black will win
and the harpies will weep.
Don't get excited, stranger.
Go on, take him out.
Make your plays, gentlemen.
Hey, Swan, open the door.
Please, go away, Louis.
Come on, open the door.
I've got something for you.
Part of the money you won tonight.
I don't want it. Keep it.
What you acting so hot for?
I don't know.
Just go away and leave me alone.
Women are like frogs. You can never tell
which way they're gonna jump.
The old man of the sea.
How are you?
Son, still feel a little depressed
over your bad luck last night.
- Yes, I remember.
- I never seen the like before.
Don't let it dampen
that fine western spirit of yours.
I still have two burros left.
That's right, ya did.
But you ain't got 'em now.
They run away.
A very interesting city.
Surprised I have my boots.
- Any complaints?
- No.
No complaints.
Wisdom was never bought at so cheap a price.
You still feel pretty bad, son?
Maybe it's somethin' you ate.
Gall and wormwood sit hard
on the delicate stomach.
Gentlemen, I don't want to depress you
with my problems...
...but is there a way for the shorn lamb to
earn enough money for his passage home?
A shorn lamb
of infinite accomplishments and...
...a great mass of personal charm.
I like the way he talks.
I don't.
Nobody's askin' you.
I like a windbag like that around.
- Go on, get him something to do.
- If you say so.
Get busy on those.
You mean these interesting vessels?
We call 'em spittoons and we like 'em shiny.
With all deference to my benefactor,
I think I'll call them cuspidors.
- How do you feel, son?
- Like a useful member of society at last.
That's fine.
- You ever wait on table?
- No. I'm sure I have a talent for it.
You can begin now.
It ain't hard to be a garsin.
Just stick up for your rights
when they get fresh with you.
And always take a bottle in your right hand
and when they're comin' to...
I may spoil her appetite.
Good morning.
Would you like to see the menu, ma'am?
- What are you doing here?
- I'm waiting for your order.
I don't want you around here.
I don't blame you after last night.
I'm very glad of this chance to apologize.
I don't like sarcasm
so early in the day from waiters.
There's no sarcasm intended, ma'am.
You hate me, why hide it behind silly words?
That's not an accurate account of my feelings.
The worst I feel is kind of philosophical.
What are you standing there for?
I told you I don't want you around here.
If you don't mind, I'd like to work here until
I get money to go back to New York.
You could steer clear
of the harpies next time.
What would you have for breakfast?
Would you like to see the menu?
I'll give you your fare back
to Gramercy Park, Mr. Carmichael.
I'm sorry, but I have some notion
on the subject of handouts.
- I'm not good enough to give you money.
- I'm not bad enough to take it, ma'am.
If you don't hate me, I hate you.
With all of your talk about being a poet...
...you're small, mean, righteous,
and no different from the rest.
- Would you like to see the menu, ma'am?
- Bring me some toast, coffee and jam.
And yes...
...some lamb kidneys in wine sauce.
Yes, ma'am.
I just met a fellow
who told me something very interesting.
I told you what was going to happen to
you if I ever caught you lyin'!
I caught you.
What a pleasant way to begin
a conversation, Louis.
And before breakfast, too.
- You wasn't alone in the rain.
- You mean yesterday.
You know what I mean. Yeah, yesterday.
You was seen.
Come out with it. Don't sit there
like a dog barking at a cat in a tree.
I was seen doing what?
- Who was he?
- Who was who?
Who was the man you were with yesterday?
You're hurting my arm.
I'll hurt worse than that
if you don't tell me.
You were seen with him by the water,
talking to him.
- Who was he?
- I told you...
I beg your pardon, ma'am.
There are no lamb kidneys.
Would you like the wine sauce by itself?
We're talkin', can't you see?
Go on, get out of here.
Sure.
Who was he?
Louis, I told you I got lost
in the fog and I...
I stopped somebody to ask the way
and he told me.
- That isn't a hanging offense, is it?
- I'll find out if you're lying.
Waiter.
Bring me a steak and a piece of pie.
Did you hear about
the Chinaman being killed last night?
Yes.
I was wondering, Colonel, if I couldn't...
...weave it into this piece
about the climate.
Sayin' how sorry we was that the Chinaman...
...was goin' to miss the salubrious spell of
weather we're expectin' next week.
All topics sound hollow
and commonplace compared to...
...the glorious climate of California,
Mr. Wigham.
Mr. McTavish was in again.
What did he want?
He had an item about the
roulette wheel at the Bella Donna.
He says it's crooked,
that they stole a small fortune...
...from a young fellow
playing there last night.
It's quite an interesting item, Colonel.
Avoid all mundane matters,
and we shall flourish like a green bay tree.
The beacon of the press.
In the hell to which all journalists must
descend when they die...
...we shall sit at red-hot desks
with quills of fire in our hand...
...and spend eternity writing about
the salubrious weather of that region.
Let us serve our apprenticeship here
thoroughly and intelligently.
How do you spell "aurora borealis?"
Call it Mr. Chamalis' rosy-fingered dawn.
What's that?
You've got eyes, go on and read it.
It's news, that's what it is.
News you wouldn't print
in that yellow-dog paper of yours.
You'd better not put that up.
There'll be trouble.
There will that...
I strongly advise against it, sir.
Mr. McTavish, take that down.
You had...
I warned you.
Go on back inside
and write a story about the climate.
Stop where you are, sir!
This is the first honest news the Clarion
ever had and it's going to stay there!
Stop or I'll shoot!
Mr. Wigham.
Colonel, are you hurt bad?
Get a doctor quick.
Land a hand here, someone.
- Mr. Wigham.
- Yes?
I want you to change
the policy of the Clarion.
I want you to write a story...
...I should have written myself long ago.
I want you to tell
the people of San Francisco...
...that no city can exist
without law and order.
Don't try to talk, Colonel.
Write a story about that flag.
Write that wherever it flies...
...it brings a promise of life...
...liberty and the pursuit of happiness.
There are some people in this town
who don't seem to know that.
Let the Clarion tell them.
- Print the news.
- I will, Colonel.
We'll carry on.
Law and order.
Print it.
You've got a job. We're here to help you.
Two of you, come with me.
I don't need anybody to go with me.
Here you are, gents.
At last we've got a paper in this town.
All about law and order.
Here you are. The Clarion.
Take one.
The voice of San Francisco.
No charge, brother.
- All about law and order.
- What you think! Law and order.
She's come to San Francisco.
Buy the paper, she's free.
Law and order in San Francisco.
That's a new one on you, brother.
Law and order has come to stay.
Law and order is here to stay.
"Law and order".
- I'll give then some law and order.
- Lot of 'em running around down there.
Selling those things all over the streets.
And they've got guns to back 'em up.
I got guns, too.
The first thing is to bust the machine
that printed this, like I should have done.
Go to the paper
and take some of the boys with you.
I won't need anybody.
So you killed Col. Cobb.
You must be crazy. You think you can
go on killing and destroying...
No. Never mind about that.
I found this under your pillow.
Who gave it to you?
It's about love. Poems. Who gave it to you?
Do you want me to take
the little wheel tonight?
I'll find out who he is,
but I'm giving you a chance.
- Tell me.
- There's nothing to tell.
Some rat with a book of poems.
That's what you went for.
That's what made you push me away?
- Who is he?
- Stop it!
I bet he held you and made you happy.
You stupid fool.
Nobody's touched me and nobody will.
- You and nobody else. Understand?
- He kissed you, didn't he?
You kissed him like you never done to me.
Throwin' yourself on some rat.
I wish I had. I wish I could tell you
something to make you howl and shoot!
I'll do the shooting.
But somebody else is going to do the howling.
Here he comes.
Anybody with him?
Keep on walking, Mr. Jacoby.
- Which way?
- We'll steer you.
Turn right here.
You call this a fair fight?
You're not in a fight, Mr. Jacoby.
You're on trial, Knuckles.
- For what?
- Murder.
Where's the trial going to be?
The trial is going on now, sir.
Can I get word to Chamalis
to get me a lawyer?
I'm representing you, sir.
- With a gun in my back.
- That's right.
Is this the man you saw
shoot down McTavish and Col. Cobb?
That's him.
Allow me to cross-examine the witness,
Mr. Slocum.
Are you sure, sir?
Dead certain!
- Where's the rope?
- Here.
- Wait a minute. Who do you think you are?
- We're Vigilantes, sir.
- You're what?
- The Vigilantes.
We're bringing law and order
to San Francisco.
What monkey business is this?
I thought there was going to be a trial.
You have been tried, Knuckles.
I didn't hear any trial.
There wasn't any judge or jury.
- Gentlemen, what is your verdict?
- Guilty!
No, wait a minute. You can't do this.
Get Louis Chamalis.
- Who done it?
- The Vigilantes!
They're holding meetings everywhere.
- Who?
- The Vigilantes.
They've gone crazy. They'll be after us.
We must get away. They'll hang us like that.
- Stand up, Rubber Knees.
- But Louis!
This is my town and it's going to stay mine.
- But they're too big...
- Shut up!
Climb up there and take him down.
Vigilantes?
Come on.
Kind of quiet around here, ain't it?
Them Vigilantes sure depressed the business.
- What's troubling you?
- I'm feeling pretty low tonight, son.
Seein' Knuckles hangin' up out there,
reminded me I done somethin' I don't like.
- That's easy to believe.
- You're right.
I'm a no-good, terrible old man
with the heart of a coyote.
Yes, I'm certain of it.
I wish you wasn't so ready to believe me.
Why?
It makes it harder to confess.
Confess what?
I ain't gonna beat about the bush, then.
There's one thing that's
botherin' my black soul in particular.
I found something that don't belong to me.
There it is, you recognize it?
Somebody dropped it by mistake.
- That's mine.
- I was wondering.
Where did you get it?
Off the floor.
Don't look at me like that, son.
Say you forgive me. Just say it once.
Thanks.
It's the first decent thing
I've done in my whole black life.
Sort of overwhelms me.
I feel like a little white kitten, reborn.
- May I reward you, sir?
- The reward.
I took that out myself in advance so as not
to delay matters with any bickering.
I see.
Thanks again.
Looks like the fog's gonna lift
and that boat'll be sailin'.
- You shippin' on it?
- Yes.
Hate to see you go, son,
but things'll be more suitable in the East.
For poets and failures.
He's goin' away, Swan.
This is the second time we say goodbye.
I'm sailing after all.
I thought you didn't have your boat fare.
It seems that this old gentleman
rescued some of my loot the other night.
It dropped under the table in the excitement.
And so with a bag of gold, the prodigal
returns to Gramercy Park, licked.
There won't be any bands to play,
if that's what you mean.
Or any poems to write.
No, I guess not. I won't have much time
for writing poetry and...
Anyhow, I kind of run out of subject matter.
Write about a harpy
who smiled at you and cheated you.
Write about that.
That's what you believe, isn't it?
That I'm a cheat.
No. I don't believe that.
Then why are you crawling out
without giving yourself another chance?
He's just got enough for another ticket,
let him go!
That's no way for a man to go,
to crawl out of the West...
...just for the price of a ticket.
- Not when there's still a chance.
- Now listen, I'm agin' it!
Go away thinking that I stole your money
and sent you back, licked and broke.
- I'll try the black again.
- Son, it's pure folly.
Weigh it for him, Bill.
The gentleman from Gramercy Park
bets on the black.
Here it goes.
This teaches me.
I'll never do a good deed again.
You're stakin' your whole future
on a ball rollin'.
It's an outrage.
It's not much of a future, win or lose.
- 17, on the black.
- Moses in the mountain! You win!
- How much did he have, Bill?
- $320.
- Are you letting it ride, Mr. Carmichael?
- I don't know. I...
The play is made, here it goes.
Snatch it up, son, while there's time.
22 on the black.
Sufferin' Moses! You win again.
I can't believe it!
- Make your play, sir.
- Pick it up, son.
- Here it goes.
- Pick it up. It's on a number.
- Are you leaving it on the number?
- Son, it's a million to one, I tell you.
You'll write something
about the fog, won't you?
About how people forget where they are
and who they are?
13 and it's black.
You won again, Mr. Carmichael.
A bonanza!
Pay off, Bill. The game is closed.
Do I win all that?
The Bella Donna pays 35-to-1
on a number, always, Mr. Carmichael.
Hurry, Bill. Get him on the boat.
I'll take him.
- I don't know quite what to say.
- Say it to somebody else, not me.
I've seen quite enough of you
for one day or for one lifetime.
I'm afraid, Mr. Carmichael,
I'm not as good a loser as you were.
Come on, son, don't stand around now.
You know the purpose of
organizing the Vigilantes?
- I do.
- Sign here.
- What do we do first?
- Get Chamalis.
That's fine by me.
- The guns are in there. Pass 'em around.
- All right, Boss.
Law and order?
Here are my orders
and don't get 'em wrong.
Find out where these Vigilantes are meeting.
- What are you going to do?
- Set fire to the city.
Burn down every building
with a Vigilante in it.
- There's a wind coming.
- It's blowing the right way.
Just a minute. We'll need plenty of money.
- How much have you downstairs, Bill?
- We ain't got much.
What do you mean?
You tell him, Swan.
- What happened?
- We lost.
- What table?
- Mine.
How much?
Bill counted it out.
A little over $40,000.
- Who ran the wheel?
- I did.
Go on, boys, you've got your orders.
I'll be along. You stay here.
Who was he, Swan?
A Mr. Carmichael.
Who's that?
One of your employees.
The fellow with all them fancy words.
So that's him?
That's the fellow you traded me in for.
Where is he, Swan?
- Gone.
- Gone?
Listen.
I'm going out and bring your little friend
back to see you again.
I'm bringing him back
so that you can listen to his pretty poetry.
Lock her in and keep her waiting
till I come back with her sweetheart.
You heard what he said.
- Mr. Chamalis is looking for you, sir.
- I was told.
I don't think this is
quite the place for you to hide.
I'm not hiding.
- Then what do you want?
- I don't know.
Don't you understand?
They're outside that door.
He's looking for you to kill you!
He's out there.
He's going to kill you.
Why should he want to do that?
Because he's mad. Crazy mad.
Because he's laboring under the delusion
that I'm in love with you.
Are you?
You must be mad, too.
I'm much worse than that, I'm stupid.
Love is the only thing I've thought of
or read about since I was knee-high.
That's what I've always dreamed of,
meeting somebody and falling in love.
When that thing happened, I was going
to recite poetry to her for hours...
...about how her heart's an angel's wing...
...her hair the strings of a heavenly harp.
Instead I got drunk,
and hollered at her and called her a harpy.
I'm pretty stupid.
I love you.
Why are doing this to me?
Why did you come back to hurt me,
make me cry?
Please go. Thank you.
Thank you for being
what I thought you were, nice.
- You're coming back with me.
- No.
I love you.
That's why I can't come.
If you just wanted Swan,
it would be different.
But you want somebody
that doesn't exist anymore.
I stole your money. I gave it back to you,
and that pleased you, that's all it is.
It pleased you.
I wasn't as bad as you thought.
You must go.
They're looking for you. They'll kill you!
You're wasting a lot of time talking
because you're coming with me.
No.
You're dreaming of something that isn't me.
- You'd look at me some day and...
- I'm looking at you now.
I'm no good, do you hear?
Don't make me say it again.
Too much has happened to me.
It happened to Swan, not you. Listen.
There's something inside of people
that can't be touched.
They can stand in mud up to their necks,
but that thing inside stays bright, shining.
- I want to believe you.
- You must believe me because it's true.
Loving wipes out everything else.
All this never existed. You'll see.
Are you sure? No. Don't tell me.
Even if you aren't sure,
even if it isn't true...
Take me with you.
Stay where you are! Keep quiet
and nobody's going to get hurt.
Where's Chamalis?
Here he is, found him by the inlet.
Come here!
- Where'd that windbag go?
- I ain't got no conception...
- He was seen with you.
- I was tryin' to collect some money.
What did he say?
When I was grapplin' with him...
...I slipped in the mud and he on top of me
like 20 wildcats clawin'...
The Vigilantes came in looking for you!
They're bustin' the place!
- Where's Swan?
- She got away.
I seen her running through the fog
with somebody.
I took the other window. Listen, boss...
Shut up! She went with that fellow?
She'll try coming around to the boat.
But she's too smart to come down this way.
But, Boss. Listen...
Shut up! She'll probably try
rowing around to the off side.
We'll get some boats.
You stay here and watch the wharf.
- What about them?
- Stay here.
Come on, we'll get some boats.
- Right where Old Atrocity said it would be.
- Bless his heart.
Hurry, darling.
You just sit there and steer.
Say port or starboard and I'll obey.
Do you still love me?
Ask me that when I'm an old woman
with gray hair.
I'll tell you I haven't
begun to love you yet.
I'll have to wear this dress
for three months.
- You'll get tired of it.
- We'll put it in a museum.
There's a good one in Hoboken.
- I thought I heard something.
- No, that was me, flying through the air.
Head straight for the big boat.
Row carefully, darling.
He'll figure out where we're going
and come after us.
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
But I wish I had some other dress on.
I must look so foolish.
It would take me from here to China
and back to tell you how you look...
I heard something.
That's a bird hunting for fish.
We've turned the wrong way.
Starboard, Mr. Carmichael, darling.
It's hard rowing when you're so emotional.
Darling, where's your money?
Lordy, I forgot.
I left it right outside your window.
That's the most idiotic thing I've ever done.
- $30,000.
- $40,000, darling.
- Do you mind?
- I don't mind anything.
Same here.
I'm rowing out of the Golden West with...
I heard something.
Someone's rowing over there. Listen.
Keep pulling, you weasel.
- Chamalis.
- Don't mind.
I don't.
I take it back about not liking the fog.
I'm very fond of fog.
So am I.
They're moving in the same direction.
Darling, the fog is thinning.
- Is it?
- A little. Here comes the moon.
This is one poet that hates the moon.
There they are, boss.
Pull to the left. Pull hard.
They've heard us. They're coming this way.
Don't, you fool, you'll hit her.
Get down!
I'll never forgive that moon.
Are you all right?
I'm very frightened, but otherwise...
Can you row any faster?
I'll try.
- Jim, I love you.
- I adore you.
Whatever happens...
- What is it?
- A little accident.
We can't make it, Jim.
Jump over, you can swim.
Get down.
You hit him. Keep pulling.
- Do you see them?
- No.
Here, darling.
I'm not much help, I...
That's all right, but hurry, come, darling.
- Mary.
- Darling, they're coming.
They landed somewhere around here.
- Can you see them?
- Keep quiet.
Mary, you go on.
Quiet, everybody. Listen.
You thought you'd get away?
- The moon was on your side.
- Wait.
Get out of the way.
I'm going to put him out of his misery.
Before you shoot, listen to me!
You wanted me to love you. You held me
in your arms and asked me to love you.
Do you still want it?
If you do, I will. I'll love you.
Don't kill him. Let him go.
Let him go and I'll love you
the way you've always wanted me to.
I'll forget him, I swear I will.
He's never even touched me.
He's never even kissed me.
Let him go?
- He's never touched you?
- No.
On account of him, you'll feel for me
like I've always wanted you to?
- On account of him?
- Not just on account of him...
...but if you do this, you'll be a fine man.
You'll be the kind of a man
that a woman could love.
- How do I know that you'll do that?
- Because I give you my word.
Not Swan's word but the word of someone
you haven't known yet.
Somebody you'll like much better than Swan.
I'll do it. I got to do it.
That's what I want.
Come here. Pick him up.
- What for?
- Pick him up.
Throw him on that boat.
I want him on that boat!
There are lots of people in this town
trying to give me orders, but you ain't.
- Do what I told you.
- Thank you, Louis. Be careful.
He'll make it.
We'll have him on his feet
before he lands in New York.
- The tide's changing, sir.
- Folks, you'd better be saying goodbye.
We are sailing.
Goodbye, son.
Goodbye.
You left something outside the window.
I gave it all to the Captain.
There was five bags.
Can you imagine. I must have missed this one.
Goodbye, son.
Mary.
Yes, Jim.
We made it.
Be quiet, darling. Don't talk.
Nothing can ever come between us anymore.
No.
Go to sleep, darling.
Lay aloft. Unfold the topsails.
We'll take good care of him, miss.
Come on.
- Thank you, Louis.
- You did thank me.
Thank you again, and I'll always thank you.
You'll never regret it, I swear it.
So that's the way a woman looks
when she's in love.
Hurry, Louis, don't stop.
And that's the way she cries
when she loves somebody.
- Hurry, please.
- Wait a minute.
You're going to love me now.
- You're going to look like that for me.
- Yes. I'm going to keep my word.
You're never going to regret it.
I'm never going to regret it
because I'm never going to see you again.
I don't take presents off spittoon cleaners.
I don't take presents off anybody.
I give 'em.
I've got things to do here
without tying myself up to somebody...
...who's going to cry for somebody else
all the time.
What's the matter? You understand English?
Go on back to him now.
Chamalis, we want you.
All right.
What are you standing there for? Say goodbye?
Is that the way a gentleman does it?
Come on.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org