Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
So there's a nigger,
a kike and a wop
and they get surrounded by Indians.
The chief walks to them.
He says, "Listen, we're gonna kill you,
"we're gonna skin you,
we're gonna boil you.
"We're gonna make a
canoe out of you.
"But you get one final request."
So the chief walks up to the nigger, and
of course he orders a bucket of chicken.
He eats it, he's killed.
They skin him, they boil him, and
they make a canoe out of him.
So the chief goes up to the
Jew, "What do you wish for?"
He says "I'll have
a knish and a bagel."
But he takes his time eating it.
Then they kill him,
they skin him, they boil him,
they make a canoe out of him.
And finally, the chief
walks up to the wop.
He says, "What do you want?"
The Italian says, "I want a fork."
The chief says,
"What do you want a fork for?
"You don't want something else?"
The Italian says,
"No, give me a fork!"
He says, "We don't have a fork!"
He says, "Find me a fucking fork!"
So the chief goes out,
finds him a fork, he brings
it over, hands it to him.
He walks straight up to the chief.
He says, "Here's your fucking canoe!
"Ma, I'm coming!
"Here's your fucking canoe!"
Get the fuck down!
Will somebody shut off
that fucking music?
Take it easy.
You seem a little confused.
Let me see if I could clear
things up for you a little bit.
This parking ticket
belongs to a van that's registered
to one of your garages.
It was found at the crime scene.
It was found two hours ago.
One of my vans was stolen.
Yeah?
Did you report it stolen?
I didn't have to. It was found
after a couple of days.
Oh, you didn't have to.
You found it.
You're a lucky guy.
I don't know how it got there.
The fucking shit was stolen.
And are you aware of the fact
that that van and others like it
have been linked
to a series of robberies
over the past
eight months all over
from Bay Ridge to Kings Point?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Mmm-hmm.
What's this?
Is this your firearm?
It's never been fired.
Is it registered?
It's eight years old.
Answer the question, is it registered?
You're a funny man, you know that?
Yeah, I got a sense of humor, sure.
Yeah, I noticed.
Unregistered firearm,
take it downtown.
Listen, you got nothing
on me, all right?
I quit years ago.
So get off my back.
Come on.
I'm working on cars now,
with my brothers.
I spent two fucking
years in the joint.
You think... You think I'm
gonna give my family up again?
Go 'head, look.
You ain't gonna find shit.
All these... All these
weeks you're telling me...
All these weeks you're
telling me it's a guarantee.
There's no chance it could
be anywhere else but here.
No, well...
Yeah, and what do we find?
So, it wasn't here, I...
There's no point. He doesn't have
a permit for his gun. That's it!
He's got no money on him,
no nothing!
We've got a parking ticket
that connects him
directly to the crime scene...
Oh, give it up, Frank.
Give it up.
We blew our warrants,
we blew our arrests.
He goes away
for six months. That's it.
We got one other guy.
You wanna talk to him?
He's down at the morgue.
You know that girl back there?
All right, now.
You're really out.
That's Frank.
How's Pop?
Uh, it depends on the day.
They took him off the
ventilator though this morning.
You wanna go see your kids?
No. I wanna see Pop.
Pop, what are you doing up?
That's you, boy, that's you!
How you doing, Pop?
Get over here,
you big son of a gun.
Oh, buddy, oh, buddy.
I'm doing great.
I can go four rounds.
They just took out one lung.
I hope the geniuses
left the good one.
- I'm breathin' pretty good, huh?
- Yeah.
Hey, Frankie boy.
Hey, Pop.
Hey.
You look good.
Hi.
Yeah. You shouldn't
be up, so come on.
I know, I shouldn't.
Get in here, now.
Mother Teresa.
Come on.
I'll tell ya what, they got
two, three nurses here,
and I'll bet ya, I can be as
good as I was, at least once.
Mmm, okay.
So, what are the doctors saying?
The doctors say, they say, uh...
They say, "You got insurance?"
And they say,
"Wait until you get better."
I'll be out soon.
Yeah, I don't know why I ask you.
I'm gonna go ask them myself, okay?
Yeah, sure.
I'm gonna let you two talk.
Love you, pal.
You're not too
talkative, huh, buddy.
I mean it's all right.
It's all right. I mean...
The good thing is you're out.
I'm just on leave, Pop.
It's a furlough.
I don't get a job,
they keep me in.
Yeah.
It's a long time you was gone.
Frank, been a long time.
Kids are on the couch.
Kids, this is your father.
Come on, get up.
Hey, what're you doing?
It's me.
I'm your father.
Come here, give me a kiss.
We can take it back.
No, it's okay. Thanks.
Thanks!
Mom, can I go play these?
Of course, sweetie.
Go ahead.
So, I, uh, I hear
you been left back?
Yeah.
Yeah? You gotta buckle down.
"Yeah, yeah."
It's not enough to say
"yeah" all the time.
He goes out every night.
You listen to your mother.
You screw up in school, that's
how you stay in the sewer.
Frank!
Come on, join.
No.
Come on!
I taught him everything he knows.
Let me ask you something, Frank.
How close could you be with this
guy I've known you for 12 years.
You never mentioned him
to me once.
Not once.
Well, we... We, uh,
we had some problems.
But that's behind us.
I just wanna try to help.
You've always been
good to me, Frank.
You know I trust you.
It's just, um, I don't
want any trouble here.
I understand that.
It would really help me out.
Can you help me?
I might, yes.
I still need to ask Fabio.
He is the one who runs the
joint here, you know.
That's who calls the shots.
I'll talk to him.
Okay, thanks.
Clean this spill here. When you are
done, go and clean the bathroom. Okay?
I'm gonna try to, uh, find
you a better mattress, too.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
All right, well, you know,
make yourself at home, dude.
Oh, the toilet's broken
so, if you wanna flush it,
you gotta jiggle the, the bar
and if that, that doesn't work,
you gotta lift the ball inside.
Yeah, no problem.
But I'm serious about this
because the whole thing will...
Will flood if you don't...
All right.
I got it. It's good.
You want a beer?
Here, an ashtray.
You know those guys?
No.
So, uh, how was
first day at the lot?
It was okay.
It's a start though, right?
I'm sure something...
Something better's gonna come up.
These guys don't look familiar to you?
Frank, do me a favor.
Stranger?
Jesus Christ, you scared me, man.
What do you say, Chris!
What are you doing, man?
Whoa!
Hey.
It's about fucking time, man.
How you're doing?
Look at you, man!
Oh, man.
I'm doing all right now.
What about Big Sal?
Oh, man! You won't be seeing
him around here no more.
He bought a bar,
over in Manhattan.
He's doing all right.
I hear he plays poker
with the DA these days.
Can you imagine?
That scumbag.
What about you, Chris?
Any plans?
Keep the judge happy.
Here where it says "print" and then
the timing when she got here...
I'm gonna... I'm also gonna give
you some forms to fill out.
So, please fill these out.
You keep the pen.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
Well, I didn't know
you worked there.
I just wanted to see
how you was doing.
What do you want from
me, huh? He's in jail.
Don't you feel like you fucked
things up enough already?
Hey, wait a second. He is the
one who fucked things up!
Get out of here!
I'm sorry.
You been following me for weeks.
I've seen you.
What do you want, Frank?
Okay.
I been thinking about you a lot.
I been thinking about
what's happened between us.
how it ended,
and I've been worried about you,
and I wanted to see if we
could be friends, okay?
I just wanted to see
if I could be there for you
if you needed me sometime.
That's all I wanted, okay?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Can you be seen with me now?
Can you be seen
with the "colored girl"?
Come on, that's not, I...
You just said it yourself, that was
a long time ago. Yes, yes, yes.
And that things are different now.
Leave me alone.
Don't ever come back here again.
Do you hear me?
What's wrong?
Natalie, what is it?
What's the matter?
$40 short.
It's the second time in 10 days.
I already had to spend $50
out of my own pocket last week.
You need help recounting it?
No.
No, I already counted
three goddamned times. It's gone.
Okay, so there's 40 bucks missing.
It's not the end of the world.
Yeah, maybe not to you.
There you go, end of story.
No, no, no.
It's... It's not about...
End of story.
How're you doing?
A bunch of us are going to dinner.
Do you wanna come?
Sure.
Well, get in.
Okay, just stop holding onto me.
I lost a lung not a leg.
Rachel, honey, stop over
here, and get me some cigarettes.
- Would you, please?
- Cigarettes? Dad, are you crazy?
Please.
Hey, Pop?
Yeah.
Can I ask you something?
Sure!
When I went to your house to get
all the stuff for the hospital,
I found a letter.
Yeah.
Uh, from Mom.
And, you know,
you always told us that
she, she left us and...
That's right.
Well, the letter, you
know, it's to the judge
and she's begging,
begging him for custody
because I was so young when you...
"When you" what?
You was too young "when you..."
When I what?
When I wouldn't let you grow
up in a whorehouse, huh?
Listen, your mother...
Your mother was a bitch!
She was a real bitch.
She beat the shit out of
your brother and sister
on a daily basis with whatever
she had in her hands.
She was a violent drunk, she
was a twisted, fucking slut!
And it was because
of your fucking safety...
It was because of your safety
that I kicked her out.
Your safety. Yours.
So you have... You have no memories
of her! You got none!
You have none, and if you did,
you'd throw up. I promise you.
When she died,
it didn't matter to me,
it didn't matter to... to her.
It didn't matter to any of us.
Well, look, just stay
out of the past, son.
Just stay out of
the God damned past
and... and live
your own life now, okay?
Please.
Please, okay?
Okay. Let's go, honey.
Come on, Ven, Ven, Ven,
Ven, Ven. Come on!
Hiya, pumpkin.
How you doin', huh?
Hi, Daddy.
Hey.
She has an ear ache.
Oh, has she got a fever?
Yeah, but it's going down.
Hey. How are you?
How are you?
Are you all right?
What's it look like?
How are you?
You need anything?
No.
Wait. Look what I got for you.
You like it?
Yes.
There it is.
What?
Is it true?
That they got nothing?
No. I mean yes, it's true, yeah.
You promised me.
You said this wouldn't happen.
And look where we are now.
Babe, babe.
I can't, Anthony.
I can't do it again, okay?
Babe, babe.
They got nothing, all right?
They ain't got shit.
I'm getting outta
here soon. Trust me.
Fucker!
You get out, you don't even call me?
Jesus, Mike.
Where the fuck did you come from?
- Good to see you.
- Hey! Hey!
What're you doin'?
Chitchat?
We're paying you to chitchat? You wanna
chitchat, you go back to prison.
You're paid to work, so get
a fuckin' move on! Okay?
Let's just go back to work, okay?
What the hell is goin' on?
What do you wanna know?
Please, don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
I asked you a question.
You wanna know what I did?
Why I went away?
Yeah.
I got 12 years for killing a guy.
He raped and killed
a woman I was with.
Listen, I spent most
of my fucking youth
in correction houses and
prisons, that's who I am.
You wanna leave, leave.
The few times I've seen my
father, he was behind bars.
But what I hated the most is
that he always lied to me.
I'm not sure I can get past this.
But if you want me to,
you gotta always be honest
and you gotta tell me the truth.
Yep!
Hey, Frank, there's a
woman here to see you.
Oh, about what?
She says it's private.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Hey.
Look, I'm... Uh, I'm sorry
about the other day.
I don't want any trouble.
Why, am I trouble right now?
Please, Vanessa, I can't
really talk right now, okay?
I'm working, all right?
Oh, so you can come to my work
but I can't come to yours?
Don't touch me.
You want some help, Frank?
No.
You wanna go for a drink?
I'll be outside.
You want something to drink?
No. You locked up the wrong guy.
Vanessa, listen to me.
No, you listen to me.
I wanna know one thing.
Is it because of me
that you locked him up?
Is it because of us?
What are you talkin'...
You know exactly
what I'm talking about!
Do you think I could actually
do that even if I wanted to?
Do you have any idea how much
evidence we got against him?
No. You got nothing.
You don't know Anthony.
He's a good man.
Yes, he was trouble but
that's all in the past, okay?
You have no idea what
this man has done for me,
for my mother when she
was sick, for my family!
When he got out,
he promised me that
he was gonna stay clean
for me and for my kid.
I understand.
Some guys,
they don't keep their promises.
You're right, they don't.
Where's the bathroom?
Straight back.
Stop following me!
I'm not following you!
Just stop that!
Don't touch me!
- Just stop... Let me just...
- Don't touch me!
I don't ever wanna
fucking see you again!
You understand that?
You fucking left me...
I... I didn't leave you!
You left me!
I didn't understand myself, I was
stupid, all right? That's all!
Why do you wanna fucking
come back into my life?
You fucking screwed up once,
and now you wanna fucking
take away the one fucking guy
that has been good to me?
I have a kid with him!
You fucking...
You don't fucking understand!
For you, I was like...
Oh yeah, a good fucking deal!
Do you know what it was
like every fucking year?
I fucking hate you.
I hate you.
Hey.
No, no, no!
I wanna be with you.
That's what I know,
And I ain't gonna leave you again.
That's Vincent and Partenza.
They're working with Scarfo,
the one your brother put in the joint.
You know them?
I know him. I don't know them.
Guys from Philly.
They started up three, four years
ago, doing girls and scores.
We've become friendly.
They're prepping a job right now,
except they're having trouble
with some guys tipping the cops.
They need someone reliable, Chris.
I could introduce you.
No.
Understood.
You change your mind, you let me know.
It's your call.
Whoa, Monica, babe.
You look gorgeous!
Hey!
Old habits die hard.
I was in the neighborhood.
Oh, yeah?
You want a drink?
I'm with clients.
Gotta go.
Take it easy.
You okay?
Well, I'm good.
It belongs to the city.
But it's got potential. Just imagine,
hot dogs, french fries, drinks, huh?
I just don't wanna go into
this by myself, Chris.
So what do you say?
You interested?
What, you want us
to go into business together?
Yeah!
I don't got a cent to my name.
We don't need much.
What do we need, huh?
A coat of paint?
Look, the deal is, the park
commissioner has to pick us. Right?
But Martin thinks that anybody
he recommends has a good shot.
Chris, this is something
we could call our own.
Mikey, we just been inside.
It's not our best
attribute, I know that.
But the mayor's looking for good
stories on his work release program.
So the redemption angle works.
Come on, give it a look.
I mean, look at this.
It's pretty much built for us.
I mean fix this up a little,
throw a nail here.
Paint it.
We change the sign, you
know, "Mike, Chris, Chris."
Whatever you want, or we don't
even have to change it.
♪ Girl, I can understand
how it might be
♪ Kinda hard to love
a guy like me
♪ I don't blame you much
for wanting to be free
♪ I just wanted you to know
♪ I love you better
than your own kin did
♪ From the very start
♪ It's my own fault for
what happens to my heart ♪
How you going, you're good?
Yeah, I'm good.
And you?
Good, good.
Couldn't be better.
I love this song.
You know it?
No.
How the fuck would I know it?
Yeah. Hey, look.
I'm, um...
I'm sorry that I... I...
That I stopped coming to visit you.
Just, you know...
You know there was
all the shit that went down
and I knew that...
You having a cop brother was
going to be tough on the inside.
Oh, so you did it for me.
Not one visit
in nine fucking years
but you did it for me?
Fuck you!
Listen to me, I didn't do
anything that I... that I...
Don't worry about it.
Life goes on.
♪ Now you must do
what you gotta do ♪
He's living with you, isn't he?
I'm not sure that's such
a good idea, Frank.
What, is this
your personal opinion,
or is this coming from higher up?
Well your brother has a very loud
reputation, you know, so people talk.
A man's allowed to help
his family, isn't he?
Frank.
I'm not gonna turn my back on him
just because I'm a cop. You know.
He's trying to get his life in order again...
I'm not asking you to do that.
What are you asking me then?
I'm just asking you
to be careful, that's all.
All right? You just do
what you think is right.
But be careful.
Oh, fuck...
Hey, is this the guy?
All right, lose the hat.
Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Mike! How are you?
Mister Herley.
Hey, wow!
Mike you really did it, huh?
Jeez.
Well...
Well, great! Great job!
Now, I know what I said, Mike,
but unfortunately there's nothing
written down, right? So...
How... How can you say that?
I mean, just like that?
I'm sorry.
If it was up to me, you'd get it,
I mean, I gave you my full support.
So what's the problem?
Well, the mayor's been getting
these anonymous letters.
You know, and some of
his people have too,
and, you know, they're
not too happy about it.
Wait, wait. You knew about our records,
so did the commissioner, right?
Yeah, right. But, this guy,
you know, he's gonna make a
stink with the whole city.
So, I mean,
what do you want with me?
You said it was as good as done!
Yeah.
That's what you said! Right?
Right! I did.
And, and I said I'm sorry!
And I am very sorry.
But, you know, we got
an election comin' up
and, the mayor, he's just...
I mean it's just too risky!
Who sent the letters, do you know?
There's no point even telling you.
But if it's any consolation, Mike, that
guy's not gonna get the bid either...
I don't fucking care about that!
Mike.
What I care about is you
keeping your fuckin' word!
You fucking weasel!
Don't touch me.
Do not ever touch me again!
You guys, now you're in real...
Now you're in real trouble!
This is...
Now you're in...
You're in such trouble!
Fucking weasel!
Fuck you!
You are fucked!
If I fuckin' had a gun...
Fuck!
- Prick!
- Fuck!
What is this?
You're fucking serious?
I don't have a choice.
You're coming after me
with a judge now?
You owe me, Chris.
10 years of child support.
I was in fucking jail!
What do you think
you're gonna get outta me?
I hear you're starting a
business with your friend.
Yeah, well that just
went up in smoke.
I know you inside and out, Chris.
You make promises
and then you break 'em.
I'm telling you, I'm not
gonna let this drop,
because there are a lotta things.
Things even money can't undo.
What do you want from me?
What do you expect me to do?
I don't have anything.
You know, my brother has
to lend me a fucking room.
I'm at the end of my fucking
rope, you know that.
Oh, yeah. Poor thing!
Oh, it's been so difficult for you.
Nobody is helping you.
And you wanna change.
Yeah, you wanna be a nice guy now.
Don't give me that shit, right, you
can't change, you're trash to the core.
You shut your fucking mouth!
Go to your room, honey, okay?
Word is you found
yourself a nice young thing.
Why don't you pimp her?
Huh? You out of practice?
Oh, she too good for that, right?
Me, am I too good for that?
You shut your fuckin' mouth!
You wanna know something?
Your new one,
she'll be hooking soon...
See?
I know you real well.
Yeah, I know you too.
You just want that money to
sniff it up your fuckin' nose!
No one's telling you to go on whoring.
So stop judging me!
Hey, what's the matter?
I think it's better
we stop seeing each other.
What did I do?
You didn't do anything.
This fuckin' pisses me off.
It pisses me off to have
to do these shitty jobs.
Pisses me off to see you
at that fucking desk.
And all this being with you like this,
without money, without anything.
It fuckin' pisses me off.
Can't you see I don't give
a shit about any of this?
I mean do you really think
that I care about money?
Is that how you really see me?
Come on, Chris, I just wanna be
with you, that's all that matters.
I don't care
if you bring me stuff.
It's better this way, believe me.
Yeah, give me a beer, please.
A Miller.
What'll you have?
So, the situation here is
we've got two crews
that can't get out.
We're trapped here,
that's the way I see it
and we're going to remain
stuck for very long time.
Did you hear what the police said?
We got some unbelievable news. Information
from monitoring the police scanner...
Fuckin' pigs.
Shut his fuckin' mouth!
He thinks we're all fucking idiots.
Shh!
They wanted to kill those people,
so they fucking killed 'em.
Yeah, shut the TV off Frank.
I'm watching, Pop.
It's fucking disgusting...
Bunch of fuckin' assholes.
Shut the damn thing off!
You know, nobody's
making you watch.
You can go in
and help with dinner.
Oh, you're supporting the cops?
What a fucking surprise.
Frank.
Hey, you don't know what the
fuck you're talking about, okay?
They had bombs inside there, they had
grenades, they came out firing shots.
If the cops fired, that means
they had no other option!
What a fucking joke.
You got no idea what
the SLA is capable of.
Your guys slaughtered them
like fucking animals.
I didn't do anything, A!
And B, shut the fuck up, you don't
know what you're talking about!
Guys, it's Thanksgiving!
You know what?
Take your turkey and shove
it up your ass. I don't give a fuck.
Don't you fucking tell me I don't know what
I'm talking about. Not ever, you hear me?
I've known all about cops
since I was 12 years old.
As far as I'm concerned, they got
exactly what was coming to them.
What, you think they had a choice?
Yeah. That's right, they had a choice.
So did you.
Don't try to make us think that
you're the victim all of a sudden.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't put your fucking hands on me!
Please, please!
Please, my God.
What is the matter with you guys?
Chris, are you crazy, come on!
I mean, we're never together. Now we're
all together we gotta act like animals.
Do I gotta beg you guys?
Please, stop making trouble!
What, what are you talking about?
Me making trouble?
I didn't do shit, Pop!
I didn't mean you.
I'll tell you what... There he goes,
he's got a smile now. I tell you what,
I'm out of this nuthouse. If the department
needs me, tell them to call me at home.
No! Nobody's leaving.
I been cooking all morning.
I mean, what're you guys,
10 years old?
Sit down on the couch,
shut your fucking mouths.
No Dad, I've had it!
Please, have some manners for
once in your life, please!
He's got a fucking
smile on his face.
All right, all right.
Okay?
All right.
You little fucking prick!
Yeah, yeah,
go fuck yourself, convict.
Oh, come on!
Hey, hey, hey!
Dad. Dad, you all right?
Oh, my God.
No, no, I'm okay. I'm okay.
All right.
You're bleeding.
Sit the fuck down.
You two assholes,
sit the fuck down!
Dad, you're all right?
Go fix the turkey.
Okay.
Gimme...
There's three of them.
The two DeStefano brothers
and Heredy...
They got a bar over on
Nassau called Gantry's.
A little neighborhood spot
that's always empty.
They open it up for lunch but
they're always in there real early.
It's ideal.
The address is
on the back of the picture.
I just need to
get back on my feet.
I'm not gonna make a habit of this.
Understood?
Understood.
Any questions?
It's good to have you back.
Listen, Chris, I'm sorry.
Monica is on the street now.
I had to kick her out of here.
She was using.
You know the house rules.
Yo, Chris.
I got something coming.
A helluva job.
You sure you don't
wanna be a part of it?
It's gonna be big!
No, Mike, like this.
Chris...
Chris, Chris.
Chris, I wanna go home.
Chris...
Shut the fuck up and listen to me!
Nothing's gonna happen to us!
Trust me, okay?
Just stay here, and watch.
Someone comes,
you knock three times.
All right? You understand?
Three times!
What are you looking for?
You looking for a friend of yours? Huh?
And I was scared, you
know but the funny thing is
I did it for him.
I just wanted to help him.
I didn't want him to keep getting
in more trouble, you know?
I think about it now,
I feel pretty bad,
'cause maybe that was
the start of it.
And I wasn't the end.
I didn't tell nobody
that story before.
I guess I'm kind of
ashamed of that.
And he always held it against me, too.
He never said nothing,
but he always held it
against me, I know he did.
He was pissed, I was pissed, too.
I was really pissed.
I can remember the first
time that he was in prison,
and he told me if I was
gonna come to visit him
I had to put on...
I had to put on a lot of sweaters so I'd
look bigger because I was so small.
Did you do it?
Of course I did.
I'd have fucking done
anything he told me to.
And I'm standing there, and he's, you
know, he's behind the thing and,
I'm looking at him
and he's clowning around.
I can't remember what
we said to each other.
But I felt... I mean
I felt pity for him but...
I was so pissed 'cause
I fucking idolized that guy.
You know,
he was my hero, you know?
I couldn't understand, you know?
I couldn't understand why he left
me on the outside, you know?
Where's Janie?
I didn't bring her.
Why not?
I left her at my mother's.
What the fuck took you
so long to visit me?
Anthony, I'm... I'm leaving you.
Fuck you.
I made my decision.
You lied to me and I...
I don't trust you and I
can't do this anymore.
Fuckin' bitch.
Look at the way you talk to me!
I will not have you fuck it up while I'm
stuck in this shithole, you hear me?
Fuck you! I wasn't the one
that fucked it up!
You don't care about me,
you don't care about how I
fucking feel, how we feel.
Janie needs a father,
she needs a family.
What, you gonna provide that,
back here?
Even if they let you out, it's
gonna start all over again.
I know it, I know it.
Anthony, I don't
trust you anymore.
No.
Anthony...
Baby, look at me.
I'm sorry.
Stop it, stop it,
you're hurting me.
Ow! You...
You're hurting me.
Stop crying.
Fucking bitch!
Listen to me.
Look at me...
Don't ever, ever forget to bring
Janie again, you hear me?
Ever.
I don't want to see you again.
They fired me.
Fuck 'em.
You'll find a better job.
I don't know.
I made a mistake.
I wasn't thinking straight.
I'm sorry.
Where's the box?
Um...
Open it.
You like it?
I don't know.
It's beautiful.
You wanna get married?
You really hurt me.
And I don't wanna be hurt anymore.
I've had enough troubles
in my life.
All right.
I'm gonna make you so
fucking happy, you'll see.
I'm so sorry we didn't bring
anything, we didn't know.
Oh, I thought she said
she didn't want to but...
Ok, don't even listen to him,
this is so great you're here!
It's the first time Frank's brought
someone home for Christmas,
so, that's a present in itself!
Thank you!
You wanna open it?
Okay, Pop's.
Whoa!
What, this is for me, here?
Yeah.
"Leon," it's me!
Wow!
Frank, Frank.
Jesus.
You get this?
I... Uh, not me!
Me.
Chris, I mean you're nuts.
I got one.
Yeah, but now you can put that one in
your room and watch it in your bed.
Yeah.
Well, it's very special.
Thanks, buddy.
That must've, uh...
Well, thanks!
Oh, that ring is...
Oh, God.
Yeah. Yeah.
He had a good day
at the racetrack, so...
Yeah, are you
cutting the ham, or not?
She really wants her ham!
It looks like we could feed
the entire Israeli army here!
Evening, ma'am.
Do you think we could have a
word with Frank for a moment?
Frank. Frank!
Can you come here a minute?
Frank, I mean you know, really...
All right, all right.
It's not cool.
I'm sorry, Frank,
but we got to bring your
brother in for questioning.
We came to pick him up.
What... What'd he do?
Uh, someone hit
a garage last night.
The one your brother worked.
$5,000 was taken.
And those fuckers killed the dog.
No, he was with me last night.
He must have gave them
the information, I...
I'm sorry, Frank.
Listen, hey guys, you know,
it's Christmas Eve.
Let me bring him in tomorrow.
You don't think we don't know
it's Christmas Eve right now?
You don't think we'd rather
be with our kids right now?
Talk to Connellan.
And get out of the way.
And you don't get involved.
Otherwise we'll haul your ass in, too.
And we've gotta
search your place later.
Are you kidding me?
I look like I'm kidding, Frank?
You want to frisk me too?
Frank.
I'm only gonna tell you once.
Get out of my way. Now.
Please.
My apologies, folks, really.
We, uh, need to talk to you.
What'd I do?
Yeah, we'll talk about it
at the precinct.
Well, I'll tell you
what you talk about,
talk about getting the fuck
out of my house. Get out!
Pop, leave it.
Don't worry about it.
It's Christmas, you
lowlife prick, get out!
Pop!
Baby, baby.
Don't worry.
I gotta get my jacket.
Frankie.
No, he needs to
go talk to 'em, Pop.
What are you lookin' at, asshole?
Get the fuck out, get out!
Right, come on guys!
There's nothing I can do.
You can't go with them?
Nothin' I can do.
Nothing you can do.
Okay. I think that's bullshit.
Bullshit.
Hey, how you doing?
You good?
Jeez! What the fuck happened here?
You want a beer?
I want you to leave.
You kicking me out?
I'm kicking you out and the
sooner the fucking better.
How about right now?
You just fucking used me.
Oh, fuck you!
And while your pals were
cleaning out the safe,
you got your stupid cop little brother
to vouch for you, right? Huh?
I'm too fucking stupid for words.
You can fucking say that again.
This whole thing makes me
fucking sick. Right?
Why would you ever change?
Oh, shut the fuck up!
I don't need a lesson from a cop who's
fucking the wife of the guy he put in jail!
Say that to me again?
Get out!
I don't want to...
I don't want to
ever to see you again.
Well,
you might see me on Friday.
These photos were taken two weeks
ago at Lou Rotella's place.
This is Matthew Bachman,
a safecracker.
He did time with your brother.
We're pretty certain
he was at the garage.
One of the mechanics
noticed his tattoo.
It's a jail gang's marker.
It's exactly the same
as your brother's.
Then why the fuck
did you release him?
The mechanic got scared.
We found his co-worker last night.
Someone left a bullet in his
head as a Christmas present.
I'm gonna be very honest with you.
I'm not thrilled he's
living at your place.
Hey, look at me.
I'd never cover for him.
Not ever.
I know, Frank.
You're a fine officer.
But this looks bad, Frank.
It's too gray for us.
Either your brother moves out
or I'm gonna ask for your shield.
It's your call.
Son of a bitch.
It's the only solution.
And I'd rather that you hear it from
us than read about it in the paper,
or hear about it out in the hall.
You going along with this?
We made the decision together.
I'm sorry.
Best to you in the New Year.
Sorry.
Lieutenant, I got some news.
There's word about a van, parked
at a Warde's truck drop-off point
at a bank in Flatbush,
since about a week.
I've got a dry cleaner across the
street pointing surveillance.
Seems to me that they're prepping
for a score. Maybe a big one.
Alright, let everybody know.
We'll meet up in 10 minutes.
Right.
Frank, I want you in on this one.
Don't go resign on me, all right?
Have I ever let you down?
What makes you so sure
it's gonna happen today?
I just feel it.
You feel it?
We're here 'cause you feel it?
I know it all right.
How's that, you asshole?
Okay, well, we'll see, I mean...
The truck's gonna be here
in a minute.
Nothing's moved for hours.
We'll see.
You understand this is
my car and not yours, right?
Yeah.
All right.
That's ours there.
There it is,
that's our truck, right?
Yeah.
Okay, everybody stand by.
Truck's pulling on the set.
If this is going down, it'll
be on the exit so be ready.
But do not move, I repeat, do
not move until my command.
I'm gonna say that again, whatever
happens, nobody moves until my cue.
That's it.
There's nothin' happening.
All units head back
to the station.
Fuck.
Well, that's that.
Nothin' happened.
Hold on.
It's my fucking brother.
We gotta follow the car.
You sure?
Lieutenant? We need to follow the truck.
Something's coming.
Frank, we wasted
enough fucking time, here.
If they were gonna hit it, they woulda
done it while they were loading.
I wanna see you back in my
office in half an hour.
Follow the car.
Frank, you hear what they were...
Follow the fucking car!
All right, all right.
If you're wrong
you're in deep shit!
Fucking red light.
Don't fucking move!
Don't move.
Car 157 to Central,
emergency message.
We got a 10-30 in progress on 33rd
Street between 2nd and 3rd Avenue.
Suspects are armed
and posing as cops.
What the fuck is that?
Fuck!
Move.
Holy shit!
Frank, what the fuck, Frank!
Hey, what is this,
you just called for backup?
Frank, they're gonna
be here in a minute.
There's a lot of them!
Let's get it goin'!
What the fuck are you lookin' at?
Look the other way!
Hurry up!
Go!
Police! Drop your weapons,
put your hands in the air!
Let's go!
Go, go!
Don't fucking run!
Freeze!
Move over!
Do it!
Don't move! Don't move!
Do not fucking move!
Do not fucking move,
put your hands...
Put the gun down.
Put the fucking gun down!
Chris?
Put the gun down.
Mom, I'm going out!
All right.
The three perps that were hit
could not be identified.
So far, there's
no evidence of prints,
and ballistics is still pending.
We wanna know what you know.
Hey, we were all there.
Come on, Frank, you said,
"That's my brother."
I heard you say it.
Come on.
I had an instinct.
Obviously, I was wrong.
So, Frank,
is there anything
you're not telling us here?
Frank!
Frank.
You know how much
I respect you as a cop,
and as a man,
don't throw
your life away for him.
This is not for me anymore.
And I don't know if it ever was.
Oh, man!
You, uh...
You see your brother,
you talk to him?
No.
Let me go inside...
Do you need anything?
No.
He, uh...
He told me he tried to call you
and come to see you
but you didn't want to.
I got my reasons, Pop.
He's getting married soon,
and, I mean...
He's your brother.
Well, that ain't everything.
I'll let you two deal with it.
What's wrong with us?
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
I'm fucking dying,
that's what's wrong with me.
I...
I know that you think
I was always better, I was...
I favored Chris.
Hey... you...
No, no, no, listen to me.
You know, when...
When your mother left,
you weren't more than
a year and a half.
I was...
...very resentful.
You know, about your mother...
Every time I looked
at you, I... I saw her.
And you can't imagine how much...
how much you look like her.
And she...
She was beautiful.
I know this is, you
know just all wrong,
it's... I mean... it's... It's wrong and
it's a horrible god-awful thing to say
but it took me time...
...not... not to think
of you as a burden.
I mean that doesn't excuse that
I wasn't with you all the time,
but all that,
with all of that,
all of it,
I just...
I just want you to know...
I think that you're
a hell of a good man, Frank.
And...
I don't know why this is so hard
for me to say all the time,
but I guess it was my dad too...
But I love you, son,
I... I love you
and I'm very proud.
I love you and I'm proud.
It's all right, Pop.
I can see it's hard
to be a father.
Yeah.
But...
...not really though.
Not really.
Hey, banana-head, what are
you doin' over there?
Huh? Come on, swings...
So you can be here this afternoon?
Yeah, I'll be here.
Okay, thank you.
I'm sorry, Frank.
About what?
About the fight we had.
You're sorry about
the fight we had?
"You might see me on Friday"?
I don't know what
you're talking about,
but I got something to tell you...
I'm gonna get married in two weeks
and I really want you to be there.
I know you'll come, Frank.
You got a great heart.
I know you'll come.
Congratulations!
How are you? How are you?
It's good to see you.
You look gorgeous!
Of course I do!
You talked to Frank?
Yeah, yeah, he's...
He... he said he'd come.
He was supposed to come by the house.
I think he's been delayed.
Delayed?
Delayed my fucking ass.
Everybody can I have
your attention, a few words...
Hey, just give me a minute!
I was nine years old
when my pop died.
He was a good man.
That was the toughest day
of my life.
I wasn't left
with much, you know, uh,
a mother who was never home,
or who couldn't care less.
No brothers, no sisters...
Nothing.
That day I became part
of Chris's family.
I never went hungry.
Nobody bullied me.
He became my older brother,
the family I never had.
I was just... I was just a kid
three houses down...
And he did that for me.
I gladly call you my friend, even
more important, you're my brother.
And I love you.
So let's raise a glass and wish
these two beautiful people
a wonderful and prosperous
future together...
- Salud!
Oh, look who it is.
You gotta be kidding me.
Get in.
Bye, Bubby!
Bye.
Nice location.
How many of these
did you say you had?
Got two more which should
be finished in a month.
I pay the rent,
take care of the fines.
If you're interested,
you take care of the rest.
You collect the money,
make sure the girls
are working, not fighting,
finding new talent...
As for us, we want nothing to
do with the girls. Understood?
What's in it for me?
You gotta name your price.
Thousand a week.
You don't sell yourself short.
Do you know who's gonna
spend that money?
I'm doing all of this shit
to feed them, remember?
All right.
But your girls are gonna have
to make at least 3,000 a week.
Are you in?
Yeah. But one condition,
I ain't hooking no more.
Long as I get the money,
I don't care.
Now listen, no fucking drugs.
I want a clean house. I hear anything
like that going on with them...
Um...
That's over. I'm clean.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Trust me, this is
just the beginning.
You wanna try it out?
Come on, Chris...
Fuck me.
You're dying to, I know you are.
I just got married.
Yeah...
And?
It'll be your wedding present.
Come on...
Here is one of the rooms.
Room. Bathroom.
Another room.
And another room!
Come!
And when you're done,
you put your take in here.
And no drugs in the house.
We stay clean, am I clear?
You stay here.
Open up!
Holy shit!
Get down here,
you fucking piece of shit!
I wanna see my daughter,
you hear me?
You got my wife, my kid...
Who the fuck do you think I am?
Vanessa!
Come on, Frankie boy.
Is that all you got?
Shut your fucking mouth!
You fucking coward!
You're fucked,
you know that, right?
Shut your mouth!
Watch your head, now...
You fuck!
Listen.
We're not gonna be able
to hold him for too long.
You know that, don't you?
All right.
Take care of yourself.
I think maybe we should
leave town for a little while.
Wait for things to cool down.
He won't cool down.
How ya doin'?
Can I come in?
You're going on a trip?
I... We're gonna...
Go away for a little while
in the morning.
Where'll you go?
Bridgeport.
Oh, Kellner's old place?
Oh, uh, Pop left a box
of old movies for you.
Now listen, Frank.
You didn't come to the wedding.
I been thinking about it,
and that's all right.
But Natalie's pregnant.
And we want you to consider
being godfather to our child.
It's gonna be the best thing
I've ever done in my life.
But I gotta tell you,
if you say no,
I'm gonna be really pissed.
You look really good.
Thanks.
Yeah. It's ironic, you know?
I'm sittin' here in a ratty
old T-shirt and jeans,
and you got on you
your fancy suit,
and probably rolled up
in a nice car.
If you're gonna give me a fucking
lecture, you can forget about it.
See, I can't ever trust you again.
Which is why I'm gonna do it.
I'll be the godfather to your kid.
Yeah, he's been out
a couple days...
Look who we got here!
It's been a while.
How you doin'?
Good night.
What's up, man?
I heard about your
little score, nice job!
Thanks.
How's the family?
Enjoy your night.
You never know
when shit gets ugly, right?
What the fuck is that
supposed to mean?
Your brother, you know...
Now you listen to me,
you fuckin' punk.
You touch a hair
on my brother's head,
and I will fucking kill you.
You understand?
Have you got any tape?
Jesus, what do you wanna do?
I need him to disappear
for a few days.
Don't you think he'll be more than a
little pissed off when you let him go?
Then he'll really go
after your brother.
My brother's leaving
the city tomorrow.
We need to keep him
here until Friday.
Chris, he's gonna come after you.
Let's fucking do him now.
Let me handle this.
Help me tie him up.
Chris!
Yeah...
What the fuck are you doing here?
You think I belong to you?
I don't belong to you, I belong to me.
Get the fuck inside!
I belong to me.
What the fuck did I tell you?
You told your friends I was giving
free ones? You think I'm yours?
Look what this fucker did to me.
I told you I ain't hooking no more!
I did everything you asked me,
I stopped using,
I collect your fucking money!
What did I fucking tell you?
I said you don't come
and talk to me ever!
What the fuck is going
through your mind?
They got cops all over the place!
Are you fuckin' stupid?
Say, baby!
What you doin' walkin'
by yourself tonight?
You wanna go party
with us tonight?
It's cool!
No, no, baby...
Here you pay after you fuck...
Sorry, honey.
You're already fucked.
All right. Let's go.
Hey! Hey! Shit,
I don't know her!
Don't touch me, pigs!
All right. Let's go.
Let's go!
Get off!
Don't touch me!
Come on! Shut up!
You think you're smart?
Right?
I don't think anything.
Yeah?
Well, you're not as smart
as you think you are.
What do you think is
gonna happen to you?
I don't know.
Same as always,
I don't give a fuck anymore.
Yeah, see, this isn't the
same as always, sweetheart.
That little Italian girl,
she told us everything.
Everything.
Now, if you really are
queen of that hive,
well, then, you deserve
what's coming your way.
But if you're just
a working stiff, well,
that's kind of a waste,
don't you think?
All right.
We're going to put you
back inside.
Why don't you think it over for
a little and get back to us?
Oh there is one more thing,
Miss D'Amato.
You are aware that
the Italian girl is a minor?
You didn't know that?
Well, think about that.
Possession of narcotics,
underage girls,
it'd be a long, long time
inside for you,
no question.
Yeah.
That's all.
Have a seat.
Police, open up!
Hey, sport, police, mind if we come in?
No.
Is this your mother's room?
Yeah.
Go back to sleep, kid, we'll
shut the door when we're done.
It'd be better if you'd shut up!
Well, this kid's got balls!
Don't worry we'll be quick.
See?
Yeah.
Frank, it's me. Sorry
I'm calling you so late.
I know how you...
What, you woke me up to apologize?
No, no. I, uh...
It's about your brother.
You... you were right,
he was, there. You...
You... you put a bullet into him.
You still there?
Yeah.
You know,
I don't have to tell you, you
know, me telling you this is...
When?
Uh, first thing in the morning.
Hello?
Was that the phone?
Yeah. It was nobody,
honey, wrong number.
Go back to sleep.
Police!
Chris!
Police! Police!
Don't fucking move!
I just called your place, somebody
picked up but didn't say nothing.
It's the cops.
They're after me.
Chris, Louis is dead.
What?
They found his body in the cellar.
Bobby just called me.
We don't know where Scarfo is.
Look, I want you to give
this to Natalie. All of it.
What about your brother?
Scarfo's all over him,
he wants him bad.
I know.
They left!
What?
They left, they gave me
the keys for the plants.
What's up?
Is he in trouble?
His brother was here about half
hour ago, lookin' for them.
Did you tell him where
they were going?
Yeah. Grand Central. Why?
He's running!
The 8:30 New Haven
line with stops in
Mount Vernon, New Rochelle, Harrison,
Stamford, Norwalk, Westport,
Fairfield and Bridgeport will
be departing on Track 18.
Police! Freeze!
Get on the fuckin' floor now!
On your fuckin' knees, now!
Now! Down now!
Police, freeze!
Get the fuck on the floor.
On the floor, you hear me!
Get down! Get down! Get the fuck down
before I blow your fucking head off!
On the floor, you hear me?
Get down.
Hands up!
Get your fuckin' hands up, now!
Good.
Lay down!
Lay the fuck
down! Now!
Get down!
Lay down! Now!
Lay down!
Now!
Lay the fuck down now!
Down!
Get down!
Lay down!
I'll put one in your fucking skull.
Oh, fuck!
Get down!
Download GOM Player to experience
the highest video and audio quality!