Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Damn, you're done doing that damn bed
? Shut your mouth!
- You make me sick!
- You got, bitch?
- Help me!
- Shut your mouth! Help! Help me!
Damn!
Shut up!
- Whore! Shut up! Shut up!
I told you shut up! No!
- Police! Drop the gun!
- Get back, cop!
- Back off, or I'll blow your head off!
-Help Me
Okay, go ahead!
I do not want anyone is hurt here ..
not hurt you!
- Stay away!
Yes, but let it go!
Die!
Damn!
Okay, thank you gentlemen.
Let's go to the next question.
- Hello! -I Have killed her husband, but the wife
killed you, Turner.
Besides
schools will have to have eyes in the back.
Attention all cadets.
Ready? On your feet!
You ready? Forward!
'm Here to promise and declare....
'm here to promise and declare....
As you defend the US Constitution....
As you emerge US Constitution....
enforcing laws.... New York State....
....
enforcing laws of New York....
and I will faithfully
my duties paid........
Faithfully and I will pay my duties........
as an officer in the Department of the New York City Police
....
as an officer in the Department of Police
New York City....
and will provide the best
skills.
And will provide the best
Ready? Forward!
Be careful, go!
Here, come on, smile! Forward!
Come, come quickly!
There are a lot of people!
Here, here!
Click here!
Love, take my picture with Megane
sun? Come on!
Tata will make a picture of me
and mother!
I can not believe,
you became a cop shit!
Are you the law!
How do you feel?
With a great desire to smoke!
Megane, are very proud of you, I love you
.
And I Tracy, thank you for coming
Come and make this picture as a police
.
- Oh! Oh! Oh! What beautiful uniform!
- Not bad, huh?
- Yes, it's beautiful,
like you! Thanks!
Hi, draga.E mama.Voiam to congratulate you ..
.. And see you tomorrow night,
Sper.Salut.
- Get a little longer.
- No, thanks, Mom.
- Glad to have you here.
- Yeah, it's always nice to be together.
- Yes, it's true.
- Look, I quit.
Say's subway strike, but I have not read ..
No news in newspapers.
All buses were on laundry ..
and bet that yesterday was not found any taxi.
I wanted so much to be
at the ceremony.
- Shut up, Shirley.
- Then my father talking.
- I have nothing to say.
- Frank, do not do this.
- I want to talk.
- About what?
Do not start insulting.
I want a quiet lunch.
My daughter's a fucking cop.
They Turner, how is it?
Do you like action?
- Why what?
- How did you become a cop?
- I wanted since childhood.
- Yeah, me too.
I looked at the guys dressed in blue
and I thought:
'.. Nobody messes with a cop.' '
- Since you were a kid, right?
- I wanted to draw in people!
Kidding?
Bravo, Turner, bravo.
I can not help myself!
Hi, two coffees and one of them
.
- Look, lady, goodbye.
- Thanks.
All the lying, not moving.
You open Cash and give me money.
So you want to carp
here, motherfucker?
One dollar and fifty-seven, agent.
Oh, God!
You think I'm an idiot, huh?
I saw!
'll Kill you if you do what I tell you, motherfucker!
Nobody move, dumb!
Put the money in the bag now!
Nobody moves, I say!
Shut the fuck up! Shut up!
Put your money here, javro!
You Down!
Come on!
I do not play, look!
Do not move either!
I do not play, are seriously
girl sucks!
Give me the money! So!
Put the money in there, come on!
Come on!
Quick! Quick!
You finished timp.Ai least, asshole?
Think I'm a fool,
and do not see, huh?
Stay here, you understand?
I play with life ..
in this place!
are not willing to risk for you!
If you do not sit down, I'll kill
like dogs!
Give me the bag! You want to put a bullet in capu`ala
stupid?
Police! Do not move!
Put the gun down!
Get the interval, love!
Drop the gun!
Look, I came here
I fuck with you, you understand?
I told you to put the gun down now!
Yeah, fuck you!
Oh! God! God!
Turner, what the hell! Lord!
- Good evening, sir. Hello.
- Three to two for the Mets.
To recap:
bullets are your guy.
You say that this man had a gun
but no weapons were found ..
At the crime scene.
Even the cashier says ..
suspect had a gun,
but not sure it was a gun.
Witnesses confirmed that a knife could be.
Chief, I would like to add one thing:
cashier was shocked.
Yes, this is not discussed.
But the fact remains ..
.. As you empty the charger ,.
And IAI head off ..
For one who, believing he had a gun
.
I think in that situation, you reacted
..
In a little exaggerated.
'll Give you another mission,
Turner.Poti agent to leave ..
to sharpen pencils for a while.
- Stanley, look....
- Please, Nick.
... A moment, you will like it!
Look, there is one of Hackensack,
Saturday night .. a bitch
sit in the front seat beside the taxi driver ..
head between his thighs.
Fantastic! taxistul take a dump ..
.. It raises its head and says, what happens?
Has "cock" his mouth.
Man loses blood, but does not want to go anywhere
..
even the hospital because it cunoscut.Ok?
Cabbie's all upset because the car is full of blood.
Whore out a needle and thread:
and you know what?
Stanley, I've sewn "rooster"
opposite!
What the hell to say wife?
Agent Turner in service twenty-four hours ..
.. You head off a poor
And 24 hours later,
is already out of service.
It happened in justified circumstances.
- What are you threatening?
- It looks like a Magnum 44.
- You tried to disarm him?
- It was two meters.
Then how can you say that was a Magnum 44
?
Because they are convinced.
I saw.
- Pot?
- Yes.
Have found no weapons at the scene,
Agent Turner ..
and nothing in the body of the victim.
Know. But I've seen.
It was, I saw him.
- I saw the reflection of metal!
- And then you shot?
- No. Then I pulled the shot!
- He shot him first?
I asked him to throw the pistol to the ground ..
but he did so,
targeted it in my direction.
- How fast?
- What?
Here, put that thing away,
I am el.E well?
Hey, it's just a comb, you see?
You know, Turner?
You're lucky if you resist 36 hours in service.
- Who says so?
Investigator Nicholas Mann, homicide team.
- We shall see!
- Who says that?
- Sit down, sit down!
- Excuse me.
- Hey, Turner's mother.
- What?
Mama!
What are you doing here?
Nothing, I wanted to see you.
I called, but you were not home.
I wanted to say I'm sorry
for last week.
- Want a coffee?
- Yes.
- So that's because if you're working on?
- Yes, mother, you see,
All those people who are dressed like me
have the same job, the same job
.
- Come on, let's go.
- But show that you are good!
Something goes wrong, honey?
You know you want it good.
Something that should not be shown.
Hits you again, Mom?
No.
No?
Okay.
80 I said 80!
I close!
- 60!
- 130! - 50!
40!
190!
40! 40!
30 and 90!
5 today! 5 '
's More, it's more.
- 10 and 90!
- Okay! All right!
- 90.10 and 90!
- It's all right!
Bum!
Enough! Get out, go to another
parte.Haide!
Looking for someone?
None in particular.
- Okay, nu.nimeni.
- I imagined!
- I made a pleasant surprise!
- No, Tracy!
- Give me the mine.Howard!
- Tracy!
Howard, she's Megan!
Megan, this is Howard.
- With pleasure.
- Speak!
- Ciao. Oh, Scuse!
- Vuoi un po 'di sangria, amore?
- Megan?
- Hm, hm.
- You want a beer, you like?
- In regula.Bine!
- So you're his girlfriend Tracy.
- Yes, since we were girls.
Tracy has little buddy.
- Thanks.
- How do you know?
- I am his accountant.
- Do not believe you!
- Yes!
Not look like an accountant.
Well, an accountant
very helpful.
- Thanks.
- Please.
- And you, what do you do?
- I'm a cop.
- Come?
- Indeed!
Jenny, come here.
Do not remove!
- Are you okay? Yes, desigur.De what?
- You look weird.
Like you have eaten something bad.
A police?
Have gun?
- Yes.
- But you're not on duty? No.
Can I ask you a question from civilian to civilian
?
Sure!
're A very attractive woman,
beautiful. Indeed.
Why did you
becoming a cop?
Because I like to give people heads
wall.
's Good,
it was very nice talking to you, but now leave.
Do you have more work to do today.
- Hello! Oh, wait a minute,
Howard, wait a minute!
- Excuse me, what car do you have?
- Honda Civic. Why?
That silver with broken headlight?
- I'm going to exchange
- The reason I noticed
that the headlamp is broken,
stamp is because the car has expired?
Good thing you reminded me
's because the new car?
And tonight I would have taken?
I do not need a ticket
We have taken many fines?
- Howard!
Howard, relax!
Hey, asshole! Are you blind?
Excuse me, sir,
you need help?
Listen, what do you do?
Ehi!
Ehi, what are you doing?
Oh my God!
Calm down! Please!
Stop, please!
Not! No!
Do not tra...
excess of legitimate defense
Turner agent?
I
would advise to take a few days off.
Excuse me, would you tell me
I am suspended?
Until further notice.
One moment.
I'll take that.
Even, and this.
Taxi!
Want to share it with me?
Everything is wet.
- No, thanks.
- But there's no problem!
- Grazie.Signorina, it's here!
- I like to walk in the rain.
Remember what happened
one who wanted to remain in the storm?
Higley!
Please here.
No problem, really.
I take pneumonia.
Where do you want to go? please.
- Ln the middle.
- Okay. Perfect.
- Should it rain!
- Really? - Yes.
But we never take.
- Hello? My name is Eugene.
- Megan. Thank you for picking me up.
- Where are you going?
- Between 17 and L8.
- Ok. - It's in your way?
- No.
No, like they do every day
!
The nicest thing that happened to me
.
- Cute?
- Yes, yes.
I do not like rain,
I prefer winter with snow.
What I like when it snows
, is that the city
becomes very quiet.
Everything seems to stay.
Noise suddenly stops.
And like anything will happen.
And I like snow.
It makes me feel safe.
Safe.
Better not be late.
Well!
want to wait in traffic? Are you hungry?
- It can be done?
- Indeed. Yes, of course.
- Keep the rest. Thanks.
- You sure?
Come on!
Yes, desigur.Sigur.
Thanks.
- Good evening.
- There are two of us.
This way, please.
Maybe we should go elsewhere.
- Hunt does not know what to say!
- Just say no! - Do not want!
Lady!
- Thanks.
- Have a seat.
It's very nice here.
In short, there in the rain,
cold, wet
reminded me of one my cat
And I could not resist.
For what purpose?
Kidding? No one!
Ok, ok,
stop here.
- Do you like champagne?
- Yes very much!
Ok.
For our meeting!
Why do not you talk a little?
Unfortunately, there is not much to say,
am trader. Stock
market, contracts, purchase, sell.
A kind of society you for misanthropes, think.
People who buy now and then betting all
rest will go to hell.
I do not want to talk about it.
Know, the first time I laid eyes on you
It's very unusual for me:
stay here with you tonight
Glad you accepted.
I wants to know you better.
I hope you'll allow me.
Thanks for dinner,
was very good.
I hope we meet again.
There's no problem.
- Goodnight, Eugene.
- Goodnight, Megane.
What are you doing tomorrow night?
- Yes?
- You Megan Turner? - Yes.
We are at the Interior Ministry.
I should follow.
- Can I know why?
- Come with us, please.
Only moment.
Homeless that died last night in the west.
Where
was not too daring, it would be almost silly.
I wish that all crimes be so easy.
Do you have responded to that?
- I have no idea.
- Maybe it coming one.
- Think, Megan. Come on!
There are other Megan Turner in New York?
Yes, Megan Turner Augusta,
eighty-six years old,
living in a hospice in the Bronx.
Check, but I'd say
it's a formality. Not the kind of person
which has its name on a bullet.
I do not see myself writing my
name  bullet.
Every day we learn something new.
Where were you at midnight?
Slept.
Agencies have awakened, Nick!
Okay.
Right, Megan, beautiful girl you
Can you put someone, then
you had a violent reaction. An old fiance
or else. No!
- I have no fiance?
Got a question!
Ok, so it's an acquaintance.
Look, I do not know anyone, I
my mother, my father, my friend,
Tracy and her husband, John.
- And loved?
- I did not!
No chance to be me.
Yes! Could it be Augusta,
eighty-six, or
or insane predilection for name Megan.
I doubt it.
I think there is someone who likes you.
This man knows and you may not know him.
- But you're our only lead.
- Is suspended, remember?
Not anymore!
Nick, I think we need to talk
.
Only accept advice from my boss.
I want to know, even when he goes
pee. Is that clear?
With it, we have more chances
and little risk. Within the limits.
We can do this with a civilian?
Come on, Stan,
give me a hand!
- I take full responsibility?
- Completely.
- With your department! Oh my God!
- Nick! It must be
a way out, right?
The way out?
The way out for you?
Oh my God!
Turner! You.
- What is this? - It's a badge
nominal investigator.
You know nothing, absolutely nothing.
The dangerous as they are.
- Yes, but risking
I not? That's right!
- Thanks.
- Sign here.
Lnvestigator Turner.
I like how it sounds.
- How do you feel?
As someone who returns from hell.
Watch.
What?
At me!
When you!
Okay, what is it?
Why me?
Why you?
It's just a stupid question, I'm sorry.
I'm very happy,
I am very happy to be here.
- Thanks. I'm on the highest peak in the world.
You want to go higher?
Watch!
You know, when you're here
and look down
people look like little dots.
There seem to be worth much.
.... We just me in the world.
Want to join?
Soon.
Soon!
Ok.
I want to know if you decided to give him
slippers.
Shit!
What are you doing here my rifle!
How was dinner?
- Hi!
- Good.
And mine was wonderful!
Tuna salad without bread!
Never buy?
- Nick, his work...
- Yes, works with Exchange
commercially, I know.
And...?
Nice apartment
nice clothes, nice salary.
Your mother would agree.
If you do not understand Turner
every aspect of your life for myself.
Is that clear?
Now you have a secret
Do me a favor.
What should I do?
Expenses.
Hello?
Where?
Give me five minutes.
Sorry! Let me go!
I do not see anything!
Has to do with other crimes?
Come on! Come on! back!
'm Relationships with other victims? Detective!
Can I have a rope,
please? I need a rope.
Guys, it's too crowded.
Try to keep them at bay. Agree?
Megan, come here.
Do you know this man?
Well, look! Gunpowder burns
chest.
He was shot goal.
Now examining the scene.
Apparently a scuffle took place
, his briefcase
's up there.
- The body is here.
So this guy went.
Killer to come,
he turned and hit him.
Why?
Maybe he likes seeing his face.
- May. You could
to reconstruct?
Just in case the projectile.
Rahat.
Go!
Let's clear this place!
- 40!
- 10!
40, I say!
- 30, 90!
- 60 for me!
60 per me!
60!
5 today!
Another heinous crime was discovered
tonight, on the outskirts of the city.
The victim, a man of fifty years
, bank clerk
who returns home after a dinner with friends
.
Investigating authorities and homicide team
directly involved in the investigation.
Police chief said that was formed
a special unit to coordinate their actions
although now there are no other
clues leading to the killer.
What?
Who are you?
Why are you talking to me?
You ..
You are God, Eugene!
are unique, Eugene!
Pray for him as your name
make them afraid.
As the son of Justice will appear and new slaves
want protection
under great wings yours.
You are not alone, Eugene!
Oh, my God!
Stop!
Stop talking to me!
I can not hear you!
I can not hear you! God!
Want to join me?
Hello.
- Nothing?
- No!
For the moment, I have no idea.
Use your right hand.
Wears gloves and leather-soled shoes gate.
Use a very small dagger.
Look further!
Yes
I only six hundred thousand
to watch.
Every minute that passes and you have no idea
Who knows, maybe someone out there
As risking their lives.
Fuck! Give me a moment of peace!
But you think that I do not think about it?
Do not you think, but I am thinking about it
while talking to you at any time from this life
dirty?
What world are you?
Come here!
Oh, excuse me!
No, it's not your fault,
not have to apologize.
- It's a thirty-eight, right?
- Now!
Not!
Eugene, I have to get the gun!
No, leave it there!
Morning,
your face is there
when I open my eyes,
Megan, I think you're the most beautiful woman
I've seen in my life.
Get it!
Take the gun, hold it in your hand
!
Want to get the gun?
Strange it
in hands!
What's the point?
Hold it in your hand
please!
Look!
In so!
Ok!
Bum!
What!
I do not understand
I knew
The first time I saw you.
How?
I finally found my light,
I saw the light in you!
Did you see my light?
La supermarket.
Eugene, you and me
I met at the supermarket.
You've shot without blinking
,
without a little emotion.
I know, I saw you!
You were there?
You only
able to understand
And the gun?
She gave me light!
Oh, God!
Megan,
to see together
this light.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used against you in court
!
Non capisci anchor?
You have the right to an attorney.
If you can not afford
The state will provide a lawyer.
I know you better than you know yourself.
Agent Turner require reinforcements,
1-0-1-3 agent ..
immediate reinforcements, 6-0-1 East 61.
6-0-1, East 61 °.
Apartment
floor fifteen, ten
apartment.
Floor fifteen, ten
And then put me in contact with the investigator
Nick Mann.
Nick Mann!
Do not move!
We are part of the same person, you and me.
If we would know each other better.
And you want while.
Is just beginning between us.
It's just the beginning.
Do not worry!
You look worried,
There is no reason.
We have everything we need to live.
And then, then
death
beginning is interesting
Life  this.
My jacket, my shoes.
What are the facts?
What are you working these days?
Man working at the Stock Exchange,
has an impeccable past.
That does not mean that now is not guilty.
That means, my friend,
as may be something out bine.poate
More if you put a bait agent,
that had even a relationship. This way.
Remove my client handcuffs!
Why not listen before
allegations, Mr. Dawson?
Have you finished?
Have you finished? Can I go?
Law, the law, yes
know the law.
Leave me alone?
I already know the way.
I have performed well here
or even not satisfied me.
He's detective?
'm Detective Megan Turner.
I have ordered the arrest.
And what is the evidence?
Knowledge detective in charge of the investigation.
It finds that Detective
arranged a meeting with the aim of arresting
my client! It's a trap.
And she's an ordinary race.
I think Hunt is responsible for the recent murders
Just think? and put a person in jail
Because "you think"? It's a joke?
No, I, I know.
Good, good!
Where did you find it?
Knows palm read?
Media will be of great value in this episode
.
- My client confessed?
- No!
Found the murder weapon?
- No! Then you shit!
We rely  We are willing to Detective Turner.
And exactly this will happen.
Now I want that my client be released immediately!
And if you see someone in that department
only a few meters away from him,
denunciation, the whole department
police in New York.
And, detective, if only trying to talk ..
with my client, a directing traffic to get to the periphery
for the rest of your days.
Release it!
Come on, Megan, do not do that!
You were with him?
Sefu, it's a personal thing!
Yes, I saw him a few times.
Why did not you tell me this?
Because I thought it was him!
Now you're in good company
because nobody believes it was him!
What makes you so sure?
For saying so! Or, rather,
he not said, but was involved.
He said the first time he saw me
,
when I killed
hot at the supermarket!
He was not there, boss,
among witnesses that damned!
I think it's gone!
Home,
he wanted to see how I held the gun.
Sefu, from what I said, I think it's for
how to say, it represents
Divine hope!
Have to follow him!
No, Nick, you do nothing.
And neither do you.
That man knows us!
If you approach him
I am going to the bottom.
Whole department goes down.
Even the mayor will reach the bottom!
See, if you were married, you could
to do these things!
Yes, but then you could not depend
you.
Look, boil water!
What is Johnny?
Right now he tears your hair out!
He took children out!
Nice!
Nice! Try to stay too!
No, I meant only
You, children,
and John are your life.
Yes!
And you!
I'm glad to be your friend, Tracy.
And I am happy
to be your girlfriend.
Sunday cooking, will make lasagna,
my specialty.
Will and John with children.
Come because I invited
even that guy that you talk!
Tracy, do me one favor, lifetime
Please do not try to put you.
's A good boy!
- Leave me alone, Tracy!
I assure you that is right!
That was that!
Course, that's not right.
Megan!
So, again! Well, continue to breathe
so! Come on!
Easy, easy!
- Goes well!
- Megan, I'm Nick.
Agente Turner!
- Tracy! Oh!
- Poor!
Calm, good.
Oh!
Come on, get up.
Stand up so!
Yes it to me!
Lean on me!
- Are you better?
- Yes, it's better.
Must stop it!
- Yeah, yeah, sure.
- I have to stop, Nick.
Yes, we'll talk.
Now stay calm.
Hurry to the hospital,
may have a head injury.
Slowly.
- Nick, I want to see him dead!
- Yeah, right now, you need to rest!
Wasting time
must stop him!
Not! You have to go to hospital.
Losing time, believe me!
Must stop him!
- Yeah, sure.
- Now!
Okay, let's go!
You look good!
Get up!
Excuse me!
Raise your hands up! I see them!
Come back!
You're beautiful.
I like how you did!
Have you thought of me?
When I think of you,
see your future, moving quickly
through my eyes.
And see you dead!
- What the hell is going on here?
- Why did you do that, Megan?
- What?
- That!
's Dead crying Fuck you!
's All right, enough!
Can I see the warrant?
What is going on here?
You forced door Login
and ransacked without a warrant is a violation
!
- Detective, is history!
- Detective Turner
e eyewitness in a murder trial!
Well, Detective Turner,
tell me what you saw.
I saw this man, as a slew
,
on my best friend, my eyes
.
Dawson, I'm tired of this story
!
Descend the stairs together with her,
He came after me and put the gun back mia.
While she continued to walk, did not see it.
- I tried to warn her!
- Anybody could come back.
How can you say it was me?
Detective, you see the accused face?
I told you that I was attacked from behind!
How can you speak of identification, ha?
Dear God, I know him well
!
But she said she actually did not see his face
Well?
No.
He will have to resign by the end of the day.
And I think she needs help.
Mr. Dawson, I will personally handle your customer
disappear as quickly as the face of the earth.
Dawson will make us trouble in the Department.
Hoyt people can not give us
should know that.
You believe me, Nick?
We have no proof, Megan!
There's nothing substantial.
It is based on feelings,
assumption instinct.
But you believe me, Nick?
Yes, I believe you!
Look, why not take a day off tomorrow?
You need to relax.
If you have to go somewhere, let me
I will provide a car
Department, yeah?
Not want to put you under observation,
do not worry!
But do not trouble!
I mean, you're a police officer,
you should know how to take care of yourself.
Had two children.
Know.
Sorry, Megan.
Mama!
Mama! Sorry for Tracy!
- Ah! Excuse me!
Would you show me? What's in arm, mother?
- None.
- Mom, please!
Do not say anything, Shirley!
You did this?
He had an accident,
fell down the stairs!
Mother, he knew did this?
Tell me! Please tell me!
- Do not answer, Shirley!
- Shut up, Dad! Shut your mouth!
I'm tired of you!
You hit again asshole!
Not have to say anything!
You're under arrest!
Kidding? My daughter arrest me?
Look, that's enough!
Stop, come on, that's enough! !
Get me out of this car
immediately! Do you understand?
And he handcuffs me that I miss
wrists! Come on!
Finish, I am your father!
Wed ashamed of!
Give me one good reason not to arrest you!
- I can not believe!
- Dad!
Why?
I do not know.
I crazy!
If you try it again
We return.
- I'm back.
- Frank!
Hi, Shirley, do you?
Megan, honey,
your friend is here!
Frank, this is Eugene Hunt.
- This is my husband
Frank Turner. Good.
- Mama!
- What, dear?
None.
My mistake. I thought you and I know our
some time.
- No.
Mom, Dad, you can go for a second beyond
The kitchen please?
- Megan have a guest!
I want to exchange two words only with Eugene.
- Only!
- Come Megan we are not children!
There is nothing you can not say
in front of your parents.
- Would you give me your coat?
- No!
I'm a little cold so I prefer to stand, thank you.
And I have the same problem,
I not think it necessary to get it out.
Police force are still employed to find
any trail that leads to the mysterious killer.
- Did you hear?
For some time!
- Sit down!
Always kill killer
With a Magnum 44 whose owner asked
authorities responsible for the investigation,
veto.
- I do not want to watch TV.
- Okay, stop it.
Excuse me
I came here to know a little.
Really I wanted so much to come. True!
Talking to you, is we know a bit!
Lord, Mr. and Mrs. Turner, you are really lucky
to have a daughter Megan.
True!
Megan Soaking is the most beautiful thing in the world.
I did some things I do not have time.
I think the time has come to leave.
But I am here to meet your parents
.
Ok.
Yes, I understand.
Eugene, wait a minute,
not go so hurry!
Yes!
- What? Sit, it seems like you're pretty
rushed to leave.
Yes. It's true, I kinda hurry.
Forgive me!
I hope you do not take this as an act of rudeness.
Ah, no.
Sorry to go so fast.
I'm sure we revedrea.
Yes, I hope so.
It was nice to meet you.
- With pleasure. It's nice to know
Megan's friends.
It's a real surprise.
How about a warrant?
Hoyt tries right now.
But the judge's signature required.
- Dawson
bastard will have to listen. Fuck '!
Megan  Where are you? No do not tell me!
Let me guess!
You Eugene's apartment.
Wait to cool the engine.
Remember
have nothing against it.
So be careful, okay?
What is Nick?
Not at all trust in your people?
I trust, I swear to you Megan!
's Look!
Damn!
Looking for something?
All right!
I got one!
Come on, Eugene!
Get it!
You never know, maybe I'll be
before you head to your flight.
Megan  Do not do it! It's okay
Nick just wanted my gun.
And then?
Then go home to rest.
We have nothing against him, remember!
Gun must be here somewhere.
Will return!
They say it's a good year for coffee.
And you can see that, in
coffee grounds at the bottom of the cup.
Tell me, why did you follow?
After you think you can not, right?
- I wanted to see how you impedance.
- Nonsense!
- I do not say!
- Yes, damn it!
You know what I like in town this?
As you can easily lose
As in a glass of water
believing that swim in the ocean.
Oh, God!
You need to calm down Turner,
must be here.
Look, it's beautiful night!
Ok. E
beautiful night!
What pushed you to become a police
?
Him.
Yes.
It's a job that takes time.
- Yes, it's true.
- I bet your wife does not like.
A hatred.
Ah, I'm sorry.
I do not.
Look!
What are you doing?
Megan, come here, Megan!
Shit!
Go to hell!
God!
Where the hell put the keys?
Stop!
He said here
but is bullshit.
Do you smoke, lady?
Fuck!
Watch.
Watch me.
I want to see you!
I want to see how I look.
I want to see your face
respect .. light ..
and then .. nothing.
You've reached the bottom, man!
10-13! 10-13
an agent needs help!
- Suspect...
- Nick're good?
Yes, yes ,. I'm fine.
Male.... black hair.
It could be anywhere.
If you see someone who looks like he
even remotely
give me a sign!
Megan, I'm going home broken.
So rest.
- I hope you whiskey!
- Yes.
Yes, check all hospitals
suspect is injured.
Yes, it's good.
Chief, will you do me another favor?
Thanks.
Preserve the unity here in front.
I need it.
Almost killed you not.
Yes, indeed!
I did not put you in that situation
.
Megan's wrong.
Passed.
I'm afraid Nick.
I'm afraid.
Damn has a gun!
Go! Come on!
He ran!
Call the ambulance!
Boss! Tell us something!
Please tell us what happened!
E wounded agent, huh?
Megan!
Are you better?
He was.
Yes.
- Now try to rest!
- Nick?
'll Be fine.
I'll be back later.
- What time?
- Almost 5:00.
In a little and the sun will rise.
That makes me sleep a while.
Megan!
Sorry, you come here a minute?
- Can I have a cigarette?
- Of course!
Thanks.
Sure, something bad happened.
Police!
All the earth!
Sit down!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7fkcm
Help other users to choose the best subtitles