Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
All right, easy.
Lousy morning for it.
Mr. Andrew Marsh,
bagged and tagged.
Better him than us.
So what did him in?
Looks like cardiac arrest,
but l'll call you later.
-Mr. Garrett.
-Morning, sir.
l'll be outside.
Sir.
Lieutenant...
-Nice quality.
-Nice ass.
That was the tape in the VCR.
The power was still on.
The sucker had a heart attack
watching his home movies.
What do you need me for?
He was tied up.
l've heard remote, but--
What the hell is this?
That is a nipple clamp.
-How would you know?
-He's from L.A.
l just happen to be
a well-informed individual.
How does this thing work?
Who cares? Bag it.
This is kinky shit.
Harry, take a picture
of these gouges for me.
Looks like she had him
chewing on the wood.
No, it looks more like
she had him handcuffed.
Who found the body?
Secretary came by
to pick up some papers.
Hell of a shock.
Want to talk to her?
She wouldn't leave.
Thought we'd steal the silver.
Can you blame her?
Do you want me to identify her?
lt's Rebecca Carlson.
His girlfriend.
They had a date last night
according to Ms. Braslow.
This is Bob Garrett from
the District Attorney's office.
Ms. Braslow was Mr. Marsh's
secretary for six years.
She killed him.
You've got your first witness.
The Resurrection and the Life
will raise him up in glory.
Then may he see the light
of Your presence, Lord Jesus.
ln the name of the Father,
and of the Son...
and of the Holy Spirit, amen.
Bless this grave...
and send your angel
to watch over it.
Forgive the sins of our brother,
whose body we bury here.
We ask this
through Christ our Lord.
Amen.
Go in peace with Christ.
Thanks be to God.
Miss Carlson?
-l'm sorry l'm late.
-Frank Dulaney?
l look that much like a lawyer?
Who else would speak to me?
His friends think
l shouldn't even be here.
Will you represent me?
There haven't been
any charges filed against you.
But there will be.
You know that.
Do you think l killed him?
That's a question
l never ask my clients.
What matters is whether the
state can prove you killed him.
l loved Andrew.
Why is it so hard
for everybody to believe?
You know why.
You're young and beautiful...
and you were involved
with a wealthy older man.
He wasn't old to me.
l'm sorry l said that.
A big part of my life
has been taken away from me...
and people are saying
it was my fault.
They've taken something good
between two people in love...
and made it dirty.
l didn't kill him.
You believed her?
Actually, l did.
You're a romantic.
Not at all. l just know
bullshit when l hear it...
and this wasn't bullshit.
Sharon, how can you say
she didn't love him...
without having met
either one of them?
He was too old.
He's right.
That's a very narrow
view of love.
lt's what the jury will think.
Did he have any family?
Lots of wives, no kids.
The register broke down again.
lt's the register.
Going to be here a while?
No. We're going home.
l have to lock up tonight.
Why don't you hire a manager?
Because at least
l won't be stealing from myself.
Last time this week?
Want a kiss?
lt's OK. Nobody noticed.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Jamie!
How'd you sneak past me?
l saw some friends.
Those are your friends?
These are my friends.
Can you really
screw someone to death?
No.
Besides, you don't have
to worry about that stuff yet.
Do you?
No.
Because
you are a good-looking guy.
Let's go.
OK, let's go.
The neighbors saw you go
into Marsh's house at 8:30.
She's not denying she was there.
Did you have sex with him?
Yes.
Did you handcuff him to the bed?
Don't tell me it's relevant,
Bobby.
You didn't have to answer that.
No, but we appreciate
her honesty and cooperation.
-Bullshit.
-When did you leave?
Around midnight, l suppose.
lf l had known
it was going to matter...
l would've paid more attention.
Well, it's true, Frank.
There's nothing wrong
with saying that.
Miss Carlson,
do you use cocaine?
Cocaine use is illegal
in the state of Oregon.
l've never used it in Oregon.
Can we move on, please?
Did Mr. Marsh use cocaine?
Never.
The toxicology tests
came back positive for cocaine.
Then it's false positive,
because we never did drugs.
Not even poppers?
She just said
they didn't use drugs.
Amyl nitrate is often available
to heart patients.
Were you aware of
Mr. Marsh's heart condition?
He had arrhythmia.
That's not a heart condition.
Mr. Marsh had an advanced case
of heart disease.
He said it wasn't serious.
Why would he lie to you
about it?
l never know why men lie.
They just do.
Men lie.
Would you describe yourself
as a dominatrix?
Back off of this, Bob.
-A sadomasochist?
-That's it.
lnterview's over. Let's go.
You want to charge her?
Go ahead.
Otherwise, you can reach
Miss Carlson through my office.
Fine.
But l don't think
that'll be necessary.
-Reese.
-Right.
Rebecca Carlson...
you're under arrest
for the murder of Andrew Marsh.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you...
in a court of law.
Rebecca, l'll have you out
as fast as l can.
...one will be appointed
to you by the state.
Trying to get your name
on the front page?
You fucking sandbagged me!
Jesus, Frank,
don't take it personal.
Spending too much time with
criminals affects your judgment.
-You don't have probable cause.
-Sure, l do.
Marsh's will leaves
all $8 million to your client...
which would've
given even me motive...
and she admits to being there
the night of the murder.
You don't know it was homicide.
The method's self-explanatory.
What are you going to do?
Tag the body
as the murder weapon?
Exhibit ''A''?
lt's not a crime
to be a great lay.
Sure. l'd have
to have myself indicted.
This case is ridiculous.
Drop the charges,
save the state some money.
You can't convict.
Cocaine slipped to a rich old
man dying of heart disease?
l think l can make that case.
Not without intent.
She'll get manslaughter.
Tell your client 20 years.
Seven, if she behaves.
There they are.
Did you do it, Miss Carlson?
Get me out of here.
Bobby Garrett's going to stage
a big ugly trial.
Does he really expect me
to plead guilty...
to spare myself
the embarrassment?
l'm not guilty.
l'm not going to plead guilty.
l'd feel better
if you weren't in the will.
Andrew put me in his will?
Don't start jerking me around.
You're the primary beneficiary.
How much?
Wouldn't you ask?
Come on, how much?
Eight million, give or take.
That's a hell of a motive.
l know how Bobby works.
He's going to build his case
on your sex life.
He'll drag out every dirty
little thing you did.
lt wasn't dirty.
Not to you. Not to Andrew.
But people here have very
conservative views about sex.
No, they don't.
They just don't talk about it.
They're such hypocrites.
Those hypocrites will be
sitting in the jury box...
listening to Garrett say how
you led Andrew into perversion.
l didn't have
to lead him anywhere.
Andrew knew
exactly what he wanted.
All we did was make love.
ln handcuffs.
lt was different,
but it was still making love.
Have you ever seen animals
make love, Frank?
lt's intense.
lt's violent.
But they never
really hurt each other.
We're not animals.
Yes, we are.
You're great
when you get a big case.
How about the rest of the time?
You know what l mean.
l have to take a shower.
You don't get as rich as Marsh
by being a nice guy.
l want you to find out
who he fucked over--
business, personal, social--
anyone who might want him dead.
l'm hitting all the dealers...
with a list of
their nearest and dearest.
Maybe we'll get lucky
and come up with a user.
Joanne Braslow is here.
Garrett brought doughnuts.
The man's considerate.
But he always eats them all.
lt wasn't normal.
They didn't have normal sex.
How do you know
what kind of sex they had?
l wasn't peeping
through the keyhole...
if that's
what you're implying.
l would go to the house to
pick up and drop off papers...
and l would find
their little toys all over.
Would you characterize...
your feelings toward
my client as negative?
l don't have much sympathy
for drug users.
Do you have personal knowledge
that she used drugs?
l personally saw her
shovel the stuff up her nose.
ls that good enough?
ln front of a secretary?
l was at the house one morning.
l thought
she was still upstairs with him.
l went into the powder room...
and she was spooning coke
from a little vial.
What did she say
when she saw you?
She was too busy to notice.
Did you tell your boss
what you had seen?
-No.
-And why not?
l wanted to keep my job.
That didn't include
telling him...
his girlfriend
was a cokehead slut.
Frank...
take the last doughnut.
You fucking lied to me.
You lied on tape.
You were asked
a direct question--
''Do you use cocaine?''
And l said no.
Now they've
got an eyewitness...
that can testify not only
do you use cocaine...
but you used cocaine
in Marsh's house.
Joanne's lying.
l didn't say it was Joanne.
Who else would have been
in the house?
Do you know the expression
''smoking gun''?
She was in love with him.
Don't you see that?
Andrew Marsh must've been
a goddamn lovable guy.
Everybody loved him !
l haven't touched coke
since l was 17.
She makes a good witness.
l want you to meet somebody.
lt's right over here.
Dr. Novaro?
Ah, Miss Carlson.
l've been waiting for you.
Sorry l'm late.
This is Frank Dulaney.
He's my lawyer.
-Could you give me my medicine?
-Certainly.
There you are.
Go ahead.
You got to be kidding.
lnvestigate.
What the hell is it?
Chinese peony roots.
What's it used for?
-lt's an aspirin substitute.
-Tell him why.
She suffers from dysmenorrhea.
Cramps.
Miss Carlson,
l'm ready whenever you are.
Thank you.
You're supposed
to be on my side, Frank.
Could've at least given me
the benefit of the doubt.
You're right. l'm sorry.
Do you mind
waiting 15 minutes?
Not at all.
Look around.
Just a little pain
in the lumbar.
Here, pussy-puss.
Hello, kitty.
Such a beautiful kitty.
ls it still raining?
Can you drive me home?
Sure. l'll give you a ride home.
l've never been in one of these.
Now's your chance.
Come in.
lt's a bad idea.
Why?
l'm your lawyer.
lt doesn't look good.
Nobody's looking.
Good night, Rebecca.
Are you scared?
Not if you tell me
l shouldn't be.
We're going to kick their ass.
All rise.
Superior Court for
the county of Multnomah...
is now in session.
The Honorable Judge
Mabel Burnham presiding.
l can't change the titillating
nature of this trial...
but if l had wanted
to work in a circus...
l would've learned
how to ride a trapeze...
so l will not put up
with any performances...
by counsel or by the gallery.
Are the people ready to proceed,
Mr. Garrett?
Yes, Your Honor.
Andrew Marsh made
what turned out to be...
a fatal mistake.
He fell in love.
He fell in love...
with a ruthless,
calculating woman...
who went after an elderly man
with a bad heart...
and a big bank account.
You all can see the defendant,
Rebecca Carlson...
but as this trial proceeds...
you will see
she's not only the defendant...
she is the murder weapon itself.
lf l hit you...
and you die...
l am the cause of your death...
but can l be called a weapon?
The answer is yes...
and what a deadly weapon
Rebecca Carlson made.
The state will prove
that she seduced Andrew Marsh...
and manipulated
his affections...
until he rewrote his will,
leaving her $8 million...
that she insisted on
increasingly strenuous sex...
knowing he had
a severe heart condition...
and when that didn't
work fast enough for her...
she secretly doped him
with cocaine.
His heart couldn't take
the combination...
and she got what she wanted.
She is a beautiful woman...
but when this trial is over...
you will see her no differently
than a gun or a knife...
or any other instrument
used as a weapon.
She's a killer...
and the worst kind--
a killer who disguised herself
as a loving partner.
Mr. Dulaney.
Ladies and gentlemen...
you were told
during jury selection...
that the testimony
in this trial...
would be sexually explicit...
and you may find it offensive.
You may even be disgusted
by what you hear.
But l want you to remember
that Rebecca Carlson...
is not on trial
for her sexual tastes.
She is being tried for murder...
and to charge her
with murder is ludicrous.
The state would like you
to believe...
that she somehow fornicated
Andrew Marsh to death.
But the state's case
is built on fantasy, not fact.
And the facts, as they are...
are entirely circumstantial.
lt's not a crime
to be a beautiful woman.
lt's not a crime to fall in love
with an older man.
This case should have never
come to trial.
But since it has...
l know you'll listen
to the testimony objectively.
And when you hear
the evidence objectively...
you will acquit Rebecca Carlson
of the charges against her.
Dr. McCurdy,
did you find any indication...
that Mr. Marsh used cocaine
on a regular basis?
No. His nasal membranes
were way too smooth...
for even occasional use.
Were you able to determine
how he ingested this drug?
A bottle of nasal spray
found next to the bed...
was filled with a solution
of water and cocaine.
The victim had a head cold
at the time of his death.
l believe he was drugged
without his knowledge.
Objection--
lack of foundation.
The witness is speculating.
Motion to strike the testimony.
So ordered.
The jury should disregard
the witness' comment.
Was this the spray you found,
Doctor?
Yes, that's it.
Entered as People's Exhibit ''A.''
Now, Dr. McCurdy,
what would cocaine do...
to someone
in Mr. Marsh's condition?
lt would accelerate
his heartbeat.
And if he were having sex...
while under the influence
of such a stimulant?
lt would be the same
as shooting a loaded gun at him.
Now, you said
in your autopsy report...
that Mr. Marsh was restrained
at the time of his death.
Can you explain that, please?
From the marks on
his wrists and the bedstead...
l believe that the victim
was handcuffed.
At the time of his death?
Yes. The bruising and friction
was quite extensive.
Thank you, Dr. McCurdy.
Your witness.
Dr. McCurdy, you testified
that in your opinion...
Mr. Marsh suffered
his fatal heart attack...
while he was restrained.
Yes, sir.
And your evidence for this...
is the marks on his wrist,
am l right?
You are correct.
Now, couldn't those
same marks have been made...
while he was flailing about
in the throes of sexual ecstasy?
l suppose.
Did you find any older marks...
indicating
the use of restraints?
Just on his ankles.
Where they wouldn't
show in public.
Objection--counsel's
drawing his own conclusion.
Sustained.
You know better, Counsel.
Dr. McCurdy,
can you medically say...
that Mr. Marsh
didn't decide to get high?
lt seems very unlikely that
a man in his circumstances--
Dr. McCurdy, are you
a licensed psychiatrist?
Objection--argumentative.
Sustained.
How did you reach
your conclusion...
about what Mr. Marsh
would or wouldn't do?
Common sense.
Did you find any evidence
of that in the autopsy?
Do you know for a fact that
Mr. Marsh had any common sense?
You just testified
he liked unpleasant things.
Your Honor.
No further questions.
lt's going to be a long trial
for you, Counselor...
if l have to start warning you
on the first day.
Where do you work, Dr. Paley?
l am an emergency room
physician...
at Memorial Hospital.
Were you on duty the night
of February 5th of this year?
l was the admitting physician.
-Did you admit Andrew Marsh?
-Yes, l did.
What was the reason?
Cocaine poisoning.
Did Mr. Marsh discuss
the circumstances with you?
Yes, he did.
l read my notes again
before l came to be accurate.
According to my notes,
the patient told me...
that it was the first time
he tried cocaine...
and it was going to be the last.
Would you describe
his condition, please?
He presented
a galaxy of symptoms.
Hyperpyrexia--
which is a high fever...
associated with
cocaine intoxication--
severely elevated
blood pressure...
arrhythmia,
shortness of breath.
And while l was
examining the patient...
he experienced
status epilepticus.
ls it common to have
so many symptoms occur...
in cases
of cocaine poisoning?
This patient
was particularly sensitive.
l thought he was lucky
to go home alive.
Did you tell him that,
Dr. Paley?
l told him if he ever
tried cocaine again...
he would be committing suicide.
Your witness.
No questions for
this witness, Your Honor.
Did you see Mr. Marsh
the day before he died?
How did he look?
He was pale and sweating.
Did you talk about Miss Carlson?
And what did he say?
That he was worried.
l was worried.
He said that
if she kept it up...
she was going to kill him...
his heart couldn't take it.
Thank you. No more questions.
Miss Braslow, this strikes me
as an intimate conversation...
for a boss to have
with his secretary.
Did you often
discuss his love life?
We had
a professional relationship...
but l had been
his secretary for six years.
He liked to talk to me.
Did he also mention to you...
that Rebecca was thinking
about moving back to Chicago?
Yes, he mentioned it.
So, the woman that
he loved passionately...
was thinking about leaving.
Couldn't that have caused...
the stress and anxiety
you observed?
Objection--
calls for rank speculation!
Counsel for the prosecution
has already used this witness...
to establish the state of mind
of the deceased.
He opened the can, Your Honor.
And l do see worms crawling
all around you, Mr. Garrett.
You can't have it both ways.
Objection overruled.
Answer the question,
Miss Braslow.
l suppose it's possible.
Now, you testified
that you saw Rebecca...
inhaling cocaine
in the bathroom.
How do you know it was cocaine?
lt was white powder.
Were you ever a patient...
at the Mount Hood
Substance Abuse Center?
Objection!
Your Honor, Miss Braslow's
medical history--
Your Honor, the prosecution
has introduced cocaine...
as one of the contributing
causes of death.
This is a reasonable
line of questioning.
l'll allow it.
Weren't you a patient...
at the Mount Hood
Substance Abuse Center...
from January 5th
to February 5th two years ago?
Yes.
What were you being treated for?
Substance and alcohol abuse.
And was that substance cocaine?
Was that substance cocaine?
Yes.
And didn't you supply
your boss Mr. Marsh...
with the cocaine
that sent him to the hospital...
with cocaine poisoning
this year?
Your Honor,
l have in my hand...
a copy of the admissions report.
The square right here
is designated...
for the signature
of the responsible party...
the person who brought him
into the hospital.
Would you read
that name out loud, please?
the name out loud, please?
Joanne Braslow. But l--
No further questions.
Your Honor,
l submit Defense Exhibit ''A.''
For your files.
Did you always
want to be a lawyer?
lt was a fallback.
l wanted to be
a pro hockey player.
What happened?
l broke my ankle skating.
l was showing off.
How old were you?
Seven.
When l was a kid,
l liked to steal strawberries.
l'd sneak into
the neighbor's yard.
l remember they had a big fence.
l'd always scrape my knees
climbing over it.
On the other side,
they had these wild rose bushes.
The thorns
would dig into my legs...
and cut my thighs
when l slid down.
But the strawberries
always tasted so sweet.
Because of how much
it hurt to get them.
When you first met Andrew...
how did you know
that he was like you?
l was at a party...
and there was
a huge crowd of people...
but we just saw each other,
and we knew.
Just like that?
Look around.
You want me to look around
and tell you...
if someone here
has the same taste that l do?
That's right.
All right. Who?
l'm not going to tell you.
You're not going to tell me?
No, l'm not going to tell you.
Why not?
Because he doesn't know it yet.
Yes, it would be nice.
What would?
You and l making love.
ls that what you think
l was thinking?
There's nothing wrong
with admitting you want me.
You take a lot for granted.
Frank...go home.
Thanks for dinner.
Good night.
My way.
Are you scared?
No.
Would you see
if Michael's up yet?
The people would like to recall
Dr. Alan Paley to the stand.
Dr. Paley,
you're still under oath here.
Take it seriously.
Do you know Rebecca Carlson?
Yes.
Did you, in fact,
date Miss Carlson?
Yes, we dated.
Keep your rude mouths shut
or get out of my courtroom.
This is the only time
l'll ask nicely.
Proceed, Mr. Garrett.
Did you ever discuss...
anything about your patient,
Mr. Marsh, with her?
His picture
was on the social page...
and l mentioned
that l'd treated him.
What was her reaction?
She was fascinated.
Did she ask you anything
in particular about him?
She wanted to know...
whether cocaine would kill him
if he tried it again.
And what did you say?
l told her it would be
a Russian roulette.
Your witness.
Dr. Paley,
why didn't you mention...
your relationship
with Rebecca earlier?
Nobody asked me.
Did you have
sexual relations with her?
Objection--irrelevant.
Your Honor,
if you'll allow some latitude...
l can establish the relevance.
You'd better.
Objection overruled.
The witness is directed
to answer the question.
No.
No, you did not have
sexual relations?
No, we didn't.
Because she refused
to have sex with you.
Objection--Your Honor...
the counsel is trying
to manufacture--
Get up here, both of you!
Mr. Dulaney,
if you're just bottom-feeding...
you're going to choke
on the mud.
l'm working toward
a specific point, Your Honor.
Work fast.
l'm getting tired of seeing you
this close to me.
Objection overruled.
Dr. Paley, do you remember
your last date...
with Rebecca at
the Cat and Fiddle restaurant?
lt wasn't that memorable.
Well, do you remember...
trying to force yourself on her
in the parking lot?
Objection!
l can bring in
the parking attendant...
and two customers to refresh
your memory if l have to.
l didn't hear the reason for
your objection, Mr. Garrett.
Wasn't that the last time
you saw Rebecca...
until appearing in court,
Dr. Paley?
l don't remember
the last time l saw her.
ln fact,
didn't you attempt...
to blackmail her
into seeing you again...
by threatening
to falsely testify against her?
No. You're crazy.
Your Honor, l have a tape...
from Rebecca's answering machine
l'd like to play.
Objection--we don't know
where this tape is from...
or who made it,
or under what circumstance.
May l approach?
l have reports from
two independent audio labs...
that Mr. Garrett himself
has used to verify evidence...
in other trials.
They both conclude
that the voice on the tape...
was recorded over the phone,
with no tampering.
l'll allow it.
l know you're there.
Pick up the phone, god damn it.
You think l won't do it?
l can put you away, Rebecca,
for the rest of your life.
You'd better call me...
or you're fucked
one way or the other.
What did you mean, Dr. Paley?
You never told her
about Andrew Marsh, did you?
Yes, l did.
She asked me, and l told her.
Perjury is
a criminal charge, Doctor!
l am not lying.
No further questions.
You were brilliant.
l didn't break him all the way.
You burned him down.
-Gabe, hit P3.
-You got it.
See you tomorrow.
-OK.
-Bye.
Could somebody hit P4, please?
Thank you.
Let's go.
Somebody's going to see us.
Come on.
The people call Jeffrey Roston.
Do you know him?
May l approach?
Your Honor, this witness
has never been mentioned...
by the prosecution.
Our investigators didn't
contact Mr. Roston...
until yesterday afternoon
in New York.
What took so long?
He just came home from
an extended vacation.
All right. l'm going
to allow the testimony.
That's it, Counselor.
Take a seat.
Mr. Roston,
what was your relationship...
with Miss Carlson?
We were lovers.
How long were you together?
For about a year.
How would you describe
your sex life with her?
lt was...very intense.
l know this is very personal...
but l'm going to ask you
to be more specific.
She was always trying...
to get me
more and more worked up.
By what means?
l couldn't do everything
she wanted in my condition.
What condition is that?
l had a bad heart.
What happened next?
l had bypass surgery.
How are you now?
l'm fine.
My doctor says
l can live to be a very old man.
How did your relationship
with the defendant...
progress after the surgery?
lt just ground to a sudden halt.
She left me.
Why did she say she was leaving?
She didn't. She just left.
Why do you think she left you?
Objection--question
calls for a conclusion...
on the part of the witness.
Objection sustained.
When you say
your sexual relations...
with Miss Carlson
were intense...
in what way?
lt was as if she were trying
to push me...
as far as she could.
Can you give the court
an example?
Sex was a game to her.
She got off on the control.
She always used to tell me
it had to be her way.
A few nights before my bypass,
l woke up...
and she'd tied me to the bed.
With handcuffs?
No...
with my own belt.
And what did she say?
Mr. Roston, l know
this is difficult for you...
but it is important.
Please tell the court.
She said
she was going to fuck me...
like l'd never
been fucked before.
Bailiff, clear the courtroom.
Everyone except the reporters.
After she tied you up,
Mr. Roston...
what did she do next?
She started...
masturbating...
and telling me how much
she wanted me inside her.
lt drove me crazy.
Did your heart
start to bother you?
Yeah.
We were making love...
and she was on top of me.
And every time l got close...
she'd stop.
And l couldn't take it.
l couldn't breathe.
l was suffocating.
l begged her.
l really thought
that l was about to die.
Did you change your will...
while you were involved
with Miss Carlson?
Yes.
And who was
the primary beneficiary?
She was.
l was very much in love
with her.
And l was a fool.
Thank you, Mr. Roston.
No further questions.
Counsel.
No questions.
l can explain everything.
You're a little late.
l needed to know
before he testified!
Why the fuck didn't you warn me?
You need to hear about every man
l ever had sex with?
Just the ones with bad hearts
who put you in their wills!
You think l killed Andrew?
So does everyone
in that courtroom !
You made me
look like shit in there!
You are not on trial!
The hell l'm not!
l must've been out of my mind
to get involved with you.
To make love to me?
Yes.
But l'm not going
to compound my mistakes.
You're my client. That's it.
l don't want anything
to do with you beyond that.
Just like that?
Like l don't have any feelings?
Hey, l'm not your type.
l'm too young and healthy.
That's not fair, Frank.
No...but it's accurate.
Fuck you, too.
Hi.
Where's Michael?
l took him over to Kevin's
to spend the night.
Why didn't you tell me?
l could've stayed at the office.
l got a shitload of work.
You mean you could've screwed
your client.
That's paranoid.
Oh, man.
Fine.
Go away!
Talk to me.
People see your car
down by the river...
in front of
her goddamn houseboat.
lt gets back to me, Frank!
She's my client.
l'm allowed to have
conferences with my client.
Why can't you have them
in your office?
l can't believe you listen
to this bullshit gossip.
l talked to her!
What?
She called here tonight
looking for you.
What did she say?
She didn't
have to say anything.
l could hear it in her voice.
ln the way
that she said your name.
You're making this up.
What did she do to you, Frank?
How did you get
those marks on your chest?
What are they?
What are they, bites?
What happened to your back?
l thought we were happy.
l thought we were a family.
l trusted you.
lt has nothing to do with you.
You son of a bitch.
How dare you stand there
and say that to me?
l love you. You're my wife.
Go pack some things.
l don't want to see you
when l get home.
Please, Sharon.
l don't want to lose you.
Then you shouldn't
have fucked her.
What the hell
did you say to my wife?
Nothing. l asked if you were
there and you weren't.
Why did you call?
l wanted to know
if l still had a lawyer.
You're such a liar!
What do you think, Frank...
l called to tell her
all the nasty details?
Maybe l gave her some advice.
Maybe l called to reassure her
that it was over between us.
Maybe that's what l said.
Gets easier, doesn't it, Frank?
Let's play another game.
You fuck.
Frank!
Frank, get up!
Conference room !
Come on, hurry!
Now, this guy was really
into filming this shit.
He could open up
his own video store.
How does this help us?
Wait. Just watch this.
l would've missed this, too,
but the phone rang.
l let the tape play
while l talked.
Garrett thought
the show was over.
This isn't a blank tape.
lt's been erased,
just not quite all of it.
This was
during his artsy phase...
before he went back
to using the tripod.
''We had a professional
relationship.''
You're embarrassing me.
The court
recalls Joanne Braslow.
Miss Braslow, how much
did you stand to inherit...
before Mr. Marsh modified
his will in Rebecca's favor?
$250,000.
And according
to his final will?
$10,000,
which is still a large amount...
and l'm very grateful to him
for remembering me at all.
After all
your years of service...
it doesn't seem like a lot.
l'm not greedy.
No. ln fact, you're a saint.
He cut you out of his will...
he dumped you
for a younger woman...
and you still say
kind things about the man.
Objection--counsel's
arguing with the witness.
Move to strike, Your Honor.
l'll sustain it.
Strike counsel's remarks.
Joanne, you have to start
telling the truth now.
Weren't you a very personal
friend of Andrew Marsh?
What do you mean?
-Weren't you lovers?
-No.
Do l have to enter
into evidence a videotape...
that Andrew made of you...
that indicates
how very close you were?
We dated.
Until he met Rebecca?
Yes.
Did you love him?
Of course l did.
Didn't you think
it was cruel of him...
to confide in you
about Rebecca...
after he'd broken up
with you?
Objection--the testimony
has no relevance...
to the issues in this trial.
l'll withdraw the question.
Were you hurt?
What do you think?
l was crushed.
But l knew it wouldn't last.
You expected him to come back
to you after it was over?
Men don't marry women like her.
Didn't he tell you
he asked Rebecca to marry him?
She turned him down.
She'd already gotten
everything she wanted.
But you didn't?
Objection--counsel's
putting the witness on trial.
l loved him.
l never would have hurt him.
Even if he asked?
Your Honor?
That's enough, Mr. Dulaney.
Objection sustained.
Strike Mr. Dulaney's question.
Was that your entire bag
of tricks, Counselor...
or do you have
another line of questioning?
You testified that you ran
errands for Andrew Marsh.
Such as going to the drugstore?
Buying nasal spray for him
because he had a cold?
You signed a house charge
for nasal spray on April 8th...
the date
of Andrew Marsh's death.
l'd like to introduce...
the receipt
from Montclair Pharmacy...
as exhibit ''H.''
That was the bottle
used to kill him.
There was no other nasal spray
found in the house.
ls it true that
you put in the cocaine...
because you were jealous?
Because he cut you
out of his will?
Because you have
a cocaine habit to feed?
You're out of line, Counselor.
Strike his remarks.
l don't think l want to answer
any more questions...
without an attorney.
She killed him.
She set me up
to take the fall...
and she almost got away with it.
You know what bothers me?
Why did she charge a three buck
bottle of nasal spray...
that could be
traced back to her...
if she'd planned
to kill him with it?
l don't know.
Let Garrett figure that out.
Maybe it was
a crime of opportunity.
Maybe she's just stupid.
You mean maybe l did it.
Maybe you did.
lf the evidence
hasn't convinced you...
how the hell is it supposed
to convince the jury?
They can't wait to convict me.
All you need
is a reasonable doubt.
But l know how their minds work.
The women hate me.
They think l'm a whore.
And the men see
a cold, heartless bitch...
they can pay back
for every chick...
that's ever
blown them off in a bar.
You have an inflated opinion
of yourself.
l have to testify.
-No.
-Frank!
They're going to convict me...
if l don't tell
my side of the story.
The only reason l'd ever let
a client take the stand...
is if the case
was going so badly...
there wasn't any other choice.
The difference is
your clients are usually guilty.
You told me that.
No. l said
they usually did it...
which is different
than being guilty as charged.
l'm not going to let you
fuck up my case.
You owe me
the chance to explain, Frank.
Wish me luck?
The defense calls
Rebecca Carlson to the stand.
You swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth...
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
l do.
l'd like you to recount,
as you remember...
the events on the night
of April 8th.
We came home from dinner early.
And Andrew still had a cold...
so l thought l'd put him to bed
and go home.
But you didn't go home,
did you?
No. He wanted to make love.
And that made me want to.
He was a very physical man.
Would you say you loved him?
Very much.
Why didn't you marry him?
Because his marriages
never lasted.
l want it to last.
Rebecca, you heard
the forensic testimony...
about the use of handcuffs.
What were they doing
in the house?
Andrew bought them
for Valentine's Day.
For you--
For you to use on him
while you made love?
Yes. He liked that.
He was always in charge
in his life and his work.
ln bed, he liked to have
somebody else in charge.
lt was a game we played.
Watch yourselves, or
l'll clear this courtroom again.
Rebecca, did Andrew
indicate to you...
that he was having
any problems at all...
like shortness of breath...
while you were
making love that night?
No. He was fine.
And after you finished
making love...
what did you do?
l kissed him good night,
and l went home.
When did you find out
he was dead?
Not until the next day.
And when did you find out...
you were a beneficiary
of Andrew's will?
When you told me.
Your witness.
l'm less interested
in your relationship...
with Andrew Marsh,
the nature of which...
you've made abundantly clear...
than l am
in your relationships...
with Jeffrey Roston
and Dr. Alan Paley.
How long after you stopped
dating Dr. Paley...
did you start dating
his patient Mr. Marsh?
lt must have been
about four months.
Four months in which you tried
to meet your victim...
at galleries
and museum openings?
Objection!
Counsel's baiting the witness.
Not at all.
l'm establishing premeditation.
By baiting the witness.
Overruled.
Answer the question.
l never heard his name
before l met him.
You never saw
his picture in the paper?
l don't read the paper.
ls it your sworn testimony,
that by coincidence alone...
you happened to date
both Andrew Marsh...
who died from a combination
of sex and drugs...
and the doctor who treated him
for drug poisoning?
Portland's a small city.
l even dated a man
who dated a woman you dated.
Do you think you're capable...
of just answering
the questions put to you?
l'm just trying
to explain myself.
The night
of Mr. Marsh's death...
were you watching
a pornographic videotape...
you'd made of yourselves?
Objection as
to the characterization!
An explicit videotape?
Andrew used to say...
''Why watch strangers
when you can watch friends?''
lf you had
finished having sex...
and Mr. Marsh
was asleep as you stated...
why was the VCR still on
when the police arrived?
Because l forgot
to turn it off before l left.
Because Andrew Marsh
was already dead...
and you were in a hurry
to make your exit?
Objection!
Argumentative isn't the word...
for counsel's approach
to cross.
Sustained.
Watch yourself, Mr. Garrett.
Miss Carlson...
you stated that
you handcuffed Andrew Marsh...
before having sex with him
the night of his death.
lt wasn't before. lt was during.
l stand corrected. Thank you.
Did you engage
in any other forms...
of dominance with the victim?
Did you, for example, beat him?
Objection!
The specifics of
the sexual relationship...
between the victim
and the defendant...
have no bearing
on the charges against her.
The state has
an obvious interest...
in a pattern of abuse...
that ended with
the death of the victim.
Answer the question,
Miss Carlson.
Succinctly, please.
l never hurt him.
Did you humiliate him?
l never humiliated him, either.
He picked the games.
You have a weakness...
for rich older men
with bad hearts...
don't you, Miss Carlson?
l like confident men
who aren't afraid to experiment.
They tend to be older.
And l own a gallery.
People l meet
tend to have money.
l don't ask for
profit-and-loss statements.
Are we supposed to believe...
Jeffrey Roston and
Andrew Marsh are coincidences?
They had nothing
to do with each other.
They both had bad hearts,
didn't they?
And they both wrote you
into their wills.
But l already testified...
l didn't know anything
about Andrew's heart.
But you knew about Roston's.
Yes.
And when you couldn't induce
a heart attack...
before he had surgery
to repair it...
you bailed out.
He wasn't any good to you.
lsn't that right?
l left him when l found him
in bed with someone else.
That was grounds for leaving...
as sexually liberated
as you are?
l couldn't compete.
You couldn't compete!
What was she possibly doing?
Using a razor blade?
He was in bed with another man.
l never knew that about him.
l felt betrayed.
l couldn't handle it,
so l left.
lt was easier for him to think
l left because of the money...
but l left
because l couldn't stay.
Mr. Roston isn't here
to defend himself.
You can say anything you want.
Yes, he is.
Ask him yourself.
No further questions.
Redirect, Mr. Dulaney?
Your Honor, the defense rests.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury...
in the case of the People
vs. Rebecca Carlson...
have you reached a verdict?
We have, Your Honor.
How do you find?
The jury finds the defendant...
not guilty.
The defendant is released.
This court is adjourned.
-Thanks, Gabe.
-Nice going.
Thanks.
You almost convinced me.
Trial's over, Frank.
Walk away.
Stop whining.
You knew you were going
to blow your career.
l'm doing you a favor.
We will live happily ever after,
but not together.
lf you stick around me...
you'll get indicted
for perjury and murder.
l'm home free.
They can't try me twice...
but you are a different story.
Shit!
He heard us.
He's my lawyer.
lt's privileged.
l'd have given you
the same goddamn defense.
But you wouldn't have been
as believable.
lf l didn't fuck you?
lt works.
You slept with him?
l don't think we ever slept,
did we, Frank?
Don't look so hurt, Alan.
l fucked you. l fucked Andrew.
l fucked Frank.
That's what l do. l fuck.
And it made me $8 million.
So you're fucking
Dr. Paley here...
and he mentions
a rich patient--
a rich, delicate patient--
and you figure you can
fuck yourself into the will.
You know how to do that.
l'm hard to resist.
The coke came from Dr. Paley,
didn't it?
Made it untraceable.
Why are you telling him?
He's telling us.
Fuck if you didn't
play me perfectly.
Paley goes on the stand,
makes you look guilty as hell.
Then you set me up
to destroy him...
so l can make you
look innocent.
Sort of a reverse
character witness.
You're a real genius.
Sorry l can't say
the same thing about you.
l always thought the message
on the answering machine...
was a little over the top,
but you even bought that.
What are you
doing here anyway...
ambulance chasing?
Looking for a new client?
Talk to Alan here.
He thinks he's in trouble.
You don't give a shit about me.
You're right.
l've forgotten you already.
l threw my life away for you!
Paley, what are you--
l'll kill you!
Stop it!
Paley!
Bitch!
Oh, God.
You're going to be all right.
Get me out of here, Frank.
Do you believe in karma, Frank?
No.
Whatever you call it...
people usually get
what they deserve...
except for lawyers.
You should have won the case.
l did.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org