Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
There comes a time in your life
when everything falls into place.
That dream, you've been working
towards for years.
You've torn your knees for it
on the dance floor.
You gave up everything else for it.
You kept going until
you really couldn't anymore.
There comes a time when every dance
you ever danced counts.
When you can feel every step,
every flow, every move...
in the deepest fibers of your body.
That's the time when you know
you don't live to dance...
but that you dance to live.
That time is now.
There's news.
Stop. Please stop, sir.
Chanel, I'm really late. I had to work
overtime, and I missed the bus.
Can you please pick me up?
- You have to learn to fend for yourself.
I've got a job, okay? If my daddy
worked for me, I could manage.
Byeee.
Is that Tara?
- Don't answer it. Go.
I'm with them. I'm one of the dancers.
Thank you, ladies.
Where were you?
- Ladies, you were really awesome.
I think you deserve a drink. Or ten.
Which of you girls can sign this?
Here, please.
Thank you. Here you go.
You'll split it with your friends, right?
Mail?
- Yes, upstairs.
Samuel, what are you doing here?
What are you doing?
Honey...
- I'm going to New York.
Oh yes, by the way. It's over.
In the Battle of Broadway
the five best Dutch dance crews...
will compete for a special award.
The grant for the trip is still uncertain,
because of cutbacks.
Do you remember how he danced?
How he looked at one spectator?
- At me.
And that sparks would fly
when he danced.
He was a tiger. Just like his son.
Maybe I'll find him.
Listen.
You're going to New York
to win that contest.
Not to find someone who's got nothing
to do with you anymore. Okay?
Just forget it.
Forget it.
Brainpower's new single, Light It Up.
Four tens, home boy.
- Great.
Cool track.
- No, man. I don't like hip-hop.
It's Brainpower.
- Listen, dude. This is real music.
Have a good trip, my man.
I came by your place.
- Don't ask.
Hey, I'm sorry, man. Ray...
- Quincy.
It's been a long time.
Are you in the contest?
- You know I am.
You know what that means, don't you?
- That you're going to lose, right?
You're good at that.
- Contestants, please report.
So many women, so little time.
- See you later, okay?
I'd like to get to know you...
Be careful.
- Hang on. Let me.
Give it to me.
You're going to New York too?
- No, I'm waiting for a ferry boat here.
Oh, my God. Look at Tara
in her new outfit.
Is that a real one?
Your ticket.
- Thanks.
Still no payment for the video.
- They'd pay cash, right?
Do you have it?
- No, do you?
We're not completely sure why, but it
seems our grant has been canceled.
And...
the whole thing's been called off.
Well, that's it, then.
That's it, then? We've got tickets,
don't we? Dumbo?
What will you do there?
- What do you think?
Who's going to New York with me?
Well?
Forty dancers in that hall,
and you're coming along.
Do you know each other?
Sure we do.
- No.
What's the plan?
- The plane's going to New York.
And if you don't push the stop button,
so are we.
The two of us, for a week...
- To win that contest, yes.
Fortunately for you, you're with one
of Holland's biggest talents.
And what's his name?
Very funny. My crew won everything
in the Amsterdam area.
And is your crew on the plane as well?
Is yours?
Well. One, two, three, four.
Five.
Look at that. Paris Hilton's coming too.
Five dancers.
Sounds like a crew to me.
You think we could, guys?
- Why not?
We don't know each other.
- They don't know that in New York.
If we arrive as one crew, we're in.
Yes, and we'll win that shit,
and be on Broadway, baby.
Or won't we?
Be like that.
- She's your type.
I'm going to nail her.
We're approaching New York Airport,
JFK.
The Fasten Your Seatbelts sign
has been lit.
Hey. The 34 bus will take us straight
to the Dance Academy.
I don't do buses.
- Excuse me?
- She doesn't do buses.
Not even with a condom?
Check that chick, man.
Did you see that?
Yes, Daddy.
Don't think I'm going to breakdance.
- Because?
If I enjoyed mopping the floor
in my tracksuit, I'd be a cleaning lady.
Wow. Check this out.
Can we do this?
- Sure. It's crap that everything's full.
Sometimes you just have to be
assertive.
I can't wait to see this.
You got a problem?
Smart move.
I know you from somewhere. Since
when do you dance with the Spanish?
So you don't qualify.
We're going to have a coffee break.
Those morons.
- Don't get worked up.
I'm not. Didn't you see
what that guy did?
Yes. Dance better than you.
- Fuck you.
What was that?
- She's right, though.
We hardly know each other. We have
different styles, and no routine.
What are we doing here?
Wait.
Excuse me?
- Sorry, but I don't do bad hotels.
But this isn't a bad hotel.
It's a perfect hotel.
Yes. You can even rent rooms
by the hour.
Oh, yuck. By the hour...
Fortunately, you only need
five minutes.
You know, guys? Good luck. We'll call.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
- It was open.
You can't just walk in.
- I wanted Samuel.
He's not here. Go.
- Have you seen Ray?
He's not in my shower either. Go away.
- Just tell me...
No. Go away.
Did you forget something?
Moron.
Damn, Tara. Where were you?
- Just around.
Wow. That's bad, Mama.
See? We're good. We can win.
- You'd say so, yes.
With these skills?
Not.
Awesome. Catch you later.
Was that the look of love?
- You wish.
I promise. We'll do something nice
tonight.
Here's some money.
You'll be alright, won't you?
That was good.
- Hey, you're Dutch?
Yes, we arrived yesterday.
- How do you do that with your foot...
Wait, I can show you.
You lean on this arm...
Like this, you mean?
Just you wait.
Ray, your bag.
Not the bag, not the bag...
That's my father. He lives here as well.
Were you going to see him?
Okay, cool. I'm coming with you.
Sure. You can't let a ten-year-old kid
alone in a city like New York, can you?
Wise guy.
Seeing those guys at the Academy,
I really think we have to be creative.
I've got a fun idea, let's try it.
Here, for you.
A blue one for you. Samuel.
Sorry Tara, I don't have a pink one
for you.
Guys, let's get serious. If we want to
win that battle, we have to try harder.
It's a small world, isn't it.
Come on, Nina.
That's nice.
Come on, Ray.
Come on, Quincy.
Finish her, man.
Okay, Samuel. Get him.
Ramona. Met her in the park
this morning.
I really have to get up earlier.
That's right. To practice.
This really won't happen to us again.
Is that clear?
- Crackers.
How do you know he still dances here?
That picture's old.
Yes, but this is him.
They'll be open tomorrow.
Are your parents divorced?
Because they don't talk.
Mine are divorced.
- Mine aren't.
They were never married. My dad
had to go back, after a dance contest.
I got it from him. The dancing.
Here, look at this.
I made this for him.
Is that you?
- Yes, and this. It's all me, actually.
Here, a battle. So he can see
I've got his talent.
He can see all this tomorrow.
What are you doing?
- I'm thinking.
We need something
no one has ever seen before. Ever.
That means you keep your shirt on,
Casanova.
But think about what we did yesterday,
at the club.
All together, and yet...
- No. I'll work it out in my room.
See you later.
Gross.
- Relax. Breathe in, breathe out.
And no one's using this?
Right, this doesn't really work.
Let's try something else.
The theme's Broadway,
so I want to use that.
Ray and Samuel...
Samuel, pay attention, please.
I want you to lift me.
I know it sounds vague, but I'm
wearing a hat. And you make it float.
Please.
Okay, the lift...
And Tara?
- I'll be with you in a minute.
It's 5, 6, 7, 8, then two bars,
then we do the lift. You're on this side.
After that, we do the hat.
5, 6, 7, 8, lift me up.
Okay, wait, wait.
We've got two bars to do the lift.
5, 6, 7, 8, and then I'll count, one, two.
Is that clear? One more time.
Five... Samuel, please. I'm over here.
God damn it. Think, guys.
- Come on, Nina.
This won't work.
- We're creating, that's how it goes.
But shouldn't I...
- No.
What about me?
- Definitely not you.
Nina, come on.
Daddy, you're going to party.
Act normal. I can't do salsa.
Dude, you just said 'great'.
- You'd have said the same thing.
You can dance salsa, right?
Get away from me, man.
Those guys are bad.
- Be cool, man.
Right. You can do that.
You know, if I created our routine, I'd...
But you're not creating it. I am.
You just decided that, did you?
We have to be good in that battle.
And you're just screwing around.
That's right. Running around,
going to parties...
pulling chicks...
- Come on. Listen to her.
Like I said, if I were creating
the routine...
I'd draw inspiration from this.
Inspiration?
- Yes. For new moves.
I'm sorry, but if I want to see some new
moves, I'll watch the porn channel.
Come on then, you hot babe.
So, as I was saying...
different moves.
That's not a routine yet.
- No, but it's something.
Are you coming? Stud?
Can I have my phone?
- Here it is.
It's late. I wanted an early night.
- Don't be that way.
What about this?
- You drink it.
What are you doing?
- Such a great party.
Oh man, you've got a big nose.
Hey, look at this.
Sit down and stay down.
Look, I can do that too.
I want to go home.
Thanks a lot, dude.
I told you you'd fall in love with me.
Nice, thanks.
Let's go to the Cielo
to dance off the tension.
No, we've got loads to do yet.
We'll have dinner,
then we'll dance until it gets light.
Didn't you hear me?
We have to focus.
Look. This is what I wanted to do.
I changed the entire composition...
I've only got tonight to work this out.
Come on. I just want to have fun.
- Fun?
Going home with my tail between
my legs because I lost, that'll be fun.
If I go home without winning,
I'll have failed.
And when you go home...
you'll have a good story, a nice trip
and some pretty chicks.
I just mean...
this is the chance I've waited for
all my life.
And you've achieved much more
than you ever expected.
Are you serious?
Which one do you think it is?
That one.
It could be him as well.
You wait here.
- Okay, chill.
Ray, your father. Did you find him?
I just want this to work.
Do you understand?
Isn't Quincy here?
- How should I know?
Come on, you don't need to do this.
This?
Oh, you think I...
I was just visiting a girl I met.
- I saw you dance.
All those clothes, the taxis, the hotel...
Is that worth all this nonsense?
Acting like a whore to pay for it?
- A whore?
I'm not a fucking whore, alright?
I just want to say you shouldn't do this.
I don't care what you think.
I'll never go back to how it used to be.
'If you can't afford it,
you shouldn't want it.'
No. And you keep your mouth shut,
you hear me?
Come on, Tara, listen to me.
- You heard me.
Come with me. Trust me.
Now you. Here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Come on, Tara...
I mean well.
Come with me.
Tara, please work at it.
The battle's tomorrow.
Keep going.
Ray, where's your head at? Damn...
- Wait.
What are you doing? Chill out.
No chilling out. It has to be good.
It won't be good if...
- Because you can't do it.
Just do it for once, instead of moaning.
Moaner.
- Jesus.
Yeah, what?
- Nagging bitch.
Five minutes.
What is this?
- They're trying hard.
And you keep pushing them.
- They're not trying, you know that.
Where were you yesterday?
- What do you mean?
Where were you?
- What are you talking about?
You were with Tara.
What's going on with you, anyway?
Nina, there's nothing going on.
Is there anyone here
who came to dance?
Well? Does anyone really
want to do this battle?
You. All you do is hang out
with your girlfriend.
Yes, your girlfriend.
And Tara, I don't know why
you're here, but not to dance.
You're walking around
with Mini Michael. That sucks.
What are you doing?
- And you should really shut up.
You're only here for the women.
Well, you've had two. Congratulations.
I'm out.
Nina, wait.
Listen to me.
- What do you want?
Fuck this. I'm going.
You know...
That's what I mean.
- I can explain.
Leave me alone.
His dad worked all night long.
He was lying on the sidewalk.
- Great example.
Great example.
I'm sorry my mind was on other things.
I was looking for my father.
- And?
Did you find him?
- I thought I'd understand if I met him.
But I understand even less.
My mother lied about everything.
What do you mean?
My father's not a dancer at all.
Yes, but you did find him, didn't you?
Give me an hour, okay?
- Ray, come on.
The contest is today, man. Ray...
Where are you going?
- Just leaving.
But the contest?
- Nina's gone, Tara's gone.
Nina's gone?
- I saw her leave.
And you didn't tell me?
- I've got problems of my own. It's over.
Are you leaving?
Then why are you still here?
- As if I had a place to go.
I fought with everyone.
You think you have to do it
all by yourself. If you don't trust us...
nothing will ever happen.
What was going on with Tara?
She's dancing at a strip club.
To pay for all that nonsense.
- You're serious?
She's in even deeper shit than we are.
We have a dance contest to do.
- As if you still want to.
All you have to do is apologize.
Am I right?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Tara.
That I've been such a bitch.
Come here.
It's okay.
I was a lot worse.
I hate to bug you, but if we want
to win that contest, we have to go.
Yes, let's go.
- The subway's this way.
Wait.
- Right. The lady doesn't do subways.
No, the subway's fine.
But the bus is quicker.
- Very sharp, Tara. Very sharp.
Oh, there's that guy again.
Just ignore him. Come on.
Sweet thing.
Moron.
Sit down.
Must have been slippery.
Are you okay?
Where does it hurt?
- It's my knee.
You have to go to the hospital.
Go ahead and dance.
- It's not worth it.
Just go and dance, okay?
Hey, kiddies.
Does your little knee hurt?
Don't do it, don't do it.
Think of your knee.
You can forget it.
When you arrive,
you often forget the journey.
The pain.
The injuries.
The sleepless nights.
The sacrifice.
All you remember is the highlights.
New York.
Together with you.
Hey guys, do you hear that?
They're calling us back to the stage.
Come on.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org