Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
The ice hockey game
between Toronto Maple Leads...
...and Detroit Red Beats has
been quite interesting so far.
Overtime has been given to them.
In this final round, both
the teams have made two goals.
What is this?
The centre of Leads
Rajveer Singh has got the puck.
And he is at the breakaway.
He has crossed the red line.
There is nobody
between him and the goalie.
Rajveer Singh
hoodwinked the goalie...
...and moved him from his position.
And goal.
What a goal!
Rajveer Singh has done a miracle.
He won the game like a dream.
The crowd is dancing
with delight on the victory.
Mother. Mother.
Take this.
Do not fear.
Rajveer.
Dad.
Today...
Today, I am dead.
Dad, what are you doing here?
Working. And you?
You are sleeping.
Have you laid eggs here
that you sleep here every day?
I just took a short nap.
Son, remember.
You can get either success or rest.
If your uncle sees you sleeping,
he will fire you.
Useless fellow, all
this can be yours.
Just once show your
uncle you are capable.
I don't think I will
lose this job, dad.
Why do you feel like so?
Which idiot will do this job?
Rajveer, what do you see here?
Trucks.
Be a bit farsighted.
Yes, dad. I should
say I see my future.
Mr. Darvesh and Mr. Rajveer Singh,
please come to the office.
Come and answer your uncle.
Why do you worry so much, dad?
I can't save you every time.
Uncle Sammy is very cool.
Yes. Uncle Sammy.
You will tell him you
were sleeping in the truck.
You are ashamed. Fine?
Fine.
Uncle Sammy.
Rajveer.
Come in.
Brother, hello.
Hello.
Uncle, aunt, sorry. I...
There is good news. Reena is
getting married next month.
Sonu, herfiancé, has
agreed to come to Tornado.
It's God's grace.
Congratulations.
He is a gem.
You will be pleased to meet him.
He is a talented boy.
He is an expert in stock exchange.
You are next, Rajveer.
My niece in
Jalandhar is perfect for him.
Check her out on facebook.
Stop your marriage bureau.
We will conduct
Rajveer's marriage...
...when he will do the entire shift...
...without sleeping in the truck.
Am I right?
He dreams of fair
damsels sleeping in the truck.
Once again congratulations.
Congratulations.
Thank you, brother.
Raj. Raj.
Raj, pass it.
Raj, nobody is here. Pass it.
Raj, here.
Raj, I told you to pass it here.
You gave a good pass.
You want a pass or goal?
Zero, you fool.
Raj, henceforth we will
consider you equal to two players.
There is another option.
Put your stick in
your mouth and play.
This is not possible.
Why?
His tongue is very smooth.
Smootherthan his hands.
Do pass it to us at times.
I see.
Hero.
Look. Look. Look.
Who are they?
Leave. Yourtime is up.
We still have10 minutes.
They are Hammerheads.
Hammer my foot.
They are barging in. It's our ice.
Hammer...
Watch it.
What's your problem?
I don't have any problem.
I am just waiting for you
jokers to leave the ice.
Smarty, don't lock horns.
Leave before I lock horns.
Lock horns.
Yourfather locked horns by
bringing you into this world.
So?
- Push. "Fool."
Yes. What?
Listen.
Yes.
Ensure that your player
doesn't commit a murder...
...and soil my ice.
Look, I don't want to lock horns.
I just want to score goals.
Two for Raj. And
zero forthe foreigner.
Good shot.
Come on. Lock horns.
Leave.
Stop. Leave.
Raj. Come on. It's over.
Have you gone crazy?
We have come here to
practice ice hockey...
...and not judo or karate.
Fools.
Coach.
Yes.
Shall I try?
I have good players. You
go and play with marbles.
Coach, the kid should get a chance.
Yes, coach. Let's see
how much guts he has.
Come on.
Fine.
Raj. Come on, Raj.
Come on, Raj. Well done. Well done.
Pass.
Come on.
Pass it here. Hey.
There you go.
Raj, you are playing well.
Here. Here.
Dan, I have been waiting for
you forthe past half an hour.
Do you want to come with me or not?
Yes. I want to come. I was
watching this Indian player play.
He is not bad.
Lick the glass.
Hey.
He is not that good too.
Hey. Hey.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Good. Good.
Yes. Come on, Raj. Yes!
Yes
Goal!
- Yes!
Come on.
Did you see? I told you. He
is not less than them. - Yes.
Yes.
Okay. Enough, kiddo.
Everybody, come. Come on.
This was Enough forthe kiddo.
Coach.
Done? That's it.
Yes. Over.
I was the best player.
I will send you the
ticket of ourfinal match.
Don't mind. You are
not worthy of this team.
Good practice, guys.
Indians don't have any
value in the rink, Raj.
Forget it. It's their loss.
See you.
Shameless.
But you were playing quite well.
So you were watching.
Nonsense.
You are calling hockey nonsense.
Not me. Right?
This is human rights' case.
They were slandering you openly.
Now, I am used to it.
There are rules in Canadian chart...
...of human rights
against such behavior.
What happened? Why are you laughing?
I swear. You look prettier
when you are fuming with rage.
Are you a lawyer?
Almost. I am studying law.
Fine. If you everwant
to save this poor man...
...you will find me here.
Getting beaten.
Who are you?
My brother. The great Dan Winters.
You must have heard about him.
In some season he had played...
...for Red Wings for a few days.
Yes. Four matches.
I think you play well.
Thanks.
When you are not kissing the glass.
You shouldn't have let
them take advantage of you.
Did you hear, lawyer?
Next time save me.
Good. But I don't think
you can afford my fees.
No discount for
friends and relatives?
And you are?
Your new friend.
Rajveer.
You have started
helping strangers, Melissa.
No. - Since when did
you become my father?
Since the time you
started helping strangers.
Concentrate on your studies.
Thanks forthe advice.
Let's settle one thing.
I am just a tenant in your house.
And you are my hassled brother.
Fine.
But curb your social service.
Who died? And where is the body?
Gurveer.
Why did you leave
from work so early?
We had our hockey practice.
I had told you.
Mother, today it was great fun.
Today, I played with Hammerheads.
It's a champion team.
They have been winning the Hyundai
cup forfour consecutive years.
They took you in theirteam?
No. They didn't.
They didn't take you in theirteam.
But...
I was thinking of retiring
and settling down in Miami.
It was an equal competition, dad.
Competition?
Lavleen, will you ask your son?
Where did the word 'work'
disappearfrom his dictionary?
Son, he means to say...
Tell him.
Had I played cricket,
he would have...
...danced with delight at each shot.
Look, he thinks you...
India is the king of cricket.
Crores of people watch cricket.
Ask him. Does anyone in
India even know about ice hockey?
Look, son. Hockey...
Ask him.
In Canada which
channel shows cricket?
Ask...
My neck is tired.
Shall we eat?
Yes.
I don't know where my
son has disappeared.
I don't know him.
He cut his hair. He
dozes off at work.
Mother, tell
fatherto talk lovingly.
Otherwise he will spend his old
age in an old age home... - Raj.
Eight dollars.
When I came to this city,
I had only eight dollars.
I provided education to my brother.
He converted eight
dollars into eight billion.
I didn't ask anything
from him. Besides a job.
And if my son is capable,
he will run his business.
I don't think that
day will ever arrive.
I am there. I am a good son too.
Shut up.
If you think you will play
ice hockey, you are mistaken.
Don't worry, dad.
As a hockey star's father,
you can retire early.
Then you can rest on a beach and
see bikini... - Stop your nonsense.
Enough.
Henceforth you will
concentrate on yourwork.
And in yourfree time you
will do service in Gurdwara.
Henceforth, no hockey. Got it?
Henceforth, no hockey.
You never saw me playing.
I don't even want to see.
Can I eat his 'Ras Malai' (Sweets)?
Keep quiet and eat yourfood.
Are you fine, brother?
Yes.
Dad says all that
because he loves me more.
I am kidding. You are his brave son.
You do so much drama.
What are you doing? Leave.
"I am your good son."
Leave, brother.
Don't do that.
Fatso. - Don't do it again.
Son, please finish your dinner.
I have lost my appetite, mother.
Son, try to understand yourfather.
I admit he is a bit stubborn.
When you cut your hair,
he kept quiet.
When you left university, he
arranged for a job for you...
...at your uncle Sammy's place.
You also have some duty,
don't you, son?
Please eat.
My darling son.
Come on. Come on.
Pass it here.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Take this.
Goal. Yeah!
Ourteam?
Yes.
'Kabbadi' (lndian game).
'Kabbadi'. 'Kabbadi'. 'Kabbadi'.
Shut up.
We can win the Hyundai cup.
What are you saying?
Have you gone crazy?
Okay. Okay. Tip-cat.
You are watching too
many cartoon films.
Raj, we play hockey like kids.
That too very badly.
Rubbish.
Yes. Have confidence, friends.
We will give
Hammerheads a tough time.
What do you say?
Fine. Listen.
They are smarter,
speedier, and beefierthan us.
Yes.
Fair-skinned. Have you seen it?
Hi, guys.
Hi, Reena. - Hi.
Do you know me? - Bye.
Bye.
Reena is So pretty.
She is my cousin.
Whenever I see her on news,
I wish I was her microphone.
Hindi. Hindi. She has got engaged.
So?
No problem.
And she is not yourtype.
What's my type?
Flirty type.
Hey.
He got angry.
Rajveer, we are leaving.
Everything fine? Take this.
You fool.
Get ready.
Later.
"This is my world, beloved."
"This is my world."
"Move, move now."
"We will not be touched."
"Got the game on stuck."
"We cannot be seen."
Have faith.
I Have faith.
I have full faith
that we will be mocked.
What are all of you doing here?
Practicing for Hyundai cup.
Practicing for defeat?
What do you think? We are losers?
What do you think?
I am the coach of this team.
Wow! You will surely
become the coach of the year.
So what should we do?
What do you mean by we?
If you know what to do to be
the coach of the year. Teach me.
Guys.
Everybody come here.
Come here.
You farted again.
How's it going?
Fine. Perfectly fine.
Your name?
Singh. Deva Singh.
Yours?
Inderjit Singh.
Jassi Singh.
You are also a Singh?
Right. Rajveer.
All of us are Singhs.
So many brothers?
Brothers from different mothers.
Okay.
Singhs.
You have only two options.
Enterthe ice, have fun and lose.
Or be strong, break some
bones and give yourself a chance.
There are two types of hockey.
Hockey that you play on the street.
And real hockey.
Watched by entire Canada.
The ice on which it's played,
it's softerthan Rajveer's cheeks.
I don't know whether all
of you can play or not.
But I know how to find out.
Isn't he the ice cleaner?
Seems to be him.
"Move, move now."
"We will not be touched."
"Got the game on stuck."
"We cannot be seen."
"Unstoppable force is
the Indian dream team."
"You know who we are."
"We are the Indian royalty."
"We run the world."
"This is my world, beloved."
"This is my world."
Sonu, this is our Speedy Singh.
It's nice, sweetie.
Shall we leave? I have just landed.
Let me rest for a while.
Darling, my entire
family is waiting for you.
They are not going anywhere.
We are Indians. We can
be late. Don't worry.
One moment. It's from
the TV station. Hello.
'Desi Tadka'.
I have told you so many
times I won't do a cookery show.
"Your beloved's truck is
flying through GT Road."
Son, since you are going
to be my company's driver...
...let me tell you
what you have to do.
Atruck is delicate like a woman.
You should treat her
lovingly and politely. - Okay.
Keep her happy. There shouldn't
be a shortage of adornment.
But always drive safely.
You mean, seatbelt, right?
Right, uncle. Okay. Give it a name.
Melissa.
- It's a nice name.
No. It should be a Punjabi name.
Okay. How about Malinder?
It's good.
Hello, Malinder.
Come on.
You fool. Is this
how you handle a woman?
Now, I know why you
don't have a girlfriend.
Step on the accelerator.
Alright.
- That's it. It has started.
Last time my stomach rumbled...
...so badly that my eardrum exploded.
Brake. Brake.
Where is the brake, uncle?
Reena. Reena.
You are forcing me.
Start the car.
Hold on, Sonu.
I said I am coming.
I will try to come
as soon as possible.
What is this, Sonu?
You are so petrified
of meeting my dad.
Don't worry. He will like you.
Hello.
Did you poke my niece on facebook?
If you poke her, she will like it.
I will do it today.
Look. I Have her photo.
Yes.
Ms. Punjab. Third runner-up.
What is this, aunt? Only third?
She would have won
if the other girls...
...had not slept with the judges.
Why should I keep quiet?
I heard it.
I will tell everybody in school.
Son, no.
She is cute.
Everybody, please pay attention.
He is my Sonu.
Hello. - He is my elder
brother Darvesh Singh.
My sister-in-law Lavleen.
Hello.
And theirtwo lovely sons.
Gurveer and Rajveer Singh.
How are you?
You are so strong. Do
you lift trucks? - Good.
You will defeat Khali.
Naughty kid.
Rajveer.
Reena has told me a lot about you.
This is what you call her,
don't you? You call her Reena.
And I call her Sonu's sweetie.
You drive truck so well.
I don't know how we survived today.
Next time I will try my best.
Good.
It's good that you left
college forfamily business.
History is the witness that
undergrads have always succeeded.
Sonu, look. Yourwould-be wife.
Wow! - Amazing!
It's looking good on you.
I had ordered it
especially from France. - France.
By sending a Punjabi team for
the famous Hyundai Tournament...
...Tornado's Indian community has
created a place forthemselves...
...in Canada's national game.
This is Reena Singh from S.I.N.
Wow! You look so beautiful.
- Amazing!
Rajveer, you are also playing,
aren't you?
Rajveer has decided
to give up hockey.
Now, he has to concentrate
on other important things.
For instance, learning
his uncle's business.
Right, Rajveer? - Yes, dad.
Wow! Nice plan, uncle.
You are perfect forthis.
"Move, move now."
"We will not be touched."
"Got the game on stuck."
"We cannot be seen."
"Unstoppable force is
the Indian dream team."
"You know who we are."
Throw it out. "We are
the Indian royalty."
"We run the world."
"This is my world, beloved."
"This is my world."
Come on. Have a meal and come here.
Excuse me.
The doctor has come.
I have taken training in first aid.
Maybe he has hurt his head.
You look like Katrina Kaif.
What problem do you have?
I hit him softly.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Lie down. You will be fine.
Breathe.
Breathe deeply.
"Come to me."
"Dance and show me, beloved."
"Move yourwaist."
"Come to me."
"Come, let us both dance."
"Dance merrily."
"You are teasing me tonight."
"I want the dance floor by my side."
"My side."
"I feel like seeing
you day and night."
"Dance with me."
"I also love you."
"Don't you know that my
heart belongs to you?"
"Come to me."
"Dance and show me, beloved."
"Move yourwaist."
"Come to me."
"Come, let us both dance."
You will enjoy it. Trust me.
Take this.
Move, you fool.
What happened?
I am not interested in kissing you.
Come on.
Get up.
Get up. I was giving
you fake CPR. That's it.
Get him out of the ice.
Where did Taj Mahal go?
The music stopped?
What?
- What's happening?
You slipped here and
fell into Bollywood.
Beloved.
I love you.
I think you have got
a major concussion.
Sorry. I spoke rubbish outside.
You were embarrassing
yourself and not me.
How do you feel now?
Tell me.
Will you come on a date with me?
I don't date hockey players.
You are lucky. I am
a truck drivertoo.
But I don't date them as well.
I will leave both
these things for you.
Especially those
who leave theirwork.
I think locker room
is only for players.
I am waiting for you in the car.
How are you now, Raj...
Rajvinder.
Raj is enough.
What is your sister's problem?
You think I am your spy?
What have you
thought about coaching?
Ten turbaned men.
All ten are Singhs.
I can't pronounce
theirfirst names properly.
They can't skate properly.
Leave alone play.
What can be worse than this?
It will be a miracle if we
play the first round well.
What?
You said we.
If it's in your destiny,
what can a person do?
Why are you following me?
What do you mean?
Why are you in my
favorite restaurant?
Don't act smart.
My friend praises this place a lot.
I have never eaten Indian food.
I thought I should try it.
How is your head?
You seemed unstable at the rink.
I am sitting in front of you.
I am perfectly alright.
Rajveer.
How are you, son?
Is everything fine at home?
Yes, Mr. Patel. Everything is fine.
Meet Melissa.
Hi.
First date?
Yes. - No.
I will consider it a yes.
Okay. Did I hear it right that
you are practicing hockey nowadays?
You are in that team about which...
...your sisterwas talking on TV?
No. No. - Yes. You are.
You are the captain.
Think whether you
are the captain or not.
If you are, I will
waive today's bill.
Waive today's bill?
Yes. I am the captain.
You heard it right.
What will you have, captain?
If you permit, shall
I place the order?
Okay. Let's begin
with 'Chicken Tikka'.
Good choice.
- 'Tandoori Jinga' (Fish). - Okay.
And mixed fritters.
Okay.
Cottage cheese vegetable. Curry.
And chicken 'Biryani'
(Flavored rice) too.
God bless you. - Afew flatbreads,
garlic and butter.
And rice.
And curd salad to keep her calm.
Anything for you?
No.
This will be enough.
Are you ordering
forthe entire team?
I am afraid it will be less.
Okay. Why were you not
telling him you are in the team?
My father doesn't like this game.
Why?
Have you noticed that
I look different from...
...the otherteam members?
Yes. They wear a turban. And
you don't. What's the big deal?
It's a big deal for a
boy born in a Sikh family.
When a Sikh boy cuts his hair...
I used to get angry
when people would see...
...not me but what was on my head.
I was 12 years old when a few boys...
...were playing hockey in my lane.
They allowed me to play on the
condition that I am the goalie.
I started playing.
After some time the game was about...
...who drops the turban from my head.
I broke my nose.
Both my eyes turned black.
That's why you cut your hair?
You may say so.
What is this?
I have made this forthe captain.
It's special.
Wow! My mouth is watering.
You also have it.
You begin.
Okay. Fine.
No.
What happened?
I am dead. It's so spicy.
Are you fine? What happened?
Drink water. Mr. Patel. Mr. Patel.
Peppermint.
Is that so?
After burning my mouth you
are trying to entice me.
I am not flirting with you.
Are you fine?
Because you can file a
human rights case on Patel.
Thanks for giving me a
taste of Indian food.
Okay. Will Chinese
be okay next time?
Goodnight.
Somebody give me a massage.
My legs are broken.
- All of you don't have energy.
Chess players are more energetic.
Friends, he is kidding.
Because you don't have to
move in a chess tournament.
Am I right?
All of you insult me there.
Henceforth we will stay
on the ice for longer.
I want more
commitment from all of you.
Coach, we want a nice uniform.
Right?
Yes. True.
It feels as if a team
of beggars is playing.
Right?
Yes.
I like it. Look, red color.
Its designer.
All of you are right.
We look like beggars.
If somebody has money and
pity for us hapless people...
This is the time.
What do you say? Is
Speedy Singhs okay?
It's great.
What do you think?
Should I invest money in
this Punjabi hockey team?
We will have to see Mr. Singh's ROI.
Return on investment.
Look, we can't take a major decision
without a business proposal.
So...
You are intelligent.
Thank you.
Uncle, what profit in
supporting your community?
Deva's team's name
will be Speedy Singhs.
It's great, isn't it?
Speedy Singhs.
It's a good name.
Fine. Let's have a
fundraising party.
I will invest the remaining money.
Deva came imploring for his team.
I understood it will be really
beneficial to invest money in...
...lndian community's ice hockey.
Hello. Hello.
I told him.
Let's invest in a
profitable venture.
See this.
Today, it's so lively because of me.
Please. Please. Enjoy yourself.
He has come to ask for more money.
Eat something.
He spoke nonsense.
You must be hungry.
Look, we don't get along well.
But soon we will be family.
When Reena marries you.
What do you mean?
She is crazy. I don't
know what she sees in you.
Right. Good one.
If that is the case, we
will behave like nephews.
Just bear in mind that I am
your boss's would-be son-in-law.
What do you mean?
You will have to work
under your brother-in-law.
Punjabi boy crazy for hockey.
Good luck, bro.
Well said.
Be real.
Coach Winters.
I have met you before, haven't I?
Hi.
It is betterthat you
concentrate on your game.
Drunkard, be careful.
Don't fall down.
Reena, your mother is sloshed.
Take care of her.
Why has everybody come here?
Mom.
Uncle Sammy.
How are you?
He is...
Inderjit.
How are you?
- It's fun.
Uncle Sammy, he is
our coach Dan Winters.
How are you?
Pleased to meet you.
She is my sister Melissa.
Good to see you.
Mr. Singh is the owner
of Speedy Singh transport.
As well as the
sponsor of this event.
His lovely wife.
Hi.
Hello.
His beautiful daughter Reena.
Hi. How are you?
Fine.
I think my face is up.
By the way, pleased to
meet you, Mr. Winters.
I am fortunate.
Your support is very
important for ourteam.
And your nephew is
ourteam's best player.
Rajveer.
He is also in the team?
Yes.
No. No.
He is not in the team.
He is not in the playing team.
He is like a supporterforthe team.
He is the team's supporter.
That is what he meant.
He doesn't even know how to play.
Don't worry. By the way,
I am the goal keeper.
I have heard you have written
my name on all your equipments.
So you know?
Yes.
I see. Yes.
Son.
Yes, mother.
I know what you are thinking.
Is that so?
Yes.
I just want to say
that we are proud of you.
I always knew you are
not like yourfriends.
They are wasting their
lives for a stupid game.
I told you, Lavleen.
Someday he will
realize his responsibilities.
Papa, listen.
I am proud of you.
Monica.
One moment, son.
Let me enjoy the dance.
Melissa.
Do I know you?
Shall we have a dance?
You will get to know me too.
I am a very bad dancer.
Come. I will teach you.
You will raise a lot of funds.
You are happy, aren't you?
It will be good help forthe team.
Yes. That's true.
When are you meeting me again?
Why? You can't see
me clearly this time?
I mean, just the two of us.
We are not alone here.
That is yourfamily?
Yes.
How do you know?
Because they are the
only people staring at me.
Did you see my eyes? - That's
how I know they are yourfamily.
How does he know that foreigner?
Foreigner? - The same
foreignerwith whom he was dancing...
...as if he is
dancing in his marriage.
That foreigner.
Do you know?
He is punishing me because I
didn't let him play ice hockey.
It means, if he can't
play foreigners' game...
...he will get a foreigner girl.
They were not doing anything wrong.
They were only dancing.
We also danced only once.
We had two kids.
Not just that.
Patel told me he had come to his
restaurant with a foreigner girl.
She ate like a pig.
You are talking nonsense.
Yes. When he will marry
that foreignerwitch...
...you will know what is nonsense.
Stupid tie.
I hate ties.
What else do I hate?
Apple pie. What is it called?
Peanut butter.
Untie it.
Come on, boys.
How did they come here?
It's our practice time.
Maybe I did double booking.
Coach, you did that deliberately.
Sooner or later, you have
to play with Hammerheads.
Why not today?
Let's see how good you are.
Don't you trust my capability?
If you have so much confidence,
go and prove yourself.
Go.
Fine. Today, we will see them.
Terminator.
Have some pity on us.
Fine, scoundrel.
Take this.
You...
Go, kiddo. Go and drink milk.
Take this.
Deva. Deva, get up.
Deva, are you fine? Come on. Get up.
Deva. Deva.
Rogue.
Enough fortoday.
It was nice to play with you.
Bring him here.
Are you fine?
Yes. I am Fine.
Deva, sorry. You got hurt.
If you had not got hurt,
they would have been...
...still hammering us.
I don't know why they are jealous.
Fine. We were overconfident.
Okay. Me.
Our plight will be bad.
We need help.
We need practice.
One moment, friends.
I will tell you what the problem is.
We need some strong boys.
Oh, my God.
This is 'Kabaddi'.
India's great sport.
This looks like sumo and wrestling.
Actually, it's very simple.
But difficult to explain.
We are not here forthat.
Nikku Singh.
We would play hockey
when we were kids.
He is very beefy.
That's what we need.
Uncle.
Yes, Sonu.
Sir said to take your
approval forthe road schedule.
It will be good to send
Rajveer on his first trip.
Good. I will do my best.
Thank you.
No problem.
Hi, papa. Sorry. I am late.
You fool. At times come on time.
Take this.
Our hero has come.
Liked it at the Gurdwara?
Good. Very good.
The food's aroma is great.
Thank you.
Mother, teach Reena cooking.
It will be good if she
learns it before marriage.
I am noticing everything, Sonu.
You never leave a
chance to taunt me.
Did you give them the good news?
Good news?
Well, Akshay Kumar is
coming to town for shooting.
Really?
I am going to take his interview.
What are you saying?
He is a nice man. Family type man.
Good, Sonu.
I hope this hero
doesn't take Reena away.
How? On a flying saucer?
Will you have beer?
Yes. Why not?
No, uncle. Sonu won't drink.
He swings like a
child aftertwo pegs.
Yes. Mentally, he is a kid.
Raj, sirwants you to go
on yourfirst road trip.
Tonight.
You are going to New York. To
deliver an important package.
Is that so? You are also
coming along with the package?
You are right. I am
an important package.
But it's not your cup
of tea to send me back.
Don't worry. It's nothing illegal.
Nothing will happen to you.
Rajveer, you got to
handle some responsibility.
Underthis pretext you will
practice driving a truck too.
Sonu, please stop pulling Raj's leg.
Uncle Sammy.
Yes, son. Tell me. I wanted
to talk to you for a moment.
Yes. Tell me. - I think there
is some problem in the schedule.
Papa was saying I have
to go to New York tonight.
But I... - I had told the
office not to put you on schedule.
If you go to New York,
how will you play hockey?
How long have you known, uncle?
Since the time you came to
me with yourfriend Deva.
You should have told yourfamily.
You know father.
How do I tell him?
He wants to see you successful,
Rajveer.
But he doesn't understand me.
Nephew, don't worry.
Go and show them.
Thanks, uncle. The
first goal will be for you.
Score a goal for your dad.
He loves you.
Uncle is the best.
Hi, mom. Today my dinner
is out. Okay? - Yes. I know.
That's why I have packed
potato stuffed flatbread.
Amazing, mom!
Tonight is very special for you.
You will like New York a lot.
Big Apple. - Yes.
This is yourfirst road trip.
Take this, son. - I still
remember my first road trip.
Take care of the truck.
It's a great truck.
Okay. Sure. I should be leaving now.
Come. Give me a hug.
He is very happy for you today.
May Lord be your savior! - Okay.
I will leave now. Thanks. - Bye.
I am very happy today.
Rajveer, you look great.
Fantastic. - Come on.
Alright, boys.
- That's it. Enough.
Enough.
It has started. And
all of you are ready.
Put your blood and sweat.
Coach, just give us a second.
Okay. - See you at the ice.
Fine. - Okay, coach.
Come on. Let us have a group huddle.
Come on. Come on.
Raj. - What?
Let's pray.
Okay. You need me?
Blessed is the person who says...
God is truth.
I welcome all of you to
the first Hyundai cup match.
Today, Speedy Singhs are
competing with Caliber.
Show them, Sardars.
Very good.
That playerwearing a helmet...
...isn't he Rajveer?
You recognized him now, you fool.
Lavleen, do you
remember God's photo?
I used to always keep it with me.
God has been so kind to us.
I am thinking of giving
this photo to Rajveer...
...before he leaves for New York.
Yes. Go and give him.
He must not have left.
Yes. I will be able to sleep
peacefully if God is with him.
Yes. Go and give him.
Give him my love.
Tell him to drive carefully.
I will tell him.
Pass it. Pass it.
Cut in. Come on.
Move it, man. Move it.
Go. Go.
And Rajveerfrom Speedy
Singhs has made a goal.
Rajveer, take God's
photo to New York with you.
The first match is between
Speedy Singhs and Caliber.
Where is Rajveer?
He has not come.
There are a lot of expectations.
Dan Winters is quite
excited about his team.
Let's see whetherthe team
lives up to the expectations.
It's a foul.
Very good.
Well done. Well done.
Great passing by them.
And a splendid goal for
Caliber in the second period.
Okay.
Come on. Buck up.
With this foul Speedy Singhs
get a penalty of two minutes.
Caliber scores another goal.
In the third period.
With this Caliber is
ahead of Singhs, two to one.
Fine. I wanted to win.
But we played well.
We showed that we are there.
We showed many things.
Do you want to say something?
Yes.
Why to beat in the game?
He saved our honor and
showed that we know how to play.
Honor?
Honor is earned only by winning.
I think you are forgetting you
are the captain and I am the coach.
This is coach's game plan?
A stupid penalty.
Not at all. I have an easier plan.
You will do whatever I say.
This is fine.
You played well.
Thanks.
Hey.
I think you are spending a
lot of time with my brother.
Yes. You are right.
There is same tension on yourface.
Cheer up, captain. You played well.
Thanks. You should be in the class.
Yes. But as the team's lawyer,
it's important to watch...
...Speedy Singhs' matches.
Okay, lawyer. I want to
file a case on my coach.
You are upset because of the
penalty. - How do you know?
I understand ice hockey quite well.
I would be with Dan
in all his matches.
Was he good?
He was second rated in NHL.
Good skater. Good stick handler.
But a bad team player.
His ego and anger ruined his career.
You keep his rookie card with you.
He was always a rookie.
So I am very emotional.
You don't like hockey players.
I didn't say I don't
like hockey players.
I don't date them.
Until now.
Rajveer.
You fool.
Uncle.
How are you, son?
Soni. - Hi.
Don't worry. He knows everything.
Aftertoday's game you have
become famous all over Canada.
Famous.
Look.
Really? Even after losing?
Whether you win or lose,
what difference does it make?
We didn't have a team before.
Listen. Tomorrow we will
tell yourfather. Don't worry.
Fine, uncle.
But I will stay in
your house tonight.
I am in New York. Remember?
Yes. Surely.
Today, stay with Sonu.
Oh, no.
Take his autograph.
Listen. If you are lucky,
I will show you my tattoos.
If you don't wet your bed, I
will also show you many things.
What did you say? Okay. Okay.
"Move back, beautiful damsel."
"Ourtrain is heading towards you."
- It won't make a difference.
Who is Melissa?
Leave it.
Give it here.
What do you care about Melissa?
Relax.
You can't score a
goal in the match...
...I doubt you will score in love.
And you can't tell your
parents about your game...
...what else can you tell them?
Are you done?
Almost.
Go to sleep, my head's paining.
Headache. That's your
family ailment, just like Reena.
Someday you will make a good wife.
Sexy bed. Where will you sleep?
I will sleep right here.
You can sleep with me here.
But I get really
naughty in the morning.
Naughty. Quite naughty.
Come on.
Seems like you don't like your nose.
Really? What a bad joke.
Elephant to the ant: "Look,
my mom's here".
Ant: "Quick, hide behind me."
Be quiet.
I will sleep on the floor.
Do you want this pillow? - Yes.
Fine, take it.
You know Reena's doggy Foo Foo.
Prefers this pillow as well.
Oh no.
And don't use that blanket as well.
Why?
Because that is Reena
and my personal blanket.
I feel pity for you.
Here.
You can use this as a blanket.
I nevertaught him to lie.
And Sammy. Even he hid this from me.
You asked your son
something that he loves the most.
So now it's my
fault that he is lying.
Even George Bush
doesn't lie this much.
Can you stop loving me
if someone asks you to?
I feel really angry when
you use these female points.
Which other points do
I have? - I don't know.
And if he's scared to
talk to talk to you...
...then you talk to him.
But please, just talk to him.
Don't lecture him.
Very good.
I am very happy with what you did.
The singing, dancing. Drinking.
Fighting. All that was
left was getting locked up...
...but you took care of that as well.
But next time... keep my
sister away from all this.
Coach, I don't remember anything.
I don't know anything.
Get out of my locker room.
Come on.
I told you to invite
him to the party as well.
Coach.
I am sorry.
I take full responsibility of
whatever happened last night.
Good.
Nice to hearthat.
So everything's fine?
- Do you think everything's fine?
You aren't worthy of that.
You can't do that.
I just did.
Okay. Then I won't play.
We will win this game
and go to the finals.
We both know that it's
impossible without me.
Is that so?
Yes, It is.
Remember, once you
are out you are out.
That's a stupid reason.
You can turn away from me...
...but what will you say to yourself?
About what? About saving you?
Saving me? You were
only saving your ego.
Just say what you understand.
Fine.
Let's talk about Hockey?
Just because Dan took away...
...the captainship
from you, that's why?
I left the team because...
...I don't want to hearfrom
someone who cleans the ice.
Let me tell you something, big man.
Come right here, behind the bench.
And remember, I don't like quitters.
Look, that's all there was left.
Hey, coach, sorry...
I am No longer your coach.
I am sorry.
Look, I made a mistake.
I should play forthe team.
Wait. You think the
Speedy Singhs will lose...
...if you don't play?
Well, you are wrong.
They won.
We won?
Yes.
4-3, in the overtime.
We made it to the finals,
and without you.
That's great.
I don't believe it.
Yes.
Afterthe game the Hammerheads...
...lodged a complaint that Singhs...
...cannot play without a helmet.
Why didn't they do
anything until now?
I feel they never imagined
that you will make it this far.
They will nevertake off
theirturban to wearthe helmets.
So it's no use now.
Daddy, I was scared.
Daddy, look at him.
I am scared he might beat us too.
No, son, no one will hurt you.
Always remember.
When the Lord's your benefactor...
...no one can hurt you.
Our Guru has blessed
us with this turban.
He gave us his blessings.
Rememberthat? Understand. Look.
This is the Golden Temple.
I will take you there.
Akshay Kumar.
Next year I will take
you and your motherthere.
But how can ourturban protect us?
I will tell you how.
Look, this turban is our crown.
It's our inner strength.
History stands witness, son.
Whoever cast an evil on us,
always faced destruction.
The Sikhs have won so many wars...
...due to the grace of this turban.
And you know...
Daddy, who is he?
He is our great
emperor Kng Ranjit Singh.
He showed the world that...
...our Guru has turned us
into fearless warriors.
Glory to Lord Guru!
- Glory to Lord Guru!
My brave son.
Cut it.
That's a cut.
Here.
Great shot.
Yes.
Can I Have an autograph? - Sure.
Thank you.
Name?
Darvesh.
- It's for my father.
Father. Interesting.
He is Rajveer Singh.
Ice-hockey captain.
I mentioned about him earlier.
Oh Yes.
Nice meeting you.
Speedy Singh.
Yes.
It's an honour meeting you.
I wish that was True.
I am working on it.
Well, I wish I could come and
watch yourfinals. - Me too.
Anyway, good luck.
And if you win the party is on me.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
See you.
Maybe this will work.
But it will cost dearly.
Do you think you can
get this done in a week?
Yes, of course.
Where did you get this money from?
Trucking.
By driving trucks.
What's the league's
problem with us wearing a turban?
Coach.
What are they saying
Okay, we are all here.
Tell us what you wanted to.
I think it will be
better if Raj tells you.
What are you doing here?
This is ourteam meeting.
First thing.
Friends, please forgive me.
You all deserve this championship.
Much more than that.
That's not possible, friend.
We won't take off the turban.
We have hit dead end.
End of story.
I heard.
But I learnt a lot seeing
the courage of this team.
Coach, I don't deserve to
be the captain of this team.
Is that all you want to say?
No.
Look.
What is this?
Centuries ago, the
Gurus wore this in wars.
Now you all will protect
our respect and honour.
But this time, the
warwill be on the ice.
Listen, listen, listen.
Just a minute. Just a minute.
The officials won't
allow us to wearthis.
By the way, your
sister has informed them...
...how they can be worn.
Friends, with your permission.
According to Civil Court
Part one section eight...
...my clients are being
stopped from following theirfaith.
That's a human rights violation.
That's right.
Good point.
I don't know whether
this will work or not.
It already has.
And Raj has paid for
this from his savings.
And you can return it by
defeating Hammerheads.
Good luck.
Come on, coach.
Coach, please.
Friends. I told him if
he leaves he's gone.
And I am true to my words.
But I nevertold him that
I will nevertake him back.
"Wearwedding turban with
full moon studed on it"
"Today is the occassion of
your life time"
"Let's celetrate today,
our brother is going to mary"
"Brother is going to get maried"
"Let's all of us celeberate"
"Brother is goint to get married"
"Went on to toil for 12 years,
afterwhich he brought love"
"The wedding crown only looks good"
"Wedding crown only looks good
where groom's friends dance"
Excuse me! Please excuse me!
What? What happened?
Rina refuses to come out of her room.
But, why? - I don't know.
Oh, she is a devil!
She's is putting us down.
- Groom here already.
Go talk to him.
Go talk to your bride.
Why, what's wrong.
Just go, please.
In the dressing room.
Reena.
Reena, what are you doing?
What happened?
I don't know if I'll be
going ahead with this marriage.
You are telling me now.
I feel sometimes you
become so selfish.
You just want everything to
be the way you want it to be.
Not everything.
You came to my party and got drunk...
...even though you knew
that you can't digest it.
That was a party. - You don't
everwatch me reading news either.
I watch you all the time.
What was I wearing on Thursday?
Purple. Green. Sea green.
No. Red silk blouse tucked
into a bellbottom jeans.
What difference does that make?
I mean I record news.
Do you actually think we
are right for each other?
Look Reena, I have never
felt like this about anyone.
Reena, I have nothing except you.
I will try not to
think about myself.
I am kind of rascally.
But I have no control overthat.
I know. I know only you
can make me a better man.
Only you.
Alright.
Thank God you came out.
Sorry.
I have parked my
elephant in the no parking zone.
I might get a ticket forthat.
Teach him to at
least button his shirt.
Please calm down.
They will come.
I am calm. - You are not.
I'm sorry, dad.
Come, my Punjabi son. Rajveer Singh.
Welcome. Come home now. Okay?
Come on. Come on.
God bless. - Come on. It's
time forthe nuptial rounds.
Come on. Come on. Please.
Coming.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
this day is no ordinary day.
And not because I'm getting
married to my beautiful wife.
But because our reception will
take place at a hockey match.
My brother Rajveer
will play in that.
And my wife will cover it.
Go Speedy Singhs.
Seek His blessings.
And return victorious.
Whoever utters His
name shall be happy.
This is crazy.
These guys are spoiling the marriage
function for a hockey match.
This is foolishness.
Give me your hand.
And you're not going anywhere.
This is forthe championship,
father.
And I am playing.
I will really like it if you come.
No.
Go.
It's an auspicious day.
I will stay here.
Life is full of surprises, isn't it?
I don't like surprises.
Your son is special.
You must watch him play.
You might change your mind.
Great. Are they here forthe
hockey match or a wedding?
This must be the
biggest Punjabi contingent...
...everto watch a hockey match.
It's time forthe
finals of the Hyundai Cup.
Underdogs Speedy Singhs
Vs favorites Hammerheads.
Speedy Singhs performance has
won the hearts of the Canadians.
This is Reena Singh from SIN.
And I just got married.
All of you actually
look like warriors.
Thank you, Mr. Singh.
Thank you, coach.
Come on, Raj.
Come on, guys.
I could've never
done this without you.
Don't mention it.
Some things are better left unsaid.
Thank you.
Go Speedy Singhs.
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
Rock it! Go for it.
Speedy Singhs are wearing
the warrior Sikh helmets.
They look like
warriors ready for battle.
You saw those jokers?
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
Absolutely, Absolutely.
Today we'll find out if
Rajveer lives up to the hype.
'O Canada, our
home and native land.'
'True patriot love in
all thy sons command.'
'With glowing hearts
we see thee rise.'
'The True North strong and free! '
'From far and wide, O Canada,
we stand on guard forthee.'
'God keep our land
glorious and free! '
Alright. Boys, it's time.
Team work.
One, two, three.
Singhs!
Go, Tanveer.
That's a nice bucket on your head.
'Rajveer Singh has been
pushed away from the puck.'
'Hammer heads have put
in the Singhs zone.'
Come. Have a seat.
'They're taking a shot
from the corner point.'
'Lnderjit saves it.' 'But it
has rebounded and they score.'
This is just the beginning.
One minute into the game,
the Hammerheads...
...are leading by 1-0.
'There are more than 3 minutes
remaining in the first round.'
'And Hammerheads are
still leading by 1-0.'
Speedy Singhs have put
into the Hammerheads zone.
They've lost the Puck at the corner.
And Rajveer has been hit.
Oh my God!
What a hit!
Hey! Where is the goal?
Referee, are you blind?
He is blind.
O poor kid. Are you hurt?
Get lost.
I'll smack the referee. Jerk.
'This is bad.'
'We need assistance to
take him back to the bench.'
'He is badly hurt.' 'I hope
they don't sit him on the bench.'
'They need his talent badly
against the mighty Hammerheads.'
We're having lots of
troubles there.
Leku, go and destroy them.
Got it?
How are you now?
Absolutely fine.
If I see anything wrong...
...I will come to get you.
Only if you can catch me.
They are still leading by a goal.
The pace is picking up.
There are just three
minutes remaining.
A hard hit on the boundary.
Speedy Singhs have
changed their line.
Rajveer Singh has
picked it up from the line.
Put it in the Hammerhead zone.
And has taken out the defender.
And he can score.
But he has passed it to Jassi Singh.
And a goal!
Goal. Outstanding.
Well done.
What a goal.
Good. Very good.
We are starting the third period.
Everyone is together.
Friends, the game has
become more interesting.
Singhs have put the puck
into the Hammerheads zone.
And they have lost it.
Churchnick has put back
it to the center line.
Rajveer has cut the pass.
And has put the puck overthe
blue line of the Hammerheads.
He has the puck now.
He is dodging and
dunking the opposition.
And he has scored.
A beautiful goal by Rajveer.
Speedy Singhs are leading by 2-1
forthe first time in the game.
The entire stadium has erupted.
Hammerhead has control over it now.
There are is just one
minute remaining in the game.
And the Hammerheads
goal keeper is going out.
And a new attacker is replacing him.
Careful.
Picking it up from the corner.
Passing the puck.
Passing it again.
This is a difficult shot.
Oh! What a save by Jassi Singh!
Rajveer has it now.
He is off with it. He has
passed it to Deva Singh.
He takes aim at the unguarded goal.
Amazing. This goal
could seal Singhs victory.
Yes. Yes.
Oh. But he has saved it.
To the goal. To the goal.
Libiyu has the puck now.
He passes it to Martin.
The Singhs are already celebrating.
They must go back.
But they aren't able to.
Martin is unmarked.
And he has scored.
Oh. And time up.
And both the teams are even now.
We are into overtime now.
This is really disappointing.
Victory was within Singhs grasp.
Now the team that
scores first in extra time...
...will be the winner
of the Hyundai Cup.
Okay. Come on.
No worries.
Listen to me.
All I've known is that
winning is everything.
And we can do this
right here right now.
But you guys. You guys can
do something more than this.
About which I had never
thought before meeting you guys.
Tonight, you can show
the entire country...
...that you belong here.
Yes. I know you look different.
But if you go there and
do what I know you can do.
It will be clear
that you are champions.
Not them.
Three for Singhs.
One, two, three.
Singhs, Singhs, Singhs.
Singhs, Singhs, Singhs...
The extra time will start now.
Both the teams are super charged.
The team that scores
first will the champion...
...of this year's Hyundia Cup.
Singhs, Singhs, Singhs.
Singhs, Singhs, Singhs...
Your dreams of winning
will be destroyed for good.
This is the day of reckoning.
And the game begins again.
Both teams have swapped sides.
Hammerheads entering the
Singhs zone with the puck.
Morton is moving ahead.
He has picked up the
puck from the corner.
Rajveer Singh's
fabulous intervention.
And the puck is out again.
Morton still has the puck.
He has passed it to Libiyu.
Morton gets the pass again.
Morton passes it to Basal.
Basal has the puck.
He has passed it to
Churchnick Churchnick I's attempt.
What a save by the goalie.
Basal has the puck again.
Another attempt.
And he has saved it again. Amazing.
He has passed it to Rajveer Singh.
Rajveer slips it
through Morton and Churchnick
Amazing.
Fantastic dribbling there.
What is happening?
Rajveer Singh has broken away.
Now it is between the
goalkeeper and Rajveer Singh.
'Have you ever seen me play? '
'And I don't want to see either.'
'You deserve this.'
'And remember. I
hate people who ditch.'
'Son, you'll make me proud one day.'
He is taking the puck
to the left. Now right.
Overthe
goalkeeper's head. And goal!
Rajveer Singh has won
it for Speedy Singhs.
Yes. Yes.
Rajveer Singh has
won the match forthem.
And Speedy Singhs are the champions.
Yes. Yes.
Look. Look, that's my son. My son.
We won! We won!
We've won, coach.
You've done it.
Thanks, coach.
You are special.
Sorry, coach.
Go meet your dad.
I know this wasn't easy for us.
But today, you haven't made
just me proud, but all of us.
I was wrong.
Gurveertold me how
well you explained to him.
You're not just a good brother,
but a good son too.
I am glad that you
fulfilled your dream.
We're not that different.
You and me.
Love you.
I love you, dad.
God bless, son.
When did you come?
Mom.
My son.
Well done, champ.
Brother.
Did it, uncle.
Congratulations, brother.
Raj... - Come on, everyone.
Let us have a snap.
Sure.
Come on, everyone. Come. Come on.
So how does it feel?
To be honest, it feels great.
Okay. I quit hockey for your love.
I will never ask you to
leave something you love.
And you know I don't
like people who quit. Champ.
Come on, sweetheart.
"Yes."
"We were always told growing up."
"Just try to be the best
always try for success..."
.". And second place
is not an option."
"That's what we were told."
"So no matterwhat came up
in my life, I got through."
"That was my motivation and
now nothing can stop you."
"We will... never loose."
"Neverfear.
Overcome all and persevere."
"We are the best and
we down to show it."
"Any place any day
we will overthrow it."
"We will... never loose."
"Neverfear.
Overcome all and persevere."
"We are the best and
we down to show it."
"Down to show it."
"We are at the top
and never going down."
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
"Made it now take a look around."
"We are at the top
and never going down."
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
"Made it now take a look around."
"We win. We never lose.
When we enterthe battle."
"The enemies pray when
Punjabis enterthe fray."
"We are at the top
and never going down."
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
"Made it now take a look around."
"We are at the top
and never going down."
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
"Made it now take a look around."
"At the top and I'll
never coming down."
"Always stay
focused superstar bound."
"Always was the
dopest never got weak."
"Hairto the sky but
my earto the street."
"Put on the gas hands on the wheel."
"Got on my lap coz I'm
going forthe kill."
"Drink forthe nerves
smoke forthe stress."
"But death to the haters
and to hell with the rest."
"I don't pay my dues play my moves."
"Blow and hunt it down
walk a day in my shoes."
"Long time coming long time gone."
"Ten years been but
ten minutes strong."
"Never gave up I just won't lose."
"So many hits but I
just won't bruise."
"Rappers just dying and I
put them out of their misery."
"This Ludacris and I
came to make history."
"We showcase such great
play that we win the game."
"Punjabis are the
pride of the Sikhs."
"We are at the top
and never going down."
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
"Made it now take a look around."
"We are at the top
and never going down."
"Punjabis are bravehearts."
"Made it now take a look around."
"I am in love."
"A beautiful girl has mesmerized me."
"I am in love.
A beautiful girl has mesmerized me."
"Everyone is congratulating me."
"Come on, girl.
- Ourtrain is heading towards you."
"Dance, beautiful damsel.
"Come on, girl.
- Ourtrain is heading towards you."
"Dance, beautiful damsel.
Professional Translation Services
www.gts-translation.com