Subtitles DownloadedFrom:
WWW.ACAENTRENOS.NET
"Movies And DVD"
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Armando! Why do you care so much
for one calf
When the real money is on all the cows
Esteban, one day,
The ranch of my father will go
to the possession of my brother and I.
And we will need this calf.
And many, many others.
I keep telling you, he cares more for
a calf than what he does for women.
Yes, you're right, Manuel ...
But only cause I have not met my ideal woman.
I propose a race to the house!
Hopefully on the way home
nothing bad will happen.
And the fight will be fair!
Hide!
I have a bad feeling!
He's a drug dealer!
We must help this man.
And get murdered too?
Maybe he only
wants to know something?
Blessed Virgin Mary!
Praying will not help him.
We have nothing more to do
but to pray for him.
What are we doing here?
Perhaps your brother already come home?
Fuck yeah! Fuck yeah!
- Be quiet!
Come in.
Father, do you have a minute for me?
Well, what do you want?
- Excuse me, I did not want to bother, but ...
Where have you been, Armando.?
As you ordered, we directed
our cattle to new pasture.
And why so long? The house
and other work is incomplete, Armando.!
Something wrong, Dad?
- Don't bother me.
Armando!
- Yes, father?
Oh, come over here ...
I'm sorry ...
I have being disturbed by many thing.
Let ... I
I want to help you.
., ., listen.
You're so much like your  mother.
She had a kind heart,
and you too are very kindly.
But your mother was a silly,
And you too are such a fool.
But I got smart, Dad!
- Yes, l know,Armando.!
But to help me, you have to be
Well, at least a little  more intelligent.
And if you were smarter, you would know
that you ...Are a complete idiot.
Look ,such a hefty skull ...
Raul!
- Raul, your brother!
Is Raul!
No, no, no ... Agree on everything
with the Japanese and give it to them ,later will discuss it.
See you later.
- Raul!
Brother!
We're so close, brother!
And that! We have experienced many thins together!
Raul!
- Dad!
Finally the most Intelligent of my sons come back
You are my Favorite son, which
I always love more.
Oh, hell!
I almost forgot ...
Sweetheart!
Allow me to introduce you
Senorita Sonia Lopez.
Sonia Lopez!
- It is an honor to meet you!
Very, very nice!
Let me look at you.
And you should be,Armando!
Armando Alvarez, Senorita Lopez.
Welcome to our home .
Oh, thank you! Call me Sonia!
And I'll call you,Armando.
That would be nice, Sonia.
Hello! I am, Sonia.
I am Esteban de Los Santos Escobar Chavez.
Señor!
Thank you, Esmeralda.
you are Welcome.
Señor!
- Thank you!
Please!
Thank you, darling!
- Raul, you brought much joy to our father.
That's why I'm an Alvarez, right?
Know if would get rid of drug dealers
from our ranch ...
This morning I was with Manuel
Esteban and witnessed a murder.
And why did you not tell me?
Father, I saw that you were very upset.
They killed a man.
I think it was the Lynx.
The Lynx.
Senorita Lopez.
Sonia ...
How nice to see you.
I am glad that you came to us,
Here our very own Armando. Do not have
experience with the ladies.
As if they do not like them at all!
Is that true, .?
You don't have interest in women?
I would not say so, Senorita Lopez.
I have not met
the woman of my dreams.
And what should it be?
My woman, Senorita Lopez
Would love this land
no less than I love her...
More than all the gold of the world ...
She would have to enjoy the
scent of a cactus flower.
She would have to sleep under the stars,
and let the wild wind ...
caress her body
and shelter her soul.
Her joy will be my joys,
her dreams, my dreams ...
and our love ...
like a beautiful song ...
and this song is pure truth!
See, you're a hopeless romantic ...
What  woman would
agrees to sleep on the dirt?
I beg ...
Sonia! Come here!
Father, I ...
that if, Senorita Lopez
Sonia and I
We ask your blessing,
to marry.
Ask for blessings? You get married?
What a joy!
The Lord blessed the house of Alvarez!
Thank you! For Raul, and you, Sonia!
Good luck! For you!
For you!
For us!
- Thank you!
For you!
And for you, brother!
So is it true?
It is written here that Raul
is marrying this girl.
It is.
She's the most beautiful woman
I've ever seen.
Yes, she's very pretty.
It looks like you're not very happy, ..
Are you jealous of your brother?
Jealous?
No, Manuel,
I could never be jealous
of my own brother?
Simply, I love him very much,
and I am worried for him.
Worried?
Don't know, he's changed.
I think , you're just jealous!
I am so jealous!
If I had a woman like that
She would never leave my bed!
can you tell me the joke?
No,I think not, Senorita Lopez.
Our joke was about you.
Horseback ride?
I have not sat in the saddle for long
but I'll be happy to try !
Esteban! Manuel!
Check on the herd. And I'll meet you later.
Alright.
You are a good rider, Senorita Lopez.
Skillfully operate, excellent posture.
This is a naughty stud ...
obviously this was not your first.
I learned to ride before walking.
I see.
I was nine years old,
When my father was killed.
And I was sent to the city, to live with my uncle.
Interesting...
- My uncle was a wicked, bad man.
He drank industrial alcohol.
He beat me and put out cigarettes on me
Interesting.
At age 12 I ran away.
But he found me, beat me
and said that he would marry me.
Interesting.
And your uncle?
I have not seen him in long time.
I need you to ask about something.
Do you love Raul?
Raul is very good to me,
and I  to him.
Do you love him?
I have to know this.
I propose  a race! to show you
what kind of rider I am!
Well, we'll see!
How beautiful!
What is this place?
It ...
is called ...
Seven tears lake .
I come here to swin when I was a boy
This is the most beautiful place
I have ever seen!
How did you know,how to get here?
Wind told me to ...
Sometimes he talks to me ...
This is where my mother was killed.
It was her favorite place.
I have a lot of work.
Go, my hair is still wet.
don't take too long.
this region is full of bandits.
Armando will  protect me.
And it's true!
My son,this is my father's rifle.
He handed it to me,
When I was a kid
now I give it to you.
Go! You must build our house.
Armando!
What do you want?
Armando, give me the rifle!
Boy, give me the rifle!
No! Do not touch me! No!
Let me go! No! No!
No! Scum! Don't dare to touch me
Armando save me!
And she loved to come here.
I am sorry.
Long since it happened.
Perhaps I could
stay here forever.
That,I doubt it.
Why is that?
Here, there is nothing to buy!
No shops,
or expensive clothes,
or designer shoes.
This is not Dallas!
Such opinions you have about me, huh?
is not important what I think about you?
I have nobody else.
You think I'm cheap,
who's only after Raul's money?
Is it not so?
You have not answered my question ...
What question?
Do you love my brother Raul?
Take me  back to the house,Right now
First answer the question!
Bongo? Kong?
Shots!
- Where?
Over the hill.
Hunters?
- No, not hunters.
What if someone is in trouble?
- It's not our business.
You're a coward,
A coward!
Forgive me, Lord!
And accept my soul!
No, no, calm ...
We'll take you to the hospital!
Let him die pacefully .
He is missing an arm.
Give me water, .!
Spend the water on it?
There's a trunk! They are in the trunk!
Collect them!
Here, drink. This is the water.
Drink. Silence.
I know you. You ... Are you Sonia.
Thought so - the trunk is full of drugs.
Armando.
better to help me
put him on a horse!
He comes ...
The Lynx!
Maybe God will have mercy on me
and I will die sooner!
He's dead!
He was dead long before.
It looks like it is now yours.
You are now a bride with a dowry.
You do not want them?
Perhaps like a wedding gift
From an old friend?
Just before he die
I am tired of this ...
You don't love my brother.
Let me go! You're hurting me!
I thik that I know
what kind of woman you are.
You do not know nothing about me.
I  know that you won't be  Raul's wife,
while I'm alive.
And  you think
Raul so innocent.
Lies!
You silly shepherd!
Your brother is a drug dealer!
You did this!
And so help me God,
If this is true, and my brother
is a drug dealer,
You will never bear the name of Alvarez!
I take care of my family!
And the Devil take care of you.
Are you sure that Raul
is indeed selling drugs?
I do not know, Manuel ...
But I feel that something was wrong with him.
Since he's returned.
And this morning with Sonia?
Or maybe she's lying ?
All sluts lie.
You are right, sluts Always lie.
But Senorita Lopez
She's not a slut.
I love sluts.
You two wait here while I speak with Raul.
It is true?
What do you mean?
That you are a drug lord.
I have my business in Mexico City
what is the difference to you?
You have disgraced our family.
No, ., no.
I'm here to save our family.
Feel the difference?
You are dragging our family
to the very bottom of hell!
Listen ...
Yes.
I move drugs across the border.
I do sale them drugs .
To the gringos!
I don't sale it to our people.
To Americans,and I would be glad to sale them
chocolates,if that is what they want, but no!
They want drugs.
This is not the America
that our father worshiped?
This is a country of greedy children ...
They buy houses,without money.
TVs and cars without any money.
And shoved in their mouths,like monsters ...
These fatty shit-burgers ...
it's irresponsible to feed sweet to children
They are not children, ..
No ...
they are all adult and crazy.
Well they really cry like babies.
"Aw, Look at the Mexicans!
They gonna fuck us up and  killed
with their drugs! "
Fuck them all!
And fuck all those
children addicted to drugs!
Fuck them!
Fuck all those women that shove up heroin
And snort coke without stopping!
Fuck those potheads Doctors from California
What do I have to feel sorry for them?
If they want to snort shit
Somebody have to sell it to them, Armanito!
Yes, is not easy ...
But  we are infected with their greed!
We are going to end up
killing each other,
So we can feed  those chewing shit-burgers.
Crazy kids
Hey, .:
This country will become stronger, thanks to
the addiction of the Americans .
Oh, I know what I'm saying.
Whats Up?
Are you Raul?
You know perfectly well who I am.
And I know very well who you are
The Lynx.
Yes, the Lynx ...
Well, Raul, and what hell are you doing around?
Came to visit relatives...
I'm here
because ...
this is my land.
You fool,always playing around?
Such a joker your Brother .
But look Raul ...
I don't believe it!
You already took my woman
And I think you want something else.
This woman was never yours.
No? ...
No.
And I repeat ... I'm here
because ...
this is my land.
. ...
- Yes?
Can I call you Armandito?
I like it.
You know, what your brother does?
Know what he does for a living?
Is very dangerous for you.
And for him too.
It is dangerous for your entire family.
Hey, chill, chill, chill.
not all herdsman
Like Canadian slim menthol.
No, no, I like them slim.
Well, so what ...
Just come to give this to you ...
I think belongs you.
Thank you!
You are welcome...
Oh, Raul ...
This will get ugly.
alright.
Adios!
Have a nice day!
Chao!
Bye bye!
Bye, bye!
Good luck!
It appears that your Lynx
Doesn't want to follow your plan.
., go home.
Mexico,is no place for cowards.
I live my life on this land ...
And this land is all  I know.
I'm just a cowboy,
And that's all i know.
I do not know.
Why does not the moon shines by day and night?
I do not know!
Why the bird flutters in the sky?
Why so the turtle is slow ?
I do not know!
That's the way!
Why do not people love each other?
I do not know!
Why is brother against brother?
Why is a flower
red, and the other blue?
I do not know!
How should I know anything?
Where from? Where from?
And why would I want with it?
Viva Mexico!
I am a man of this land
I am a rancher.
And I do not know!
I lead a simple life,
I am the cow's friend!
Don't know how to kiss
After all, I'm just a cowboy!
I do not know!
Why girls are warm?
And my bed so cold?
I have only questions,
But I do not know the answers!
After only a cowboy I
And I do not know!
The only thing I am sure of...
Only the love!
Look!
It's a Lynx!
A white cat!
This is estrange ...
Let me kill it!
No. You can not kill such a beauty.
He came to us for a reason.
Yeah, so I shot him.
I do not know the reasons
But I think,
Has something to do with me.
Look at this country.
So beautiful.
So much pain?
He slept like a log last night.
I slept on a bottle of tequila .
What is this?
I do not know.
I have a bad feeling ...
You two do not get out.
Be careful.
. Alvarez?
Yes. That is my Name
I'm Vincent Blankardo.
Once I was your father's friend.
You found the body of my mother.
It's true ...
Too many years ago ...
., this gentlemans are from U.S.A ...
D.E.A
All right.
And how can I help them?
No, sir,
I do not speak American.
., I need your help.
Of course
We know that your brother
transports drugs across the border ...
We know that he came here,
to reclaim the area ...
From the Lynx.
I don't think I can help you, sir?
Parker.
My name is Parker ...
And I think that you
can  help me.
Listen,piece if shit
I make only one call,
And ten Helicopters will hoover...
Over that hill ...
and turn your ranch
Into a fired fart
So think carefully.
It is better this way, ..
Talk to Raul.
Find out everything for this Señor.
Now go find out.
Ladies and Gentlemen!
I want to thank  everyone of you
For honored me with their presence.
Tomorrow will be a
significant  day for the family Alvarez,
I'll be happy to share this
with all of you.
My sister, Carmen,
came from Guadalajara.
Margaret,that come all the way
from Puerto Vallarta.
My cousin and his wife, Hernan Dolet
- My friends for life.
And of course, Sheila from Atlanta
also arrived! Sheila!
Tomorrow we'll have a double celebration!
First, my beloved son, Raul
returned to the fold.
Second, he brought with him
This delightful woman,
Which he enjoys making love!
I raise my glass to Sonia, friends!
For Sonia! Cheers!
I also have something to say.
I thank you all for coming here from so far,Some ...
But I want to thank especially
to whom many of you often
called a fool, and slow-witted.
And he is a man with a big heart.
My toast is for my brother
.. For your happiness.
Come on, .!
You did not say back
a toast to his brother Raul?
Yes
I drink to the happiness of Raul.
I want you to enjoy the pleasures of earthly life ...
Even if it leads to the death of our family!
What are you talking about!
Calm down!
It pains me to say this,
but I do not want to see you
at the wedding of your brother!
Do you understand?
Get out of my house!
As you say, father.
Let him go!
Where are you going? Sit down.
You stay here with the guest
Go back inside,
Get back with your people.
Let's not create problems!
You think I like
What Raul is doing?
It's your business too.
We can change it
but i need your help!
You must know something.
What should I know?
He ...
That who is called the Lynx ...
That is my uncle.
I understand.
Won't stop till he get what he wants
You ran away from his problems,
but it brought them along.
Then, save us,Save your brother.
Save your family,Save me.
There are things
from which there is no salvation.
Father! Father!
Raul, who did it?
It was .?
Quiet, quiet, Dad ...
Do not say anything ...
Just do not die!
Do not die, Dad!
Hold on!
Armando was right.
Why should we stepped
on the threshold of this house?
Hold on, Dad! Hold on!
That's it! Everything will be fine!
Help!
Hello, Blankardo?
It's done.
And Sonia?
Sonia is still alive, as you requested.
All right.
And Raul?
Raul is still alive.
So, wait, wait, wait.
I pay you,so you will protect me
You are a police, That i pay!
Why are you not honest with me?
Why?
Do not worry,He will come to you.
We must figure out how to lure him.
His woman
Woman?
Sonia?
Sonia ...
My Little niece ...
Excellent, thank you!
Stop!
Esteban, my friend, what happened?
Your father got shot!
What?
At the wedding! Shot by assassins!
And Raul?
- Raul and the woman are ok.
But your father, you Father
He's dying!
Let's go! Hurry up!
Armand, come here.
Yes, father!
This is me!
Do you remember your mother?
Yes. I remember, but a little bit.
She was a very beautiful woman.
She was very beautiful.
The most beautiful in all of Mexico.
You got her eyes ...
Yes you told me many times ...
I had the eyes of a chick
Chick
I have not been kind to you.
I used to compared  you with
donkey and pigs.
Made fun of the way you speak.
Gave you to the circus a couple of times.
Please forgive me
I guess ...
I never forgive ...
you for the accident.
And now I'm very sorry about this.
I was hoping ...
that when I see
your mother in heaven;
I would say that her house
and her family is in order.
And what do I tell her now?
Father, you have to lie to her.
Tell her that Raul
married to a beautiful woman
and they have many children,
And the Alvarez family
is known throughout Mexico
for his generosity and honesty.
I'll lie to her...
Because I am ashamed
for the truth, ..
I'm so ashamed.
Dad ...
I'll kill the motherfucker that did this!
He was not killed by a man
He die of shame.
Sonia ...
Took his horse and left.
Take Esteban and find it, ..
Please
I'll help you find your woman.
But after we  Find her, alive or dead,
You will not see me again. Ever.
You hope that the water
wash away your shame?
Leave me alone.
I forbid you to swim here!
This is a holy place for me!
Swim?
No ...
I don't know swiming.
None ever taught me to swim.
Please!
I do not want to live!
You kill yourself?
you are an Imbecil!
How to live on?
You do not understand
I do not have salvation!
But you knew,
what you were getting into
When you come with Raul here.
Yes ...
Of course, I knew.
But he said that he will change ...
That he wanted to star a new life in the ranch
Tha everything will be diferent
And you, believed him?
Yes!
No ...
I do not know ...
Please .,
let me die, Raul, do not need me.
I came not for Raul.
Came for you
I not good...
I am worse!
Look at them.
Such pacified.
Wait a minute!
I thought you said
Raul's woman?
You said that she was Raul's woman.
She is the woman of Raul.
Why are you sleeping
with this dirty hairy shepherd?
I beg you,uncle ...
Well as long as you are happy ...
Cause raul don't have dick
I even began to
like the joke about the dick.
What do you want from us?
This is the land of my father.
You are trespassing.
No, I would not say so.
It would be better saying,
That you just trespass your  brother's wife!
Good joke, right?
Leave us alone.
Grab her
Let's see whether  Raul still interested on her.
Defend yourself
Or I will break you
apart with their bare hands.
I did not come to fight ...
Kill him
As symbolic that
You die at the same place,
where is your mother ...
If you would have let me rape her
She would not have died that day.
You!
kiss her for me, ..
Oh, you coward!
Wait,the gun is still  hot!
Shut up, motherfucker!
Let the coyotes devour him
And we need to reserve a couple of
bullets for her brother, right?
You never know
That went well...
You underestimate Raul.
No,no,no,
but he made a huge mistake,
In wanting to take away my territory.
So now he loses everything,
including you.
.!
I am the spirit of Ji-Kin Chan Kauuilya,
He who Darkest the Sky.
I am the King, Jaguar, lord of the mountains.
You know me as a Lynx.
Your journey has just begun.
It's time for your vision.
Mexico, is no place for cowards.
Save your brother.
Save your family. Save me.
TRUTH
A kiss for you  mother, ..
I hid in the mountains
but you are hiding
within himself.
It's not important where to hide, if ...
hiding
hidden for a reason.
TRUTH
I'm not putting the other cheek!
Neither for man, nor for beast!
I am!
Armando Alvarez!
Say it again.
I am.. Armando Alvarez
Let us do it once more.
I am Armando Alvarez
All right.
I am
He captured Sonia.
I'm glad you're coming with me, too.
No, Raul. I'm going alone.
Do not be silly.
I already had it for too long.
Lynx on the phone. How to help?
He gathered a small army.
Let them.
I'll take it.
Just keep out the Americans.
They did not
want to climb it.
They want you to
killed each other.
Excellent.
First we kill Raul,then we will take care
Of these pompous Americans.
Ok?
Bye! Bye!
Give me a minute.
Who the fuck thik he is this Lynx
He thinks he can come
into my house without an invitation?
Easily take my woman?
No!
I will not let him throw
a drop of my own blood!
The Lynx fucked up !
And you know what?
We will not allow him to
to get away this time!
He is a dead man!
Come with your uncle ...
I can give you all  Raul just promised ...
and more.
You are beautiful.
Thank you.
Slut!
Nobody will come to your rescue
He will come And will kill you.
Who? Raul?
I'm not talking about Raul.
You mean that hairy shepherd.
Yes ...
Sonia, why deceive yourself
I told you that I killed him.
He's dead!
And the wind whispers to me,That he is not.
that who's named the Linx
My name is Armando Alvarez!
I'm talking to you, Lynx!
I'm surprised that you're alive.
I want the girl
Let her go, and we leave in peace.
You're joking?
I can kill you with one shot.
I give you just one more chance.
Let go of the woman,
and I will let you stay alive.
Armando run!
Do you have a cigarette?
Yes ...
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fuck, . ...
You will never learn to roll one right?.
I promise. I swear. I'm sorry.
It'll do.
Heck,
I'm dying here, and you love me
such a muck of grass?
I'm sorry.
She ...
loves you.
I just realized it. Go for it.
It is a pity,
Dad would have loved to see it.
Go for her ...
It's all over ...
I'll go see dad.
Stay here, please!
It's all over.
Mexico will be a better place
without me ...
It's time ...
I am Armando Alvarez!
I've come to kill you!
How dare you come this way?
So rude,without an invitation as well?
You invited me when you took my woman.
Do you want her? Then catch her!
Well, now both die.
"The fire bull"
Fuck this
I thought than ...
when this would happen,
I would be surrounded by people
TV cameras ...
The police ... Special Forces,
President, and all that ...
Apparently, will not be like that ...
Damn.
You're under arrest
for murder and drug trafficking.
You will be extradited to the U.S.
where you will be judged.
There will be no trial.
This is for my mom!
Oh, you son of a bitch!
You run out of luck
fucking wetback.
Not all ... Americans
are bad, ..
Not all Mexicans
we are drug dealers.
Are you ready, Sonia?
- Yes. Let's go home.
Good bye!
Good bye
You want to walk?
Subtitles Downloaded from:
WWW.Acaentrenos.Net
"Movies And Dvd"
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org