Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Okay.
One picture and we're history.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Come on.
Oh, man, do we have to do this?
You want everyone in school
to think we're chicken?
I could live with that.
You wuss. Come on.
I don't see anything. Do you?
No, I don't see anything.
Let's just take the picture
and get out of here.
Fine. Here, take the picture.
Wait, I should be in the picture, too,
or no one will believe I was here.
Shut up and take the picture!
You take the picture.
- You take it!
- You!
Guys, don't fight.
I'll take the picture.
Say "cheese."
A ghost!
"...and to the Save the Dolphins
Foundation, $11 million.
"To the Save the Pumas
Foundation, $1.2 million.
"To the Patagonian
Wasp Salvation Fund,
"$1.4 million.
"To the Dyslexic
Dalmatians Foundation..."
To hell with the livestock. What
did the old stiff leave me?
I believe that what the
bereaved is trying to express
is that the sudden death
of her only father
has left a great gaping void
in her bank... in her life.
And Carrigan wonders what he
has left her to fill it up with.
Let's see.
"Bobcats, owls,
"snakes,
"daughter Carrigan,
"Whipstaff Manor in Maine."
And?
And I'm late for lunch,
so if you'll excuse me...
Are you telling me that I just spent the
last two days holding his clammy hand
waiting for him to kick it, and all I
get is one lousy piece of property?
No, it was lousy 50 years ago.
Now it's condemned. Enjoy.
Wait a minute. This is not fair!
I'll contest, and then I'll drag you and
all of those damned dolphins into court.
Knock yourself out.
Dibs, this is all your fault.
As usual. If you would have
just forged the damn will.
This is condemned
seafront property.
Dibs, don't you get it?
Flipper got more money than me.
Carrigan! The deed's in there!
My God.
"Buccaneers and buried gold,
"Whipstaff doth a treasure hold."
Treasure?
Dibs, you idiot! Get it out.
I knew that place was worth something.
There's treasure in that house
and finally, I'm going
to get what I deserve.
Carrigan, I think I need a doctor.
There's plenty in Maine.
So, what do you think?
I think you're going to get wet.
Wait! Carrigan!
Dibs, light!
What a dump.
This place is fabulous.
You could just do so much with it.
- I know it's a bit spooky.
- Dibs.
Hello.
Who is it?
Afraid I can't answer that.
Why not?
It's kind of hard to explain.
Is he the caretaker?
Are you the caretaker?
No.
Is he a drug dealer?
Is he... Are you a transient?
No, not exactly.
Then tell him to show himself.
Show yourself!
Here's the thing. If I do, don't
scream, okay? I get that a lot.
Are you a burglar?
I must warn you that I am armed.
Hello?
Cut the crap. If you don't show yourself,
I'll have you arrested for trespassing.
Okay, calm down, lady.
Here I come!
Hi! I'm Casper.
No, you shouldn't do that,
or you'll wake the...
Too late.
So tell me. You have experience?
I have quite a bit of experience. Not,
you know, like, exactly doing it,
but I've studied it, and I've
talked to people who have done it.
I've seen the videos, and I feel very
confident that with my knowledge
I could do it, no problem.
Then you can handle this?
It's like no problem whatsoever.
Piece of cake. Piece of crumb cake.
Well? How did it go?
It was fine. Was no
problem. Piece of cake.
Who you gonna call?
Someone else.
What do we do now?
What do I usually do when
something stands in my way?
Are you sure we're not going
a tad overboard here?
Dibs, I have huffed and puffed. Now
I want to rip this place down.
I want my treasure. They can't haunt
a pile of rubble, for Christ's sake.
People, please!
You're sweaty male construction
types, for Christ's sake!
Dibs, do something!
Come on, get out of there!
Charlie, quick, keep running and
don't look back! Run, Charlie!
Wait! They were just
kidding! Honest!
Every time.
All I want is a friend.
Did you ever feel the way
Priscilla Cow felt
that you'd like to be
completely different?
Almost everybody feels
like that once in a while.
But most of the time
I hope you can be
glad to be yourself.
That's really something
to celebrate.
A ghost!
More on the Pentagon playboys
as the story unfolds.
But, now...
step aside, Sigmund Freud.
Jump back, Joyce Brothers.
It's Dr. James Harvey,
therapist to the dead?
Are you depressed? Are
you anxious? Are you lonely?
Do you need someone to talk to?
No problem, if you're a ghost!
You can call them ghosts if you like,
or as I prefer, the living impaired.
But the bottom line is,
they need help sometimes
just like the rest of us.
After the sudden unexpected
death of his wife, Amelia,
Dr. Harvey gave up
conventional psychiatry
and some say conventional sanity.
Now, along with his loner
daughter, Kat, short for Kathy
Doc Harvey travels from town to town,
searching for paranoid poltergeists,
scared specters, the
depressed and the dead.
How do you feel about
your father's livelihood?
Please don't ask me any questions.
Do you believe in
ghosts? Ever seen one?
Does your father
hurt you in any way?
He's my father.
Could you just talk to us?
Look, it's the first day of school
and I'm sure I'll have homework,
so could you please...
Carrigan.
What part don't you understand?
No, not "I ate fish." I hate fish.
Don't you people have cows here?
Listen, I have had a
long and tiring day.
Do you think that you could bring me a
pint of Häagen-Dazs ice cream, rum raisin
and a Diet Pepsi? Think
you can handle that?
Now you want me to hold. Fine.
...and with therapy they can
begin to process this pain.
They can pack up their emotional
baggage, and they can move on.
My Harry passed away five years
ago, but he was so miserable.
His spirit would not
leave the apartment.
So I called Dr. Harvey.
He came over
and in a few weeks Harry left
smiling.
The living-impaired are
known for haunting us.
My question is,
what's haunting them?
It's a lack of resolution.
Ghosts are simply spirits
without resolution.
With unfinished business. And it's
my job to find out what that is.
And so Dr. James Harvey
continues his work
dragging his daughter along for the
ride. This week they're in Santa Fe,
but next week, "boo" knows?
Now, from the ghost
shrink to shrinking...
Yes, I'm still here.
Get me Santa Fe.
That's life!
That's what all the people say
You're ridin' high in April
Shot down in
I'm sorry about your
Cactus Spooners.
Crooners.
I don't care what they said,
you are not demented.
You're a picture of mental health.
They were talking about you.
Try explaining afterlife therapy
to a bunch of junior high kids.
Some people go through life
never questioning the norm.
But you and I, we're doing something
extraordinary with our lives.
No, we aren't doing anything.
You're the one who's been packing up my
stuff and moving me around the country.
I mean, in two years, I have
been to nine different schools.
I've eaten in nine
different cafeterias.
I mean, I can't even
remember anyone's name.
For once, I would just like to be
in one place long enough
to make a friend.
Honey, you will.
Right.
I mean, come on, we're
moving to Friendship, Maine.
Even I might make one.
You better, Dad, 'cause
a single guy your age
is more likely to become a bank
hostage than to make new friends.
You sound like your mother.
You're not gonna find her.
Mom's not a ghost, Dad.
Yes, she is. She has
unfinished business.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
I'll tell you what
you go with me this one last time.
If I don't find what I'm
looking for, then it's over.
No more moving,
no more ghost mining.
You promise?
I promise.
Deal.
It's not so bad.
If you're Stephen King.
Dr. Harvey, hello.
I'm Carrigan Crittenden.
And this is Dibs.
Hello. I'm a close personal friend.
And this is my daughter, Kat.
His close personal daughter.
How nice to meet you, Kat.
Very nice to meet you.
You have a beautiful daughter.
Very beautiful.
We are very happy that you could
come all the way to Whipstaff.
Very happy.
The both of us.
You're kind of hurting my face.
Sorry. Now, Dr. Harvey
exactly what kind of time
frame are you looking at?
Please tell me you'll just go in
the house and spray and that's it.
No. As with a traditional
psychological cure
it can take weeks or even years...
Excuse me!
Did you just say the word "years"?
It's conceivable.
No, it isn't. Days is conceivable.
Weeks, maybe.
Possibly.
Months, no. Years, forget it.
- Forget it.
- Dibs, check.
Get the bouquet. Now, Dr. Harvey
I will be watching
you very closely.
These are for you.
Have a lovely night.
Wow.
It's her. She's here. She's
in my house. I did it!
What if she likes me?
What if she doesn't?
"Hi, I'm Casper. I'm a ghost."
No, that's total disaster.
"Yo, I'm Casper.
What's up? Give me four."
God, I'd kill for a pinkie.
See? That was easy.
Yeah.
Pennies should hold for now
but we ought to get a box
of 20 amps in the morning.
Right, yeah, 20s should be fine.
All right, I'm gonna
go find a room, Dad.
You gonna be all right alone?
If I'm not back in 10 days,
send a search party.
"Stretch"
"Fatso"
and "Stinkie"?
Man, they had cruel parents.
I wonder where Doc and Dopey sleep.
Dad, I found my room!
There's a girl on my bed.
Yes!
Space master! In here.
It's very scary.
Have you seen any surprises yet?
Please. This is the
deadest place yet.
This is a nice room.
Right. This place is
a freak's holiday.
Mom belongs over here.
How about if I help you unpack?
Why bother? We'll just be repacking
in two weeks anyway, right?
I'm kidding.
This place is fine.
Good.
Night, bucket.
Night, Dad.
We're gonna be glad we came.
You watch.
Hi.
Man!
Perfect first impression.
What a jerk!
Better?
Honey!
Honey, what?
Dad, I saw a ghost!
- It was a real, live ghost!
- Slow down. What are you saying?
I saw a ghost.
And it had a head, it was round, it
was white and see-through, and...
Wait a minute. Now maybe...
Dad, please.
Do not think I'm as crazy as I
thought you were. I promise.
No, but remember, ghosts
can't hurt you, okay?
They're simply spirits with
unfinished business, all right?
Let's just see about
this ghost, all right?
Come here. Come on.
Over here. Check here.
See? No ghost there.
And then we can check
over here, all right?
No, there's no ghost in there.
We can even check over here.
There. See?
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
Dad, put me down!
This is insane. What are you doing?
I can walk, you know.
My God, this is big.
- Dad?
- What?
We're in a closet.
Right. Now I want you to stay in
here no matter what you hear, okay?
Okay.
- Wait!
- What?
Dad, I'm sorry.
For what?
For not believing you. For
thinking you were a total loser.
Apologize later.
Blew it!
Uh-oh.
It's them.
- Giddyup there!
- Go, horsie!
Man oh, man, them ponies run
faster when we go down to Belmont.
Here, Flicka.
Hey, guys. Have fun?
Look, it's Casper!
Now on a scale of 1 to 10,
10 being fun and 1 being you
yeah, we had fun.
Giddyup there.
Say, Bulbhead, why ain't you
inside doing your chores?
Yeah, where's dinner? I'm starving.
Look at me, I'm wasting away here.
I know. How about you guys relax out
here and tonight we'll eat alfresco?
Sounds great. Who's that?
Short-sheet, you wouldn't be trying to
keep us out of the house, would you?
No!
I can see right through that
bulbous little head of yours.
It's just such a lovely night.
I thought we'd have fun just
eating under the harvest moon.
Shine on, shine on harvest moon
Up in the sky
Bye-bye!
Hold it.
Fatso, you smell something?
Yeah.
No, besides him.
Hello?
No need to be afraid.
Yeah, right, don't be afraid.
I'd like to make contact with you,
but just one little thing, please.
Don't pop out from under a rug or
through a keyhole. No spooking.
Let's get beyond that.
I would like to approach you.
Now I'm coming in the room.
I'm in the room.
Can you deal with that?
Dive!
Dad?
I'm gonna kill you, your mama
and all her bridge-playing friends.
You think you got it
tough? I got a facelift.
There was one just
like it underneath.
Dad?
Boys, we got a closet case here!
Smell-o-gram!
Sushi, anyone?
California roll coming up!
All for one and one for all!
Catch your pants before they fall!
On the runway, we have Dr. James
Harvey wearing smashing underwear.
Marky Mark he's not!
You are good.
Stop. It's you.
Are we scary or what?
And it looks as if we're gonna
go into sudden death overtime.
Anybody for a little shish ke-doc?
I am.
Who do you think you
are defiling our domicile?
Dr. James Harvey, your therapist.
Dad!
Are you okay?
Dad.
And he's down for the count.
A winner by a clean stink out!
Get back.
What the hell is that thing?
Not the nose!
I'm being hosed!
No!
This sucks.
Dad? Are you okay?
I'm fine. Why don't we go regroup?
- Get your hand out of my mouth!
- I found half a Twinkie!
- Who let one?
- Who do you think?
Who's got their
pointy head in my...
That's not my head.
You know, fellas, we're
never this close anymore.
Morning. No, please don't scream.
I promise, I won't hurt you.
I'm a ghost. Yes, I admit it,
but I'm a friendly ghost.
You have to trust me. If you
scream, you'll wake up my uncles
and they get awfully cranky. I'm
gonna let you go now. Okay?
You're so cold.
Yeah, but it saves in
the heating, though.
Come on.
It's okay.
I can see right through you.
It kind of happens when
you don't have any skin.
What are you made of?
You know that tingling feeling
when your foot falls asleep?
I think I'm made of that.
Sunny-side up kind of makes me yak.
No problem.
So, can you go invisible?
That one's easy.
It's fresh.
Go ahead.
I've never done this before.
Me, neither.
- Can you hurt me?
- No.
Can I hurt you?
No.
Cool.
Morning, Dr. Harvey.
Some breakfast?
You okay?
Good.
How about a paper? The New York
Times? The Journal? Hong Kong Press?
- Sure.
- Coming at you.
Hope you're hungry.
I love the smell of
fleshies in the morning.
I'm melting.
Auntie Phlegm.
What a world!
- They're gone.
- What happened?
They must have crossed over.
Don't think so!
Guess again, Bonebag!
Fellas. Good morning.
Casper.
How dare you serve these
air-sucking intruders before us.
I was just...
Give me my
meal!
Okay.
I feel like Oprah on hiatus.
You look like Oprah on hiatus.
Ketchup, please.
You know what the problem is?
Casper's got no respect for us.
After all we've done for
the little glowworm.
What the hell do you think
you're doing, Bulbhead?
This floor used to be dirty
enough to eat off of.
But we have company.
Yeah? Company loves misery.
You guys are disgusting,
obnoxious creeps.
Thank you.
I mean, what's your problem?
He's just cleaning the floor.
Shut up, Skinbag.
- Piss off.
- Take a hike.
- Get a grave.
- Honey!
...school thing and you
don't want to be late...
- Drop dead!
- Too late!
You go have a lot of fun.
I know you will.
All right, guys, we've obviously
gotten off on the wrong foot here.
Now, you know and I know that
you really shouldn't be here.
So I'll tell you what.
Why don't you go ahead
and finish your meal
and we can meet in my office
and start the process
of crossing over.
What do you say?
It's your hour.
Watch it!
Amber, wait up!
Had that locker last year.
Thanks.
My name's Vic.
Kat.
Coming, Vic?
Okay, gang, let's settle down!
Put a lid on it!
I got a couple of
announcements to make.
First. The asbestos removal from the gym
is taking a little longer than planned.
So we're gonna have to push
back the Halloween Dance
just by a couple of months.
As most of you know, my parents
have finished the new boathouse.
So I'm sure it'd be no problem
having the party at my place.
Great. That's done.
Secondly, we have a
new student today.
I'd like you all to
meet Harvey Kathleen.
Would you like to come up and
say hi to everyone for me?
Why don't you tell us something
special about yourself, Kathleen?
It's Kat.
I guess I just moved here
with my dad from Santa Fe
and Friendship seems like
a pretty friendly place.
So where are you guys living?
In outer space?
No. Whipstaff.
You've heard of it.
You actually live there?
Yeah, I mean...
I know it looks kind of funky and
stuff from the outside and everything
but, I mean... I don't know,
inside it's kind of cool.
Yeah, if you drink blood.
Mr. Curtis, check this. We're dead
for the Halloween Dance, right?
This girl has a seriously creepy
house with room to spare.
Wait a minute. I thought we were
having the party at my place.
Okay, we'll take a vote.
Whoever wants the party at
my house, raise your hand.
Whipstaff?
"Johns Hopkins University."
Very impressive.
- Very.
- Pull!
Not this one.
Thank you, gentlemen.
What a dish, Doc.
The little missus, perhaps?
Fatso, you animal!
Is she available, Doc?
She's my wife, Amelia.
She's deceased.
Even better.
But we're not here
to talk about me.
See? Now don't you feel just awful?
I was just goofing.
Don't be goofing on Amelia.
She's as nice a person as they come.
She's always treated you right, Stinkie.
I got no complaints. She's
always been an angel to me.
Wait a minute. What are you saying?
I'm saying she's a peach.
None better. Why?
You've actually seen her?
What, you think I'm blind?
Of course, I've seen her.
Who hasn't?
What, you're not looking
for her, are you, Doc?
That's not really the focus
of our sessions here, is it?
But as long as you raise the issue
you wouldn't have a way of
contacting others like yourselves
would you?
I didn't think so.
Now that's not generally
allowed there, Doc.
I mean, you got to
go through channels.
Yeah, paperwork.
- Red tape.
- A holy mess, you know what I'm saying?
But for you, I don't know, maybe
we could work something out.
You keep that ghoul
Crittenden off our backs
and I'd say we got
a deal. Right, boys?
Deal?
Deal.
Fatso, you know where
Amelia floats. Go.
It's that easy, huh?
We got a ghost-to-ghost network.
We share haunting stories.
We throw parties.
The parties are always
pretty dead, though.
That was fast.
I think it's for you, Doc.
Go.
Amelia?
My man!
What are you doing... I mean, hi.
Can I come in?
No. It's so much
nicer out here in
the flesh... Fresh air.
So did you ask your
dad about the party?
Yeah.
He kind of hit the ceiling, but
I think it's gonna be okay.
Cool. So listen
if you're not hooked up with anybody
else, you wanna... I don't know
you wanna hang out
with me at the party?
I'd love to.
All right. Cool.
All right, see you.
Okay.
- Well, did you ask her?
- Yeah.
And she actually believed you.
This really bites.
No, it's absolutely perfect.
See? I'm a good dancer.
I don't need a costume.
I'm always the life of the party.
Casper! Listen,
I know you want to go.
Come on, we'd have a
great time together.
Casper, I have a date.
What's this Vic guy
got that I don't?
A pulse.
Big fleshy deal.
A tan.
Very bad for your skin.
How about a reflection?
Okay, but can he do this?
Come with me if you want to live.
Casper, no. Don't!
Casper, no. Oh, my God.
High, this is very high!
Casper!
Casper, this is beautiful.
I come here every night.
Alone?
What were you like
when you were alive?
I was...
I don't remember.
You don't remember
anything from your life?
No.
So, nothing?
You don't remember what
school you went to?
How old you were?
Your favorite song?
What about your dad?
Not even your mom?
Is that bad?
No. It's just kind of sad.
I wonder why you don't
remember anything.
Guess 'cause when you're a ghost
life doesn't matter
that much anymore.
So you forget.
Sometimes I worry that
I'm starting to forget.
Forget what?
My mom.
Just certain things.
The sound of her making
breakfast downstairs.
The way she put on her
lipstick, so carefully.
I do remember.
She always used Ivory soap.
And when she'd hug me,
I'd breathe her in so deep
and I remember, before
I'd go to sleep
she'd whisper in my ear,
"Stardust in the eyes, rosy cheeks,
"and a happy girl in the morning."
If my mom's a ghost, did
she forget about me?
No. She'd never forget you.
If I were alive
would you go to the
Halloween Dance with me?
Can I keep you?
Casper, close the
window. It's cold.
Hey, Dad.
I found your Visa card.
Where was it?
In your wallet. I was thinking,
maybe I could use it
to buy this perfect costume
I saw in a store downtown.
You always made your costume.
No, Mom did.
I think I could come up
with something pretty good.
Why don't we just roll you in aluminum
foil and you could go as a leftover?
Don't worry. You always look cute.
I don't wanna look cute. Cute's
like when you're nine years old
and you've got papier-mâché
around your head.
I wanna look
nice.
Like date nice.
Really?
Honey, you know, I think maybe
it's time that we sat down...
It's a little late for that, Dad.
How late?
Don't worry, not that late.
Good.
You know that I would love to buy
you everything that you wanted
but until Miss Crittenden pays me,
that thing is pretty worthless.
That's okay. Don't worry about it.
I'm sure I can come up with
something perfect for the party.
It's my party, and
I'll die if I want to
Die if I want to
Dad, please.
Whatever you do, don't
let those guys crash it.
I think they're actually getting
to be quite focused now.
You will die, too,
when it happens to you
Big finish.
Scream or sugar?
The patient has finally arrived.
Late again, I see.
Could this be an expression
of hostility, Doc?
It's your hour, Freud.
What, so silent? No pearls
of wisdom today, Doc?
Come on, Doc. Stay
tough, don't stop.
Come on, Doc, hang with us
homeboys. Wait a second.
What? You ain't thinking about
packing it in now, are you, Doc?
We're just starting to have fun.
It ain't often we meet a
bonebag as amusing as you.
Boys, this is serious.
I think the doc is having one
of them fleshy breakdowns.
Time for drastic measures.
You think we should sing a song?
No. I think it's time we gave
the doc our own prescription.
But what about the party?
The party'll have to wait.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Gentlemen.
- Happy hour.
Ninety-nine bottles of beer on the
wall, ninety-nine bottles of beer
Here's to dead guys!
This is an outrage.
This is appalling.
You pay a man to get ghosts out
of the house and what does he do?
He gets the ghosts
out of the house.
Exactly.
It's about time.
Look familiar?
I know this!
I had five fingers. I remember.
Hootie!
And wait!
Check it out.
Hands up, Kat!
It was my mom's.
Can I?
Go ahead.
It's perfect. Do you think I could
wear it to the party tonight?
Casper?
I begged and begged my
dad to get me this sled.
He acted like I couldn't even have it
'cause I didn't know how to ride it.
Then one morning I came down for
breakfast and there it was, just for me.
For no reason at all.
I took it out and went
sledding all day.
My dad said that's enough but I couldn't
stop. I was having so much fun.
Then it got late, it got dark.
It got cold
and I got sick.
My dad got sad.
What's it like to die?
Like being born.
Only backwards.
I remember, I didn't go
where I was supposed to go.
I just stayed behind
so my dad wouldn't be lonely.
Is that your dad?
"McFadden claimed that he was
haunted by the ghost of his dead son
"and that he invented a machine
to bring him back to life...
"The Lazarus."
Sorry. I guess we'll have
to take the long way.
Hurry up! Come on!
My dad hid it so no
one could find it.
But I remember where it is!
Wait till you see it.
Don't you know a shortcut?
You got it.
Casper, no.
Wall! Human! Stop!
Hey, over here.
Go ahead. Sit down.
I would hold on.
Why?
Casper!
Well?
What was that?
The "Up and At 'Em Machine."
My dad was a great inventor
but he had trouble getting
going in the morning.
Didn't he ever hear of caffeine?
What is all this?
My dad's lab.
Kind of a slob, wasn't he?
Here, he could do whatever he
wanted to. No matter how busy he was
he would drop everything
to play pirates with me.
Man, we had so much fun!
Aye, matey. Buccaneers
and buried gold.
Whipstaff doth a treasure hold.
Come on.
So where's this Lazarus thing?
You're looking at it.
Down there?
That's useful.
I know there's a way
to get it going.
I just can't...
What about that?
That?
That's the vault.
Wait! It's got to be this!
Hey, I did it!
Lazarus.
- What is this?
- Careful!
That's what makes the
whole thing work.
Kind of an instant
primordial soup mix.
It's what brings
ghosts back to life.
Just enough for one.
Pull the lever.
Which one?
I don't know. Try one.
Casper.
I'm gonna be alive.
How am I gonna do this?
I couldn't even get my
Easy Bake oven to work.
Casper?
Am I alive?
Do you have any idea
what this means?
Yes!
No.
You don't have to be
scared of death anymore.
One minute you're a ghost
next you're back on your feet
free to come and go as you please.
- Hell, you could even fly through...
- Walls!
Thick walls.
Thick as steel.
Certainly could get to
whatever's behind those walls.
Like a treasure, for example?
Then snap, crackle, pop, you're back
alive and on your way to the Riviera.
If you were a ghost.
If you were.
Damn it, Dibs.
This won't hurt a bit.
Stop being such a weenie!
It's just business. Come on!
If you would just...
So there you are.
Dibs, you're taking this
way too personally.
Wait!
Carrigan?
Are you a ghost yet?
Carrigan!
What a tragic waste.
She had my favorite sunglasses.
Not so fast, little man.
The bitch is back.
Warden threw a party
at the county jail
The prison band was there
and they began to wail
The band was playin' hard
the joint began to swing
You shoulda heard those
knocked out jailbirds sing
Let's rock
This Dr. Harvey's got a lot of
spirit, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, but he's got his whole
miserable life ahead of him.
So we could do him a favor
and put him out of his misery.
Yeah. Good idea.
We've been the ghostly
trio long enough.
Time to make it a quartet.
Can I just say something here?
Get a little personal?
Yeah. Why not?
Well, you know.
I just got to tell you
you guys remind me
of what it's like
to hang out with the boys.
I mean
you are absolutely
there for each other.
I mean
you look like right in the face.
You say, "I'm a ghost.
I don't need you."
You know what?
I'm gonna tell that
Miss Critten Picken...
Crichton Critten.
I'm gonna tell that lady
you ain't going anywhere.
It's your house.
You're haunting it.
Possession is nine-tenths
of the law...
- No.
- Yes.
No.
Yes.
I didn't think so at first
but you guys are great.
I love you.
No.
What a sweetheart.
I can't croak him now.
Me, neither. No way.
All right, boys.
The night is young.
We are going to clean out
every bar this town has got!
We're gonna booze
it until we lose it.
Come on.
I think my ears just popped.
Come to mama!
My treasure!
You mean my treasure.
Miss Crittenden?
In the flesh.
Well, in a couple of minutes.
Dibs! What are you doing?
This is no time to shave!
Helping you. Remember?
Remember what?
This!
You stole that. That's Casper's.
So sue me!
Dibs! The capsule, now!
Coming. I'm coming, okay?
Keep away from me!
Here!
Jump in!
Perfect.
We're here.
Okay.
Hi. Come on in.
This is the room.
Stay together, you'll be safe,
and I'll be right back.
Amber, do we have to do this?
She wants a Halloween party.
She's gonna get a Halloween party.
That's my treasure!
- Stay back! Keep away from me!
- Casper.
Don't come near me,
you spiteful spook.
I'll knock you into the next world!
Come on. Let's go.
Hey, Poppin Fresh.
It's my turn in the oven!
Dibs! Get this thing cooking,
you flaccid little worm, you!
How kind of you to drop in.
You know, if there's one
thing I've learned from you
it's always kick them
when they're down.
And, baby, you're six feet under.
Oh, what a shame.
Sorry, sweetheart.
We're through.
I am not gonna forget this, you
ungrateful lousy little worm, you!
You can haunt me all you want
but it's gonna be in a
great, big, expensive house
with lovely purple wallpaper
and great big green carpets.
And a little dog called Carrigan.
A bitch, just like you!
I got the power!
I got the treasure!
And you have a flight to catch.
Any other takers?
No. But aren't you
forgetting something?
What?
Your unfinished business.
My what?
You know
unfinished business.
All ghosts have
That's why they don't cross over.
Unfinished business? I have
no unfinished business.
I have my treasure, my mansion.
I have everything!
I'm just perfect!
Wait, I lied!
I have unfinished business.
Lots of unfinished business.
I'm not ready to cross over yet!
Wait! You tricked me,
you rotten little brats!
No!
My treasure!
A ball? That's your treasure?
Are you kidding?
It's autographed by Duke Snider
of the Brooklyn Dodgers.
My favorite player.
Casper
it's time.
Honey, I'm home!
Dad?
No. What have you done to him?
Nothing. He's just a little dead.
I'm free!
I've never felt so good in my life!
I can fly!
Rookie.
Stinkie, work with him.
Dad?
Who's the girl?
Dad, it's me. It's Kat!
Kat?
Kat Ballou?
Katatonic?
Katastrophic?
Kreplach soup?
Flash flood alert.
Don't you remember?
Yeah, I remember!
No, this.
Kat.
Sweetheart.
What have I done?
Kat, don't cry.
Please.
Come on, Dr. Harvey. You
need this more than I do.
Casper.
This is the way it's got to be.
Dad?
Honey.
It felt like the strangest dream.
I thought we almost lost each
other for a minute there.
Oh, bucket.
Your party started without you.
Your date's probably waiting.
Maybe we should get going.
Where are we?
Well, go ahead.
What about you?
This is your party.
Go do your thing.
Go hang
or chill
or kick it, or
whatever you call it.
I think you got a date out there.
Thanks, Dad.
I hope no one saw that.
Hold still.
I'm trying. Could
you weigh any more?
Just shut up and get
your head down.
You got to see this.
People are gonna freak.
Let me see.
Cool.
Thank you.
You're...
That's right.
Kat's mom?
Are you an angel?
That was a very noble thing
you did tonight, Casper.
I know Kat will never forget it.
She needs her father.
And I know yours will
never forget it either.
You've fulfilled his
greatest dream, Casper
and I know he is very proud of you.
And for what you've done
I'm giving you your
dream in return.
But it's just for tonight.
Sort of a Cinderella deal.
So I have until midnight?
Ten.
Hey! Cinderella got until midnight.
Cinderella wasn't 12 years old.
I told you I was a good dancer.
Can I keep you?
Casper?
Hello, James.
Amelia.
It's all right.
It's just me.
I thought I'd have a hundred
things to say when I...
How?
Let's just say you know three
crazy ghosts who kept their word.
James, I know you've
been searching for me.
But there's something
you have to understand.
You and Kat loved me so
well when I was alive
that I have no unfinished business.
Please don't let me be yours.
But, Amelia
I don't...
I don't really know what I'm doing.
What parent does?
James, Kat is growing up
beautifully because of you.
No wonder I miss you so much.
Just a couple of things, though.
Don't pick up the extension every
time she gets a phone call.
French fries are not
a breakfast food.
And don't ask her to
wear a T-shirt under...
Under her bathing suit.
I know.
- Our daughter is a teenager.
- A teenager.
Wait.
Where are you going?
Where I can watch over both of
you until we're together again.
Good-bye, James.
Casper?
Boo?
Not bad for my first party, huh?
Couldn't have been better.
It ain't over yet.
Boys?
Casper the friendly ghost
The friendliest ghost you know
Though grown-ups might
look at him in fright
The children all love him so
Casper the friendly ghost
He couldn't be bad or mean
You know, he jump and play
Sing and dance all day
The friendliest ghost
you've ever seen
He always say "Hello"
And he's really glad to meet ya
Wherever he may go
You know, he's kind to
every living creature
Grown-ups don't understand
Why children all love him the most
But kids all know
that he loves them so
Casper the friendly ghost
Casper, your friendly
Your friendly
He always say "Hello"
He's always glad to meet ya
Wherever he may go
He's kind to every living creature
Grown-ups don't understand
Why children all love him the most
But kids all know he loves them so
Casper the friendly ghost
Professional Translation Services
www.gts-translation.com