Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I think it's best to start with my father's New Year's eve party.
His party to celebrate the start of the new century.
We do it as a new thought.
The father was born in Romania and as a child moved to Scotland.
We stayed in Scotland After the mother's death, -
until father decided to move families and business -
on the outskirts of London this terrible town.
The townspeople were skeptical and inquisitive.
It is hard to describe how passionately I wanted to change away from home.
Mr. Reisner! You know that it will bring the quality.
Unpack it immediately!
It has a festive! Do not you think?
It is an electric signboard. It appears no matter how far away!
Plot is not yours.
And the control of each decided that century changes until next year.
It is celebrated in years. All agree.
Paul!
Come quickly to see!
I happen to disagree, and I'm going to keep the feasts.
I guess it just landed?
I am proud kyltistäni, and I do not intend to demolish it.
The municipality's decision must be respected. And a sign on the neighbor's land.
Why does a nice New Year's Eve 1899 not the last day of the century?
The child turns one year only after living years. - It's silly.
Other countries celebrate next year. - But not the father.
No, not the father.
Why do you celebrate New Year in general?
That is a different time your religion, is not it?
You may know I'm also a Scot.
and Scots they only celebrate the new year.
We shall have another meeting tonight, I warn you.
See you tonight; You all have your invitations do you?
WELCOME TO THE NEW CENTURY.
It is early to welcome the rest of the guests welcome.
But there is 15 minutes to go.
Cup.
Welcome, in 1900.
Bravo.
New year, new century.
And a new beginning for our town.
Do not just keep talking.
at the same time we congratulate my son, Paul.
He joins groundbreaking of the Institute.
He will become a world-famous.
His departure tomorrow is going to be spectacular.
compared to this evening.
The carriages will pull six horses.
None of horses.
Welcome, even if the new century would be.
The taste is good, at least.
Father has ordered a phone. - So, is shown.
The new year starts in style.
You were gonna sneak unnoticed. - I'm not sneaking anywhere.
You wanted your party, I want to to go like this. Goodbye, Dad.
I designed another kind of goodbye. I ordered the horses.
That's ridiculous rakkine! - No, the space is in abundance.
Prepare is.
I'll walk you travel. Remember that you can call at any time.
Yes, father.
Drive faster.
I distribute my advice, because you do not need them.
But be sure to keep with you defense instrument.
I'm just going to London. - There are four murders in the night.
Keep a sharp stone in your pocket. It is a useful piece of advice.
A stone at you to defend. - I promise to be careful.
Too bad you do not come juhliini. We had a very nice.
A waste of time.
Of course you will not be able to to produce me down.
But do your best. Your very best!
It is the road to success!
Do not drive on!
A satisfied grin. - The Miser saved money to travel.
Is this a hospital? - It is a new research institute.
There are only doctors and volunteers.
Ice. Please indicate, if you need the phone.
Hello, I'm Dr. Reisner.
I'm ... - You came early.
You were supposed to come tomorrow. - I am sorry.
Can I see the room?
Clara.
This is a former hospital wing. Beware of puddles.
Here is some mistake. I'm a doctor, I do not ...
You what? - I'm patient and I do not volunteer.
Yes, I know it. You're Dr. Reisner.
This is Reisner bed. those are other doctors beds.
Clara unload your belongings.
Your colleagues are next door. Talk to each other, although the beds.
Days. I'm Dr. Reisner.
Are you doctors? Viewfinder Weather-White doctors now.
You are looking for and found. - He is not down.
Bacteriology. - Cardiology.
Physiology, humeral region. - Physiology, humeral region.
You too?
Physiology, cardiology, bacteriology, pathology ...
And a dose of rheumatic fever.
He did not believe me. - No, not yet.
I'm Felix Russell. For others clothing, you're almost naked.
I do not know how to study attitude towards the roads.
But in London, researchers have the lowest caste. Science is not art.
Scientists just sit laboratories with machines.
The machines are considered vulgar.
That is, the layout will help. - It is necessary!
A nice one. - Exactly.
The whole building is as yet no money.
This better toys is not nobody.
Reisner ...
Are you Jewish? While it would not matter.
Yes I am.
Who is this laboratory? - Mine. You need to be there.
It's ... We did not know, are you good. That's why you got the smallest.
Maybe things will change. - Maybe so.
Electric chair that converts into a horseless vaunuksi.
Friends with you can fit aboard.
I collect these, future machinery models.
Who is that little nook? - All of us, once a week.
You must however, still have to wait your turn.
The time of this public space.
But everyone knows the doctors, what the girl looks like.
At least I hope so.
I went to this one officer's house. Although it should perhaps be mentioned.
He barked doctors thrown bad language. He has lost two brothers.
Welcome.
This is an honor for me. I did not know that you are ...
Not coming not engender the sense of honor. I wanted to talk before the start of the work.
I want you to understand now the basic idea. You are free.
There is no order of the day, does not control.
Follow the instincts. If any.
You can decide if the use of time, and I evaluation results.
It can happen at any time.
I remember a job interview. The physiology of the examination is sufficient.
You do not need luck.
You're here so far.
Until I decide otherwise.
James is a laboratory assistants. And me and Russell.
Is this your first day with? - It is.
James is surprisingly good.
Anywhere else they can not be help.
What drug was it?
Thank you, Doctor. I would not have survived without you.
Tongue out.
Wait a minute.
What do you say Reisner? - Who gave this?
All the same, it, as long as you stop its use. It is harmful.
I need a base solution.
And thyroid malt. Hurry.
Oh, is that you?
Laboratory work. I thought that the... - Instead of beds.
I will do even more between. - Not both would do.
You are afraid that infect diseases. You can of course made up each of your mind.
Consider the matter. Will be announced later.
This can be a dangerous place.
Infections spread easily. Take care of cleanliness.
Yours also. - I promise.
Washed before purine your bags. You do not get an infection.
At least not from me. - Soothing data.
I've been doing well without your advice.
He does not stand up.
This is haimauutetta. for the treatment of diabetes.
Do not be sad.
Look up. Your blood sugar will not be allowed to fall.
Look up.
Have you gone mad? Does not produce a vaccine can be used.
Wait a minute.
They are my subjects. Do not interfere with the work of a colleague.
The vaccine is completely unpredictable!
Did you go to access the colleague. It is unheard of.
He prescribes treatment could have been fatal.
Untreated haimauute is been shown to be unreliable in use.
This gentleman ... is a phone call.
I do not have time to come. Ask the caller to order.
Go ahead, that was it.
So, Dad?
You knew who to call. - Who else? What's the matter with you?
I want to know, of course, how are you doing.
Tell the details. The details!
This is a bad time. - Details!
The duration of one minute.
Be quiet! - I can not hear.
Everything is fine.
I'm busy, I have now stopped.
Everything is fine. And also long-distance calls are successful.
If only not only have to shout so loud.
Gentlemen! Sign thing is forgotten.
So we can come back normal order.
All is forgotten.
Doctor! Come on!
Edwin poor.
I'm serious. - How come?
Him was not anything. Here's how it works.
You take his place.
Kisastamme should be fun. You are ambitious!
This is a great place.
But I may not yet dry. - You do not even close.
James. - So?
The case is sensitive, but I ask anyway.
Now that I'm still here. The room ...
It cubicle ... In the evening, it's my turn. - I could wait for your question.
Do you happen to know a suitable partner? A woman who ...
Strange that all talking about sex nowadays.
Last year, 2 000 flyers -
heterosexually, internal classes about sex.
Instructive. But hardly useful.
I may know a suitable person. - Maybe.
How am I proceed?
Do you want to organize it all? - Only the awkward stage.
Get him out. At a minimum, for a walk.
I pay him?
He expects payment?
Hello.
Reisner, you.
Hi dad.
It is good to hear your voice, but I have right now in a hurry.
The left is menstruating and tuskittelee with the bandage.
Felix, please, with us is a woman. - Thank you but the thing that interests me.
Löytyyköhän menstrual Never relief? - Inevitably.
women fear while being exposed as a leak.
The solution can be found, as long as someone to focus on the issue.
Is that what you study the secret?
I do not. At least not yet.
Why do you think that the studied something to hide? You do not know everything.
Already at a young age fared medical researcher.
First female assistant hired man.
And even a black man. - Oh, really?
Are you busy tonight? - How so busy?
I'm not.
Could we meet? - How close?
Just to meet. - Or meet. Where?
I could take you out to dinner and ... - And what?
Is not infectious worries anymore?
Agree, an experienced woman.
I mean dinner. And then... - And then the curtain booth.
I may be old-fashioned -
but I like the meals, which does not have to pay.
These are not needed.
Villieläinuutetta. Directly charlatan bag.
Would be better, if the gloves do not have holes.
Doctor!
You forgot the benefactor of the widow?
He has a lot of power in this house. - Oh, my God.
Quickest way to get there.
It is a shortcut.
Go ahead! It is the best route.
I apologize.
Sit down.
Do you all as young? - I'm not very young.
My husband saw the mind bearded doctors.
While contributing to the money he imagined valuable bearded professors.
But the professors is only one, the rest are day-old chicks.
This is a new branch of science. - Is it science?
... Inherited properties improvement, better people.
It is a race doctrine.
How do we get the best individuals to mate?
Hopefully the rules are complied with.
And the animals are treated well. - Absolutely.
The rats were allowed to do anything, but not the more advanced animals.
Monkeys, dogs, rabbits. They should not be a plant.
No they are not, I guarantee it.
Good.
best inheritables People do not come from poor parts.
Multi-growing human being is unable to provide for themselves.
You're the best now. You and the other guy.
You have to hear her, too ascendant. - Who told you?
Do not pretend that you do not know. Top Picks ...
I really do not know.
An effective cancer medication. Predict.
By 1959 at the latest.
All syöpiinkö? - It will take more time, at least 70 years.
Multi overcome the disease. Flunssakin, no later than August 1940.
No, communicable diseases can not be reached. When one is defeated, the other spreads.
Diabetes medicine is unlikely to be found in this century.
What century is this?
I believe, that the drug is invented soon.
Shortcut was good.
I had a feeling the benefits. - You will be by only.
Reisner, to participate you too.
Will the lives of people healthier and longer, or not?
I think ...
I believe that the...
not imagining advances imagination enough.
The life expectancy will rise Forecast a hundred years during the 50 years.
And more. Thus, I believe.
You get to the exit.
Except for Paul.
You are eligible researcher. - Oh thank you.
Thanks.
You are quite humble beginnings, or what?
Scottish Jews, originally from Romania. - Exactly.
In you have an edge, but do not change anymore nenäkkäämmäksi.
What can I say? - Just answer my question.
Do you want to work with me?
That would be answered in the affirmative.
There is no need to imitate me in everything. - Just me foreign affairs.
Father good, the rush to press, and the visit is not the time.
Housing was the only improve. I believe that ilahtuisit.
With little free time going around with a Russian count's daughter.
She is beautiful. A wealthy and temperamental.
"He lives in a large house In Richmond. "
Handwriting is reduced, but the news improved.
Come and get summer fruits This year, Mr. Willett!
You can choose from.
Even a Jew.
We choose the best for him.
Then he can not be relentlessly.
Continue reading.
The best part is good välini Professor Mandry.
Our relationship to get better day by day. To make progress at an astonishing rate.
I guess now the foremost researcher. Even my friend Felix sharper.
I am no longer a professor pupil, but a colleague.
A friend even. I can say what I want.
He is a fine man, interested in societal issues.
It is a great honor to be in his presence.
What a day.
They are increasing, even though unable to provide for their children.
I do not think the increase can not forcibly stopped.
Of course not.
Of course not. - Of course it can.
The key of success is education. That's what you have control over.
Better than anyone. - Who says so?
Yourself.
Perhaps there should be no return for a while. We work too hard.
It is possible.
Let's go already!
You came after all. - Didi liked.
Curiosity won.
I apologize for my clumsiness. My actions are rude.
You are of course beautiful anyway, but ... - You did not want that nolaan you.
There is no question of it. The dress was just a beautiful miracle.
I can not use it myself, at least not today ...
The rude act, undeniably.
And at the same time admirable.
You knew my size. - Doctor of experience.
This at first glance. - Let's see, osuitko right.
Do not wait any longer. - A couple of minutes, please.
What he leaves her dress your own? - Cabinet will.
Thy house?
That is not possible. - The closet of the corridor.
You were wrong. It does not sit.
That's enough! - Does not it?
I could be wrong.
It is ... rented. That, too, the matter was mentioned.
I never thought you bought the. Iltahan may fail.
We ylipukeutuneita. - Where are we going?
I know. This way.
Felix, I can not stand any longer.
Reveal your research now.
The subject is certainly one of, which no one else to investigate.
Deny, and you're dead. - I forbid.
It is associated with diabetes. - It is likewise.
Hormones, glands.
The glands produce a substance ...
Ainettako? - Do not repeat the suit, but listen.
The substance is carried through the bloodstream through where it affects.
This is a coordinated system. - Or is it?
I believe that the brain is regulating the operation of an important gland.
I will try to prove it.
I think I can isolate pancreatic secretions chemically.
Diabetes would then be treatable.
Beyond belief. - Revolutionary.
What do you think? Tell. - I wonder.
I'm not saying that I wish I had invented it yourself. - Because you could not have.
I'm supposed to believe that the matter you should consider. And I do not think so.
What do you say?
Sky, look at the dress.
I forgot the whole dress.
It's been an hour. Admit already that the idea is good.
Or do you still believe?
future clothing
men are forced to fight paritteluoikeudesta?
Perhaps the most engaging medieval lugs.
Will there be a battle of shoes? Kill Shoes?
Or do we live in harmony? Are we tolerant, loving even?
After all, we are tolerant. Or what?
That factor is to have the fish.
Paris has presented a moving staircase.
Harrods department store already has one. The inventor angle.
Professor Mandry. Alopecia estoseerumi.
I figured out more than that. Atlantic below the the tunnel, which is run over a hundred.
Free doctors.
Your doctor will check being of workers in the morning on buses.
This is the year of magic.
Balloon villas. - Urban above. Air Camps.
What if all should be fulfilled?
Someone comes up with a vision of the phone. The father should be like that.
My invention already exists. Believe it.
Do not think about him. I'm surprised.
He is on the lower level. It does not not worth it, even for one night.
the scent of summer.
Heat...
The last year of the century, and it is hot.
Part of the city of the future is in my hand.
Felix.
Now, I'm convinced.
It happened a moment ago.
I do not want to recognize, I thought it was the best facility.
But I present it with you Mandry, if you tell me about it.
The work will then be all mine. - Of course.
My sentence can be dangerous and customary. - Like you.
I was saying that the coming is the most exciting night of my life.
Maybe it is. - Let's hope.
I walk home alone?
It does not matter so much, yes but you get to come. - Tuonneko?
Exactly. Edit the route does not exist.
No thanks.
I have to talk with Felix. - I understand. Thanks for the evening.
Do you want to dress back now? - Do not hupsuttele.
Hopefully you do not have to redeem it.
Keep in mind, that you had the opportunity.
It has typos. - We were in a hurry.
The performance is vast.
What do you think? - Just uncommon ideas.
Which should be given join all assets. The study may be significant.
Not only for us, but also the body.
Press will be interested in the matter.
I, too, the ideas are interesting.
Perhaps even groundbreaking.
I will get back to. Do not talk about this.
Dr Makin United States and Dr. Leisen from Germany.
Good evening.
Soon, Paul. Very soon.
I read the Washington-acquaintance the study.
I think it was a lack of evidence. - So it often is.
Professor Mandry. - Now is a bad time.
He is too often picnics.
Still no feedback, not any.
It must not be fooled. He always affects thoughtful.
I would myself to learn the skill.
Why do not you comment on the report? - What do you mean?
We need our show. - It is wide.
It is Reisner and Russell an interesting essay.
I have read it only three times. That's a lot to think about.
I do not want to discuss it now. I must inform you when I'm ready.
I take the course seriously.
Why it was a cleaning cupboard? - Therefore, I searched for it.
the level of cleaning to keep apparently improve. I like the matter in my mind.
You did not leave it there? - I do not.
-Then Get it back. Thanks.
I feel like, that do you avoid reading it.
Do not jankkaa. - Unforgivable argument.
I have always supported you and contributed to your career.
You now have the best to remain silent. Do you understand?
I just want to know the reason for the delay.
Reisner, up.
Get up.
For a month banned. You'll also lose a month's wages.
When you return, you start your original laboratory.
I do not want to see you months.
And do not argue. Exit.
Where is Clara? - Offline.
He is always here. - He is on vacation. I do not know where.
You need to know. - I do not know.
Where he lives? Tell!
Clara!
Here you are. Thank God.
So, fortunately, the address was correct.
Did not you glad to see me? - Of course, I was delighted.
What Doctors effort?
Little problem with the professor. I went too far.
I thought I was a review above, because I am able.
Everything will be yes, because he likes me. - Of course.
You stole these devices? - I do not, of course.
And won only half. The rest are defective.
What are you doing?
May I kiss you? - Doctor is good.
Do not call me Doctor.
I'm hoping this first moment. - Valetta.
You think you should be gloves when touching assistants.
Do you still want gloves?
This is what I am. - I see no reason for concern.
Oh, thank you, Doctor.
What about you? I had already decided to quit.
Especially with doctors.
Your decision can not relate to me.
At least not now.
Do too cocky you.
Doctors had only one.
Always prepare this range.
The body was a Chinese assistant. He advised me.
Chinese food. Kind of. - The extra-sighted.
Surprisingly tasty. Although special.
It appeals only to the best the taste nerves. So as you.
Exactly.
Forget about the medicine and take to savor the cuisine of the future.
Opium users. Here lives a lot of bohemians and wanderers.
Are up to no matter what the curtains open.
I have one question.
Why does someone like you ... - Smart woman.
Working in a laboratory as an assistant, Really?
I thought I heard in danger of death.
Since I gave birth to a child.
Without a husband and without money.
Then there was no longer last of it.
It's an ordinary story.
Except I did not abject towards I do not ask the department rewarding.
What happened to the child?
The child died.
Influenza Infectious deprived it of the spirit in eight hours.
My condolences.
It was my creation.
Although not think so.
Do you want to stay here?
Although is it you seem to be place else. - Not so.
See that James considered slides concern.
An interesting list of subjects.
Write up information, So secretly.
Changes and that sort of thing.
I know what I'm looking for. I have kept my eyes open.
Paul Reisner!
Paul! There you are.
How are you? Have you forgotten everything?
Go away! We should not even be discussed.
You have fallen into the plot. - Yllätän you when I get back. And the professor.
I can hardly wait.
Those clothes suit you. - Yes.
Tell me who they are. - It does not belong to you. You'd be jealous.
Will you be all right here? - Sure. I can put on our food.
Paul Reisner! - Get out!
I thought already, that we were come to the wrong place.
A very special environment.
Yes, but the explanation is simple.
Tell. - I'll get them. In return I get to wash up here.
Jack. - Room a an older woman -
which conducts research in his spare time.
It is easy to get excited about. - Why do you have those kinds of clothes?
Merge them better. - It is not the recommended approach.
The clothes are ridiculous. - I can not be bothered to explain.
Let's go to lunch. Or a cup of coffee. London gets a good coffee.
No no no. - How come?
Introduce Research Institute. - Impossible, it is closed.
Rubbish! Shoes suddenly. And drive your beard.
We're going the same road.
Dr. Reisner, a piece of you already. - Just keep on working.
Where is the lab? - What?
Use it the old.
These are covered with dust. - It is an advantage in certain tests.
Testing must be done under all conditions.
Where is your apartment?
Paul! Have you gone mad? Mandry was in earnest.
The work progressed faster than I imagined.
Felix is ​​a bit special. Do not mind.
Come on. Here. Come on!
Dr. Reisner.
A woman is calling you.
It is his way. Let him be just.
Do not pay attention to him.
Reisner.
Days.
I want to explain. I'm not really here.
Father wanted to see research institute. I'm not here.
It is a pleasure to meet your father. Days.
It is my pleasure.
I have something to say.
I told you so? - I know, but I already explained.
You left only a week ago. Do not you believe me?
I thought, I'm not stupid. Father is the only hard to resist.
I am also sorry The rude language.
Thoughtful.
Downright elegant apology. The kind you wait too.
I may take you back to the past. - I'd be grateful.
But just me I get to take up your proposal.
A special condition. When will you make the speech? - When I'm ready.
No time limit, I do not give. It is the normal practice. - But ...
Do not continue. I offer a second chance.
Tutkimushan is not even yours.
If you do not believe it, let us take it elsewhere.
Out. Here, the work done is now the property.
Only under these conditions you get to come back. The matter is closed.
You must listen to me.
An awe-inspiring condition. The study is published.
If I were sure about your silence, I might agree.
When? - When I looked into the matter.
Postpone it again! You're jealous!
The study merits are obvious.
You want to cancel it! It is unforgivable!
Do not worry, they go to the scientific debate.
Uhmasit me. - I apologize sävyäni.
But research can not conceal. - This ends here.
If you step foot in here at all, medical career is finished.
You stay away from the other doctors. You must not stir up them.
I'll make sure you do not make any more medical research.
You can not. - Do not forget who you are.
One of you there is a difference of opinion. You do not have relations.
Remember it.
Please exit without saying a word.
I think it clever. Did you like about me. Why did you do that?
I...
I can not believe this is happening. - You follow my instructions!
You are insolent. Exit here!
Get lost!
Come on.
No no no. Wait.
The way I would like to invite you again. Come even village.
The year of harvest of fruit is good. - Thank you. If I move there in the ...
Pojallanne is relevant to you.
I am glad my son's success. - Be quiet!
Come now, we have to leave!
What are you doing? - We have to go!
I wish you had not come!
What are you doing? I demand an explanation! What happened there?
Kinastelitteko? Do not bicker with him.
What?
You misunderstood. - Explain.
I might get a promotion, a research unit.
The situation is sensitive. I did not want you meddling.
You'll see yet.
James, sit with me for tea.
After all, come to me like that?
The thought is daunting.
After all, you do not know.
Many are of the opinion, that already belong to them.
"Clara has exceeded the limit."
I have now no other than you.
Do not talk like that. That's not true.
As soon as the problem will be solved, you leave me.
And I do not leave. And why not?
Because you can not change. You should happy with my kind.
Can you imagine The designated rapporteur me to your father?
I require only that you do not lie to me.
If I do not get to use the word love, I then dependent on you.
That's the way it is.
We'll see.
If we do not get to sleep again ...
You are incorrigible.
It started already. I would have to present, I do not enjoy sex.
And again. I'm not supposed to talk about sex.
You do so.
I get at least some compensation, because you do not pay the rent.
Malta still a moment, if you can.
What am I doing in terms of Mandry?
after the breach, keep asking for forgiveness.
Simplify. Apologize.
Matele in the country, right in the country.
Say that you were completely wrong.
Although I do not think you can.
How are you?
Avaapa mouth.
Paul! What a creepy outfit. Just staggering.
Your clothes are muddy. - Such is life in the city.
You only have ridiculous costumes. They get dirty continuously.
We should introduce Research overalls. - A man has gone mad.
After all, the modern workplace and very special, but that is too much.
How do you stack up marginalized? - Okay.
I'm thinking crawl in front of Mandry.
I promise to have a word to say without mentioning your research.
Do not worry, I've moved on to other kiintoista topics. - Its faith.
My subject was too ambitious. - Was not.
We need your input. Although the granting of happens.
I went again in his lecture.
Good morning.
How much time do we have? - About ten minutes.
See who comes. Hide!
Can he see me? It is this still missing.
He would think that conspired.
You Yid halveerasitte Journal of us.
Teikäläisten is useless come to us to advise.
Keep your mouth shut. Get lost!
Another one of them? - Yes.
They always call in the evening. Get rid of the phone.
No no no. Everyone will receive such calls.
It is a feature of the device.
I wish you had not spoken Journal disparaging the city fathers.
Come along to help with New Year's invitations.
In last year's festivities look Successful completion of these compared.
I concentrated on the design of the invitation.
What do you say? - Oh, Dad.
Dr. Reisner.
Dr. Paul Reisner. - Yes. What is it?
Come on, we need to talk. - What is it?
A small interview only. Interview only.
In an interview? - Yes.
The journey is not long.
Tell me now, What is it about.
These are Devonshire, ballroom dancing.
Did you find you seek?
Are you looking for something special?
Hello, Dr. Reisner. Please have a seat.
Perhaps you know that in preparation is the new Aliens Act, -
to stanch the flood of unwanted materials.
We are preparing the entry into force of the law.
In spite of its name, the German your father was born in Romania.
I guess I know it. - Multi disavow.
Is not it interesting?
You were born in Scotland, did you livev in the
United States with the family
now turned back to Scotland and did you come here to the south.
How do you know? - We find out Only your family's steps.
We will ensure that the procedures for there is no slippage at any stage.
Is Mandry behind this?
This is a personal vendetta. You do not have the power.
You have no right to arrest me, as you know.
Goodbye.
Villain! We have become useless advice.
Gentlemen, Calm down.
You can of course leave, If you want.
While this was the preliminary session. We will meet again.
What has happened to you? Have you hurt yourself?
Where are you've come across? - Mandry organize an obstacle.
I wonder he really hate me.
Do you trust me? You have to. - I can not.
What it is? - Developed plant material.
I have not heard of it. - Dr. Kaan does not know everything.
Be a brave boy.
Trust me. Part of the business.
It will not be selling success.
I want to practice medicine. Mandry tentacles do not reach everywhere.
Who caused this?
We bring you the medicine. We will try to get you to the hospital.
Women have been sterilized.
Measures have been clumsily. They have suffered.
Who did it?
Who was it? You have to tell.
It's your boss. We were told, and then we do not know the sick.
Do not miss out victims of measure?
Hard to believe such a Mandry.
Women did not know, what happened to them.
"Reproduction of the lower classes is stop. "Do they kill?
"Favourable hereditary features should be favored. "
"By the way rappiollisuus will prevail. "
"The unprofitable spread of genes must be prevented. "
"Little älyiset must be sterilized." American race doctrine in the newspaper.
After all, Mandry was not interested in this.
Only the posh women, flaky and a pair of conservative scholars.
Mandry despise this.
he imagined to settle the population problem?
Does he controlled experiment? He opts lisääntyjät?
Is he already has another group?
Sterilization was probably about to start, Felix presented the study.
Mandry lied to me. He knew what I am.
There is no evidence. He would say ... - That the women gave permission.
That heidänlaisistaan ​​not find out.
This must not continue. Hank's witnesses.
Do you think you got it like that nice? - I may he held accountable.
You can not get in this way.
There are doctors. We can not get past them.
You have been refused entry. For good.
Am I not here either? Here, already celebrated.
I am sorry. - I'm just relieved.
He is certainly the Christmas lecture. You bet.
The lecture is a public occasion.
Machines do the work, which are now being carried out by people.
Machines will put your children sleep, read them a bedtime story.
Good luck. - It is needed.
Scared pretty terribly.
Will this succeed?
Of course.
I will speak first. I will help you, If you forget your word. Is not hurry.
How about us lonkerokädet, by stroking machines back to life?
If the machines do all the work, we need more power?
How about us skinny hands, who just twist the pieces on the board?
Toes switch devices on and off.
What about the women?
could women develop in a different direction?
Women Ethan require already in the position himself.
Women will develop stronger a gender? Should worry about it?
Will women dominant, certain animal females like?
Seriously, though, pulling together -
should the physical degeneration be worried? That's what's already happening.
It is of incurable diseases, of which suffer from whole sections of the population.
Can not stop development of events?
The lowest social class is unable to provide for themselves, -
but it still increases.
Should an increase in to plan and restrict -
in the name of a new kind of society?
Good!
Weighty issues.
Research institute has developed a solution.
Homemade caramel!
In the laboratory hand-made vaniljakinuskia chocolate.
And very delicious.
White Weather now a gift to the public.
Please send it back of the hall. There is a hungry mouths.
You're welcome.
A moment went by, courage betrayed.
I looked at him, and I said that I like him.
He was convincing.
I also will not be able to. - It's not fair to you.
I do not like it here. - I would not be able to do it.
There you are. When will you return?
When? Paul!
There will be another opportunity, I'm sure. - But when?
Excuse me. I did not know that you're here. - Do not worry, come on in.
Is everything okay?
Everything is just excellent.
As always. - Or at all times.
Hold on! Mrs. White Weather!
This takes only a moment. - I do not have time.
I'm going to the theater. - Do not you remember me?
We drank tea. My clothes were in the dust.
I remember quite well.
You will have 45 seconds.
I do not know whether there was sufficient time.
It is a plant. It is going in the direction of the fault.
Ignoring the important work Professor ... - What Works?
I do not have time to explain exactly, but ... - Do you think me stupid?
I do not, I do not. Asia is the only professional. - I've heard of you more than that.
You have the foreign name. Reisenberg.
You do not appear to a foreigner. But you do not know now.
I am not anti-Semitic, even though many of my friends are.
Your husband-funded institution Director Mandry -
sterilize women without their knowledge.
The homeless, the poor, part of the very young.
Lized many, part is dead.
Mandry is a supporter of the racial doctrine.
He wants to choose, who gets to reproduce.
Maybe Mandry considers, that it belongs to his work.
He sterilize people without permission, claiming the treatment.
How do you know? They probably gave permission.
I have witnesses. - They're trying to some money, like everyone else.
Getting tired of this. Elämmehän festive phase.
Did not you know? - People are dead. Directly or indirectly.
Such is the medicine, it improves and it kills.
Your time expired. - You have to listen.
You do not accept it. - You know my opinion?
I begin to understand, why you separated. Goodbye.
I prepare for the theater.
He uses monkeys experiments. Professor Mandry.
Monkeys and dogs. advanced animals. Visit even watching.
What did you say? Monkeys and dogs, right?
Is that what you said?
Dr. Russell, when the treatment continues?
The plant was closed down suddenly, without warning.
What will I do without professors?
Close the door.
Please, drink a glass with me. - Of course.
Have I ever behaved prejudiced against you?
Be honest.
You do not. Less than anyone else.
So you do not ever. You have always encouraged me.
Good. Well the answer I hoped.
on behalf of my job I need to think about future ways of thinking.
The work is difficult, as only a few are capable of it.
So very few people.
on behalf of the enterprise have to fight.
Neither carry forth the papers. They contain the material through.
This is your fault. - I sorry, but the thing is serious.
You had no evidence. - What a.
Did you want to get revenge Mandry? - Of course not, you know it.
Does your father, what have you done? - I called my sister.
But, Dad, I can not tell you. He will hear in due course.
What a wonderful New Year's Eve.
The new century begins, and we sit here.
I have not been called elsewhere. There was supposed to be a party.
The most important change to one hundred years years, and I have to call.
Come and join the father's party.
Please.
Possibly.
May I come in?
May I come too?
So your father's celebrations.
For.
Did you notice?
You hesitated. It started already.
Clara, do not. - Let go!
Just one day, and it started. Do not touch me!
I helped you, but you reject me at the first opportunity!
Dependent nice!
Curious thing Overnight losing addictive.
That asked to get involved in. That thought, therefore, that things can change.
You could not mention love. - I just meant ...
I know what you meant! Do not lie to me.
You do not want to introduce me to your father. - That's not true. According to the source.
Just this evening, you have to be with me. - Is it?
You're hurting me!
You are actually quite similar, you and Mandry.
Do not say that.
Where he might that be?
I have to find him. He's still here.
Are you happy now? - Do not you start.
This was an important place for me. More important than you think.
I'm really sorry.
Where is he?
Here are his things. - He went to the New Year celebrations.
He received a number of invitations, but he chose a certain party.
What? - Do you really not know?
Your fathers festivities.
He said the task of putting completed. - Of course.
Oh, my God.
Come on!
Who would want to be there now?
Oh father will be with you. This is a moukkamaista.
Moukkamaista horrible.
Can you see him?
There. - What do you have upon you?
We did a sea monster's father. Is not it a great outfit?
I am a blood-sucking mosquito. I can put people all night long.
This is how they will see, that they are indifferent.
This is Clara, which we hope ...
Hopefully, what?
Nice to meet you. I guess you feel cold. Take this. - Thank you.
We met with the rats infested in the basement. Do you remember?
Come take a look.
We need to change out.
Why on earth? - Father shunned, he has not allowed construction.
Why did not she tell me?
Managed to chase. - Not the kind you can do!
That's great. - Too bad, that your affairs went node.
So. I came to see Mandry.
But where is he?
Father.
Outfit is weird. And wonderful.
I did not dare look in the mirror. Maybe I dread not consider this.
The boat was afraid seeing my picture in the water.
Your mother would not have approved such at all.
Either you heard? We have a guest of honor.
I know who.
WELCOME TO THE NEW CENTURY AGAIN
Paul.
You should not have come. Get off the same road.
Do not you have anything else to say?
It is after all, New Year's Eve.
Please submit your conscience by, but progress can not be stopped.
Progress comfortable.
An intelligent person you know that Progress may seem a little hairy.
The approach solves.
Why did you come? - The invitation of the father.
I also wanted to meet you.
I wanted to find out Our relationship. I like you.
I also hope that you cancel your claim, -
to be refunded money for research.
I want to explain. - There is no explanation. I know.
Remember it.
Enter now to continue without share.
Consider the matter. The plant is important to me.
Refuse me. Are many of the same opinion.
You tried to make me unwanted external forms, do you remember?
I was angry, because you listened to. Thou wast angry with me.
It is a thing of the past. - We belong here by the same token. Say it out loud.
We belong here. Say!
Of course, you belong to.
But is not New Year's Eve should...
Please get on and get off. I do not ask a second time.
Let's leave it for the moment.
Your father thinks that all is well. Let us not ruin their evening her?
This is important to him. Relish your father's party.
Do not talk to him anymore. Leave us alone.
Get out!
I just...
Goodbye.
Doctor, tell me more future machines.
Shops be built on the moon? - Point I'll tell you, just collect papers.
My Quotations.
Is it you wrote this? - Yes. Those are my thoughts.
Miriam told the bad news. Is it true? - Oh yes.
cause the closure of the plant.
I wanted to be an eminent scholar. Instead I caused the closure of the plant.
That kind of accomplishment.
To think that the Mandry-mannered a good-natured man doing such a thing.
I find it hard to accept your actions.
But I do not want to talk about today. He is here as our guest.
This is Clara.
He is a laboratory assistant. I have lived with him.
Clara, is a New Year's Eve. I might die tomorrow.
And juhlissani rain. What is happening today?
Troublemakers!
They were going to boycott the celebrations, but they went laughing at her.
They are perplexed.
Do not give up. Do not give them a profit.
I, too, I might stay here for a while.
Sick-looking set, at least enough to work.
You're welcome. - God bless you.
We will not forget each other. Hopefully.
Clara, you stay here with me? Decide before midnight.
Our relationship can not succeed. - That's what you can you do not know.
I know. - Etpäs.
Got control of your own life, still you would have the same Clara.
It will not succeed.
Say, you do not know for sure. Say before midnight. - I already know.
Etpäs do not know. You have loved me a little.
I should not say it, but I say anyway.
There have been many moments when I have loved you. - Vainko moments?
You are vain! - Say it.
You can not be sure. Say it before midnight.
I will not let you.
Let.
I can not be sure, that our relationship to be successful.
My beloved, it will succeed.
Oh my God. I do not understand why I cry.
All things undone ... One manages to do them?
Will the world be better? What is happening?
Time wonderful dinner party, or what? Wonderful.
Even ones.
Felix, make a prediction.
Soon, we can ...
We can ... we can ...
I can not think.
Happy new century!
Celebrations refreshed father, clearly, because he lived for nearly 20 years.
Felix made later meritorious diabetes research.
I believe that if the annual would have gone differently -
the inventor of insulin would have been Felix.
Often at night and wonder Mandry the dark side of his work.
I did not see him ever again. He left medicine.
I heard that he committed suicide later.
Others tell, that he died peacefully.
He is best in never met the man.
For years I hoped bump into him on the street.
I was hoping to see his visage was sizable.
Clara did not want to marry me, but he became his partner.
this sanellessani He sits near me.
We worked for years in a quite countryside.
We have fought a lot of course.
That was only to be expected.
Nothing in my life though, has
ever quite - the strange feeling I had that night
excited, and worried, and hopeful
as we moved together into a new century.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org