Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
CAN NOT BE GOOD, NOT BAD,
ALL THAT IS,
MUST coexist in ...
A SORT OF
Balance or symmetry.
SAN AUGUSTINE
There's a robbery in progress at the Bank 914.
Unit 571 responds immediately.
Received.
Get me Captain, please.
- Captain Howard.
- Captain ...
We have a problem. Come soon.
Very good. Listen, guys.
There is an armed robbery in progress.
In the Coastal Bank
Savings and Loan.
You know the procedure.
We do not want llaneros
lonely, Williams.
Now, who are you?
Prepared and committed!
That's! Let's finish with some villains!
How about you, dear?
You know I could make a place.
Why do not you come here?
What if I put my foot in your ass?
- I do not know how you dare.
- Show him respect!
It will teach you to respect.
Katana. It's enough.
Yes sir.
It is fiery.
What if we raise the bet?
What do you propose?
Fifteen?
Twenty?
I sold.
For the man who
It has everything to lose.
Really?
Like hell.
You're a good negotiator.
Take the time you want.
I have nowhere to go.
When you sign this, it will be
binding. You can not undo.
Absolutely.
Well, Bones, look at this.
The vault is open.
There are records there.
I'll go look for them.
It was not part of the plan.
We have no time.
It is now part of the plan.
- What the hell are you thinking?
- Shut.
Office, there are at least three assailants.
Yes, send reinforcements.
Who do you think you're talking?
I talk with you. What do you have to say?
Calm down! There is not
time for this shit.
Shut up!
Bank 914. Yes, 914.
Are you serious?
Talk to him. This is not a game.
We have to get out of here!
Have you gone crazy?
No, I'm not crazy.
I want to get that money.
Drop your weapons! Right now! Now!
Fuck. Damn cops.
This place is full of cops.
You better not fuck.
I hate cops.
- Smith. Inside.
- Yes sir.
Williams, inside. Johnson ...
Watch the alley. Get on the roof.
Listen, man.
Nobody move a muscle
until I give the order.
Get me the Bank.
They want to see these damn.
Yes sir.
We need a direct line
the Bank as soon as possible.
Understood. In position.
I am awaiting orders.
I see.
Someone let me know
that damn bank!
Below. Below.
CHECKMATE
A DAY BEFORE
This is the Gospel of the Lord
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
How long it was
since your last confession?
Do you have something for me, my son?
Yes, Father.
And you sin?
Are you sure about this?
Some things can not be undone.
I did not want this.
It is my last resort.
I did not work in two years. I lost everything.
My house was repossessed, I have no car.
And my son ...
You can not look like a suicide.
That's all I care about.
Once done, my family
you can collect the insurance.
All that matters to me
They are receiving the money.
So please...
Jeremiah 6:13.
"For from the least to the
greatest, all are greedy for gain,
and from the prophet even unto the
priest, all practice deceit. "
Twice this.
It's okay. I'll get the money.
That's all, my son.
Wait.
You can not look like a suicide.
That's what matters to me.
I'm sick of this
damn engine, man.
Fuck!
Do not do that.
Are ago how much work on this, Bones?
Too much time.
¿Alineaste start and alternator?
What the fuck are these wires?
Hey, motherfucker, I'm doing
this since before you were born.
I know what I do. Shut up.
It's okay. Just do what I say.
I should leave it locked.
Tiny, you're killing me!
It's bean burrito.
Dammit!
Stick to clothes, right?
That stinks like shit.
Do not blame me for me,
but the guy who wrapped.
Damn man!
Get out out then.
If you need me, I'll be smoking.
These American cars
They are crap.
Bones, is right about the start.
You are wrong.
Get out.
Dammit!
What happens to you? Thought
it was the police, right?
You're a damn fool, Joey.
Quiet, yet I
You want, motherfucker.
That beauty.
Infiniti. How are you?
Too bad we have to
cut into pieces. Tuck.
Does it have to be now?
Let's enjoy
this beast for a while.
Hop on, let's warm.
Very good. I am recharged.
Yes, motherfucker!
Hey, brother. We stop here, okay?
There will be two seconds. Do not worry.
- It's okay.
- Great.
Father.
What if you change your mind?
He is no longer in their hands.
Hello. Do not worry, I'll pay.
Dude, you got truffle butter?
Yes, it's there ...
Have truffle butter?
Give me the money!
- Give me the damn money!
- Do not do this.
- Shut up and give me the money!
- Give it to me or I'll blow your brains out!
- You mess with the wrong guy.
You say I put me
with the wrong guy?
Really? I do not know why
You say, because I have the gun.
What the hell does?
- Give me the damn money, now!
- No problem.
I'll blow your brains together
with this damn place.
Give it to me now. Now!
- Okay, here it is.
- Thank you.
Fuck me!
Enters!
Come on, come on, motherfucker!
We're rich!
Motherfucker!
Do not ever steal this store!
Here you go. Anything else? They are fine?
Can I get you anything else?
- What I give?
- A Deadman.
All right.
Hey, what are you going to drink?
Do not worry, you're not my type.
Fuck!
Can you believe this guy?
He believes that interests me.
Ridiculous, those girls kissing.
Yes. I love this city.
What the hell do you want?
It is an interesting phrase.
You remember, right?
Keep it.
Dammit!
Corinthians said to know
truth is a revelation.
When I was a kid,
I spake as a child,
I thought like a child,
I reasoned like a child.
But when I grew up, I left
such childish ways!
We see only a reflection,
as in a mirror.
But what remains are these
three things: hope, faith and love.
The greatest is love.
But the cruel bring
ruin upon themselves.
Is everybody okay back there?
Everything will be fine. Keep
the wheels on the road ...
and Take us there in one piece.
Hold on, baby, hold on.
Quiet. Everything will be fine.
We are on our way.
Does your wife have a history
breathing problems?
Your inhaler is in your bag.
We have to find it.
Here it is, baby. Hold on. Here you go.
You are better?
- It's better?
- It's happening again.
Quiet, everything will be okay.
Keep calm.
How is my baby?
Lady will arrive in two minutes.
Everything will be OK.
I love you so much baby.
Just hold on a little longer.
Within two minutes.
Hello Friend.
potato, I have fear. When
I can go home?
You will return home soon.
Do not panic. There's nothing to be scared.
It is difficult to understand this.
You'll understand in a while.
You will see.
You just have to know something.
Your dad loves you with all his heart.
You must remember that.
I love you Papa.
Love you.
- The fucked, Joey.
- It Does that seem fucked?
There are ten thousand here. Let's go.
We will leave. Let's go.
- Ten thousand!
- What the hell are you?
Ten thousand! Ten thousand! Ten thousand!
What the hell is wrong with you?
What do you mean? Look at this, asshole.
They are ten thousand!
- Its a lot of money.
- A lot of money.
But you know something? Not much money.
What I say is that if you think
crawl in some shit,
I wish you'd anticiparas.
That's all I ask.
You're a fucking fagot.
Ten thousand. This is nothing. Is nothing.
Fuck that shit.
It was only a test.
You know what, brother? You failed.
- I missed?
- Shut up, shut up!
Look, Ron. Tomorrow is the big day.
If you happen to do this
tomorrow, we're screwed.
Tomorrow is our Super Bowl.
Tomorrow is when we win.
So gets your fucking
head in the damn game.
Do you understand?
Throw me the ball, catch it and write it down.
We always did and I will continue doing.
Okay. Fuck me, Ron. Fuck me.
Motherfucker.
Hello Doctor.
How is it going?
Equal. We are doing
everything for him.
Are you sure you do not
There's nothing I can do ...?
To upload the list
donor? Are you sure?
You can not do anything.
If it were me, Christopher
would be high on the list.
Unfortunately we have policies
in the hospital to follow.
I know. I get it.
All you can do is
see to continue with medication,
you are comfortable and you,
try to rest.
We are
doing everything possible.
Well, thank you, doctor.
Very good.
Everything will be OK.
This time it will be all right.
You'll have this baby.
My love, you have to endure.
Above!
- Hello.
- Come here, honey.
Hello little one.
I felt him kick.
I do not know if it will be a boy or a girl,
but sure you play football.
How do I look?
You always look amazing.
Even with your 135 kilos.
I'll see you in the kitchen.
Hi dear.
- Hi dear.
- Hey, baby.
I did not hear you come in.
I have just arrived.
I made lasagna last night.
If you're hungry, heat it.
It's in the fridge.
The left side.
I tried a new sauce.
I do not know. You might also like.
It has much garlic.
I cleaned the room of Christopher ...
and I was thinking.
I think you need a new bed.
He grew up a lot.
Maybe we could go to the store,
buy paint and paint your room.
I do not like that color.
And new sheets.
Maybe the NFL with
equipment designs.
Christopher was awake last night.
I think I'll buy
shirt you like.
That blue highlighting her eyes.
He liked.
Yes.
Okay...
- Rest.
- It's okay.
Affection...
I love you.
And I you.
Fuck.
Affection?
What happened?
I'm so fat, that neither
I can make breakfast.
You're not fat!
You should not make breakfast.
The doctor said I must rest.
I know.
- Then what do you do?
- Only me...
Stay there. I am going to
clean this up, okay?
I just wanted to make breakfast,
that is all. I'm useless.
- You're not useless.
- I'm a fat cow and useless.
I'll breakfast. You're useless.
I already lost two. I can not lose this.
We are together, yes?
Avoid standing.
Trust me? Can you do it?
- Yes.
- Very good.
I love you. I must go to work.
You will be fine?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
Stay here. Do not do anything.
It's okay.
Very good. I love you.
I love you too.
Lord, the estimated time
is two minutes.
Thank you, honey.
Well, I'm here,
desahogándome you.
What you want to talk?
Did what happened before with Rafe?
Hello?
Good morning, speaks Ms. Campbell?
Yes.
I'm Kathy Ford
Savings and Loan Bank.
I'm calling your mortgage payment.
We do not receive and has expired.
Well, I'm sure
which we did get.
Can you wait a moment?
Sure.
Sorry, I must have passed us.
Can we pay tomorrow?
In order to avoid
a fine for late payment,
need to receive this payment today.
I understand. We will ship in the afternoon.
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Thank you, Ms. Campbell,
Have a nice day.
Lauren calling ...
Hello, Paul. I know you're
busy, but called the Bank.
We have to pay the mortgage.
I go to the bank and take care of it.
I promise that after
So I rest, okay?
I love you.
Lands there.
Lord, the estimated time
is two minutes.
- Do you have the schedule to this location?
- Yes, if something changes, I'll let you know.
I understood.
We're coming, sir.
Thank you, honey.
What the hell are you doing? Are you ready?
Let's do it.
Come on, brother.
Listen, Mom is gone. Do you understand?
What are you doing here reminiscing
about this shit?
This is a great job.
Great job.
This is the shit we
He will kill. Do you understand?
Concentrate on the game.
Fuck!
Come on, fagot.
Give me one click.
Now.
- It's okay?
- It's okay.
Father.
Father, we must re-
think about this. It is not worth it.
I descended from heaven, not
to do my will,
but the will of him that sent me.
John 6:38.
RETIREMENT
- I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
Mr. Thompson, I'm sorry
the wait. Come with me.
I hate to get paid by the hour.
- Are you okay?
- If I am fine.
- Can you hold the fort?
- Yes.
- Insurance?
- Like last time?
- Not better.
Very good.
- Is it time for a ten to one?
- No, no.
Ten-dos. I'll be right back.
- Any problem?
- I'm not sure about that.
We're fine, brother.
Breathe. Calm down.
Look, I do not know what the
problem, but do not ruin this.
- Be sure to climb to the roof.
- Yes sir.
- Wait for my notice.
- Yes, I understand.
Ready?
All right, everybody. This is an assault.
Everybody down, now!
On the ground, now! Get down!
Down! Down!
I'll blow your head off!
Everybody down! Get down!
Get on the ground! I said that...!
Motherfucker, Drop
ground or I'll blow your head.
You son of a bitch!
- Get down!
- Hands up!
Anyone else want
be a goddamn hero?
Do not do it. Heroes die.
Arise! Hands up!
Than? What happens to you? What happens to you?
Shut up, you stupid fagot!
Want to be a hero? Are you a hero?
- What are you waiting for?
- I expect nothing.
Shut up, fagot!
Fill it! No marked bills!
I'll blow your brains out!
Hurry up! Move!
Office.
Move, move!
Faster!
You're the first asshole I kill you.
I want you to know. I promise you.
Arise! Now!
We have a robbery in progress.
Shots were fired. It is the Bank 914.
Unchecked!
What the fuck ...?
What is happening to you now?
Fuck! Do not look at me!
Heads down!
Shut! Come here.
I'm going down.
The units are coming.
I understood.
Get me Captain, please.
- Captain Howard.
- Captain ...
We have a problem. Come soon.
Be alert. Get ready.
Remember, this is not an assault.
It's a rescue mission. There hostages.
This is EE. UU. We are
here to save people.
We do not want heroes.
All go home tonight.
Who the fuck are?
- Prepared and committed!
- That's!
For the man who
It has everything to lose.
ACT TO ETERNITY
Are you sure about this?
Like hell.
Take your time
you want. I have nowhere to go.
When you sign this, it will be
binding. You can not undo.
I think exactly the same.
Eternity or nothing.
Absolutely.
What happens to you? Are you okay?
Dammit. It is Lauren.
Is the baby okay?
She's in the bank.
914. Yes Bank, Bank 914.
- Are you serious?
- Talk to him. This is not a joke.
We have to get out of here!
Have you gone crazy?
No, I'm not crazy.
I want to get that money.
Drop your weapons! Now!
Come on! Now!
Comuníquenme with the Bank!
Drop your weapons, now. Tírenlas!
Where should we throw them?
Down, come on, boy. Now!
Down.
- Take off the masks.
- Quiet.
Take off the masks.
Come on!
Ready!
- Yes.
- I got them...
Would you have us? For real?
Is incredible. We caught.
You dont have anything.
I do not think so. Give me your gun.
Get down!
Look who we have here. Look!
- What a beautiful piece of work.
- Thanks sweetie.
What the hell are we doing here?
- Shut up!
- Thank you .
- Are you going to check the rest?
- Dammit!
I can not believe it!
We gotta get out of here!
Give me my gun.
You have to calm down a little.
Shut up and relax.
Do not look at me like that.
- This is stupid.
- Shut.
I do not have time for this!
Let's get out of here!
- Calm down.
- What calms me?
- Are you serious?
- It's okay.
Police is coming. They must go.
He left. Take the money.
- Take the money and go.
- Shut up!
Okay okay.
Easy, easy.
Stay quiet.
- Mom?
- Yes.
All in order. Okay back there.
What shall we do, dammit?
I'll get the money back.
Shut up. And control yourself.
I do not want to go to jail! Fuck!
Is it worth it, Joey?
I'll get the tiles!
The only thing you can do is complain.
Your brother just try to take care of.
We're screwed!
You're a jerk.
Well well.
You move.
As you can see, Mr. Thompson,
your money is very safe here
in the Savings and Loan Bank.
Certainly, you should consider ...
I do not even think.
I'll shoot you.
Nobody, motherfucker move.
Dammit.
High! Fuck!
Stupid, why did you?
I do not get it.
Why the hell did you do that?
Dammit! Fuck!
Move it! Now! Above!
Fuck!
Everybody down! Heavens!
Get down!
Hurry up!
What is this? Where did these people?
Let me talk to you for a second.
Unfortunately, when I went
in the vault there was a guard.
And it will not bother us anymore.
What do you mean?
What the fuck you mean
that's not going to bother?
Hey, brother, if
you want to talk, come here.
- What's going on, Joey?
- Come here.
Come here. Everything will be OK.
Come here.
What is it, Joey?
Listen, listen. Everything is fine.
Do you understand? All good.
This is fine.
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
- What the hell?
- You know it.
Are you okay?
Try to endure.
What do you mean? I want
we paid, motherfucker.
Does this was your plan?
Who is screwing everything now, Joey?
Do not ever say that.
Do not ever tell.
- We were going to come and go.
- Listen, I love you.
And sometimes life changes, right?
People have to
adapt. This is life.
The typical Joey.
You always do things by halves.
The typical Ron, always
you act like a fag.
You know what?
Fuck you, Ron.
And to hell with the black. According?
If you're saying
You believe in this nonsense ...
I'm the one you
protects. He who loves you.
Whoever wants our
life better. I!
Fuck that guy!
Fuck the black!
I'll kill you right here.
I'm here to get money.
I'm going to that dome
and I will do it for us.
If you prefer, leave.
Go with black.
You look somewhat rusty.
You move.
Hey, what's up?
What are they doing? Come on.
What are you doing?
Someone is dead.
What will happen is
I go to the vaults ...
and I will ensure
leave nothing ...
there, to
to live our lives.
Because otherwise ...
it's over. We will
screwed. Do you understand?
Sasha ...
Are you with me or not?
Yes darling.
Bum.
Do not worry, these three are legit.
- I'm sure.
- But you seem worried.
I'm very worried.
Why it takes so long?
- I do not know.
- Why it takes so long? Come on!
But Father ...
look at all this.
Surely something is not right.
Perhaps He wants you to reconsider.
"The what
arrogant enough ...
to question
the judge's verdict ...
or the priest who represents
the will of the Lord your God,
must die. "Deuteronomy 17:12.
I have time.
I wait for you.
What the hell is this?
- My wife is there.
- You want to wait and risk?
Denise if not
you would be so impatient.
You are right.
Well, come on! I am going to
masturbate on everyone's lips.
Now cover me, come on.
There are two types of SWAT about
of you crack their ass,
at the south entrance.
There are only two. Cover me.
Shots!
Comuníquenme with the Bank!
Motherfuckers! So things will be?
They gave!
I told my guys were good.
No problem, so good.
Boomerang!
Brilliant.
You move.
Captain, I have the hotline.
The men are in place.
Hello?
This is Captain Howard.
With whom I speak?
Yes, that's a question
stupid. Who do you speak?
Fool.
is the type that is robbing the bank.
I heard shots.
What is going on there
inside? Are you all right?
Of course there were shots!
They sent two guys from SWAT!
I apologize for that,
it will not happen again.
Can we talk now?
What do you want exactly?
They want to make a deal?
It's okay. I will offer one.
It's very simple.
You let us keep the money,
you let us go and there will be problems.
You know that's not going to happen.
Seriously.
Why do not you come to the
door and talk face to face?
If it is okay. I imagined that.
So why are we talking?
This conversation is over. To hell!
This is going to get ugly.
Fuck.
These guys are psychopaths.
Give me your intercom.
Smith, Bishop. What is your situation?
position. Pending orders.
Johnson, what's your situation?
Waiting for hostages. In place.
Campbell and Williams,
What is your situation?
A Williams he was wounded.
The wound is slight.
I'm sorry, Captain, we were wrong.
- Do you think?
- Is my wife. It's in the bank.
- Let them come the paramedics.
- Yes, Captain.
This is to?
Are you sure?
It is blurred.
You move.
Stop looking at me!
Grab that bastard.
- Bring it here.
- Go Go!
Go Go! Go Go!
You are crazy? What are we doing?
Easy, easy.
I do not want you in jail!
I do not want to go to jail!
Fuck.
Take that.
Stand up! Can you walk?
- What is the message?
- He will not want to see.
NEXT DIE
Heavens!
Take him to Emergency. Fast!
Motherfuckers.
I see you got my message.
Yes. I got your message. Loud and clear.
Listen well.
Let's get out of here. Understood?
or receive another message
in a body bag.
This clear?
I understood.
He is thirty minutes.
Thirty minutes. It's okay.
Your.
- Your.
- Come on!
Back! Back!
She is pregnant! She is pregnant!
- I do not give a shit.
- Sit down!
- Please!
- Hold it there, everyone!
Low hands, feet.
Look out.
Stop looking at me!
Women Hostage in point
look, but no visual of the murderer.
Yes, there is a movement.
Hold your positions.
Father, please. Help her.
A criminal is pointing
pregnant women ...
and keeps looking at his watch.
Father, please, help.
Paul.
- I do not want to die!
- She wants not to die!
I do not want to die.
- She does not want to die.
- I know!
Look out the window, do not look at me.
I do not want to die. I do not want to die.
Are you ready to die?
Please save her.
Save her.
"Let us therefore,
boldly to the throne of grace,
for mercy ...
and find grace to
timely relief. "
Hebrews 4:16.
Campbell, do not.
- Do not!
- Campbell.
Campbell back here!
What the hell is wrong with you?
I can not, I can not ... I can not breathe.
Breathing is the least
your problems, bitch.
Better start praying to God,
It's the best thing you can do.
I asked you if you are ready to die.
I'm not here to
this shit, Bones.
Drop your fucking gun.
I told you to drop the weapon.
You're crazy.
Is this what we do?
Not kill a baby.
That's fucked up, man. What are you doing?
So you plan to do this?
Will they soften with
a pregnant bitch?
Calm down.
Where is Plan B? Not this.
You are crazy? This sucks, Bones.
This is stupid, idiot.
Father...
Enough!
Give your inhaler. He can not breathe.
Do not try to be a hero.
Shut up!
There is.
Fool.
Did you do that?
Tiny?
What's up man? What are they doing?
We have company.
Yeah, do not tell me.
We have to go to Plan B, brother.
They screwed!
Plan B! Did you hear Me?
Very good. Plan B.
It's showtime. Come on.
It was time.
What the fuck is B, Bones Plan?
Here they come!
Tiny! Gasoline!
Tiny! Gasoline! Let's go!
Fuck! Will you fly!
Somebody turn off the heat!
I see what you want to reach.
I do not turn back!
Get up, get up!
Lift your ass! Arise!
Or I'll blow your head off! Arise!
Come on. Come on. Come here.
Give me the mask!
Wear it.
He has a hostage! Stop the fire!
Put the gun down!
You think
I'm playing, right?
I'm going to kill this motherfucker.
I want to live. I want to live!
You got a shot?
I want to live!
Negative. Not a shot.
I want to live. I want to live!
Now fire.
I want to live!
Shoot him a bastard.
"Everyone who calls on the
name of the Lord shall be saved. "
Romans 10:13.
Thank you.
Mom is gone.
Wear it! Wear it!
Breathe.
What are you doing, Rob? Get down!
You are in the firing line!
OMG! Fuck! Rob!
OMG! Come on! Come on!
Go Go. Fuck!
- Are you okay.
- I can not continue.
Are you okay. Are you okay.
Come here, come here.
- I'm fucked, Joey.
- Do not.
No, Rob. Everything will be
all right. Everything will be fine.
Think about it. This weekend
week will be on the beach.
Do not? With whores and
beers. Fuck.
Please Rob not.
I need you. It's my fault.
My fucking fault!
I'll go with you anytime.
I'm sorry, Rob.
I'm sorry...
Checkmate.
Honey, wait. What are you doing?
You promised me, Joey. What are you doing?
is over.
They killed my brother!
Fuck you!
Do not!
Hello. It seems you do not have
after all those years.
Is there any problem?
Look, brother, I have all day.
No, there is no problem.
All right.
No problem at all.
Thank you.
ACT TO ETERNITY
Make sure it is sent.
Yes sir.
See you very soon.
Yes it is.
Do not leave the building.
I said do not leave the building!
Get ready.
Follow me, sir.
- She's all yours, Captain.
- Thank you.
Gee, honey, you're very brave.
God, I love you so much!
Please do.
We'll have a family.
Hey, this agreement does not
It worked for anyone.
But I think I found a solution
that will please all of us.
Why must
listen to this cockroach?
We go now.
No I do not believe it.
Welcome to my fucking world!
Where are you going? I do not think so!
Do not move or I'll blow your head.
Where is my document?
I would not do that in your place.
Remember that it is impossible for me to fail.
Checkmate!
Get out of here!
Yes, it's checkmate for now.
But I'll see you later.
You can count on that.
I went in and was at the cashier,
and the girl came out of nowhere.
The guard and I did not expect.
I'm sorry. I must attend
the call. Is my wife.
- I will contact you.
- Thank you.
Hi dear.
OMG. Thank you.
Is incredible! Amazing.
We'll be fine, honey.
Johnson, that was an incredible shot.
Lord, I did not shoot today.
- Christopher ...
- What, Mom?
How are you?
I have good news.
They have a heart for you.
You will be fine.
I love you, Mom.
the battle line
BETWEEN GOOD AND EVIL ...
GOES BY
Heart of every man.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5ubyd
Help other users to choose the best subtitles