Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Why am I so devoted?
It is not in the family.
My parents are quite distant.
Also opposed.
But some people are just different.
Some people are predisposed to believe.
A type flash between their eyes.
They are not afraid of eternity.
They are familiar with it.
And when they bind
with the soul of another...
they consider that bond as sacred.
I was always such a person.
It did take a while before I realized it.
If nuns take their vows...
They go on the church floor are
and pray for strength.
I've also done.
And if it was up to me situated
would thus end the story.
Joline?
Carl, you can not see me.
You look great.
You can not come here.
That brings misfortune.
Are you serious?
Where is your flower?
- In my hand. That brings happiness.
And because you're my daisy.
I love daisies.
- I know.
But now I'm crushed.
I love so dearly.
How are you?
- Excellent.
Is anyone there?
- Yes, they are all waiting.
What is it, Chicky?
- I want to talk to you about Love Army.
Matt and Duey booked for
Space Ass Tour in Japan.
Do you let your band to Japan?
They had to. Where they can earn a lot
yen.
You begged me if I wanted to book. You remember?
Yes, I'm mad because they Rufus
the drummer, have preserved.
If there is someone in the band?
- Sure. I.
Hold me now do not be fooled.
- What do you mean?
I have booked a whole band,
and not a person.
But I'm a great bass player.
- Yeah, but can you sing?
Not really.
- You sing in a shower?
Jo, I'm a damn good one,
brilliant bass.
I know too.
Your say on the show?
Have I promised this occur?
- Yup.
Is it then?
You're the Love Army now.
Joline, you're the best.
Are you guys still here?
- I still break.
I flirt with your brother, but I'm not sure I've
success. I have success?
Yes, you have some success.
Jo, this picture is Carl.
Say just about anything.
- Why not?
He wants to make news photos
and not photographing food.
Food is still news?
Take that series over patties.
That there are so many.
He wants to take pictures of important events.
He is depressed all those souffle's.
I give a birthday party for him. Are you?
He acted only birthday?
That was eight months ago.
He is there to now.
Sean, you can not all the time
sit on the toilet.
Nice of you that you Carl tries to cheer.
He does it so often for me.
I also have masses cool
friends to whom I can imagine.
Here we go again.
Meg, it is "in prosperity and adversity."
Is that "until death do you part?"
Or "until long as it's fun"?
Until death do you part.
- How long they will remain so, do you think?
A few years.
- Forever, Meg.
Some believe what they say.
And I 'forever' said.
So I've pretty
despite it tomorrow is sold out?
Did I say that you got free?
- Perfectly arranged.
Wait for me.
Hi, Jo. With Carl.
I remain still jut.
I have to photograph a pancake breakfast.
They understood here apparently
under photojournalism.
Sorry, Jo.
I feel a little down.
I have to be here by myself.
I just wanted to let you know that I love you.
Sorry, I'll call you up?
- Does not matter. What is up?
Nothing.
- Where is Carl?
You know how long Carl stays away?
You may continue but I do not live alone.
Think you inmates
still awake?
I do not know. Perhaps.
Do they have anything in common?
Yes, of course. Why do you ask?
Because I in Jenny's bed can sleep...
and then sleep with Jenny Mimi.
Whether she dives but someone else
the suitcase.
What do you mean?
That they may sleep with whom she wants.
She is an adult. They may decide.
She still does not sleep in your bed?
- No. Not every night.
I never go to her room. She comes
always with me, I usually sleep all
Then she comes to lie to me.
Sometimes it's nice to cuddle.
She and Mimi are still a couple?
That is true. I love Mimi.
What I do not harm their relationship.
What they have is pure,
sincere and honest.
It is very pure.
Do not look at me.
Jo, you've already seen
Jenny's new design?
I'm going to the market.
It is really quite different than what is now for sale.
Hi, Mimi. Good Morning.
Did you see who is there?
She rats burden.
Carl chases they usually...
but he is out of town on business.
Do not you, Jo?
Why she is here.
- You want a cup of coffee, Mimi?
Is that your wedding ring? That tattoo?
Has Carl also so alone?
Carl has eczema.
- What?
Eczema, a skin condition.
Jenny has a wedding ring. Not True?
Well, it's actually one ordinary ring.
He is in a safe.
I did not know you were married.
This is intense.
Unbelievable, right?
- Actually.
I'm glad it's over.
I do not mean silly, Joline.
What have I to do with it?
- You're married and that's nice.
I tried marriage,
but it's not for me.
Well for Joline,
another topic so.
I have been married, and I do not think anyone
honestly wants to be.
Because you were not really married.
I told you so.
You said you've tried it,
but that is not enough.
You want it here
not.
What did you say?
That your parents and my parents were not married?
I do not say you were not married,
but you thought of something else.
On what?
- Jenny, shut up.
Listen, I do not stay, but thank
I could stay tonight.
Sure?
- I want to be home when Carl comes.
Are you sure you save you?
- And you?
This is good, actually.
Jo, I do not know when I return.
First I think clearly.
Love, Carl.
How do you respond to a breach of trust?
Especially if it's your first?
Love Army. And the song is called
Love Army Blues. Thank you.
It is tempting to seek distraction.
And you focus on your other commitments.
You try to just do it.
And you pretend there's nothing wrong.
It was delicious.
- All kits? Do you need anything?
Another party would have
canceled. No, not Jo. I say that.
Hi, Jo.
That cake looks delicious.
A map of Carl? What he writes?
I could not stay in New York.
Not only because of the work.
It is definitely not you.
I write you soon.
I am also sad. Love, Carl.
State also where is he?
"The pear cactus catches the last rays of." That says nothing.
And the postmark is illegible.
Tuck.
There are three kinds of chocolate.
I think it will probably taste.
This is good, Jo. Now at least you know what you have
to him.
That burden off your shoulders
cases. A hairy load.
I do have some dope for you.
Everyone thinks I'm a dick.
But Carl is also a.
Jo, come out.
- We are your friends.
It's more fun here.
Do we come in?
Now we come in, okay?
All kits?
- What do you do?
My car keys are still
in the car. Stupid, huh?
That is Chicky's car.
What are you doing?
What I'm doing now?
I can not think straight.
And it goes not about, you know.
I wanted to go to my mother
Long Island to kick the habit.
If I had money,
I would go to.
Then it would be fine.
I would get back on the right path.
You never know how you find your faith.
It can get through something ridiculous.
That's just it.
Do not ask someone you trust
is worth. Trust to trust.
Who are you doing it?
For them, or for yourself?
Why are you?
- How much does it cost to Long Island?
I do not know. $ 40 or something.
This is not a joke, right?
I had no idea whether he was going to rehab or not.
But I just wanted to believe.
And that was a great feeling.
I want to say something.
Can it down?
You were just rather negative,
but I do not want to hear.
I do not bullshit about my husband.
Does anyone know where my husband is?
He went to the west.
- I know that. Does anyone know anything more?
This is a celebration,
now is danced there.
What do you care where Carl is?
I mean: Who is your example?
Mom and Dad in any event.
Were behind our neighbors?
Why an example? I do not know
surfer, I may therefore not surf?
I think you all
very good picks.
I think you're very special.
- Thank you, Jay. Me too.
Jay, I'm married.
- Pardon Me.
And I'm your sister.
- I know. That was really intense.
Most relationships fail because
partners wait for something to happen.
But if you want someone
stays with you, you should invest...
even though they behave like an idiot.
If I frugal would do...
I had enough money to search two ordinary
or a big state.
Everything was pointing in the direction
Texas.
People know much more than they think.
Sometimes you can get information
in a strange way.
The postmark was illegible,
but I thought I saw five letters.
And there are no cacti
in Idaho or Maine.
And wanderers go to Texas
to get lost even more.
Have you seen this man?
That is a statistical fact.
Probably because it is so big.
A stranger in a desert is 5 times
scarier than a stranger in New York.
I wish I could say
that is not true.
I'll see you.
Stay away from my purse.
A slap...
Mike, are you done with her?
Let's go. Come on.
Jiffy.
I've been coming
Because you are so like Blondie,
do you keep her.
Fuck.
- Wait for me.
You're a dick.
- I was hard at work for you.
I have rings for you.
I want nothing from you. You're a dick.
- Wait. Just look at this ring.
For you.
Thank you.
- No thanks.
Are you okay?
Are you stuck?
Can I have my purse back?
Give her the damn bag now but.
Let my arm loose. Release me.
Where are you now?
- In Texas.
How is it there?
- Quite intense.
Interesting, but vehemently.
I'll call you tomorrow, Meg. Bye.
Pardon, go
use the discount coupons?
With Joline from Room 1 01.
Do you have a moment?
- Yeah, you know.
That's okay. Thank you.
You would think that I would fly off Carl.
But something held me and said I had to give
man some space.
That he was not ready for.
That's the hardest one relationship.
You give partner space.
How much space will be needed.
You must rely on your feelings.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Do you bothering me?
- No, you know. Not at all.
You arouses my interest.
Do you want to drink a beer inside
?
Well, come
I do with the beer out.
Please.
- No, thank you.
I called Niko, but you may also call me
Neil.
Or what you want.
I make things in newsprint and paper towel...
and paint and glue, of course.
That's obvious, right?
I'm here drove
because I was looking for my husband.
I wanted to know if it went well with him. I Shizu him.
I want him to see me only
when he's ready.
I will not tell your secret.
- Thank you.
So you're married to that guy
who lives down the house?
Precisely with him.
You know him?
- No.
Could you maybe just
want to come in my humble stulpje?
It's a mess, but cozy.
It is a sexy mess.
Again, I'm married.
Shall I tell you something?
I think that is just so exciting.
No, I really mean that.
Women who are devoted to their husbands...
winds me enormously.
Is not that weird?
- Yes, that's it.
I know,
but I can not help it.
Anyway, it's my problem.
I should keep it to myself.
True.
- You hear me about it anymore.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Do you really want a beer?
Come only.
I'm Joline O'Neill Howell.
I'm Carl's wife.
Carl Howell, the photographer.
Course. Come in.
I did not even pay attention
when Carl told me about you.
Does not.
- I do not watch often. Sit down.
So you are Carl's better half?
This is my wife.
Since last June. Her name is Suzanne.
She's beautiful.
She looks happy.
I hope so.
Third time lucky, they say.
Three times for her.
This is my first time. For me it's new.
And for you it's the last chance.
- Congratulations.
I did not know you came. I
Carl just before a session sent out.
May I ask what he's going to shoot?
The chili cook-off in Cornudas.
That's right anyway, eh Ben?
Yes, a cooking competition.
- You're kidding.
No, I thought not.
Can you let someone else do not
?
Carl does.
He will not disappoint me.
I've noticed that he's eating well.
I do not what to do.
I'm sure you understand your box.
I would really just
tell how talented Carl.
Carl would rather take pictures
about life and man.
That kind of photos. He's at least
as well. Even better.
Do you see that calf?
Carl would have highlighted that calf.
These pictures are nothing compared to those of Carl. Not ugly intended.
I mean, if these are your photos.
Are these your photos?
I say this because Carl
currently struggling.
And that cooking competition makes it even ten times worse.
Thanks for the information.
Carl is still in his probation.
Any information is welcome.
I have to get back to work.
Have I said too much?
- You have expressed well.
Did I mention that Carl appreciates her work,
otherwise he would not do it.
I will soon tell
that you've been through.
Just do not.
- Whatever you want.
Forget
but most of what I said.
That will not happen.
He is really good.
- You said that already
Very good..
Violence solves nothing.
You must suppress your tendency to use violence to. Either way.
Yes, boy...
yet one more time.
You block the car of my uncle.
You battery is empty.
I have no jumper cables. Do you?
Are you a member of the roadside?
Come on inside.
We then use my card. That they do not notice.
I should have been on my work.
But the others are always late.
Is that Mexico?
- Yes, that is the limit. The Rio Grande.
They put me on hold.
You seem very nice.
- Thank you. You too. Sit down.
You know Carl long?
- You know Carl, too?
I met him a few weeks ago.
How do you know Carl?
I'm his wife.
I did not know. I swear:
I had no idea.
You have to believe me.
- I believe you.
What a fucking mess. I sit back
stuck with a married guy.
I did not know he was married,
but I knew in my subconscious?
No idea.
- That should. This always happens to me.
It has to do with
confidence. I've read.
I've done a banana in your tank.
Yesterday I made a banana
in your tank. Pardon Me.
What's the effect?
- I do not know.
Damn, T-Bo.
I give you no key.
He was here yesterday.
How should I respond?
- Do What U Want. None of your business.
What do you think of that reaction?
Sorry, Carmen.
I will never do anything, you know.
But I jerk that guy's New York
entrails from his body.
The New York fucking guts
of that bastard.
What did you say?
- Nothing.
You should have said something.
- Nietes.
Say something.
Come on, Carmen. Say something.
I have to tell you anything.
That's not possible.
- Yes it is, T-Bo.
I have to tell you anything.
Absolutely nothing.
But we felt something for each other.
You can not deny.
I'm awfully fond of you,
but I swear I love you.
Okay?
- Yeah, nothing wrong.
Is that your husband?
- Man? He is not even my friend.
I am eight times with him
slept.
Carmen, listen.
There is something wrong with that boy.
You should see him go and finish.
I do not know where he lives.
He always comes to visit me in
the restaurant when he is in town.
Does he know where Carl lives?
- No idea. How So?
Because he New York guts
Carl will tear out. For That.
Do you worry about Carl?
- Yup.
I'm mad at him,
but he does not die.
Would I want this guy Carl
guts ripped out?
Absolutely.
I learned a side of Carl
know that I did not like.
But who has promised to protect him
in prosperity and adversity?
At that moment I wished that it had been another.
But that was not the case.
I promised.
How long will you be here this time
?
No idea. I want to know if he
morning goes to work.
Why would he do that?
- I want to be sure.
Can I tell you what I do with you
would do if you were to break your vow...
and I would go to bed?
- Come on, Neil.
I'm not saying I do, but I want to tell
only.
Sure? It's awfully sexy.
You do not have to say.
Think just a moment.
Okay. Good. Do your eyes closed.
- Forget it.
Just do it simply.
I do you no harm.
What do I do?
I do not know, but you can
'd better stop it.
I ask if you want to quit
with what you're doing.
Why do not open your eyes?
I do them open when you quit.
Have you told Carl that T-Bo?
- Yup.
I also said that I'm
no longer wanted to see.
I do not know if he has been given the story about
T-Bo. Can be.
Did you tell that I was there?
Should it?
- No.
How was work?
Does he have his job?
We have not talked about his work. How So?
So only.
Incidentally,
your brother this morning called.
I gave him your number.
That you do not mind?
No, we have nice chat.
He said when I had to call?
- He called me.
He asked what I thought of this state.
What did you say?
- I said you've seen Carl...
but Carl yours yet.
And we both found strange.
Carl is not yet ready.
We both found it
it all comes from one side.
That's not true.
- Do you want those chips yet?
I would expect that he would support me if I
thing going through.
Really?
- Of Course.
You do whether it's a spiritual thing.
If he comes from Tibet. Sit down.
I've never been in Tibet.
What do you do now you wait until
Carl is ready for it?
Go to him only spy?
Spy  I'm not.
I like him in the eye.
I protect him.
What are you doing this afternoon?
- How Come?
I want you to meet someone.
I never understood anything of that hocus-
pocus. Although it's in my blood.
But you are different.
You do have a predisposition.
Day Grandpa.
This is my girlfriend, Joline.
Joline, this is Cinco.
They may call you anyway Cinco?
- They call me whatever she wants.
It is an honor to meet you.
Carmen told me of your special gifts.
She needs help, Grandpa.
She has problems with her husband.
Carmen said that your wife
also had special gifts.
And you know her secrets.
- I was not there.
Now I get a moment's peace.
Everyone wants me to solve all sorts of things.
I brought Pepsi.
Then get a few glasses.
You live here pretty.
There's a rattlesnake in that vessel.
Take him at once. I miss him.
A real rattlesnake?
I have bewitched him.
Do not worry.
Do not. Put the lid back on.
Do not fool her.
- Who does that?
She has confidence in me.
That even my grandchildren.
Do not start again.
Stop that. And you also get
no Pepsi me.
Come here. Sit down.
Blow once.
Again.
This may take a while.
Everyone knows what they mean rituals.
No one needs to give meaning
to something, because it is already there
It's already
before you are born.
The sky is blue and the house is pink.
That goes for you and for me.
That house is not pink,
previously salmon.
I'm going inside.
Call me if you need me.
Thanks. Bye.
- See you, Neil.
How did you find me?
- Carmen has brought me.
I like that you are there,
but I can not go out with you.
Listen, Jo. I think you should come home and this should
caps.
I really mean that.
Hi, my mother made it.
Thank you. This is my brother, Jay. Toby
lives in the pink salmon-colored house.
Hello, little Toby.
We were just here to talk.
I'll soon be here with you.
Thank your mother for me.
Carl
I can honestly pretty...
but I do not know whether he is worth it.
Does it matter whether he's worth?
Suppose Carl his both legs
had lost.
Should I dump him
for someone with good legs?
I have eternal loyalty to him promised
in front of you and God.
He is not in a wheelchair.
I mean...
That's an analogy.
He is mentally in a wheelchair.
He is mentally in a wheelchair?
You do not understand and I can not identify you.
So it seems better that you leave the car.
You're my brother and I love you.
But you must get off.
I'm in Texas.
Sometimes it is very heavy. Then
difficult to persevere.
It helps to talk with someone who understands the.
How do you do that?
- What?
His bite is deadly.
- Not for me.
I carved all with fangs
in my skin when I was little.
The first time I made a small scratch.
The second time I scratched harder.
It started to bleed.
The third time yet again louder, etc..
Some let them bite immediately.
- Who still die?
Some do, indeed.
But those who continue to live
be snake charmer.
They immediately get a reward.
And immediately force.
I do not. I must have patience,
because I'm not that brave.
I would like to call not brave, but stupid.
You can view it from two sides.
Here, I've done it in lime.
- Awesome. Thank you.
Now they suddenly do not want
talk to me, you know.
Why I'm the bogeyman?
Why are these anyway?
You have to wait and see. It makes no sense
to put her under pressure.
Waitress is that my margarita?
I'm worried about her.
- I know.
It's sweet of you
that you worry.
You have a nice family.
And so spiritual. That's you also fixed.
You think not that I mentally
is in a wheelchair or something?
Do you think of me?
- No, no, absolutely not.
Can I now my margarita?
I'll be back.
There she is.
Would they see us?
- So what? It's a car.
True. You are right.
I do not give her the idea
we spy on her.
But we still do?
No, we fit just fine on her.
That's something else.
You see that?
Row something through.
Then she sees us.
- A little bit.
It seems Joline though.
True. And that is that man.
Do you think she looks?
- No, I think not.
Why not?
They can see everything.
Joline takes her promises
pretty seriously.
If you only watch,
break your promise not? Even So?
Is there whether he knows she looks.
- How so?
If he knows she looks, she
plays a role at all.
But if he does not know, it's like he
plays with herself.
And that's okay, acceptable.
OK,
but suppose he knows she looks?
But they do not know that he knows that she looks.
So she thinks she just
is watching. Very innocent.
Because it all comes from one side.
If you are watching a movie.
It is. But if he knows that they
watching.
And she knows that he knows that she looks...
... then
Man, that's another intimacy.
- You got that right.
You can not always remain.
This gives a lot of protection, right?
Better I have not.
What is it?
Very strange.
- What's strange?
You remind me of my wife.
That is indeed strange.
You should do the following.
You break him in.
I do not care how.
I help him recover.
You leave everything untouched.
Show respect for things.
You put the sand in places you
expects him get hurt.
In places where you expect
that will be something to him.
Use your common sense.
Do not be economical. I've had enough of this stuff.
I did not think you'd see me.
- What are you doing here?
I rest for a while.
Why pour mud everywhere?
It is sacred sand.
It protects you from T-Bo.
Who?
Carmen told me that she had told you.
How do you know Carmen?
Carl, I did not think you'd see me. I wanted to give you space.
Jo, you must see.
Later, Toby. Good?
About Carmen. Am I hurt? Yup.
Am I evil. Yup.
We will have to work hard at it...
but I blame her anything.
She even my girlfriend.
She is very nice. And she has something
with Jay. My brother is also here.
I feel quite a bit
panicky, Jo. I'm sorry.
I understand that.
That was not my intention.
Does not matter.
It's all my fault.
I have not been honest and therefore
I have now that panicky feeling.
The you also surprised to see me here
and to see how I live...
and where I live. I understand that.
I try to explain it in a letter. I have two versions.
Have you ever loved someone, Jo...
with your whole heart and soul?
And then one day you notice
they all suck your happiness.
They did not mean to.
It was just the way.
Suddenly something good happens.
You hope it, because you're talking needed.
You feel that you're drowning and you
needed something to go by.
And then you see something good come down on you.
It comes right at you.
And if you want to grab it,
it goes to another.
It looks like a bad joke.
Suppose that another does not.
Would I get lucky?
I do not know, but my feeling
says maybe it is.
You mean I bring you happiness?
- It may sound strange.
But I realize that I made a mistake somewhere.
Because everything went well,
until something changed.
I realized only after a long time,
because I loved you...
I completely lost the thread.
That marked you as well?
I saw you saw it too.
I had nothing to look at you, Jo.
Absolutely nothing.
You made constant fun stuff.
And you had all earned.
But where was I? Nowhere.
And that meant?
I had to leave to get things done.
That was the only way to
no longer get lost.
And I feel that I am now not far from.
Go, sit.
I want to show you something.
Who took this photo?
Frontpage, eh?
And this?
And this? Carl Howell.
My boss believes in me.
I do not eat since Monday to do more.
Since last Monday?
- Starting Monday, yes.
And he will not return whistle me
I feel it. And you see this house?
This is a house of Casa Homes,
with option to buy. And I think about it.
But this is only a small part.
- Which?
From the step I make.
Do you understand what I mean?
You understand best,
because you're smart enough.
I assumed that you understood me
and that meant a lot to me.
I feel that I have said enough.
I have the feeling that you only have to go. okay?
I can not stand
that you stay longer.
It could be worse than
spiritual sitting in a wheelchair.
Some people are mentally in a coma.
If you're married to someone like...
is your vow
tested to the limit.
Well, Jo. I was not very clear,
I know.
I'm going to work
to express myself better...
But this makes no sense. Let me
by myself clear. Come on, Jo.
You need a license
to park there.
It is Mexican territory.
They are very strict.
They often come along. It looks
or remote, but that's not it.
And that pile of my fence.
It's my wood. From me.
From grandfather I learned how you could keep a vigil.
How to cleanse one's mind.
He said not much, but I was
convinced that I could do it.
Some things I had seen him.
Other things I made myself.
If a wake Carl not brought to his senses
, I would not know what does.
More spiritual people know immediately that you are one sacred mission.
They understand the situation immediately
and they keep their distance.
But you also have people who do not
understand where you're doing.
Because they have never seen the bigger picture.
I looked again. Did you see it too?
- Yeah, it's crazy.
Jo, you saw that shooting star?
Is Carmen there now?
Is that your Volkswagen, Carmen?
Fuck you, Carl.
Go back inside.
Are you Jay?
Did you 'fuck you' to me?
Yes, it's me, Jay. Fuck you.
No, get yourself Fuck you, Jay.
Do you know why?
I do not even talk to you.
I'm talking to Carmen.
Fuck you, Carl.
- That said Carmen. Did you hear that?
Can you cared
what my neighbors think of this?
They think you're a bunch of squatters.
What you say is yourself.
In the desert can change people
in other beings.
In a fox or a crow.
Carl had turned into an asshole.
I had to make my rituals
more extreme.
Is that your husband?
Well, you know.
I would be quite a bit more time to spend with your...
but it feels a bit strange
because your husband right in the neighborhood.
I mean, right across the street.
It just feels weird.
Tomorrow I'm going to Toronto. I try
there to sell some of my work.
But then I come back here again.
I wish that you fit on my monkey.
I usually make pinatas
but he is not.
You should not smash him.
Take care of yourself.
How do you know when you've gone too far
?
Sometimes you'll get clues...
But you'll be too busy with your rituals...
and not you see those signs.
You have again broken with me, huh?
I wonder why my window was broken...
and then I find eggs under my bed.
Yes, yes. Eggs.
Six, I do not know how they get there,
fucking raw eggs.
This is far, Jo. Even for you.
I'm concerned.
I'm really worried about you.
I wanted to let you know.
Should something happen, then you need
understand that you left me no choice.
Enter. Give back.
So it came.
Why I recorded.
Tell me what that man means to you.
He is my husband.
Exactly, yes. And you protected him?
Against one T-Bo, if I'm not mistaken. And he's your husband?
No, he is not.
Excuse me,
I read it wrong.
It's good to find out what
these men mean to you...
if we have a little more time.
Hopefully writing in your journal
helped you.
I think so.
- Good. I'm glad.
But maybe I should
a larger dose of medication.
The medications we give, we do not give
for fun.
Who knows, help them to see things differently. That's why I get them anyway?
No, why do not we give them to you.
We are not on a fast result from here.
We do not look here for an easy way out.
Far too many people are looking for an easy way out.
Hopefully you learn to break that pattern.
I felt like I told a joke that no one understood.
But I kept him tell
because I thought it was a good joke.
And now I sit between
misunderstood people.
Can I ask you something, Adelle?
Is it ever bother you that no one else in the moon
believe?
Maybe the good is if I stay here just long enough.
Adelle, you take those pills still in?
I should just surrender.
Emptying My spirit.
Feel Nothing more.
Go to sleep.
That's better.
It's time to get out of here.
Take a deep breath and then we go.
I can not.
Do not know what I did?
- I heard.
Then you know so that I'm too sick to go.
Maybe you were not sick enough.
Maybe you need some poison...
to be able to live without
death along with us.
You have a rare power.
It's not that you did not have power.
But if you rise from the dead
verdriedubbel your strength...
sometimes even quadrupled.
You could use it here,
but it is too limited.
That would be stingy.
Go now but.
Take your shoes.
I'm going to talk to this girl.
If you do not say, I put you
silence, mister Kakentoe.
I had you immediately have to beat up
when you came here.
I should have overwhelmed
as an avalanche of shit.
Carl, I'll talk about our marriage.
It's over.
I realize now too.
I've tried.
Really tried.
But I do not go on.
I'll get over it.
I may be someone who is committed.
But I feel disconnected from you.
You can delete tattoos.
It takes a long time and it hurts...
but ultimately you are left with a white spot.
Has T-Bo you done that?
No, I'm out of a car cases.
- A moving car?
It was a Jeep. I watched
not well and I fell out.
I hope it heals quickly.
Goodbye, Carl.
I'm still committed.
I have talent for.
Some people just have that.
If you do not look up the extremes
how can you be absolutely sure?
How do they know what they really
, or what they stand for?
From El Paso?
Or where others stand for?
That remains a mystery.
Beer?
You have dogs, I see.
Bill, Sheila, kitchen.
I came back to pick up my shower radio.
I have myself but admitted.
Coming from El Paso purpose here?
I do not live in El Paso,
I live in New York again.
Everything came there one bit
a dead end, not only in terms of work.
I had the feeling that I no longer knew who I was.
I knew you knew it yet though.
I had a wrong step put
in my life.
I felt that I did something...
why I came back.
And I'm back again.
It's just a reflex.
I sit today in karate.
You can quite nice.
- You OK? Really?
It felt good to me.
- Really? Fine.
I just came by to see
or was okay with you.
It's fine with me.
See you then. Thank you.
I will give you back your key.
Take care of yourself, Carl.
Wholeheartedly.
- It was a beautiful ceremony.
Joline, unbelievable
that you've caught the bouquet.
You threw it right at me,
exactly in my eye.
Sorry.
- Does not matter.
I did because you have inspired us.
We met at your campsite.
I took champagne for you.
- Thank you.
Did I mention that I
chocolate to have you in my car?
And a poem.
A poem?
- Right.
I want to soon nominate you.
You're not going to be obscene?
- No, of course not. Come on.
But if you want, I do it, though.
You can be quite persistent.
As is worth...
There are always people who dare
it to make a big jump.
They jump off a cliff with all
what they have and hope 's best.
What can you say about them?
Are they stupid or brave?
Are they crazy?
Or they may themselves very lucky?
That's again something you can see from both sides.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3zh5
Help other users to choose the best subtitles