Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
A disease caused by promiscuity.
A disease that Satan created.
A disease that the Catholic Church...
...can not tolerate at any rate.
We are aware that
this is a serious problem.
A problem that Jesus
himself would have denounced.
It is our responsibility
as Christians to fight...
this sexual promiscuity.
It is the responsibility
of each of us...
to stop the spread
of AIDS in our society.
We must not forgive...
The church has AIDS!
I have no voice in
this conference!
Our fellow priests are dying
and the Vatican does nothing!
Open your eyes to
what's going on!
Stop this shame
before it's too late!
How many of you here
are HIV positive?!
How many of you in this
room are HIV positive?!
I will not be silent!
Priests are dying
in the hundreds.
I will not be silenced.
You can't hide it here!
This issue can not be hid!
This issue can not be hidden,
the church has AIDS!
The church has AIDS!
To the airport!
-Good afternoon, Father.
-Quiet moment.
I like to be here
on my own sometimes.
Father Doherty.
Daniel.
-Good weekend?
-Thank you, yes.
Tom.
Jack.
-Where have you been?
-Chapel.
If you spend any more
time in that place...
you may as well sleep
on the fuckin' alter.
-Dean's list up yet?
-No, no not yet.
To God, Fitzpatrick's
not on it.
Or that other queer fella.
Oh, come on now,
where's your compassion?
I haven't got any as far
as Ernie is concerned.
You know I don't like
that lucky bollocks.
Oh, is this any good, Danny?
Brilliant, half-way
through it already.
We better read it
before he gets here.
I hope he's better
than the last fella.
A wee bit shorter too.
Holy Mary, my ass is killin' me
by the finish.
Oh well, we must suffer
for our faith boys.
We must shite!
Come on, find your man!
The biggest danger is that
center forward they've got.
If we can stop him
we're in with a chance.
He toss?
-Apart from him.
-What's wrong with him?
The best this place has seen
in a long time.
-That can be the fittest look.
-He's keen to play.
Looking at you again, Danny.
No, he's not.
He might be lookin' at you!
You never know he might come knockin
at your door at midnight...
with two cups of cocoa
and a hot water bottle.
-Bollocks!
-Them as well.
No, you don't have long to go
till your ordination,
don't throw it away now.
The long winter nights
will soon be on us.
-What's a fella to do?
-Do what the rest of us do.
It's a good team, Paul.
We should do well.
This could become Galcranagh
year to win the league.
Yes.
Especially with a
little help from him.
Yes!
Me too!
We thought you'd be
good for the team.
Oh, we will be!
I've been looking
forward to this, thanks!
Yeah, thanks.
No problem.
We need all the talent
we can get.
See you tomorrow lads,
get plenty of sleep.
That fella gives me
the jitters, Danny.
Don't be stupid, best captain
this town's ever had.
Fair enough. Hey, are you
going to the dance?
Yea...
Go on Danny!
At last!
Yes!
# From the dark end of the street
to the bright side of the road. #
# Into this life with a bump,
maybe sometimes... #
Four pints
-Cheers, lads!
-Cheers!!
-Whew!
-Fair play, chaps!
-Stop talking business.
-Meet my sister.
-Hello, Dublin.
-Nice to meet you.
Whew!
# Help me si ng my song. #
# From the dark end of the street
to the bright side of the road. #
How's it going Daniel?
I hear you won today,
congratulations.
-Were the man of the match?
-Hardly.
How are you Decklin?
See your woman over there?
Which o ne?
-The one with the big jugs.
-They've all got big jugs.
The one in the pink top,
anytime you want a ride...
she'll be happy to oblige.
She loves fucking priests.
Hasn't been out with any one else
since you joined the priesthood.
You broke her heart.
God had other plans for me.
Sure has, Daniel.
Sure has.
Enjoy yourself.
# From the dark end of the street
to the bright side of the road. #
On my way, Ma thanks.
Be back at the weekend Daniel?
Yeah.
-Good, see you then.
-See you, Ma.
Heya-Whoa!
# Your love's waiting,
till that hurt slips away. #
# He's parked close beside you.
Even true love fades. #
# Even true love fades. #
Fred, Fred, what's happened?
Jesus, Foley, you must know
someone in the Archon.
How the hell did you
find out so quick?
I got a message
from Father Sweeney.
He told me there's a story
I might be interested in.
Poor bastard
splattered himself.
Who?
Father Sweeney.
Suicide.
Big time.
God's police,
you'd better fuck off,
this is private property.
David Foley,
Galcranagh Gazette...
any chance I can ask you
a few questions?
No!
Bishop, can I ask you a few
questions about Father Sweeney.
Got any comments
to make whatsoever?
Please, just a few moments
of your time, that's all...
Foley, now, that's enough!
Foley!
Can I ask you
a few questions?
Please just a few
moments of your time.
I'll be wanting a statement
from you, Foley.
-I'm very sorry about that...
-Okay, okay.
Right if your ready
we'll go inside now.
I'll get the door for you.
I have to warn you
It's not a very plesant sight.
On the general level of
academic work this year so far,
has been exceptional.
The teaching staff tell me
you've all worked very hard.
This coming week sees a visit
of Father Joseph Venice...
from the Jesuit order
who will be giving a lecture.
And for those of you
who haven't heard him yet,
you've got a treat in store.
His talk will be based
on his best selling book;
The Longer Road.
Now, I wouldn't like
to let this morning pass...
without congratulating our hurlers...
on getting back here in one piece.
Well done, boys.
Keep up the good work.
Well done yesterday, you did
a great job for your first game.
Thanks for giving me the chance.
Last night was good,
wasn't it?
They were deadly.
-They were great!
-Yeah.
Father Dowling tells me
you're way ahead of your year.
How did you know about that?
Look, I'm having a few people
over to my room tonight,
we're going to take a look at Saint
Paul's letters to the Thessalonians.
I wonder if you'd like
to join us?
I've got some work to do,
I suppose a couple of hours
won't hurt.
-Yeah, allright.
-All right?
See you.
I'm so sorry Matthew.
-Been up to the house?
-No, no, have you?
Yeah, they wouldn't let me in.
They said it was suicide.
You sure?
Did he leave a note?
I don't know.
Why didn't he talk to me?
It's just such a waste!
It's such a terrible waste!
Galcranagh Gazette.
Anyone call?
O'Brien wants a word with you.
I heard your message Davey.
What happened?
That priest who phoned me,
Father Sweeney,
Parish of Dandur,
shot himself.
Shot himself, suicide.
Looks like it.
-Do we know why?
-Not yet, I'm working on it.
Liz was looking for you.
Yeah, I know, I was supposed
to take Martha to school.
Ah, get her some flowers.
She'll throw them at me!
Galcranagh Gazette.
No way,
I don't believe you.
I'm telling you, it's true!
Father Doherty
drank the eye bath?
-Yeah, he swallowed it down in one.
-What did the doctor say?
She was just after telling him
to take one of these three times a day.
The eyes nearly popped
out of her head.
She goes, "No, you're supposed
to bathe your eye in it,
not freakin drink it!
He thought it was booze,
it's a wonder
he didn't poison himself.
You been telling
jokes again Daniel?
Look, I'm sorry lads, I'm going to
have to postpone the class...
for an hour or so.
I hope that's okay.
Be back as soon as I can.
Hello,
Galcranagh Gazette.
Who's speaking?
Call for you, Davey.
Foley.
-David, it's Jack Dowling.
-Hi, Jack.
Listen I've got to be quick cause
I'm calling from the seminary.
Mhmm.
I need to talk to you
about Father Sweeney.
-Are you okay Jack?
-Yes, I'm fine.
Paul couldn't come, too much work.
It's unusual for him.
But I don't know where the others are.
They should be here by now.
I'm looking forward to
Father Joseph coming,
I've heard so much about him.
He's great.
Have you read his book yet?
How do you find the time?
Study, community service,
hurling captain.
This is nothing compared to what
it will be like working in parish.
Aye, you'll be there
this time next year.
Can't wait!
-It's okay.
-Not for me it isn't.
C'mon, we all need someone.
We're all human.
And we're also
called to God!
You made a promise
Noel, we all did.
And you're going to keep that
promise for the rest of your life?
Yeah!
Look, it doesn't matter
to me what you are,
that's up to you.
-I better go.
-Don't go.
-I'm going.
-You don't have to.
I won't say a word.
For fuck's sake Noel.
Just leave me alone.
What have you got Davey?
Frank Sweeney had HIV.
What?
And when the church
found out about it...
they threatened to kick him out
and leave him to fend for himself.
He was so distressed at the
thought of losing his own parish...
that he killed himself.
Poor bastard.
So who's the boyfriend?
Don't know yet,
the rumor has it,
it's somebody high
up in the church.
Who?
The pope!
I'm seeing Father Francis, he should
shed some light on the proceedings.
Your work is good Daniel.
And you're well liked.
But unfortunately I have
no choice in the matter.
What do you mean father?
I don't understand.
You have to leave.
What?
God and your conscience
spoke for you Daniel,
that's why you went
to Father Doherty.
I didn't go to
Father Doherty,
I just bumped into him.
What are you talking about?
He saw you leave
Noel's room.
I don't believe this, what you're
saying is I'm guilty by association.
No, what I'm saying
is you know the rules.
Students are not allowed to
be alone together at night.
I don't believe this!
Nothing happened
in Noel's room.
Look, take a year or two off,
see how you feel then.
I know how I feel now.
I want to be a priest.
I've always wanted to be a priest.
-You're not ready.
-You can't do this to me.
-I have rights!
-Not here you don't.
Pack your things and go.
What the hell are you doing!
What did you say
to Cathal?
I didn't, I saw you come
out of his room.
Nothing happened in Noel's room
you stupid man!
We're just doing
what's right.
You have a fucking warped
idea of what's right and wrong!
Let him go!
You're sick!
What the hell did you
tell you Cathal for?
I didn't, okay?
This is Doherty's doing, he's
nothin' more than a fucking drunk.
What exactly did you tell him!
He saw me coming
out of your room.
But nothing happened!
I know, that's what
I told Cathal.
-This will kill my mother.
-They can't do this to us.
They just have.
Oh dear God, Daniel!
What have you done?
Nothing mom, I swear to God.
You must have done something!
I told you,
I've done nothing!
What are people going to say!
Fucking hell,
this is my life!
Don't you swear
at your mother!
-I wasn't swearing at her.
-It's not just your life.
You being thrown
out of that seminary effects...
everybody's life in this house,
do you realize that?
I mean your father and I had a son
we thought was going to be priest,
now we have a son
who's on the doles!
What about our Euro grant?
I went to see
those bastards today.
That father Cathal is on
the selection board,
what the fuck is he
going to think!
They're two of
our brightest...
That is not the issue!
Okay then, what is!
The boys did nothing.
That might be so, but we can't
have this sort of thing...
going on in the seminary!
I don't believe
what I'm hearing.
Noel Kinahan approached
Daniel McLaughlin.
Daniel said no and now
both their lives are ruined,
how can that be right?
It's not a question of
what's right or wrong,
it's a question of
what's acceptable here,
and that's not acceptable.
There's nothing more to say,
it's time you left.
You can't keep
pushing this aside.
Priests can't deny their
sexuality, gay or otherwise.
You made the sacred
promise of celibacy,
I don't see you breaking it.
It's being broken every day,
all over the world.
No, not blatantly it isn't.
Oh, so as long is it's behind
closed doors it's all right.
Noel Kinahan
and Daniel McLaughlin...
are out of here
and that's the end of it.
But the likes of
Noel and Daniel...
are the life blood of the church.
They are the future.
When I came here there were
nearly 50 seminarians,
the place had life!
Five years later look at it,
it's almost empty, it's dead.
The church must evolve, we can't
live with celibacy any longer,
it's killing us!
I forbid you to voice
your opinion here.
You're here to teach
Christ's message.
-Christ died for change.
-Enough Jack!
Enough.
My decision has been made.
It's good Davey,
as usual but you're going to get
yourself into trouble...
...if you're not careful.
You always do this.
You know I reckon
there's more to come.
I think Sweeney didn't kill himself
solely because he was HIV.
The guy had it
for five years.
Oh, God.
Oh, come on, try
and understand,
it's a good
opportunity for me.
Understand what?
That you're never home, that
you never see your daughter?
You're missing out on the
most important time of her life.
This won't happen again,
once it's gone, it's gone...
and in ten years time you'll
have a teenage daughter...
on your hands
that you won't even know.
But I'm doing it for her,
I'm doing it for you.
Oh, Bollocks. You're doing it
for David Foley.
No, I suggest that
you do it now.
You know this could
get out of hand.
It's too late
to stop it now.
I don't think there's
anything to worry about,
it's only a local story.
Ah, yes, local, until the
national press pick up on it.
I think we should
let it run it course,
it will fade away.
Maybe it won't fade away.
This Foley character
wants to make his name.
Find out who else
he's been talking to.
I have a bad feeling about this,
it's here in
black and white.
"Local priest ostracized,
HIV, no suicide note."
We should let
Rome deal with it.
God will protect us,
Father Hennesey...
just as we have a duty
to protect his church.
Oppression never works.
Sometimes we have no choice.
-How are things with you and dad?
-Same.
Never had a decent conversation
with me in his whole life.
Sure, you know what he's like.
It's a long time since
we were up here together.
Years.
Just remember I told you
I was going to be a priest,
and you said you were
going to be a pilot.
Oh, pilot, Jesus, at least
you got closer than me.
Not yet I haven't.
-What are you going to do?
-I don't know.
I went to see Father Doherty,
he wants me to talk to Foley.
-That cunt?
-Every one is to you.
Foley's all right.
You scared?
No, God's on my side,
he knows what happened.
What about you? You've
got to get out of here.
I will.
Tell me, you didn't
do anything did you?
With that queer fella?
You cheeky little bollocks!
Come on!
Last one down's a poof!
Oh, shit.
Have they let you out Daniel?
A few days off Mrs. McGlynn,
community study.
You were made for the
priesthood Daniel.
I saw that in you
when you were only this high.
The way you help people and all.
I was told you had a fight
with one of the main fellas...
up at the seminary there,
and that he'd thrown you out.
There wouldn't be any truth
in that now would there, Daniel?
Oh, about the same amount of truth
in the rumor about the pope.
What's that?
He's married and has four kids
with a black lesbian.
God forgive you!
You devil you, you'll
bring bad luck on us all!
See you later Mrs. McGlynn.
You knew Frank Sweeney, Jack.
Yes.
He was ill.
Yeah.
He was struck down by God
for what he was up to.
My God isn't vengeful.
Did you talk to the
press about this?
-No.
-I hope not, Father.
This is an internal matter
for the church to deal with...
and as diocesan
communications officer,
that's my job.
We don't appear to be
dealing with it very well.
Sweeney and his like are
sinners in the eyes of God.
We have a duty to protect his
kingdom and to root out evil...
...wherever it be found.
So what you going to do about Sinead,
you gonna call her then?
Don't think so.
Come on, she's still
crazy about you.
I have enough on my
plate at the moment.
Go on, go on!
What's the matter with you two?
We're worried sick,
that's what's wrong with us.
Any tea?
That's all your good for
is drinking tea.
Why don't you go
and find some work!
Do something useful
with yourself for a change.
Dad!
So Daniel, tell us, what's
going to happen now, hmm?
What is going to happen now...
that you're not going
to be a priest anymore?
That's not decided yet.
He's nothing but
a useless bastard!
Fuck off!
I've had enough!
Don't you fuckin' talk to me
like that you little bollocks!
Sean!
Looking for a good hiding!
You started all of this
you know!
What are you
talking about ma?
This has nothing
to do with me!
It has everything
to do with you.
I'll be going back
to the seminary.
You'd better be!
Or I go and see that
Cathal fella myself.
-Good morning every one.
-Good morning Father.
Welcome to Saint Saviors
Seminary here in Galcranagh.
I'd just like to apologize
for the late start.
There are some things,
even we as men of God...
don't have control over.
I'd also like to
welcome our special guests,
and in particular to extend
a very warm welcome...
to his Lordship,
Bishop Michael Quinn.
This is a special day.
A day when we can welcome back
an old friend,
a man who has traveled as
much as, if not more than,
Saint Paul himself.
So without further adieu,
would you please welcome...
Father Joseph Venice.
Thank you, Father Cathal.
Good morning every one.
-Good morning, Father.
-Bishop.
It's good to be back.
And it was worth the four hour
delay in Rome...
just to hear myself
compared to Saint Paul.
For the past two years
I've been working with a...
United Nations committee.
We visited some of the
world's poorest countries,
countries which we in the west
have described as
developing, or even
underdeveloped.
But...
If I'm honest.
And I hope you think I am,
then I have to tell you that
the moral sophistication...
that I encountered in some
of these countries...
makes us in the west seem
shamefully underdeveloped.
-Welcome.
-Thank you, sorry I'm late.
My talk's about morality.
-Good subject.
-I think so.
And in particular,
how morality,
how Christian morality
fits into an increasingly...
skeptical world in which
morality is in decline.
You have to leave.
Why?
Don't touch me!
Please forgive the interruption
ladies and gentlemen.
If you'd like to wait
in my office Daniel,
we'll deal with this later.
Deal with what exactly?
This is not the time
or the place.
Please father, conti nue.
What better a time
or place, Father...
than when we're discussing
morality?
This is unfair to
Father Joseph, Daniel.
-He's come a long way.
-Let the boy talk, Emil.
Don't make it worse.
Get off me!
I've a right to be here...
just as much as anyone else,
I've done nothing wrong!
He deserves to have his say.
Get off me!
Let's hear what you
have to say Daniel.
Stay here.
Father Cathal has thrown me
out of the seminary...
because a priest, that priest
made an assumption about...
-my relationship with another student...
-That's not true!
...who was also kicked out not far
from ordination, and that too is wrong.
Not for you to say what's
right or wrong here,
that's my responsibility.
It's a collective responsibility,
we weren't consulted.
Look, you overreacted.
Don't you tell me what
I did or didn't do.
What are you going to do now?
Dismiss me for a second time
in front of all of these people?
Get your house in order.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Sometimes I can't see
the point in going on.
Come on Jack,
we all go through this.
The dark night of the soul and all that.
It's a test of our faith.
It's not my faith in God I'm losing,
it's the organization.
The hypocrisy... the hierarchy,
the double standards.
It took courage to do
what you did today.
Thanks, but I don't think
it's done me any good.
It will in the long run.
Daniel, I think you
should talk again...
to that journalist
that you mentioned.
Let him print your story.
You are the new generation
of the priesthood.
You have a voice,
let it be heard.
Jack, what's the matter.
I was the one who spoke to
Foley about Frank's death.
Told him what I knew.
You do have freedom of
speech here in Ireland,
as far as I know.
I lied to Father Cathal,
told him I hadn't.
Three our fathers and
two bloody mary's.
Daniel,
what do you say?
She's going to get you,
she's going to get you,
she's going to get you!
Oh... she got you!
You must be Francis.
David Foley.
-Good to meet you.
-You too.
This is my wife, Liz and
this is my daughter, Martha.
Hello.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Uh, is this a good time?
-Yes.
-No.
-I want some ice cream.
-Come on then let's go.
-We're going home David.
-Oh, come on Liz.
Liz!
Terribly sorry about that.
Thanks for meeting me
at such short notice.
No problem.
I really liked your article.
It's very sad.
I'm so sorry.
You were good friends with
Frank Sweeney then, yeah?
Yeah, we trained together in
the Irish College in Rome.
You know there's a
rumor going around...
that Frank was having an affair
with somebody high up in Rome.
Do you know
anything about it?
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah, because I was
Frank's partner.
You?
Yeah, it started out
just before we left Rome.
Does anybody else
know about this?
Wel I... they know everything,
but no, not officially.
Except for Jack Dowling.
Would you be prepared to talk
about this on the record?
# In my hands, you might see... #
# something special
that he gave to me. #
# In my hand, yeah... #
They're nothing but a
bunch of queers anyway.
God forgive you Marie,
don't say that about those holy men.
Oh, where have you been!
They're men aren't they,
they're all the same.
Yup!
-If you can't pop the pink pop the prune.
-Whoa!
That's disgusting!
-So are they.
-That's not true.
You're better off
out of it Daniel.
All that freakin
studying ain't worth it.
-It's my life Marie.
-Not anymore it isn't.
Let's get more drink.
-Daniel?
-Pint.
I'll have a whiskey.
-Hi.
Fancy seeing you here.
I'm sorry I haven't been in contact.
I thought it was best.
I know,
it's good to see you.
You too.
I heard about the seminary,
what's going to happen?
Don't know.
You going back?
I don't know.
I hear you're
out of the fortress, Daniel.
For the time being,
yeah, who told you?
Small town, it was probably
that whore in McGlynn.
-What you having, Sean?
-Whiskey.
-Are you buying Marie?
-Not for you turtle.
Ah, what's that
supposed to mean.
Away and fuck yourself.
He couldn't if he wanted to
from what I've heard.
No prick.
Aye, sure, you two'd know all
about pricks, wouldn't you?
What the fuck
d'you mean by that!
You've had more between you
than a second hand dartboard.
Fuck off home to your wife and
small one, you fucking shite!
Look who's talking...
the new tailbike.
You fuckin' bastard!
-You fucker!
-No!
Stop it, please.
We have to go, come on! Jesus, God!
Cock.
I reckon it's all
to do with cock.
If you've got a big
one you're okay.
If not you're fucked.
Are we from the
same family, huh?
What do you think Sinead?
-About what?
-Cock.
Only joking, father.
No, I mean about this place.
Do you ever think
about getting out?
Oh, I like it here.
It's my home.
I know every one.
That's the problem, every bastard
knows every other bastard.
Yeah, but this is where
I'd like to settle down.
With our Daniel?
Maybe.
Good on you girl.
You two should go away
and get married,
set up your own parish,
and I guarantee...
all the young people from around her
would start going to mass again.
Come on Marie, let's go.
I think these two want
to be on their own.
Good luck.
See ya.
# Blue mountain river,
if only for a while. #
# Take me to the river,
I lay down by your side. #
# The world is full of madness
and I find it hard to smile. #
# I'll sleep with you through winter
and wait for summertime. #
# Blue mountain river,
comfort me awhile. #
# I'll follow down the river.
I'll follow you tonight. #
# I listen to your whispers.
You dance and turn tonight. #
# We'll stay awake together,
watching silver in the sky. #
# Blue mountain river,
I wan t to rest awhile. #
# Your changing my reflection,
and the seasons in my mind. #
# And these days go on forever.
I'll need my own time. #
# Take me where you're goin,
and I'll be right by your side. #
Let me just put this here.
How long were you
and Frank together?
About five years.
The church knew
he was HIV positive?
-Yes.
-When did they find out?
They found out about
three years ago.
Around the time of
the Vatican incident.
Yes, that's what
promoted us to go.
We went there to a special
general council meeting.
We were supposed
to be discussing...
the church's viewpoint
on HIV and AIDS.
Frank and I felt that
some good might come of it.
It was total whitewash, they were
skirting around the whole main issue,
that priests are dying of AIDS...
and that it's being
ignored by the council.
By the third day I was so bored
that I decided not to go,
but Frank went anyway
and he'd gotten so angry
and frustrated that he stood up
with a banner saying
"the church has AIDS".
I bet that didn't
go down too well.
No, the heavies moved in
and he was whisked away.
The church has AIDS!
I'm living with HIV and I have
no voice in this conference!
He was strip searched
and questioned...
He could have been a terrorist,
they said.
Eventually after checking
they believed who he was...
and he was bundled out of the
building into a waiting car...
and then to the airport.
The church's response to that whole
incident was the final straw.
That's when I left
the priesthood.
I don't remember seeing
anything about it?
If the Vatican doesn't want you
to know about something, you won't.
You sure you want to
go public with this?
Yes.
I don't want Frank's death
to be in vain.
A sympathetic photographer
sent Frank this,
I thought
it might beuseful.
Jesus.
There's no point in me going
to Bishop Queeny or Cathal.
So he'll just dump you like that?
Yeah.
Even if nothing happened?
Anything remotely to do
with sex is taboo,
and they know it goes on but
as long as it's out of sight...
they turn a blind eye.
So what you're saying here is that
the common threat is celibacy.
-Or lack of it.
-Yeah.
Well you're celibate
aren't you?
-At least they got one.
-Yeah.
From the moment I joined
the seminary...
...until last night.
Welcome to the
human race Daniel.
I have nothing to say.
I have things to say
worth hearing.
Far too much...
Christian fucks!
Something's not right here.
I'm pulling over.
They've stopped.
Fuck this!
Daniel!
Jim!
Davey...
we need to talk.
What's the problem?
This is very
difficult for me.
What is?
I don't want this next article
on the Catholic Church.
-What?
-No more, okay?
Cut the shite Jim,
what the fuck's going on?
I don't want to do this, Davey.
I was like you
when you started out.
I know exactly how you feel,
but this thing,
it's... it's too big for us.
It's out of my hands.
What the fuck you talking about,
out of your hands?
Since when has anything
been out of your hands!
You're the fucking editor!
Since today,
it's from on high.
From who, God?
Oh, screw that!
More powerful than God.
But it's your paper Jim,
you say what goes in it!
Not anymore, Davey.
Hang on a minute, we're
a local paper aren't we?
Aren't we!
We report things that are
relevant to the local people...
and they don't know
what's going on.
And you don't either!
-You have no real evidence!
-But I'm finding it Jim!
This is a story of the
church's hypocrisy!
The world is full of hypocrisy!
Yes it is! And it's
up to journalists...
like me and you to point it out!
Look, you've got to drop it
and that's final.
You're serious aren't you?
You've had a visitor.
What the fuck have they
got on you Jim, eh?
Just drop it okay?
No!
No way!
Absolutely no way!
You're not publishing it
in this paper...
and that's all there is to it,
so fuck off!
Shame on you Jim.
Shame on you.
I can't print it.
Trust me on this one Meg,
it's good.
And more importantly,
it's true.
Oh, and Foley gets
the credit, okay?
It's his story.
It's me and you Lucy.
Good night.
Frank sent this
to my office in Rome...
with a note asking me to give it
to you the next time I saw you.
I thought it was a
bit odd at the time.
Oh God!
I'm so sorry Matthew.
I knew there had to be a note.
Did you ever know
about any of this?
No.
Poor Frank, must
have been torture.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
It's hard to know what
God's will is when...
...when things like this happen.
The goodness of God and
the business of suffering,
it's the eternal question, we may
never know the answer to it.
Sometimes we
prefer to blame God...
for the pain of our human condition,
but he didn't kill Frank.
God's will, will be
revealed to us in time.
That's why we need faith.
Yes, thanks.
The young priest who killed himself
and Daniel being thrown out...
is all part and
parcel of the same thing.
It says here... it's
all a cover up.
Credit it, huh?
Ah, you can't believe
everything you read.
If it's written in here
there must be some truth in it now.
Your mother will be upset,
hey Mary?
-...when she sees this.
-What?
The newspaper article,
you've not seen it yet?
All this talk about
priests up to no good,
even in the Vatican itself.
And Cardinals, close to his
holiness with this... HIV thing.
What sort of devil talk
is that anyway!
Your poor mommy will be
beside herself, Mary.
What do you say, huh?
Go fuck yourself!
O'Brien's finished.
He assured me
it would not be published.
Then how the hell did
The Irish Times get hold of it!
I don't know.
Come.
Sorry.
Things are moving quickly,
they want you to appear on
television tomorrow afternoon...
on a live debate about celibacy.
That might not be
such a good idea.
I don't think we have a choice,
we have to respond.
No doubt Foley
will be there.
We need to give them an answer.
Let me think about it.
What about this young
McLaughlin boy.
He was a good student.
We may have to reinstate him.
It might take the
wind out of things,
especially on
live television.
I'm not so sure, that would
really give the press...
something to write about.
I don't want anything
more from Foley.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
Do we know the boy's family?
Well Carl does, he's on the
European Grant Selection Committee...
and knows his father.
See what can be done there.
I want to know who at the
Irish Times gave the go ahead...
for this to be published.
I want everything
that we have on Foley...
and everything that we don't have.
The same on the
McLaughlin family.
We will deal with this fiasco
once and for all.
And I want it done properly
before Rome gets involved.
Get Cathal and
Dowling in here now.
The fuckin' Irish Times!
The whole town's
talkin' about it.
Well so fuckin' what!
If they've nothing better to do!
Marie!
You watch your language
young girl in this house.
And you calm down,
calm down everybody.
Well who cares what
people say anyway?
-I do!
-We do!
Me and your mother do.
Oh, that's right keep up
appearances for the neighbors,
never mind about
your son's life.
Don't you talk to me
about appearances.
Oh, you'd know about
all that would ya!
Just stay out of this Sean,
will ya!
Fuck off, why should I!
Now look, if Daniel
ends up going in...
If all Daniel wants to be
a fuckin' priest...
then no bastard should stop him!
Stop, Sean!
That's enough Sean!
Leave it.
What the fuck are you going
to do about it short ass?
Sit there and listen to
bollocks here...
worrying about what the
fucking neighbors think?
-Throw him out!
-You're not worth it, cunt!
I've had enough of this, that
fella's out of my house for good!
Worse than fuckin' children,
ya know that?
And you hangin' around with
Sinead again doesn't help either.
Dad you don't understand.
Daniel and Sinead are
meant to be together,
they always have been.
Jesus Christ!
I won't listen to the lies.
Don't! Don't dad,
please don't!
Liz, answer the bloody phone.
Hello.
Oh, hey, Daniel.
how you doing?
Yeah, I just got up.
The Irish Times, you're
fucking kidding me.
How the hell did they
get hold of that?
Yeah.
What's it say?
Yes, I'll call you back,
are you at home?
You're being transferred
to a parish in Barlindun,
we think it will be
better for you.
You mean it will be
It's a pity you did n't
think about this...
before talking to Foley
and his like.
I have a right to say
when things are wrong.
That is just your opinion.
There are plenty in the
church who do not want change.
And there are plenty who do.
You know you're lucky that
you're getting a parish.
I can serve God
wherever I am.
Time to leave Jack.
What you did to Noel Kinahan
and Daniel McLaughlin was wrong,
and what you did to
Frank Sweeney was contemptible.
The Catholic Church is
destroying itself from the inside.
Don't blame me, examine
your own conscience.
My conscience is clear.
I hope so Aman.
I do hope so.
He'll go straight to the press
just like Matthew Francis did.
No he won't, he's too weak.
What are we going to do
about this TV debate?
You and I will go.
As the local bishop I think I have
slightly more credibility...
than a second rate journalist.
We will let Foley
discredit himself.
He won't back down there.
We'll see.
That's fine for me, yeah,
yeah, I've got the details.
Listen, can I call you back?
It's just my other
phone is ringing.
Okay, yeah.
Talk to you then, bye.
Liz!
Hello?
Who is this?
Ah, for fuck's sake.
If you speak out on television
they'll never let you back in.
They won't let me
back in if I don't,
they've made that clear.
This is my last hope.
You never know, half the country
might petition the pope on we behalf.
I never thought
it would end like this.
It's not over yet, Ma.
Sinead's not helping.
Your father's right
about that one,
she is interfering
with your vocation.
I haven't got a vocation
at the moment,
at least not one
I can do anything about.
And anyway,
if I love a person,
why can't I have both?
Because that's
not Catholicism.
Have you thought
enough about this?
I have, I've thought
about it a lot.
And I've chosen God.
I obviously picked
the wrong one.
I don't mean that.
But I'm sure he wants me
to be happy...
and Sinead and I get on great.
I know that.
Do you know how many priests
are no longer priests...
because they fell in love?
Priests shouldn't be
falling in love.
They're human to o...
just like me.
You're right.
Wild horses wouldn't have stopped
your daddy and me getting married.
# He was born and
raised in Ireland. #
# In a place called Casamay. #
# He was his father's only son,
his mother's pride and joy. #
# And dearly did his parents love
that wild colonial boy. #
Good luck to you Mickey.
You too, John, you too,
and your family.
Don't talk to me about
fuckin' families.
They fucking well
bleed ya of everything.
No thanks for anything.
Fuck it!
What's all this I hear, John,
about your young fella Daniel?
He's not one of them
queer boys is he?
Jesus, no!
Bad rumors is all.
On my way home.
I'm sorry...
You didn't get
the grant thing, John.
-What?
-The Euro...
Lena McGlynn was saying
that tonight...
How the fuck does she know?
Sure she knows your father
before you know yourself.
Fuck!
Let them keep their shiny
Euros anyway, not worth a shite.
-I'll see at mass, Mickey.
-Good luck.
-Daniel.
-Bishop.
I'll get straight to the
point given we that are...
about to appear live
on national television.
What you are doing and what
you have said about the church...
that you have devoted
your life to... is wrong.
And so was my dismissal.
We had to dismiss you.
I had no choice.
You?
Under the circumstances
I have decided to...
consider your reinstatement,
if not at Saint Savior's then
at another seminary.
-What's the catch?
-There's no catch.
You admit that your behavior was
inappropriate and that you now realize...
that the seminary behaved correctly
under the circumstances...
and that way you can continue
to fulfill your calling.
There's more to it now.
-That shouldn't concern you.
-It should concern all of us.
Where the fuck
are my family!
I've got your family!
You touch them, I'll come
after you, I swear to God,
I don't care the fuck who
you are, I'll kill you!
I'll fuckin kill you!
We haven't touched
your family.
But see how easy it is
if we want to!
Who is this, for fuck's sake?!
Very carefully, I want you
to go into that studio...
and retract everything
you said in your article.
No, I won't do that!
Are you listening
to me Mr. Foley?
I'm a fuckin' journalist!
God's church
needs to survive,
there are forces of evil out there
that wish to see it destroyed.
Where would we be if we
didn't take a model stance, hmm?
That depends on
your viewpoint.
Fucker!
Are you listening
to me Mr. Foley?
Mr. Foley, come on
we're waiting for you,
we're live in three minutes
we need you in...
Give me a minute!
You're not listening Mr. Foley,
retract everything.
You touch them...
If you harm them in anyway
I will fuckin' kill you!
Come on Mr. Foley
we really have to hurry...
You fuck!
You know Daniel, it's a pity
that your father's Eurogrant...
was rejected because
I think that a quiet word...
to the committee would
help them to reconsider.
It would be a shame to bring
further hardship on your family.
-This way gentlemen please.
-Yes, just a moment please.
Think how proud your mother would be
on the day of your ordination.
Say hello to Lucy daddy.
It's important.
It's always
important with you,
what's more important
than your family?!
Stand by studio.
Applause in five seconds,
four, three...
Thank you, good afternoon...
welcome again to Afternoon Live
with yours truly, Gaye Burn.
Today on the show we are
debating the issue of...
celibacy in the
Catholic Church.
Let me in troduce to you our
panel of speakers...
in the show today.
On my left, we have David
Foley who is a journalist...
with the Galcranagh Gazette
and he's also the author...
of an article in yesterday's
Irish Times which is entitled,
"Celibacy, the C word,
can Catholicism survive?"
We're also joined
by Daniel McCloughlin,
who's recently been expelled
from Saint Savior's seminary in...
Oh, Daniel's got make up on,
the queer, look at him.
He's good looking
fucker though isn't he?
Shhh, quiet down
I can't hear.
We're joined by the
local Diocesan bishop,
his grace, Michael Quinn and
with him he has his Diocesan...
Communications Officer,
Monsignor Thomas.
What sort of bollocky name
is that, huh?
And we also have the outspoken
former Catholic priest,
Father Matthew Francis.
And I want to start
with you David Foley...
and your assertion in your article
that the Catholic Church and...
the priesthood will not see out
this century unless...
they remove celibacy as a
pre-requisite for the priesthood.
Umm, yeah, yeah, that's right.
I believe that the church may well
be in trouble if it doesn't...
at least deal with the possibility
of the celibacy issue.
Um, I um, um...
I, I'm not saying that
celibacy is wrong,
it's a choice
for the individual.
But you did say that
in your article, David.
Um, yeah, what I um, what I...
Well I'll quote you
from the article if I may,
you're talking about the recent
suicide of the gay priest...
Father Frank Sweeney
and you say, and I quote,
"That this incident only
serves to highlight...
the dilemma now facing
the wider church;
the question of celibacy".
Now that, I'd say
is pretty clear cut.
-Um...
-Bishop...
The more serious accusation
made in Mr. Foley's article...
is that priests, priests
that are close to the pope,
the Holy Father himself
are in relationships...
and of course this
is preposterous.
Preposterous David Foley.
You know I, um...
Come on Davey, what's wrong
with you!
Forget David Foley
go to Daniel!
Can I just go to Daniel
McLaughlin for a moment.
Sorry, father.
I'm sorry, look, excuse me,
I know you feel strongly...
about this topic and
thank you for joining in.
I will come back to David
Foley in a few moments,
but first of all, Daniel,
I want to clarify this poi nt.
This whole issue is not
about sexual orientation,
the church is in this
mess because it expects...
Catholic priests to live celibate lives
and that for many is a tall order.
Daniel, you knew that before
you went into the priesthood.
Yes.
And now you're faced
with a difficult choice.
I want both.
I want to be ordained
as a Catholic priest...
and I want to be married to
the girl I love.
You tell him!
Your grace, it really
prompts the question,
why can not this obviously
sincere and dedicated young man,
why can not he be
married and serve...
as a priest at the same time?
It goes against everything
that Christ stood for...
and would tear the
Catholic Church apart.
-Rubbish, rubbish, rubbish!
-Nonsense!
Monsignor, that really
isn't quite true is it?
Professor Martin O'Connor
of Trinity College,
would you outline briefly for us
the history of celibacy...
in the Catholic Church.
For many centuries after
the time of Christ...
priests were allowed
to get married...
and those priests
that did get married...
were leaving their wealth and
property to their families...
and the church wanted to
prevent them from doing this.
So in the 12th century
they brought in celibacy.
You see the church was
losing too much and...
it wanted to build its wealth
and extend it's empire.
Greed!
Bishop, has more to do
with wealth and power?
It is also about God and
that unique relationship...
with Him... that comes
about through celibacy.
Are you celibate, Bishop?
Bravo, wheww!
-Sit down?! Down!
-Quiet!
I think this is an inappropriate forum
in which to discuss one's private life.
Just a moment...
Not when we're discussing
the life and death of others.
Excuse me, I'll answer
the question if I may.
Please, just a moment.
Most people I know who serve God
are celibate, Daniel.
The deep spiritual
relationship that results...
from such a union
sustains our need.
You didn't answer
my question Bishop.
Are you celibate?
Answer the question!
Do you practice
what you preach!
How dare you!
No, how dare you, Quinn!
This is a note that was
left to me by my partner.
Father Frank Sweeney,
before he took his own life.
If I may, may I
read the note Gaye?
I think you had better
Matthew, yes.
Matthew, Bishop Michael Quinn
and I had an affair...
when we were in Rome together.
...this nonsense, I am leaving.
What do I do with this?
Somebody please take this...
...return to Ireland and
he threatened to rid me...
of my parish unless
I continued to see him!
Get out of my way!
Serves the cunts right for
not giving us the grant, huh!
I don't have the moral courage
to do...
what you have done and
I am unable to tell you.
I am so sorry.
This is the only way out
left to me.
You're too good a man
to hurt like this...
but I can't live with myself
a day longer.
I pray that we will be together
one day in the loving arms...
of the God we both serve.
My love always...
Frank.
-I love you so much.
-I love you too Sinead.
# You say you want
a diamond on a ring of gold. #
your story to remain untold. #
# But all the promises that we made,
from the cradle to the grave. #
# When all I want is you. #
# You say you'll give me
a highway with no one on it. #
# Treasure to still look upon it.
All the riches in the night. #
# You say you'll give me eyes
of the moon of blindness. #
# A river in a time of dryness.
A harbor in the tempest. #
# But all the promises that we made,
from the cradle to the grave. #
# When all I want is you. #
# You say you want
your love to work out right. #
# To last with me through the night.
# You say you want,
diamonds on a ring of gold. #
# Your story to remain untold
and your love not to grow cold. #
# But all the promises that we made,
from the cradle to the grave. #
# When all I want is you. #
# All I want in
the world is you. #
the world is you... #
Subripped by Andante
-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-