Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(owl hoots, bird wings flutter)
(gas hissing)
Kids, I've put your dinner
on the stove.
Okay, Mom.
Don't forget
to lock up, Chloe.
I won't.
Bye, Mom.
D.J.: This is 2SW, rocking you
through the '80s,
with Split Enz,
"I Got You."
(music begins)
Freddie, you getting tired?
Just don't get any fleas
on the bed, okay?
(music continues)
# Sometimes we shout #
# But that's no problem #
# I don't know why sometimes
I get frightened #
# You can see my eyes,
and tell #
# That I'm not lying #
# Look at you #
Mom, are you there?
Tell me, Freddie,
why do little brothers like
to freak out their sisters?
You asleep already?
Well, you're just gonna
have to move
because I need
my pillow.
(screaming)
(telephone rings)
(rings)
- Hello?
- Man: Now you die.
(knock on door)
(knock)
Help! Help!
Someone help me!
(knocking continues)
(glass shatters)
Girl: No!
Stay away from me.
I mean it,
stay away from me!
I'll call
the police!
I mean it, you touch me
and you're gone.
Stay away from me!
Woman: Cut!
Cut it.
You idiot!
I told you not to go
for the throat straight away,
you've got to rip
her blouse off first!
Like in rehearsals.
Remember?
I forgot.
Hey, everyone,
Robert De Niro here forgot,
once again.
We're going
to call it a night.
You can thank
our genius Thespian here
for your three hours
overtime.
Fucking weasel.
- What's her problem?
- You, you dumb dickhead.
Touch my tits one more time, I'll
kick your balls in, understand?
Lossman?
Lossman,
where's my Coke?
I want my Coke
in my hand,
with ice, the second
she calls "wrap" okay?
(knock on door)
Yeah?
It's you.
What do you want?
You made me look
stupid tonight,
in front of all
my friends.
No, I didn't, sweetheart.
You did that
all by yourself.
And I'll let you in
on a little secret:
you don't have
any friends.
The fact is,
you're replaceable
in that mask.
I could put a monkey
in that suit,
and it would do
a better job.
Anyway,
I've had enough.
I'm gonna speak with Jim,
and he can sort it out.
What do you mean?
I mean my producer
will speak with your agent
about discontinuing
your services.
Do you understand
that?
Oh...
nice touch.
For the first time,
you actually frightened me.
mine is making intelligent
family drama.
Yours is doing cheesy clown acts
in shopping malls.
I'm sorry, but you just can't
cut it in features.
Man: Hilary, look.
Get out of here.
Take one step closer,
I'll scream.
It's hard to scream...
without a tongue.
(Hilary screaming)
Just put those
in the car,
I've got to go talk
to "Mein Fuehrer."
(knocking)
Hilary?
It's Vanessa.
Oh, my God!
What do you want?
Sex?
Do you mean you want
to have sex with me?
Sex?
Yeah, sure.
Well, okay,
let's go.
You're going to have to take
that silly mask off.
Vanessa...?
(buzzing)
So, to answer your
question, Raffy,
that's why I don't include
the slasher genre
in my course. Fair enough?
So, Mr. Lossman,
what happened to the film?
"Hot Blooded"?
It was never finished.
There's a cut work print
in the archive, I believe.
- Would it be possible to see it?
- For what purpose, Raffy?
We have to do
a graduation film, right?
What better project than
to finish that film?
It could also make
a shitload of money.
Are the rights
available?
Hester, full marks for your
entrepreneurial spirit,
- but I don't think so.
- Why not?
That movie was a nightmare. You
don't go playing with nightmares.
I'll see you all
next week.
- Should've killed Lossman, eh?
- Yeah.
Mr. Lossman, we were serious
about the movie.
So was I, Raffy.
Look, you two have more
important things to say.
Don't waste your time
doing trash.
Raffy: But it's not
trash.
A horror film
can be just as political
as "Priscilla"
or "The Piano."
Even if it's not,
what's wrong with making
a scary film, giving people
a bit of a fright?
A few years back,
a director--
a young kid out
of video clips-- did just that.
The producer hired him
to complete "Hot Blooded."
It was the first time the print
had been screened
since the murder
of Hilary Jacobs.
What happened next
is totally bizarre.
The kid was butchered,
but the police
never found the killer.
The creepy thing is,
the projectionist was the only one
with access to the screening room.
And he was cleared.
You're saying there's some sort
of curse on this film?
I'm saying this is something
best left alone.
- Thought is deed.
- What do you mean?
You read Eastern
philosophy,
the ancients say that
what you think, you create.
"Hot Blooded" was a loathsome
piece of shit
that never should've been made
in the first place.
So what's the story
with the producer?
He tried to finish
the film
so that he could save
his investment.
One night while he was
in the editing room,
he was electrocuted.
Raffy: It was an accident.
Accidents happen.
Look,
I'm not superstitious,
and I don't believe in curses
or what-have-you.
Listen, you kids
have a gift.
Don't waste
your combined talents
on this ugly
piece of shit.
So what do
you think?
I think it'd be cool.
Let's do it.
Yeah!
(modem crackling)
I can get the rights
for next to nothing.
I just spoke
to the producer's wife--
or should I say
his widow.
Get this, she said
she's prepared
to put in some money
to see it finished.
What's the story
with casting?
The girl
who played the sister,
her name's Vanessa Turnbill
and she lives in L.A.,
and she's done
a couple of B-grade movies,
she's doing a daytime soap
at the moment, so,
I think we can
get her.
I can market that.
Um, hi.
What about all these people
who keep, sort of, dying
trying to make
this film?
Are you gonna market that,
do you think, Miss Producer?
Probably.
Yeah?
That's promising.
So, who's in?
Who wants to make
a mainstream slasher movie?
Bigger than "Halloween."
Creepier than
"Friday the 13th."
More blood and guts
than "Texas Chainsaw Massacre."
More sex
than "Deep Throat."
You're so bad.
It's time we graduated
into pop culture, boys and girls.
So what say you?
Who's in?
- Yes.
- What the hell?
Yep.
Yes.
It's a lousy deal.
Unbelievably lousy,
- but I see some merit in it.
- What kind of merit?
I done some checking.
Word around town is they're
the next big thing,
particularly the director,
this kid called Raffy.
They say she's the next
Jane Campion.
Listen, this could be the next hit
at Sundance, this kind of movie.
Look what "Scream" did
for Courtney Cox.
Give me a break.
She was a millionaire already.
I just don't know
if I can do it, Jerry.
It's gonna dredge up
all kinds of old shit.
Besides, there's a celebrity golf
tournament in Las Vegas next week.
Nessie, baby, I'll be able
to work the bejesus out of this.
Are you kidding me?
"Slasher movie gone horribly
wrong, buried for years.
Vanessa Turnbill goes back
to face her demons."
You can't buy publicity
like this.
E!, Entertainment Tonight,
Access Hollywood--
they'll go crazy.
Sweetheart, I don't want to be
reading the trades one morning,
see this movie grossing $100 mil
and you are not a part of it.
Do you and me a favor,
fly coach to Australia.
Oh! Hey!
Coach!?
(horn honking)
(car stereo blasting)
Hi.
Vanessa?
I'm Raffy,
I'm the director.
This is Hester.
She's the producer.
Sorry we're late.
We ran out of petrol.
I'll help you
with these.
We've got a press conference
in an hour.
Would you like
to freshen up?
Am I booked into a hotel,
or sleeping at your house?
Miss Turnbill, why have you
come back to finish the movie?
It's extremely rare that you find
really good parts for women.
When I find one
I just jump at the chance.
Miss Turnbill, Holly Jones,
reporting live, Channel 5,
are you worried
about the curse?
What curse?
Every time there's an attempt
to finish this film, someone dies.
Oh, there's a special clause
in my contract.
If I die,
I get paid extra.
Aren't you concerned that it will
bring back bad memories,
Miss Turnbill,
doing this film?
All of that happened a long time ago.
I've put all that behind me.
It's wonderful
to be back in Australia.
Anyway, I would have killed
these two if they'd left me out.
I only just arrived,
so if you'll excuse me?
Thank you very much.
That will be all.
I've got to get some sleep.
Can you take me to the hotel?
Your room won't be ready till 2:00.
They're still cleaning.
You want a coffee?
Raffy: Her husband must have
done well out of slasher films.
I'll be frank with you.
The only reason
I'm doing this,
is because I need
the money.
My late husband and I have
a first dollar gross position,
which means nothing
unless the film is finished
and on-sold.
Hopefully this will be
my little nest egg.
- Sign that.
- What is it?
It's an indemnity.
From now on,
I'm not responsible
for anything that happens.
It's on your heads.
It's called
"blood money," girls.
Blood money.
- Hi, Bobby.
- Oh, hi.
You doing this movie?
Oh, yeah. The production
for "Mad Max 4"
got pushed back a few weeks,
so I got a window.
Cool.
Let's meet up later,
and go over the make-up.
Yeah, sure.
Isn't this where that guy
got murdered?
You know,
watching this same print?
What guy?
Hey, guys,
got a second?
You remember
a couple days ago,
we were talking about
the possibility...
Jesus Christ, has somebody
been smoking in here?
I heard she always gets off
with her co-star.
What about when she did
that TV remake of "Lassie"?
(laughs)
Haven't you ever heard
of secondhand smoke?
Hi, I'm Bobby Doog.
I'm your co-star.
I'm playing Scarman,
psycho-killer guy.
Good casting.
(group snickering)
Hello? Hi.
"Hot Blooded"?
Oh, daddy.
Not these cans again.
I thought they'd been destroyed.
You Raffy Carruthers?
- Yeah.
- Loved your short.
Bloody brilliant.
Except that last shot
was straight out
of "Shock Corridor,"
you derivative
little thing, you.
I've written a screenplay.
You want to read it?
- You seen this?
- Yeah, screened it once.
Best thing the director
ever did.
Bit of a hack,
she was, you know.
Or should I say she was
a bit "hacked."
Last time I screened this,
a kid sat out in the front,
got his throat slit
by some psycho cleaner.
It's a funny thing, I seen
so many murders on the screen,
you see the real thing,
hey, it's no big deal.
You get these
gender specific assholes
that think that
screen violence
is going to turn us all
into mass murderers.
Well, it's crap.
I've seen hundreds of murders.
I've seen thousands of murders.
Next time somebody
goes into McDonald's,
shoots up 20 people
with a Uzi
and they find a Steven Seagal
video in his back pocket,
you know what they ought to do?
Ring "60 Minutes," and get them
to do one of their checkbook
bullshit journalism stories on me,
because I'm a walking
advertisement
for liberalizing
X-rated everything.
You know what I mean?
Art is art, eh?
Okay, everyone,
let the horror begin.
(laughs menacingly)
- Shut up, Rick.
- What?
Kids, I've put your dinner
on the stove.
Okay, Mom.
Don't forget
to lock up, Chloe.
Freddie.
(cat meows)
(hissing)
What's wrong?
I thought
I heard something.
You asleep already?
Well, you're just going
to have to move--
Augh!
(telephone rings)
Hello?
Now you die!
Stay away from me!
Hilary: Cut! Cut!
Cut!
That was her voice.
Did you hear
her voice?
Hes?
Hes, wake up.
(screaming)
Oh, God!
Bobby...
that's enough.
It's cruel.
(laughter)
- Bobby: Did I pass the audition?
- With flying colors, sir.
I did the make-up.
Not bad for a quickie
in the dark, eh, Raff?
That's your specialty, isn't it?
Quickies in the dark?
- You're a retard, Paulie.
- I didn't buy into it, Raff.
You're all a bunch
of fuck wits.
Come on,
bus leaves at 7:00 a.m. sharp.
Check your gear, please.
- Paulie: I didn't mean to do it.
- Fuck off, Paulie. Grow up.
Bobby: Don't think I went
too far, do you?
Hello?
Hello...?
Our star isn't traveling
with us, then?
- Vanessa?
- Yeah.
- No, we sprung for a driver.
- Of course.
- Has anyone seen Raff?
- Everyone off the bus!
How are we supposed
to make this film
without our famous director?
Maybe Damien could take over,
like he did in the short.
Shut up, Paulie,
that's bullshit and you know it.
We were there. You're not talking
to the cinema papers now.
(Paulie laughs)
Raff, I'm sorry.
We're all sorry.
It was meant to be a joke.
Did you pick up
the print?
Yeah, it's in back.
Raffy: Guess we broke
the curse, huh?
We screened it without anyone
getting killed.
Yeah, I guess.
You've done well,
Nessie.
But I knew you would.
And I always knew
you'd end up teaching.
(chuckling)
Hey, you got any Diet Coke
in here?
Thank you.
Number 6.
This is the place.
What place?
Where Cassie and I are finally
going to consummate
our blossoming
relationship.
(laughs loudly)
Aw, in your wet dreams,
buddy.
She's got her eye
on Damien.
Yeah, but Damien's
got a thing for Raffy.
Hand off it, now.
Raffy's got the hots for Bobby.
No way! Bobby's got a thing
for Jules.
Jules is porking Jim.
Jules and Jim, are you serious?
I thought Jim was porking Hester.
Hester's a dyke,
you dork.
Plus she's got the hots
for Raffy.
What about Raffy
and Bobby?
Well, Raffy and Bobby
is unrequited, so far.
But Raffy has shown
an interest in... moi.
- You?
- Yeah.
Was she shitfaced?
One of these days you're going
to implode with envy,
you poor, pathetic,
little creature.
Hey, I can't help that
I'm endowed
like that guy out
of "Boogie Nights."
What, with a fake dick?
They're got
to be kidding.
It's only
for a few days.
This bed's got bugs in it.
I can tell by looking at it.
If I spend one night on this thing,
I'm gonna need a masseuse.
I did a course
in reiki.
Reiki?
No shit?
Rick: So this is the house
of horrors.
Man: Watch your feet!
I don't want mud
everywhere.
Are you going to put
something down?
I don't want a herd of elephants
tramping dirt through here.
Yes, Mr. Drivett,
we'll be really careful,
I'll make sure they treat it
like it was my own house.
That's no comfort to me.
You look like you'd live in a dump.
Hey, hey!
Put that down, son,
that's bone china!
From China.
Really?
I thought it was from bone.
Now, the rules
are these:
no drugs,
no loud music,
no eating or drinking
in the house.
I've disconnected
the phone,
so you can't make
any personal calls.
Can I ask
one small favor?
Well, you can
certainly ask.
We have the original print
of the film in the bus outside.
I was wondering if we could put it
in a safe place inside the house?
Certainly,
young lady.
You can keep it upstairs
in my bedroom.
It'll be safe there.
Now you,
come with me.
I want to talk
about the location fees.
Rick: I want to check out
the kitchen, too.
We've got some shots
in there. Oi!
- Rick!
- Cassie!
(smashing)
Cassie!
You've deboned the china.
You're a moron,
Rick.
I hate you.
Somehow, I doubt that.
Rick, next time you do
something like that,
you two
can go home.
- Promise?
- Yes.
I didn't do it.
Where the hell is our
expensive import?
Oh, great, no signal.
Bad luck, huh?
Raffy: That must have been
where she was murdered.
Hester: Who?
Hilary Jacobs,
the director.
They said it was
a Swiss chalet.
It always sounded
so weird.
Who said?
Can't use your phone, huh?
How will you cope?
Okay, everybody,
can I just have a few seconds
of your time, please?
Okay everyone, come on.
Shh-shh.
Okay, the back story
goes something like this:
when they were kids,
their parents went out
left them on their own,
and the house caught on fire.
Now, Charlie got horribly burned
and scarred for life,
but his beautiful sister,
Chloe, got out unscathed.
Now he hates her
for that,
and he hates his mom and dad
for doing this to him.
His dad is the first to go,
he went in reel two.
Then an assorted range
of victims,
until we get
to reel nine,
which is where the film stopped
as he kills his sister.
Now, the scenes
we're about to film
are where the mother
gets killed,
who will be played
by Vanessa.
And this is the climax
of the film,
so I don't need to tell you
how important it is.
Now, does anybody
have any questions?
Do they sell any tofu
around here?
(sniffs)
Scare you?
Hurt you?
(groaning)
Julie: Are you ready,
Bobby?
Okay.
If you grab the front part
of that,
just get that on.
Great.
How does that feel?
Can you breathe? Yup.
Just make sure that's
fine there in the collar.
Bobby: Stupid.
You all right,
Bobby?
Here, let's get this
fixed up.
I'll just pop the collar
underneath there.
Bobby: All right!
"Now you die."
Bobby, you--!
Why don't you practice
your method bullshit
on someone else, mate?
Dickhead!
Just go back to your Winnebago
and act like a tree.
Must be the un-scariest villain
I've ever seen.
Bloody actors with some
spare time on their hands.
What's he doing
watching me piss, anyway?
Wouldn't he prefer
a Polaroid?
Dickhead.
(engine revving)
Raffy: Vanessa, keep your foot
off the brake.
Don't accelerate
too much.
Slower, Jimmy, slower.
Take your timing from the car.
It changes every take,
'cause the bimbo can't drive.
Nobody told me I had to drive
a goddamn car!
And the steering wheel's
on the wrong side.
It really affected you,
didn't it?
The killing?
Yes, it did.
You know...
horror movies aren't that bad,
Mr. Lossman.
You think about it,
they can be cathartic
for young kids.
I mean...
it's all about letting go
of your fear.
How do you mean?
Well, you go to the movies
and there's a psycho killer
out in the bush,
woodchipping people,
suddenly, the things
you're scared of
don't seem so important
anymore--
like the craters on your face,
the size of your ass,
or will that cute guy
ask you out.
That sort of stuff.
Horror movies put that
into perspective.
When you think
about it like that,
they've actually got kind
of a social value.
- I'm in character.
- Bobby!
Excuse me.
- Raffy: Cut it! Cut it!
- Vanessa: I need a stunt driver.
Detective:
What have you got?
Time of death,
28 hours ago, plus or minus.
Deceased was part-time, single,
no one noticed him missing.
Weapon appears to be
a single blade,
about 30 c's,
very sharp.
He was disemboweled,
like it was some sort
of ritual slaying.
Ta.
So who was last
in the theater?
A group of film school
students,
made a booking,
came in last night.
I need a stunt driver.
Vanessa, you read the script,
you knew you had to drive.
Every movie I've ever done,
I've always had a stunt driver.
Vanessa: Do you think
I'm Sly Stallone, Jackie Chan?
I don't do my own stunts.
Where's Lossman?
Paulie...
Paulie, please. Wait.
Cass, come on.
Paul, no, not here.
I've gotta get back.
And so do you.
I told Rick I had to go
back to town,
get some extra
batteries.
I told Hes
you were feeling sick,
had to go back
and have a lie down.
You bastard.
So we've got
all night.
- Cass: Bobby...?
- Bobby? Come on.
Oh, my God!
- Paulie!
- You want it.
Cassie?
No!
Bobby!
Shit!
Oh, shit!
Who are you?
Bobby?
Bobby, is that you?
Get away from me!
What do you want of me?
What do you want?
Cut it.
Let's call it
a night,
everyone's tired,
we can pick up tomorrow.
Yup.
You gonna ask me to ride
a goddamn horse tomorrow?
- No, tomorrow you die.
- Oh, I can hardly wait.
Julie: Vanessa, can I grab
a couple Polaroids--
Fuck off!
Oh.
We're missing
three.
Cassie went back
sick.
So did my asshole
of a boomie.
Funny about that.
Yeah.
Where's Bobby?
Where have you been
all night?
Just doing
the method.
Yeah, meaning scaring
the shit out of people.
I'm still wet,
by the way.
What?
Oh, you fake sincerity
so well.
It's the secret
of good acting, mate.
- Duh.
- Duh!
Happy with what
you got?
Yeah, it was
all right.
Damien's great.
How was our star?
Well, she can play
hysterical really well.
Do you want to have
a drink tonight, before bed?
Thanks Hes,
but I'm pretty tired.
Yeah, I understand.
Shit.
Hello?
Is someone there?
Oh--!
What are you
doing here?
Sorry, I thought you might want
some company.
You still
get nightmares?
Uh-huh. And you?
Oh, yeah.
My therapy bill at the end
of each month is huge.
Sometimes I wake up in the middle
of the night screaming.
I used to take uppers
for years
to keep from going
to sleep.
And I still can't walk
into a building late at night
without getting
the shakes.
- How about you?
- Same.
I remember your face,
looking at me.
I'll never forget that.
Flying in coach for 14 hours
makes you think.
Why did I do this?
Why did I come back?
I don't know.
I guess I just needed
to face it,
once and for all.
I'm scared.
- Scared of what?
- Those scenes tomorrow.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
I'll be there.
I don't get it, Raff,
this film.
You could've done what you wanted.
Lossman thinks you're God.
Yeah, but I wanted to do
this film.
You think it's gonna set you up
as a commercial director?
Is that it?
No, it's not.
It's more personal than that.
What's personal
about a horror movie?
I've just gotta
finish this film.
Hester Ryan?
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm Senior Detective
Ian Hollander,
from Special Crimes
Squad
and this is
Detective Carter.
Can we have a word,
please?
Sure.
So did you notice anything
unusual at the theater?
Did you notice anyone strange,
hanging around the set at all?
No.
Anything unusual
that you can think of?
No one, nothing out
of the ordinary.
Raffy: I suppose you've heard
about this curse?
Miss, we know that seven years
ago, an Angelo...
- Zabriki.
- Zabriki,
was killed in that same theater,
watching the same film,
and we're investigating
the possibility
that there's a connection
between the two.
But at the moment,
we're investigating
as if they are
separate incidents.
You see, we don't think
the projectionist
was killed by a curse,
Miss Carruthers.
We believe he was killed
by one or more
very sick individuals
who are quite capable
of being apprehended
by police officers
such as ourselves.
Do you have any idea
why someone
would want to stop this film
from being made?
Beats me.
Well, if you can
think of anything,
give us a call.
And if you could give us
the details
of where you're filming,
that would be of help.
Sure.
- (knock on door)
- Yeah?
- Can I come in?
- Sure.
You okay?
I don't know.
I don't know
what's happening.
Look, someone
got murdered,
and it's awful
and tragic, but,
it has nothing
to do with us,
or what we're
doing here.
You believe that?
I don't know what
to believe.
What I'm worried about now
is the others.
I don't think
we should tell anyone.
I don't want Rick
getting spooked,
pulling a number,
stopping the shoot.
What do you think?
I think Paulie and Cassie
didn't come home last night.
Rick checked their beds
and they haven't been slept in.
What?
Do you think there's
a connection?
I don't know, but it's
a little bit creepy.
You know those two.
They probably got shitfaced,
bonked all night,
and fell asleep in one
of the old sheds.
Raff, this isn't life
imitating art.
The projectionist
got murdered;
the fact is,
he was a wacko.
I don't believe there's some
cracked killer out there,
stalking us like
we were in the plot
from "Bride of Chucky 7,"
or whatever.
Life doesn't work
like that.
If Cass and Paulie
don't turn up by crew call,
I'll call the cops,
okay?
Okay.
You are brilliant,
and you're going to make
a brilliant movie.
We've just got to keep it
all on the rails.
Mr. Drivett?
We're back.
(dog barks)
Mr. Drivett,
is it all right if we set up
in the living room?
Hes, have you got
a minute?
What's wrong?
So this is only one
we've got, yeah?
Jules, can you tell Hes
what the problem is, please?
Cassie put all of Scarman's
wardrobe here.
All the doubles, including
the masks, but they're gone.
Do you know
what happened to them?
Do you think
I nicked them?
I'll ask around.
Thanks.
There are no doubles
of your wardrobe,
so don't make a mess tonight,
all right?
Killing's a messy business.
Okay, Bobby.
Jim: We need to patch in
a few more lights
through those windows.
Any more, we're going
to melt the circuits.
The wiring in this place
is ancient.
Any chance of scoring
a generator?
We can't phone out
from here, can we?
No.
Okay.
I'll take the bus,
see if I can't find
a friendly farmer.
Damien: Thanks, man.
Jim: I'm heading off, man.
You'd better hop out.
Bobby,
don't give me this character
motivation bullshit.
Get your ass of this bus.
I've gotta get moving.
Hey!
Some of us have got
work to do.
Bobby, man,
you're a loser.
Get out of here.
Oh, my God.
When you come
into the living room,
you're not going to see
Scarman
standing behind the column
with his shears up.
Where's Bobby?
I dressed him
about an hour ago.
- Was he any good?
- Cretin.
Look, what we'll do is
we'll dolly into a two shot
and then we just push in
to a close up of Vanessa.
Close up?
Bobby.
Got your shears?
All right, move over
next to the wall here,
and you can hide behind here
and wait for her to come.
Okay, we'll do a line up
on that shot
if you go back to first positions.
Thanks, Vanessa.
Going for a rehearsal.
Okay, and action.
Ow! Hey!
Get off!
What the fuck are you doing?
This is a rehearsal, not a take.
If we move in that fast,
I need lubricant for the track.
You'd have some left over
from last night,
wouldn't you, sweet cheeks?
Hey, come on, guys!
Hey, break it up!
One more line like that
and you can really go home.
Sounds lovely.
Should we just set up
for a take?
Do something about the mask.
It doesn't look right.
How tight is this close up?
Are we talking crow's feet?
(dials cellular phone)
(distant whine)
Hello, police?
Damn it!
(dialing)
(screaming)
(breathing heavily)
Hester: No!
(whirring)
Keep away from me!
(screaming)
(Hester screams)
Hester: No!
Is Jim back yet? I asked him
to go get a generator.
Maybe he's found a place
that sells tofu.
How the hell am I supposed
to make a film
when my entire crew
go walkabout?
You guys keep at it,
and I'll go find him.
Jim?
(Raffy screams)
Sorry, I didn't mean
to frighten you.
That's all right.
I'm a bit on edge, that's all.
I wanted to you ask you something,
away from everyone else.
Yeah?
Why this movie?
I told you already.
It wouldn't have something to do
with your mother, would it?
- My mother?
- Hilary Jacobs?
She was your mother, right?
Yeah, she was.
That's why you want
to finish the film?
Everybody thought that she
was a hack director,
but she wasn't, Mr. Lossman.
She was so much more than that.
You can tell by looking
at this film.
She was not a hack,
believe me.
She had to be smarter
and tougher than all of them.
And she was.
My God!
They've been slashed.
Who would do something
like this?
Kids, maybe, locals.
I don't know.
My car, too.
You don't think...
that this could be...
What?
Nah, don't worry about it.
By the way,
have you been Hes?
(heavy breathing)
Jesus Christ!
Rick--!
You had me going there
for a sec, man.
You're going to put me
out of a job, bro'.
Bobby: I've got
one of those, too.
Face off,
Wes Craven style.
(gasping)
Julie: I'll show you
how to shimmy.
That's great.
Okay, let's go for a take.
Can I get the cast in?
- Yeah, sure.
- Ta.
Okay, Bobby, time to do
some killing.
Come on.
Okay, Bobby, these are the shears
you're going to be using.
They're a special effects number,
so, as you can see.
When you kill her, I want you
to stab her in the stomach,
and bring it up
into her rib cage.
Hey, Vanessa?
Okay, like this:
in and up.
That didn't hurt?
So you can do it
quite hard.
All right?
You grope me,
you're history.
Raffy: Any questions?
Then, we'll go for a take.
Jules, do you want
to do final checks?
You all right
with that, Rick? Damien?
(car horn honks)
Okay,
when you're ready, Jules.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, yeah.
Right.
And,
roll sound.
Speed.
Mark it.
- 11, take one.
- Hold the roll.
(car horn honks)
Who the hell is that?
I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
(car horn honks)
Marta: The police have been
to see me.
You must stop.
You must stop at once.
What's wrong?
What's happened?
The evil is back.
Oh, I knew
this would happen.
Okay, stand by to shoot.
Roll sound.
Speed.
- Mark it.
- 11, take one.
And-- action.
Ow, cut.
Can we cut?
Cut it.
What's the problem?
This lash that's come loose.
They're gonna see it in the close up.
And that's too hard.
Can we back off?
Julie, can you fix Vanessa's
false eyelash for her?
- Yeah, yeah, sure.
- As quick as possible.
Thanks, and we'll go
for another one.
Where is the original print
of the film?
I don't know.
It's upstairs, I think. Why?
Mr. Lossman,
there is a force
at work here.
It is not human,
and it is unspeakably evil.
You must destroy
that film at once,
or you will all die.
Okay, roll sound.
Speed.
Mark it.
Julie: 11, take two.
And-- action.
Cut it, cut it!
Run! Get away from him!
Bobby, what the hell
are you doing?
That's not Bobby!
Come on!
Come on, quick!
Where's Damien?
Auuugh!
- Where's the old lady?
- She's there!
Rick: Just leave her!
Come on, let's go!
She's got the keys,
you idiot!
Wait here.
Vanessa, where are
you going?
Get in the car!
I've killed him once,
I can kill him again.
Raffy: Augh! Damien!
You know, Jules, I've never
said this before, but,
I've always found you
very attractive.
Oh, fuck off!
Okay.
Did you see where he went?
(stairs creak)
(distant scream)
(dog barks)
We need weapons.
Damn it...
I knew I should have
brought my handgun.
(radio static)
- Julie: What?
- He was just here.
- Where?
- Just here!
What do you mean?
Julie: Open the doors.
(scratch of metal)
Rick: What's he doing?
It's petrol.
Oh, my God, he's going
to burn us alive.
- Should we run for it?
- I can't move.
Rick, what do you think,
should we run for it?
Get help, Jules.
I can't move!
- I can't do it, Rick!
- Help!
Julie: No!
No!
(Julie screaming)
No! No!
Let's get
the son of a bitch!
(all scream)
Raffy, I'm sorry.
Don't go in there!
(gasping)
Vanessa: Mr. Drivett.
Lossman: She found the body.
I think she's had a stroke.
I've been trying
to revive her.
Is she still alive?
(dog barks)
Vanessa: Not any more.
Come on, let's go.
- What are you doing?
- Why the film?
This sounds really weird,
but it sort of makes sense.
Marta believed
that we created the killer.
How?
He's the character
in the film.
The only way to destroy him
is to destroy the film.
- He's not even human?
- I don't think so.
He's the sum total
of all the creative energy
that's gone into the film.
There was no creative energy
that went into that piece of shit.
I've got the keys, come on.
(outcries)
You all right?
Yeah.
Let's burn these bastards.
Mr. Lossman, behind you!
Raffy: Oh, my God.
Hey, ugly!
It's me you want, isn't it?
I'm the one that killed you.
You're disgusting.
You make me want
to vomit.
Come on, Mr. Movie Star,
do you want to kill me?
Huh?
Come on...
let's go!
Well, this must be
the place.
(banging)
You stay away from me.
Oh, shit.
Is that the girl?
It sure is.
BK 35 to Central.
Come in Central.
Scarman: Arrgh!
Hey, girlie!
Get away from there.
Leave me alone!
Hey, hey, hey!
No, don't! Please!
Arrgh!
You take care of her.
I'll go check inside.
Calm down.
No, you don't understand,
it's evil!
Auuugh!
Hold it right there!
I said,
hold it right there!
I said--
(yelling)
Don't move.
I've done nothing
wrong, officer.
I'm just a simple shopkeeper
from Crompton,
here on holidays
with my family.
Get in the car.
Everything's all right.
You don't understand!
Put down the knife.
It's not a knife.
It's only a pair of garden shears,
simply modified so I can do
interesting things, like,
cut off heads.
Just drop it!
(guttural laugh)
Oh, shit!
The magic of movies.
Don't move.
- Please, please.
- Stay calm.
Stay calm,
I'll be back soon.
Don't you just hate that?
I don't know who you are,
but you better let go
of me right now.
Or else what?
You'll lock me up?
(yelping)
I'm something special, huh?
Let me out!
Scoot.
(sighing)
Now, where were we?
No!
No...!
(screaming)
No! No!
No, no, don't!
Please, don't!
Yeah!
Die, you bastard!
(screaming)
Die!
Come on, what's wrong?
You a bit tired, huh?
Not feeling so good, eh?
Come on!
You're finished, you B-grade
piece of shit.
(wailing)
Hey...
(raspy voiced)
It's down here.
Did you see that?
- Hey, Vanessa, how are you?
- Hi, Vanessa.
- Hi, hi.
- You're looking much better.
Oh, thanks.
- Ow, ow.
- Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
So you're sure he's dead?
He only existed
within the context
of the film.
When that was destroyed,
so was he.
Thank God.
Maybe now I can sleep
at night.
Woman: We are so lucky today.
We're lucky because
we're here to see
the most exciting screening
of a very rare film.
You may have read about it
in the newspapers,
because there was
this so-called
"curse" on the film.
And that was that
every time anybody tried
to complete the film,
someone died.
In any case, this print
is the only print in existence,
and we are really lucky
to be able to see it today.
All right,
nothing more to say.
Here we go,
let's roll it.
(applause)
# I sense inside #
# The need to wrest #
# Those gripping claws #
# within my chest #
# A bad desire #
# Slipping in #
# I pray at night #
# Forgive my sin #
# No wonder I can't sleep
at night #
# No wonder I can't
sleep at night #
# No wonder I can't sleep
at night #
# No wonder I can't
sleep at night #
# I hold my head #
# I'm heading down #
# Toward the dark #
# Beneath the ground #
# I feel the presence #
# Of the dead #
# They come to life #
# Inside of me #
# No wonder I can't sleep
at night #
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org