Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[trucks caravanning]
[chopping wood]
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[chopping wood]
Colonel Azimut 340.
Enemy tank spotted.
Affirmative.
It's a NATO tank.
Yes, Colonel.
I confirm.
Destroy it.
Stop the tank.
[chopping wood]
[explosion]
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[goat neighing]
And your wife?
Well...
I write to her.
- When I can.
- That's great.
[explosion]
[gunfire]
[machine gunfire]
[chopping wood]
[car crushing]
Stan!
Stop!
Ilona!
[classical music]
♪ ♪
Ilona!
[suspenseful violin music]
♪ ♪
What do you want?
Pretty face.
Nice body.
The description
was accurate.
You should be
thanking me, Grandpa.
I'm going to help your
little birdie fly the coop.
So, would you like us to
obliterate your lifelong
roommates, or do you promise
to come along quietly?
I swear...
you're going to
pay for this.
[grunting]
Well, well!
The shepherd has guts...
But you can skip
the heroics.
We're just here to give
your sister a crack at
life beyond sheep
farming, hm?
You win a trip to a
very pretty villa.
[groaning]
[yelling]
And get rid of that for me!
Anna...
Why the hell are
we taking her brother?
Didn't we say
no witnesses?
It's called
playing it by ear.
And besides, I want to
make sure our little
country girl is
going to play nice.
I don't like it.
So, do you want her to
cower in a corner waiting
to get whacked like that
crybaby from Grozny,
or do you want her to
put up a bit of a fight?
Anyway...
If she doesn't go
along with the game...
Okay, okay.
But your souvenir stud
better not bust my balls.
I like it when
you act jealous.
[yelling]
[gunshot]
No!
[screaming]
[intense classical music]
♪ ♪
[typing]
Is this gonna make a
fucking great teaser!
In order to avoid any
unpleasant surprises,
I want to receive everything
live and in real-time on
my computer.
I can then issue any order
in a timely fashion should
the need arises.
Of course.
You understood? Go on!
Perfect.
The window just showed up.
I hope this new young
woman will prove more
combative than
her predecessor.
Don't you worry, sir.
We've made absolutely
certain she'll cooperate
every step of the way.
Her brother is going to
help us make sure of that.
She won't refuse to jump
through any hoops,
I guarantee it!
So much the better.
I know a number of people
who would be only too
happy to take your place.
We won't let
you down, sir.
We've designed everything
so that the operation will
be a rousing success.
I hope so, for your sake.
We have a festive
gathering with a few
friends, planned for
tomorrow evening.
And we'll be extremely
disappointed if we're
unable to enjoy a private
premiere of the film.
Yeah. Our technicians will
be working around the clock
to get you a version
before 5 p.m.
Don't clean up the
images too much.
The most compelling thing
about these films is that
amateur look they have.
Send the teaser out over
the network and then go
get the girl.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Ilona?
Did they hurt you?
They killed him.
[thud]
So when do we
start hunting?
Don't get upset, honey.
We came a long way, and
I shelled out a fortune.
I didn't come this
way to play footsie!
Can't wait, huh?
[laughing]
You got a problem?
Not at all.
Why you getting
upset like that?
It's bad for your health.
Are you talking to me?
Yeah!
Hey.
Don't talk to my
brother that way.
Maybe you'd better
all calm down.
Maybe you should mind
your own business.
It's just for
your own good.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
I see you've had a chance
to get acquainted...
and you got dressed.
That's perfect!
Who's the prey?
You'll met her soon.
Look honey, I went
shopping for you.
[melancholic music]
♪ ♪
Something tells me...
You can choose
your weapons.
Happy hunting!
You refuse to participate,
we kill your brother.
You try to leave the grounds,
Got it?
Now beat it.
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[growling]
Igor.
Let's go out of here.
Don't be an idiot.
Look, this will be fun.
Go on, make your choice.
This just doesn't
feel right.
I have a bad, bad
feeling about it.
Hey, knock it off now.
I already paid 100,000 dollars
and they don't give refunds.
So don't fuck
things up this time!
It's a little hunting
trip, that's all.
Here.
Take this.
You know...
handsome guys with sad
expressions make me
tingle all over.
I think we're gonna get
along fine in the end.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to eat you.
At least not right away.
[scoffs]
[typing]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
And let the
hunting game begin!
Anna.
Give them the
modus operandi.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the prey is in the forest.
Let the hunt begin.
I saw cameras.
Is it gonna be filmed?
Yes.
They're linked to our
video production facility.
Once the film is edited,
it will be distributed on
the dark web.
Allo?
What?
The dark web?
The Dark Web.
The invisible part
of the iceberg.
Five hundred times larger than
the visible part of Internet.
500 times more
interesting, too.
It's full of fascinating
sites where you can buy
weapons, fake ID's and
all sorts of drugs.
But you'll also find
very interesting sites
dedicated to porn,
pedophiles, or catering to
deviant genres and
that's where we come in.
My great snuff movies
are eagerly awaited by
millions of people
only too happy to pay
handsomely to watch them.
Let's try to be cool
to my expectations.
But can we kill
her as we want?
Excellent question.
No, of course not.
Whatever you do, when you
find her, don't finish her
off right away.
First you must bring her
to a place we like to call
the sacrificial clearing.
I love it.
It's a clearing to the
north of a domain,
designed for executions.
We've seen to it that
there are cameras everywhere.
There's no business like
show business, huh?
Exactly.
It's our business to show
the proceedings so,
in addition to the cameras
you'll be wearing,
we've hidden others
throughout the forest.
Whatever happens,
we'll be recording it.
Happy hunting.
No matter where you go,
we'll follow, my dear.
If only you knew how long
it took us to install all
those cameras.
[beeping]
[animal noises]
Oh.
You mustn't get
so emotional!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[heavy breathing]
Hey!
Don't lose her.
There's no chance
of that, boss.
[grunts]
Yeah.
That's the way I like it.
[birds chirping]
Where is this fucking coke?
Can't you knock that
off for five minutes?
Oh, gimme a break!
You know this
keeps me in shape.
[suspenseful music]
Now that you mention it, I don't
think it's helping much at all.
I don't think you have
to give me advice, okay?
I just want to find that
girl, and then get the
hell out of here
as fast as we can.
If you've got another way
to make a pile of money,
be my guest.
Sounds like
you're blaming me!
I'm not blaming
you for anything.
If only the bank hadn't
cut us off cold.
That's not my fault!
You weren't there!
I had to settle
everything!
- Calm down! Calm down!
- It's not you who shot that guy!
Who the fuck gives a shit
who screwed up first?
It's too late now.
We win this thing,
and collect the cash.
Ok, yeah, ok.
- We're the best! Yeah!
- We are the best, yes.
- We are the best.
- Yeah.
Can you let me
shoot that girl?
Yeah, of course.
Come on, bro.
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[water streaming]
Oh, and of course there's
no cell service here.
Just have to use
it as a mirror.
[laughs]
Really?
Wow, bravo!
You're at the height of
your maturity right now.
Baby, why do these things take
place in the suckiest locations?
Okay? Nicer places.
God, it smells.
It smells.
It is really hot out here,
and look at my shoes, honey!
My shoes are
getting scuffed.
Baby, can we do this in
the Maldives next time?
Ok, Bora Bora!
What about Fiji?
Fiji?
Please.
[classical music]
♪ ♪
Igor.
I'm begging you!
We gotta get out of here!
Now we're here and we're
doing it, all right?
But she's just
some poor girl!
We cannot kill somebody
like this, are we?
Hey, I didn't notice you
getting all upset when you
asked me to whack
your father.
That was different.
He was a total scumbag.
Yeah, sure.
All these people
are way different.
Something's just
wrong about them.
For fuck's sake!
Whenever I'm having a
little fun, you manage to
be a total buzzkill!
Ah!
Now you shut up,
and do what I say!
Got it?
[thud]
Looks like this may be over
with faster than we thought!
Oh.
[door opens]
You let me down.
I'd thought you would
have broken free by now.
I guess you're not really
all that strong after all.
You really should see
your face, it's so funny!
[laughs]
Hey look...
Here is a good movie, and
something tells me you
will recognize
the lead actress.
Our little country girl
is really in great shape!
That's a plus for
her, and for us.
It will make things that
much more suspenseful.
Huh?
Oh!
[grunting]
Ok!
Bitch!
Ok, I'll be on my way.
You may be a bit too hot-headed
for my taste, after all.
Hm?
[heavy breathing]
Scumbag!
[yelling]
They picked up her
trail way too fast.
I sure hope that bitch doesn't
get caught right away.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[spraying perfume]
Oh, I hope we find her
soon because I do not like
leaving the cat
at home alone.
What do we have here?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Hey, I need to talk to you.
Please help me!
What I love about poor people
is that you just don't get it!
Do you?
The idea of good and
evil is just so archaic.
Anyway, I want to thank
you for getting me out of
here all the sooner.
You're completely insane!
All right.
This requires a machete.
What the fuck
is she doing?
This bitch is gonna
ruin everything!
Honey!
I need the machete.
[grunting]
Whoa!
What the hell was that?
She was going to kill you.
I didn't have a choice!
Don't worry.
I'm going to get
you out of here.
What gives with
all the whispering?
Trust me, and
don't say a word.
Timur, step away from
the prey right now!
We can't see a thing.
[heavy breathing]
Starting now you
follow the rules.
Don't you dare kill
the prey right away.
You have to proceed to
the sacrificial clearing!
Timur, do you copy?
Calm down.
I've got an idea.
Wait, wait!
Dear contestants,
this is...
This is to let you know that
Timur has found the prey.
Shit!
But, don't worry, we've
decided to extend your
pleasure by giving
you a second chance.
You've still got a crack
at nabbing her before she
reaches the
sacrificial clearing.
And here's a clue
to get you started.
At the moment they're to the
northeast of the domain.
Latitude 42.1153149
Longitude 45.860759
We're gonna find them.
Happy hunting!
And we're back
in business!
Mag-fucking-nificent!
Move faster!
What is it?
My brother!
I can't just leave
him back there.
They'll kill him.
We'll go get him.
But they can't
suspect a thing.
Ok?
You must be a little
bummed out, huh?
You sister already
got herself caught.
So...
Now, what do
we do with you?
I know you're
going to kill me.
So cut the crap.
Ok?
[laughs]
So testy and ungrateful
right off the bat.
I propose we talk
about the future, hm?
What are you
talking about?
Stop and think
two minutes.
What's your life
been until now?
Diddling sheep?
And that brings in
how much in a year?
40,000 roubles? Less?
I don't understand what
you're talking about.
Our little business clears
three million a year.
And our customer base
just keeps on growing.
We are in hiring mode.
You've done time
in the army, right?
I need men like you.
And I imagine you know the
terrain around here pretty well.
That's a certain
number of advantages.
And I haven't even mentioned
what's in it for you.
You and your boyfriend...
I swear.
I'm gonna kill you.
Seems to me you're
really on edge.
I think you need to relax.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
I guess the property isn't
all that big after all.
Hey, asshole. Do you have
to stick so close?
You afraid you're
gonna get lost?
Shut up and listen.
Timur has already found the girl
and, he's gonna get the dough.
So what are we gonna do?
Sing love songs?
What's your point?
He's saying that maybe
we should work together.
And share the cash?
Any other bright ideas?
It's clear that Timur
knows his way around.
Are you sure you can swipe the
girl from him all by yourself?
Because it looks like you're
pretty much on your own, buddy.
Listen, he is right.
- Alright.
- Yeah.
Ok, let's team up then.
The four of us.
[grunting]
Let him go!
Drop it or I'll kill him.
Seriously, you really think
that's going to stop me?
Sorry, honey, but you
don't count all that much!
Ok, ok.
Calm down. Look...
I'm dropping it.
Brotherly love is such
a beautiful thing.
Grab some rope
from my bag.
I was kidding.
What did you think?
I wasn't gonna
let him kill you.
Now, get the rope
and tie him up.
Quick!
Sorry, but I
don't share money.
I'll track you
down, count on that.
It'd make more
sense to kill me.
Don't tempt me!
Now have fun!
This excites
you, huh, bitch!
[yells]
Let's move out!
You can expect company.
I hear there are
wolves out there.
Not bad.
Not a bad move at all!
Come on, Anna!
What are you up
to with that guy?
Nothing, thanks.
What's gotten into you?
I know exactly what it means
when you're like this.
Don't be jealous.
We've got a job to finish that
will bring in a small fortune.
Ok?
Just let's just
focus on that.
Is it true what he said?
Are there wolves out here?
Beats me, but we're not
gonna wait around until
nightfall to find out.
[animal noises]
I can't take another step.
I'm dying of thirst.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[heavy breathing]
Timur!
[grunting]
Take care of her!
[yells]
[groaning]
Things are heating up!
This is going really well!
This is gonna be one
hell of a film, huh?
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you're
still brooding.
Take your hands off!
You smell the farmer!
Why the hell are we
keeping him alive seeing
as how his sister's
been caught?
We don't need him anymore!
You never know
what might come up.
So, for the
time being...
Ok! You don't want to do it...
I get it!
I will take care of it.
And you take care of
what's happening in here,
because you're the only
one who knows what to do.
I'll handle the rest.
Bogdan!
Ok.
But then handle it!
I love it when you
give me orders.
You should try
it more often.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Igor!
Are you ok?
Why are you
such a fuck-up?
You couldn't
just kill her?
Come on, we have to
catch up to them!
Asshole.
Stop!
C'mon, faster!
[screams]
Whatever you do, don't move!
She's mine!
[grunting]
[groaning]
Are you tired, Superman?
I'm going to take care of
your fucking Lois Lane,
and I'll be right back.
[grunts]
It will be fun, you and I.
Sorry guys, I don't have
the patience to take her
all the way to
the clearing.
I'm gonna slice up the
turkey right here.
No way!
That's a negative!
There are rules and
you'll stick to them!!
[screaming]
What is the
meaning of this?
Bogdan? Anna?
Rules are as clear as they
can be, and I will not
stand for them
being broken.
Without rules matters
devolve into anarchy!
See that the contestants
toe the line immediately!
[yelling]
Igor!
Igor, come help me!
[yells]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[yelling]
[heavy breathing]
Igor!
[groaning]
Get out of here!
On your own you may stand
a chance by the river!
Beat it, I said!
[groaning]
I'm going to kill you all!
Wow! This is the best
film we've ever made!
A regular super
production!
Nice aim, but
wrong target.
Doesn't matter.
They went that way.
I can see fresh
blood on the ground!
People are gonna be lining up
in cyberspace to buy this one!
Wouldn't you agree this
calls for champagne?
You have to be able
to think clearly.
It's not over
until it's over.
I guess so.
Now, no more surprises.
We've had our dose
of improvisation.
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[panting]
[water streaming]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where do you think
you're going?
Hey, Anna!
Anna!
Am I supposed to do
everything myself?
Over there.
This must be the
famous clearing.
Let's try to find them.
We'll kill them, and
collect the money.
Yeah!
I gotta admit
that part rocks!
You, on the other hand,
are really starting to get
on my nerves!
I don't like this place.
Nothing good
can happen here.
It's normal.
It's a clearing
for sacrifices.
If we kill the chick,
we are totally exposed.
I don't like
the look of it.
You're just
scared aren't you?
You're a chicken!
[laughs]
C'mon!
Don't be a dick.
Come back here!
What's your instruction?
Make her turn back.
Nobody, but nobody
gets out, understood?
And if she insists?
Then shoot her.
Her or anybody who comes
your way, we can't take
any chances.
Nobody passes,
no exceptions.
Shoot!
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
Bastards!
[crying]
That's more
like it, sweetheart.
[gunfire]
C'mon, brother!
C'mon!
Go!
Come on, bro!
Come here, bro!
Come on!
Bro!
You should give the
wide open spaces a try.
C'mon!
Chicken!
[thud]
[chanting music]
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[grunting]
[yelling]
[thud]
[chanting music]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[thud]
Uh, you got a preference
for this scene?
Yeah, ah, hmm, hold on...
I'll find out
what comes next!
Anna!
Hey, Anna!
Ok. Use the mine.
Finish him off
with the Claymore!
What's your boyfriend
gonna think of this?
I don't always
ask him to think.
But he's not going to
know a thing about this.
Bitch.
You okay?
I'm okay.
Son of a bitch!
Well, it's payback time.
They want us
to blow him up.
Grab the Claymore out of
his bag and go ahead.
[spits]
What's going on?
I don't know.
Go check.
This mine has to explode
for fuck's sake!
What the fuck did you do?
You're sure you
pulled the pin out?
Oh gee, you're right!
Silly me!
How stupid do
you think I am?
What a moron!
This is nonsense!
Where are we at?
We're at the part
where these brain-dead
muscle-bound meatheads
need an instruction manual
to operate a fucking mine!
Fuck!
A mine?
Yeah.
They decided to kill
him with a mine?
Yeah!
Seeing as you were
occupied elsewhere, I had
to make a few unexpected
moves of my own!
Fuck!
Ok, don't move,
I got this!
Hey, watch your step.
Don't worry.
[laughing]
Hey bro!
There's something
wrong with your mine!
C'mon bro!
[explosion]
Alex!
Alexander!
[chanting music]
♪ ♪
I'll keep your scalp
as a souvenir.
[arrow whizzing]
What is this clusterfuck?
Um...
I think the prey just
shot our gym rat in the
shoulder with an arrow.
I am not an idiot!
I am not blind!
Who's left at this point?
Well...
Um...
Timur!
But, let's say he's
been in better shape.
Show me the pictures
you have taken!
Timur!
[groaning]
He can't fuck up.
He has to stay
on top of this.
Fuck!
This film was gonna pay
for our retirement!
But before that can happen,
that bitch needs to die!
She's a tough cookie
like her brother.
Did you let him have it?
That's my call where
and when, got that?
Suppose miss perfect
knocks out the last hunter
and shows up here with her
long bow, and a machete.
What's your game plan, then?
Run up and give
her a kiss?
Don't let me down.
No way, Sir!
[grunts]
[chanting music]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[thud]
Yeah!
Now that's a final round!
This is off the
charts nuts.
Go ahead, Timur.
It's all yours.
Wow us with a big finish.
It's over now.
Go ahead, Timur!
What are you waiting for?
Why are you doing this?
I just saved your life.
You're just putting
on an act, right?
In order to go
save my brother.
Your brother?
He'll be the first
one to get it!
Then I will slaughter
every last one of them.
Nice and slow.
I'll really put my
skills to good use.
And I'll save
you for dessert.
Bogdan, can you tell me
what the hell's going on?
Beats me!
But you helped me.
You wanted to help me.
Who is this man?
How did you recruit him?
Like the others,
via the site.
And you did a background
check, right?
What kind of an idiot
do you take me for?
Look him up again!
Show me his photo!
Yeah.
Look, if this is your way
of getting revenge against
somebody, it's got
nothing to do with me.
Please, let us go.
Revenge?
Why would anybody need a
special reason to kill?
The concept's built-in.
It's everywhere
you look in nature.
Kill, or be killed.
Those other imbeciles
might've been doing it for
the money, but money isn't
my primary motivation.
You're out of your mind.
I wouldn't say that.
I just like a
job well done.
My motherfucking father
always said, when you
start something, make
sure you finish it.
[grunts]
So...
That's the real Timur!
What the fuck is going on?
Do a search with a photo
of our contestant!
Yeah.
Omar Borak.
Escaped from the penitentiary
in Moursk eight weeks ago.
Dangerous, and perverted.
Sought on over ten
counts of murder.
Ok, this raging psycho
must have killed the real
Timur in order to
take his place.
Take care of him.
Yeah.
It's time to wrap
up this stupid game!
You're sick!
Just like the others!
That's why you
killed your wife!
You know, Marina was a major
nutjob in her own right.
We met in the visiting
room at the prison.
Serial killers
turned her on.
But what a motor-mouth.
I couldn't get a
word in edgewise.
She's the one who
organized my escape,
and it was her idea for me
to take the place of that
millionaire looking for
extreme experiences.
I think I provided one.
I had a blast
eating his brain.
And what about you?
Do serial killers
turn you on?
[gasping]
[choking]
[gunshot]
[sobbing]
[heavy breathing]
[grunting]
Some serial killer.
You know...
I was beginning to think this
movie would never end...
But now, at last...
So darling, how would you
like me to finish her off?
Hey, Anna, you there?
Which weapon should I use?
[yelling]
Get the fuck out of here
before I change my mind.
And you, turn that
motherfucker off.
Get the fuck out of here!
If you want to see your
girlfriend alive,
make sure you bring my
sister in one piece.
Get up!
You hear me?
Get the fuck up!
[dramatic choir music]
♪ ♪
Keep going!
[dramatic choir music]
♪ ♪
Keep going!
[dramatic choir music]
♪ ♪
Keep going!
Go on!
We're going to make this
exchange nice and easy.
Shoot, Bogdan!
Shoot!
[gunfire]
- You shot me!
- Anna!
[gunfire]
No!
[gun clicking]
[crying]
[heavy breathing]
[water streaming]
[gunshot]
Hey!
Hey, don't shoot!
It's me, Bogdan!
He's still
headed this way.
What do we do, Chief?
Kill him.
[gunshot]
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[thud]
[classical music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org