Download Torrents anonymously
Hide your IP with VPN
visit !! hide-ip.notlong.com !!
[ Chukles ]
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Once is a mistake.
Twice is...
Stupid?
But if we keep things private
and don't let...
...This thing interfere
with our work...
Easy enough.
I mean, how could this
possibly interfere with work?
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, what the hell.
I'm in if you are.
Does that mean we're...
Yeah. I guess so.
Aren't you supposed
to get me a football
jacket or something?
How about a glock?
Our only shot is to be
honest with each other.
No secrets.
I agree.
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Beep ]
Hello?
Yeah, sure.
The boys upstairs
want us to get involved
in a murder investigation.
I hate homicides.
Jaimie: What a shame.
He's so young.
And a good-looking kid.
Good-looking watch.
Iwc.
Costs more than my car.
Tom curran. 24.
Law student at usc.
Loved poker. The problem is,
he wasn't very good.
He sucked.
According to homicide,
he lost 50 grand
in the three weeks
leading up to the murder.
About five months ago,
curran left the sunset Ridge
casino at 10:15 P.M.
[ Beep ]
An hour later,
l.A.P.D. Found his BMW
in macarthur park,
engine running,
covered with blood spatter --
his.
As for
the investigation itself,
homicide
didn't get too far.
No body, no witnesses,
and nobody's talking,
especially the sharpies
working at the sunset Ridge.
So what's
the theory here?
Curran was in debt,
got in over his head
with the wrong people
at the casino.
Got himself clipped.
Jaimie: Any leads?
Yeah.
This beauty right here.
Billy Hoffman.
Former talent Agent at ima.
What does he do now?
Casino concierge.
He caters to high rollers.
Homicide likes him
for the murder?
They think he's involved,
but he's not the triggerman.
He was working
the night of the murder.
What's the connection?
They talked six times on the
phone the day of the murder,
and then got into a nasty
argument that afternoon.
About what?
Don't know.
Hoffman lawyered up the second
the investigation began.
Dean: Okay.
Has he got any priors?
Yeah. Cocaine possession.
2006.
Carter: The only other
potential lead is curran's ex,
cocktail waitress
at the casino,
but she's not
really a suspect.
Airtight alibi.
So, what now?
Hope you guys like casinos.
Download Torrents anonymously
Hide your IP with VPN
visit !! hide-ip.notlong.com !!
[ indistinct conversations ]
Carter: Excuse me.
Do you know where we can find
Billy Hoffman?
I always wondered what happened
to failed Hollywood agents.
I worry more what happens
to failed FBI agents.
Just because
I don't like homicides
doesn't mean
I'm not good at 'em.
And you think setting up Hoffman
in a buy and a bust
is our best shot?
People tend to be
a little more talkative
with handcuffs on their wrists,
I noticed.
Billy Hoffman?
Well, that...
Depends who's asking.
Jerry silvano.
Looking for a private game?
Yeah, we, um...
We actually
don't really do...
Private.
Thousand a hand.
Change your mind?
Well, give me 10 minutes,
and you'll have a room
so private
you'll feel like
you're in the himalayas.
Have you ever been
to the himalayas?
Sorry to interrupt.
Uh, they need you
at the craps table.
Thank you.
What do you want,
a tip or something?
No, I was just...
Then get out of here
before I take your wife up
on her offer to pleasure me
in the bathroom. Please.
Did she really --
oh, you always take me
seriously, Steve.
Will you get outta here, please?
Get outta here.
Meet me in the v.I.P. Room
in 10 minutes.
Dealer:
Bets down, hands up!
[ Cheering ]
Eight. Came easy.
Point is eight.
That's what I'm saying.
Keep it coming, baby.
[ All talking at once ]
Eight the hard way!
Hard eight!
[ Cheering ]
All right. I know how you do.
I know how you do. Hey, listen.
If you need anything,
Billy h. Is here to help you.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm here to make your
decadent dreams come true.
So come get some.
[ Slaps ty's back ]
Mm! You know what I mean?
Take it. Take it.
[ Cheering ]
Dealer: Seven! Winner!
Winner is seven!
What the hell you doin'?
You're supposed to lose,
not win. Remember?
Sorry, man.
[ slaps Carter's shoulder ]
I apologize.
You know?
I'm trying to lose.
I just keep winning.
I can't lose!
I can't miss.
[ Chuckling ] Yeah.
Take a walk with me.
Curran didn't get whacked
because he was on a hot streak.
Trust me.
We need to find out
who lends money to losers,
not winners.
That curran's ex?
[ Cheering in distance ]
How you doin',
Mr. security guard?
Get yourself
a new shirt, huh?
Douchebag.
Come on, what are you
bitchin' about?
What's a hundred bucks?
Yeah. Yeah.
I just can't stand all these
wannabe high rollers, you know?
What's Jerry do
for a living?
Businessman.
Any particular
business?
I don't really get
into all that. [ chuckles ]
Oh, you see, that's the beauty
of being gorgeous.
You don't have to pay attention
to details.
[ Cellphone rings ]
Billy h.
Yeah.
[ Breathes deeply ]
Well, you know the guy
at the craps table?
Good-looking black dude?
Homie just went bust-o.
Lost 15 grand
in 10 minutes.
[ Exhales sharply ]
[ chuckles ]
I love this job.
Well, I'm sorry, Ray,
but you are definitely
maxed out.
What happened to the whole
"making my decadent dreams
come true" speech?
Well, I cater
to wealthy clients, Ray,
clients that can afford
to lose.
You know, actors,
directors...
Sex-tape celebutantes.
I make their decadent dreams
come true.
But, because I like you...
Ray, I'm gonna comp
your room,
and I'm gonna give you
a free continental breakfast.
I don't want
your damn muffins.
I want your damn money.
I'm happy to pay a premium
for it, too,
if you know what I mean.
I know a guy.
His name's Tim rowe.
He's not exactly a member
of the better business bureau.
So you better buckle
your chin strip, dawg,
because this dude
don't play.
Tell him Billy h.
Sent ya.
You looking for me?
Are you rowe?
Who wants to know?
Name's Ray, partner.
Billy h. Told me
you might be able
to help me out with
my current fiscal dilemma.
Who's this?
She's something else, huh?
This is, uh,
my beautiful lucky charm.
Well, now,
if she was your lucky charm,
you wouldn't be here right now,
would ya?
[ Jaimie and rowe chuckle ]
What do you say, baby, you go
put some money in the jukebox?
Sure.
Is that your girlfriend?
We just met today
at the pai gow table.
How much you lookin' for?
5,000.
I appreciate this, man.
What kind of juice
we talkin' here?
5 points a day.
Damn. A day?
This ain't
Wells Fargo, Ray.
We don't offer toaster ovens,
either.
It's 5 points a day
or it's no deal.
You know, nding to degenerate
gamblers like yourself
isn't exactly risk-free.
[ Dog barks, door opens ]
How ya doin', Joel?
I'm good. You?
I'd be better if you weren't
such a lyin' piece of crap.
I can get you the money.
Shut up!
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Joel breathing heavily ]
Look here, rowe.
I-I'll call you later, okay?
No, no, no.
Stick around, Ray.
Might be helpful
for you to see what happens
when people stiff me.
Which finger's
it gonna be, Joel?
Your call.
Please.
I can get you the money.
My wife has these diamond
earrings worth 3 grand -- easy.
You said that last time.
[ Whimpers ]
I'm outta here, Tim.
[ Whimpering ]
Jaimie, we gotta go.
Did you get the money?
Not yet.
Why?
[ Joel screaming ]
You let broke ??? Finger?
Well, what was I
supposed to do, huh?
Bust the man,
blow my whole cover?
Least we know he's legit.
And connected
to Hoffman.
Alex: Two for two.
Sounds promising.
So what's our next move?
Go back to rowe
and borrow the 5 grand.
Pay the vig,
keep your cover alive,
and see
what you can learn.
It's worth a shot, but it's
probably a waste of time.
We need a confession.
So, if we think
rowe is our guy,
we need to get closer.
Find out what he says
when he's sad, drunk, horny...
Any ideas?
Jaimie.
He thought
you were pretty.
I don't want to Chase that.
Let's do it.
I don't like playing
that flirty-chick card,
especially
with a murder suspect.
Makes me uncomfortable.
Well, it doesn't make me
uncomfortable.
If there's an opening,
let's exploit it.
I'm good with dysfunctional men.
Trust me.
[ Chuckling ] I'd be more
nervous if he was a surgeon.
[ Chuckles ]
All right.
Give it a shot.
In the meantime,
I'll continue to work Hoffman.
5 g's.
No excuses, no tears...
No bullshit.
First payment's
due tomorrow.
Where's your, uh...
Good-luck charm?
That bitch stole my gold watch
last night.
"He who walks with the wise
grows wise.
But a companion of fools
suffers harm."
Proverbs 13:20.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Don't...
Touch me, punk!
Kappa nu in the house!
Whoo!
Yo, bro, relax.
We don't grab asses here.
So you're gonna
go up to her,
and you're gonna apologize
to her.
And then you're gonna give her
one of those $100 chips.
I'm sorry...
For...Grabbing your ass.
Come on.
Let's go.
How ya doin'?
Hey.
50/50 split.
[ chuckles ]
He didn't grab my ass.
College boys.
If only they knew how stupid
they actually were.
Yeah, kind of like
gamblers, right?
Yeah, well,
for some people,
I don't think
it's much of a choice.
No. No, I don't believe
in any of that addiction crap.
Yeah, well,
I've seen it up close,
and it ain't pretty.
Hmm.
Relative?
Ex-boyfriend.
Ex? Huh.
Kicked him to the curb, huh?
He's dead.
Well, I -- sorry.
Is it a recent thing?
Five months ago.
He got killed.
They think so, anyway.
He was cheating on me.
How'd you find out?
I saw them together.
Here.
The day Tom disappeared.
They were hugging
and saying "I love you."
So I asked
what the hell was going on.
And he just said,
"it's personal."
♪ Watch around the corner ♪
♪ and watch around the bend ♪
♪ the one you least expect
will try to get inside... ♪
what can I do for ya?
That guy
I was with yesterday?
He says
you're into making deals.
Where'd you get it?
My father gave it to me.
♪ It's what iou're looking for ♪
there's a pawn shop
two blocks down
on the South side
of the street.
Hey. Psst.
What are you
doin' tonight?
[ Chuckles ]
Thanks for coming.
[ scoffs ]
What, are you kidding?
I'd miss my mother's funeral
to be here right now.
So what's up, cookie?
It's kind of personal.
Didn't I tell you
I was a Jewish priest?
Your secret's safe with me.
I can assure you.
[ Sighs ]
I just found out
Jerry has another girlfriend.
I really like
where this is heading.
I need cash.
I just lost interest.
Not from you.
Oh. I'm back.
I need to make some money
while Jerry and I
are still together.
I have a certain lifestyle
I need to maintain.
Yeah, I'm a little...
Confused.
I might need a partner.
A partner in what?
One of your coked-out tv stars
is playing Blackjack
with these.
Mm. And again,
it's the wrong color.
Okay. Um...
I'll call you later,
okay?
'Cause right now I gotta
go break someone's arm.
Just kidding.
I didn't peg you
as a believer.
Well, I like to read
the passages.
It's relaxing.
You make sure that watch
stays right where it is.
It's an iwc.
It's worth about 10 g's.
I'm no thief.
That's not what
your boy Ray says.
I lent that punk
500 bucks.
He never paid me back,
so I stole his watch.
[ Silverware clanking ]
In my book,
that ain't stealing.
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]
Hey.
L.A.P.D.
Lookin' for Tim rowe.
Come on. Don't embarrass
yourself, big guy.
I know rowe
owns this place.
I don't know where he is.
Well, when you
track him down,
tell him Detective broder,
l.A.P.D., was here.
Oh.
And tell him
I want to have a quick chat
about a kid
named Tom curran.
Who says homicide detectives
are a complete waste of time?
Dean's outside
rowe's apartment, right?
Jaimie will be fine.
That wasn't the question.
Yes. He's there.
Good.
Any progress
with Hoffman?
Put the worm on the hook.
But before he could bite,
he had to go spank
some drugged-out actor
for playing poker
with fake chips.
[ Cellphone beeping ]
Excuse me a second.
Okay?
Yeah? [ sighs ]
Make it quick, 'cause...
What?
When?
Well, what'd he say?
And what did you say?
Just keep your mouth shut.
Everything okay?
I have to go back to work
for a while.
Sure.
Rain check. Okay?
He was nervous as hell
when the bartender called.
Plus he has
the Vic's iwc watch.
He's our guy.
There's no doubt.
Well, it doesn't prove
he killed the kid.
Hell, that's not even enough
for a search warrant.
He's guilty, Carter.
I could see it in his eyes
and his demeanor.
We need a confession,
jaimie.
That's it. That's the only way
we're gonna make this case.
Dial up your cover.
For this punk to open up,
he needs to think you're
as big a loser as he is.
What about Alex?
She's okay with me
getting aggressive on this?
Yeah.
Yeah. She's cool.
All right.
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Dealer:
You have 15, sir.
25.
Busted.
Sorry, sir.
[ Sighs ]
Well, hey, it's just...
It's just money.
Right, baby?
Well, how much was that?
That is $5,000.
What?
So if we win,
we will hook us a suite
at the peninsula.
And if we lose?
The motel 6.
[ Sighs ]
I will stick.
Dealer:
Dealer has 15.
Dealer has...21.
Better luck next time.
[ sighs ]
What do you say, baby, we head
over to the motel 6 and...
I can't.
Sorry.
Billy: Mnh-mnh.
Sexy as hell.
Isn't she, Ray?
See, the problem is, Ray,
she's only allowed
to date winners.
There he is.
What are you
doin' here?
Uh, workin'.
You?
Eh, I snuck in a few hands
of Blackjack here and there.
Made a little lunch money.
Nice! [ chuckles ]
Good for you.
Hey, you book that 5k
into evidence yet?
Yep. Took care of that
this afternoon.
[ slaps Carter's shoulder ]
Good.
[ slaps ty's shoulder ]
What time
you meeting Hoffman?
11:00.
Oh. Good luck.
Yeah. It's tricky.
It's like he's part mama's boy,
part scumbag.
Yeah, in L.A.,
that's called being an Agent.
Almond milk.
Surprise.
I'm flattered.
Did you make progress with
curran's mystery girlfriend?
No, but jaimie's still
working rowe, so...
What do you mean
"working"?
I told her
to escalate her cover
and make herself
a little dirtier.
Oh.
I get it, but...
But what?
What's the problem?
I don't think jaimie
running around in a tight dress
is an effective use
of our resources.
[ Chuckles ]
You learn that phrase
at quantico?
We need to focus
on Hoffman.
Bust him in a coke deal
and press him to see
what he knows about the murder.
I agree,
but why not Chase rowe, too?
Who knows?
Maybe he'll open up to jaimie
and start talking
about curran.
But there's something else
going on here.
Isn't there?
No secrets.
Remember?
I...Need to get going.
Hey.
[ Door opens ]
Yo, "t".
Good morning.
Come on. Let's go.
How's single life
treating you?
It's okay.
How's Melissa doin'?
Melissa is, uh...
Moved into
a new apartment.
Cost me $7,000
to get her all moved in.
But Melissa is happy.
Look, I can't believe
you separated.
Yeah. Well...
It's for real.
All right, come on, man.
Let's go. Gotta go find
curran's dark-haired bimbo.
First, we gotta go,
uh, by rowe's bar.
Pay his punk ass the vig.
I don't get it.
This gambling thing?
[ scoffs ] Makes no sense.
I mean,
you blow a month's wages
on some stupid card game?
[ Scoffs ]
5 kilos of cocaine
for 12k apiece?
From what I hear, that sounds
like a pretty good price.
But why come to me
with this?
I don't know a damn thing
about selling drugs.
Well, what makes
you think I do?
Oh...
You have so many connections,
friends, clients.
Yeah, I, uh...
I don't play with cocaine.
Bad odds.
Even if we're careful.
Look.
In years back,
my kind-hearted boss
told me to deliver
an eight-ball to a client.
It was a, uh,
half-a-queen action hero.
Anyway...
I got pinched.
And -- poof! --
my fancy Hollywood career
went up in smoke.
Just like that.
That's it.
Oh, for the love
of Christ.
I mean, if this guy
spent his time
making counterfeit
Franklins,
he'd have a shot,
but chips, really?
Get outta here.
He doesn't think
we check this stuff?
Listen.
I like the way
you're thinking,
but...
I'm sorry.
I don't play with powder.
If I want to kiss you,
Billy,
I'll give you
the heads-up.
Got it?
Wow.
You're gonna fall in love
with me.
I mean, eventually.
I...Think.
[ Chuckles ]
"Be not quick in your spirit
to become angry,
for anger lodges only
in the bosom of fools."
Ecclesiastes 7:9.
I know I need to...
Get past the anger,
but it's hard.
[ Sniffles ]
My ex is such a...
He's mean...
Violent,
and this custody
fight is...
Just driving me crazy.
I'll bet.
How old's your son?
[ Purse rustles ]
[ chuckles ]
[ Chuckles ]
He's cute.
[ sniffles ]
It's too bad
his dad's such a...
Oh, it would
just be easier
if that son of a bitch
disappeared.
She's pushing her luck.
Jaimie's fearless.
That's the problem.
Rowe:
Disappeared? How?
Like "move to miami"
disappear or...
Something else?
"Move to miami"
would be good,
but "something else"
would be even better.
Some people just
don't deserve to be alive.
Why are you tellin' me
all this?
I barely know you.
I'm getting her
out of there.
Just give her a chance.
She knows
what she's doing.
He's getting suspicious.
Maybe.
I'm pulling her. Now.
[ cellphone beeps ]
Take off your shirt.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I said,
take off your shirt.
I like aggressive men,
Tim,
but I need a little more
foreplay than this.
I want to see
what's under there.
They're called breasts.
[ Cellphone rings ]
[ Purse rustles ]
Sorry.
Ma?
Is everything okay?
Jaimie, get out of there.
Okay,
I'll be right there.
[ Sniffles ]
My son has
this stomach thing.
Throwing up.
So I need to go.
Fine.
But just for kicks...
...Unbutton your shirt.
[ Purse thuds ]
It's all me under there.
Mmm.
[ chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
I...
I gotta go.
My son's sick.
Hey.
What the hell
was that about?
Why blow the whistle?
I was close. I could feel it.
You're out.
What?
He was looking
for a wire.
Yeah, and he didn't find one,
did he?
Because it's on my purse!
So what's your problem,
Alex?
You're done.
Hear me? Done.
Do you have problem
with me or something?
Excuse me?
It's like you're rooting
against me.
Every single time I get close
to rowe or solving the case,
you just --
you get more pissed.
I'm moving on.
To what?
Hoffman.
He passed
on the coke deal.
We'll bust him
for something else.
Such as?
You sure
Hoffman's interested?
Said he's extremely
intrigued.
Yeah. With you.
He knows better.
He doesn't.
Trust me.
He's all about the odds,
and the odds on this
are fantastic.
Yeah.
Exchanging counterfeit
dollars for casino chips
is easy money.
These cashiers
aren't exactly geniuses.
How much cash you bring?
$10,000.
Figured we'd start small.
Don't want him
to get suspicious.
One gun should do it, al.
I mean,
this guy's more likely
to pull out a facial scrub
than a nine.
What's the ask?
40 cents per dollar.
How do you know
this guy again?
Why does it matter?
[ chuckles ]
Because I like
to know the facts.
His name's Dave.
41. 5'9".
He has three nightclubs,
and he buys counterfeit money
from his cousin in South Korea.
Right. And you just...
Happened to bump into him
last night.
No.
I called him,
after you made that joke
about how your client
should focus on making
counterfeit Franklins
instead of bogus chips.
What's your cut?
50%.
50?!
I'm putting up
all the cash.
You're in for 20,
and that is a gift.
Now, as for the price,
I will pay 30...
And not a Penny more.
He said 40.
Unh-unh, unh-unh.
[ Sighs ]
[ Cellphone dialing ]
[ Ringing ]
Dave, it's me.
Remember that guy
I was telling you about?
Right.
He wants to pay 30.
He says 35 is the best
he can do.
Right on.
30, or he can go to hell.
He won't go higher
than 30, Dave.
Really?
30 it is!
Bam!
That's how I roll,
bitches!
See, didn't I tell you?
I used to be a baller
back in the day?
Right? I used to run
crazy-mad circles
around
those studio clowns.
You got the money
with you now?
Yeah.
Of course I do.
Now, seriously.
Tonight?
Me and you.
Nobu.
And "no"
is not an option.
I'm serious.
L.A.P.D.
What?
You're under arrest.
Looks like we're gonna
have to reschedule
dinner, there, Billy.
Oh, for the love of Christ.
This is lovely.
Okay, okay.
So, this is entrapment.
'Cause there was
no propensity
to commit a criminal act
on my part.
None.
I mean, what do you guys take me
for, a friggin' idiot?
I went to law school
for two years, you jackass.
If you actually finished
law school,
you'd know the only thing
that matters
is what you can actually prove,
you jackass.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
You're screwed.
Counterfeiting's
a class "a" felony.
Not to mention
the drug prior.
But there's a way out --
Tom curran.
Oh, I don't know anything
about that.
Oh, really?
Oh. That's too bad.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I know something.
Wait, what did you
think I said?
No, I-I know something.
But...
I want complete immunity.
That depends
on how helpful you are.
[ Sighs ]
Curran was losing a lot of money
at the Blackjack table.
So I hooked him up
with a lender, Tim rowe.
What was your cut?
20%.
Problem is...
Curran never made
any payments.
Ducked
rowe's phone calls.
Kept gambling
and borrowing.
So I tried to help him.
Called his sister.
Told her about
the whole situation.
But instead of getting
a "thank you,"
took a swing at me.
That was it.
That was like the last
I saw of him.
Police later on that day
discover his car
covered in blood.
So who killed him?
Rowe?
He's the leader
in the clubhouse.
Did he ever say anything
about the killing?
Oh, please.
Not a word.
I mean, you know,
we're not exactly besties.
And you're okay
wearing a wire?
Are you crazy?
If I even mention the murder
to rowe,
he's gonna get
suspicious. Fast.
And then
he's gonna kill me.
You know, I'm not
exactly a hero, guys.
Yeah.
I sort of sensed that
about you.
He's right about rowe.
He's paranoid as hell
these days.
I know,
but what's the alternative?
Jaimie.
Rowe:
What are you doin'?!
I got you a present.
"100 inspirational
bible passages."
I saw it at the bookstore,
so I got it for you.
[ Chuckles ]
So, my son is
feeling better today.
Oh, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
I was thinking
we could do something later?
Sure.
Now, you just be prepared
to get freaky.
Hmm.
So, we decide to question
curran's father.
We're over at his place,
and in his office,
I see on his desk this picture
of this cute, dark-haired girl.
I ask him about it.
You're gonna love this.
The woman he's hugging
on the day he got murdered
is his sister.
His sister?
So there was never
a second girlfriend?
Exactly.
We talked to her.
The sister.
She was at the casino
convincing him to meet with rowe
at macarthur park.
Rowe called her that day
anonymously, right?
Told her about all the debts
and the problems
and said he wanted
a face-to-face with curran
or he was gonna put a bullet
in the back of his head.
But if he showed up,
he'd let him walk, head intact.
And she believed him?
Unfortunately.
Well, why didn't she tell
the l.A.P.D. This?
Well, I don't think
she's exactly thrilled
to let the world know
that she helped orchestrate
her brother's murder.
So, mystery is solved,
answer is irrelevant.
Awesome.
[ sets bottle down ]
I'm late.
I got a date
with a thai yoga instructor.
[ Door opens, closes ]
So we're getting close
to busting this idiot.
That's good,
'cause he's a punk, man.
Shooting somebody over
a freakin' loan is stupid.
You don't pop somebody
over that.
He was probably just a reckless
kid who got carried away.
You know?
You talkin' about curran
or you?
The 5k...
You borrowed from rowe.
You never booked it
into evidence.
I lost it, Carter,
playing Blackjack.
I met this cute girl.
I'm hanging out with her.
We had a couple drinks,
you know?
I mean, I got caught up
in the buzz, the excitement.
You blew 5 grand
on some bimbo?
Do you realize
you just gave this prick
the perfect defense?!
"Undercover cop
pins murder rap on my client
to get out
from under his debt"?!
That's crap, man.
It's reasonable doubt!
And that's all
that matters!
Not to mention your reputation,
your career.
You don't gamble away
evidence, ty.
I'll make it back, okay?
I'll make it back quick.
24 hours.
You give me 24 hours,
I'll get the money back!
I promise!
Wire's all set.
It's pretty sensitive,
so no need to talk loud
or anything.
Carter:
Just be calm,
and lead with that story
about curran's sister.
It's the best way in.
I promise you.
Billy:
Right. Sister.
She came to the casino
late last night.
She's feeling all guilty
about getting duped
in setting up the murder --
I got it.
But pretend that
she's actually in the loop,
that she knows
who rowe is,
that curran told her all about
the loans and the threats.
Carter:
You need to sell the idea
that the sister can tie rowe
to the murder.
Make this about you.
Okay?
You're worried about getting
swept up in the investigation.
That's why you're there...
To protect yourself.
I'm out.
I can't do it.
Okay? Listen to me.
If you want to get me
for counterfeiting,
give it a shot.
It will not stick.
'Cause like I said, I went
to law school for two years,
and my second cousin
is a defense attorney, okay?
Truth is, you're probably right.
You might win.
I'd say it's 50-50.
Here you go.
Heads, you do five years.
Tails, you walk.
You wanna play
those odds?
[ Slams desk ]
Go ahead. Be my guest.
Go ahead!
I got no upside here!
Do you understand that?
I screw up, I'm dead.
I hit it
out of the park,
and I go back
to even --
a working stiff
in a second-rate casino
taking people's money!
It ever occur to you
that there's a kid out there
at the bottom of a ditch,
and that you could
actually help
his grieving parents
find closure?!
I know it sounds crazy,
but why not help...
[ slaps Billy's chest ]
...'Cause it's
the right thing to do?
You're right.
That sounds
completely crazy.
You know what?
I'm sick of this.
You got five seconds
to decide.
I-I...
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
I'll do it!
All right?
And by the way,
watch and learn, Carter,
because I am gonna get
a confession.
Good.
Just remember
to tell rowe --
Carter! Please.
I might be a pussy,
but I'm a great liar.
I was an Agent, remember?
Thanks for getting the wire
in rowe's office.
Glad to be of service.
Look, I know I've been pretty
outspoken about your tactics.
Oh, really?
I didn't notice.
What are you trying
to say?
You pulled me out too soon,
and I'm pissed.
Years ago, I was [Sighs]
I was trying to get close
to this gun runner.
Things got flirty,
so I ran with it.
Then one night, he wanted more
than witty banter.
Got rough.
Hit me a few times,
broke my jaw.
So, yeah...
You're probably right.
I did pull you too soon.
[ Exhales sharply ]
If you don't mind,
I'd...
Prefer to keep this
between us.
Well, looks like our
white night just arrived.
[ Car alarm activates ]
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
About the cash, Carter...
Um, look, I sold
my baseball-card collection,
but the stupid son of a bitch
only gave me 1,500,
so I might need
a little bit more time.
I took care of it.
I booked the money into evidence
this morning.
Well, I'll pay you back.
I will.
Does Alex know
about this?
No.
You gonna tell her?
Now shut up
and listen to the damn wire.
Curran's sister
knows my name?!
Yes. Why else
would I be here?
What else did she say?
That curran told her
about the loans,
the interest payments,
and the threats,
and that you told her
to get him to macarthur park
the night
that he disappeared.
Are you wearing a wire,
Billy?
Yeah, I'm wearing a wire.
Just for you.
I thought it would go good
with the jacket.
What are you, crazy?
You happy?
Why is this chick going to you
and not the cops?
I'm not sure.
She tells me
that her brother trusted me.
I know. I mean,
I-it's stupid, I know.
That's what she told me.
Yeah, but that doesn't explain
why she's going to you
and not the police!
How the hell am I supposed
to know why she's talking
to me, Tim? Am I shrink?
Dude's pretty good.
I'm gonna ask you
one more time
why you're really here,
Billy!
To save my ass.
The cops
have been harassing me
ever since this kid
disappeared.
And if they go after you,
they're gonna drag me
into your mess.
They're gonna bust me on some
trumped-up accessory charge.
I know it.
The good news is,
we still have time
to take care
of this problem.
What are you saying?
You saying we should do
something to this broad?
Yeah, I'm saying,
if she's telling the truth,
you're going down.
[ sighs ]
Which means
I'm going down.
And guess what.
I'm not going down.
This...Preppy son of a bitch
steals my money.
Stiffs me.
I didn't want to kill him,
but he was going
to the cops.
What was I
supposed to do?
What was that?
What was what?
That little smile.
Let's take him down now!
[ Gunshot ]
Damn it!
[ Gunfire ]
Alex! In here!
Jaimie, secure the front!
I need an ambulance
right away.
[ Both grunting ]
[ Panting ] I'm a cop.
Did you really think I'd get
freaky with your dumb ass?!
[ Straining ]
Hey, Billy?
Wow.
If I knew you were coming,
I would have put on
a more revealing gown.
Too bad he didn't shoot you
in the mouth.
[ Chuckles ]
Baby girl, uh,
give us a couple minutes?
Please?
Thank you.
[ Siren wails in distance ]
You're actually
pretty brave...
For a coward.
Rowe confessed to the murder,
told us where the body is.
So, like it or not,
you actually did a pretty good
thing here, Billy.
Uh...Um...
...Mozza.
You and me...
Saturday.
I'll take that as a yes.
You have the key?
Yep.
Too bad.
[ Chuckles ]
So...
How we doin'?
What do you mean?
Us.
The first week together.
Oh. Right. "Us."
Yeah.
I'd say we did
pretty good.
Me too.
But like we talked about,
the key is being open
and honest.
No secrets.
Absolutely.
No secrets here.
You?
Nope.
Oh, good.
[ Moaning ]
Download Torrents anonymously
Hide your IP with VPN
visit !! hide-ip.notlong.com !!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org