Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(DARK, EERIE MUSIC PLAYS)
(LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
(CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Here we are, top of the eighth,
and Fourth of July
is just around the corner...
- How's the specimen?
- His tail came off.
WOMAN: Well...
maybe you should let him go.
I'm gonna nurse him back to health.
I don't know lizards...
is that compassion or torture?
Uh, I'm gonna go with the latter.
You gonna want cheese?
Yes! Did you text Jesse?
Yeah, he's with Rat Face.
He said he'd be home
eight minutes ago.
I'll call him.
And it's Ratner, not Rat Face.
Don't be cruel.
Not being cruel.
It's descriptive.
There's something wrong with that kid.
Hey, we got people coming over in five.
Get your butt home.
An epic game of Modern Warfare.
MAN: Yeah, that's
what save buttons are for, pal.
(SIGHING) OK, I'm coming.
Tell Dad to chill.
WOMAN: OK. Bye.
(SIGHS)
Dog, this shit is weak, man.
(SULTRY JAZZ PLAYING ON VIDEO)
I've totally done this stuff,
like, so many times.
(SCOFFS)
- You've been a bad girl.
Well, I guess
you better punish me, then.
Ooh, that feels so good.
(MAN AND WOMAN MOANING
WITH PASSION)
(BIRD CAWS IN DISTANCE)
(CRICKETS CHIRRING)
MAN 1: - Boy, this beer works.
MAN 2: - Works every time.
The Fed can prime
the pump in DC all it wants,
but all it's gonna do is raise the price
for a cup of coffee in California.
- Mm-hmm.
- Alicia told me he's back in rehab.
I think you have to point
the finger at the parents.
Do you know they have
an open relationship?
- Wait. What?
(LAUGHING)
How long have you known this?
- What kind of relationship?
- Eat your food. (SILENT MOUTHING)
Tell me everything you know,
right now.
(CONVERSATIONS CONTINUE INDISTINCTLY)
You're gonna kill that thing.
No, I'm not.
I'm rehabiting him.
- It's "rehabilitate," brainiac.
(GIGGLES)
MAN 1: - A three-year-old?
MAN 2: - Let's go four.
MAN 1: OK, four-year-old.
A compromise. Four.
I got two scary words
for you, though: China, India.
- I'm terrified.
(CHUCKLES)
MAN 1: I'll give you a dollar
if you eat that potato salad.
- A dollar? (GIGGLES)
- I just don't know what you see in him.
- You're so much smarter than he is.
- Ratner's smart.
He's so not smart.
That stunt he pulled
with the car, that's smart?
His parents forgot about it.
Why can't you?
- Oh. Hello. Why can't you?
WOMAN: - Oh, come on. Come on.
Daniel... Come on.
I just think you should be hanging out
with kids your age, that's all.
I'm old enough.
TV ANNOUNCER:
...the Dow Jones Industrial Average
plummeted another 148 points today,
causing some analysts to predict
a major recession on the horizon...
I have my father's hair.
WOMAN:
Your father doesn't have hair.
That's something to look forward to.
- Daniel.
- Sorry.
(WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
Daniel, come on.
I've gotta prep these viewings.
We need this.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
"Recovering my courage
with an effort,
I take a cautious look out.
In the middle of the room...
(CONTINUES OVER WALKIE-TALKIE)
...in front of my father,
stands the Sandman,
the bright light of the lamp
falling full upon his face."
(WALKIE-TALKIE BLIPS)
- Lunar Base to Command Control. Over.
JESSE:
Go for Command Control.
Why does the Sandman
steal people's eyes?
So he can feed 'em
to his children on the moon.
Why doesn't he feed them
something else?
Sam, everyone knows
eyes taste the best.
SAM:
You think he'll steal mine?
(STATIC CRACKLING)
JESSE: Maybe.
But yours are still pretty small.
He'd probably take mine first.
SAM: - Lunar Base, over and out.
(WALKIE-TALKIE BLIPS)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(CRICKETS CHIRRING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOORKNOB CLICKS, DOOR CREAKS)
(DOGS BARK IN DISTANCE)
(GASPS)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(POPEYE SINGING SONG ON TV)
(TV CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
You guys gotta keep
this door locked tonight, OK?
- I didn't touch it.
- Me neither.
What kind of animal eats all the lettuce
but leaves the bacon?
DANIEL: A rabbit.
A very large rabbit,
with opposable thumbs.
Maybe it was a mutant lizard who's mad
at Sammy for imprisoning her offspring.
No... Don't listen to your brother.
You want juice?
Ahh! Gotta go.
- Wish me luck.
(ALL) Luck.
I have a second showing at two
up on Croft.
I should be back before then.
Oh.
Luck.
You were laid off from Jacobson?
Uh, yes, sir. The development I was on
ran into cash flow issues,
and the entire design team was let go.
(CLOCK TICKING STEADILY)
(QUIETLY CLEARS THROAT)
But I was thinking of making
a switch anyway, so...
(BANGS ECHOING)
How did it go?
- It went well.
- Really?
- When do they get back to you?
- Mm... next week, most likely.
Daniel, that's great.
I'm proud of you.
(RETREATING FOOTSTEPS)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(CLICKS)
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS)
(SIGHS)
(WALKIE-TALKIE BLIPS)
SAM: I want to hear
the other one again.
(JESSE OVER WALKIE-TALKIE, INDISTINCT)
"Ah, little wretch, little wretch..."
SAM: Lunar Base
to Command Control, over.
Enough scary stories, Sammy.
Say good night to your brother.
Mom says I have to say good night.
JESSE: - Night, Mom.
- Night, Jess.
You, sleep, now.
- Night, Mom.
- Good night.
(INSECTS CHIRRING)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(GASPS)
(GASPS, PANTING)
(SHOUTS)
Oh, Sammy, you scared me.
I had a bad dream.
You had a bad dream?
Oh, it's OK. It's OK now.
It's OK now.
Sammy...
...do you know who did this?
The Sandman.
The Sandman?
Is that one of your toys?
He was in my dream.
And did he tell you to do this
in your dream?
He did it himself,
before he came to my room.
Well, there's no sign
of forced entry.
You sure all the doors
and windows were locked?
Yeah, I'm sure.
We check them every night.
And other than the food,
nothing's missing?
- No.
- No. Nothing.
OK, well, as I see it,
we have two scenarios:
(CLATTERING)
Either the person who did this
had a key or, uh, it was...
...someone in the house.
Uh... no, I don't think so.
No, we were all asleep.
I'm not saying
it's anything sinister.
People do a lot of strange
things when they sleep.
Got a call over on Langford once,
family kept waking up to a mess
in the kitchen every morning.
Turns out the teenage daughter
was a sleep eater.
- A sleep eater?
- Yeah.
It's like a sleep walker,
but instead of getting up
and walking in their sleep,
they actually go to the kitchen and eat.
(CHUCKLES)
It's the craziest thing.
Look, Officer,
this wasn't a cooking mess.
This was like a mathematician's
idea of a geometry joke.
I don't know whether to be
pissed or impressed.
Well, maybe you just got some
real bright kids on your hands.
- I see you have an alarm.
- Yeah.
We have the system,
but we let the service lapse.
Trying to cut back a little.
Yeah. Well, I'd suggest
turning it back on.
It's money well spent.
Be safe.
Three bedroom, two bath.
It needs a bit of updating,
but that's just a chance
to really make it yours.
Wait till you see the kitchen.
(QUIETLY)
I checked the comps, honey.
This is a great buying opportunity.
(PHONE RINGS)
MAN:
You know, I gotta take this.
Why don't you ladies keep going.
I'm gonna catch up.
Sure.
(GIRL WHEEZING)
OK... come here...
It's OK.
(WHEEZING CONTINUES)
- It's OK. It's all right.
- Do you need anything?
- No-no-no, I got it.
Hang on. Here we go. OK, OK.
OK. Deep breath. Ready?
- You better?
GIRL: - Mm-hmm.
MOTHER: Yeah?
All right. Good girl.
It gets easier.
My oldest, Jesse, was sick
all the time when he was little.
It was like he was allergic
to the entire world.
How'd you get through it?
I worried a lot. (LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING)
Yeah. And I took it day by day.
And he got older and the episodes
happened less and less and...
Now, hardly ever a cold.
(WHISPERS) That sounds nice.
(MOTHER SIGHS)
So what do you think of this place?
Is it a "buying opportunity"?
I know I'm supposed to be
selling you... (CHUCKLES)
...but you can probably do better.
(BUTTONS BEEPING)
MALE NARRATOR:
A silent hunter, the great white shark
stalks its prey
with near invisibility,
its attack both unstoppable and fatal.
Here off the coast of...
I think maybe we should cut
back on the cable for a while.
Well, maybe we should
just wait a week,
because you might get
the good news on that job.
I...
Yeah, I don't...
I don't think I got it, Lace.
Wait a second. I don't understand.
You said it went great.
Oh, no, it went OK. It did.
But there's just...
there's a lot of competition.
So... (CLEARS THROAT)
- You lied?
- Come on, Lace.
You did, didn't you? (SIGHS)
Why would you do that, Daniel?
Look, I just didn't...
I wanted to not give you bad news.
- OK.
- For once.
- So you lied about it?
- I didn't lie...
...exactly. I just... (SIGHS)
You know, you've been
so stressed lately...
Do not do that!
Do not make this about me.
(ARGUING CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(SAM OVER WALKIE-TALKIE)
Lunar Base to Command Control.
Come in, Command Control. Over.
(SIGHS)
(WALKIE-TALKIE BEEPS)
Go for Command Control.
Picking up hostile transmission
on all frequencies. Over.
JESSE: Just ignore them, Sammy.
Try to go to sleep.
SAM: Command Control?
Yes, Lunar Base?
Do you think Dad's gonna leave?
No.
Why would you say that, Sammy?
Sammy, why would you say that?
'Cause Tau told me
his parents argued every night,
then his dad moved
to an apartment by the airport,
and now he only sees him
on the weekends.
Don't worry Sammy,
Dad's not moving anywhere.
Now try and go to sleep.
(DANIEL AND LACY
CONTINUE ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
(ALARM WAILING)
(GASPING)
Stay with your brother!
(DOOR CLOSES)
(ALARM CONTINUES WAILING)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
WOMAN: - This is City One Protection.
May I have your name
and password, please?
Yes, my... It's Daniel Barrett.
My password is "Lacy214."
Thank you, Mr. Barrett. Are you
currently experiencing a break-in?
Uh, I don't think so.
I don't know.
We were sleeping,
the alarm went off.
- Uh, I'm at the keypad now.
(ALARM STOPS)
Uh, it's not telling me
what sensor was tripped.
(STATIC CRACKLES OVER PHONE)
- You there?
- Yes. Yes, Mr. Barrett.
We believe this was a false alarm
due to a system malfunction.
What kind of malfunction?
What sensor was tripped?
WOMAN: - All of them.
- What?
The system is reporting
that all eight entry points to the house
were breached at the same time.
I don't understand.
How is that possible?
We're not sure what happened either,
but we'll send someone out tomorrow
at 9:00 a.m. to check your system.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
OK. Thank you.
(PHONE BEEPS)
They said it was a false alarm.
A system malfunction.
Daniel, what's happening?
Mr. Barrett, have you talked
to your children about this?
Yeah... They both said
they were asleep.
And you're sure
they're telling you the truth?
Hey, I've got kids, too. Right?
I mean, they do stuff like this to get
your attention, then they lie about it.
Happens all the time.
It's no reflection on you as a parent.
Oh.
I understand how that can happen,
but this doesn't seem
like one of those things.
My wife doesn't feel safe
in the house right now.
Listen, I know this can be tough,
but... is there any reason
for either of your children
to be angry with you or your wife?
Any... discord in the family?
Kids have a way
of picking up on these things.
Excuse me, Mr. Barrett?
I'm all through here.
I couldn't find anything
wrong with the system.
So what set it off?
Well, it could be any number of things.
It's technical.
Bottom line, though, I don't think
anybody actually tried to get in.
DANIEL: Look, do either of you have
anything that you want to tell us?
Like What?
LACY: Um...
DANIEL: Uh, look,
we know things have been
a little strained around here lately.
LACY: And... when that happens,
that can create feelings
towards us that, um...
It's about the photos, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
Did either of you take them?
We were sleeping.
How could we take them?
Sammy?
Sam, did you have that dream again?
About the Sandman?
What dream?
Samuel...
...did the Sandman take the photos?
It's OK. You can tell us.
I can't.
What's going on, Lace?
What do you mean, you can't?
He told me not to say.
LACY: Daniel, stop.
I don't care about the photos right now.
Daniel, are we gonna talk about this?
Now you want to talk?
When were you gonna tell me
he was having these dreams?
I didn't think it was a big deal.
- Kids have nightmares.
- Yeah.
Yeah. They don't act them out, though.
Obviously, I was wrong.
It's not funny, Sammy.
Just tell them where the photos are.
(WHISPERING)
But I don't know where they are.
I didn't take them.
(SIGHS) The Sandman isn't real.
You do understand that, right?
(ARGUING CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Daniel, stop!
What are we gonna do about this?
I don't know, Lace.
What do you want to do?
Want to put him in therapy?
How we gonna pay for that?
He's our son, not a cable bill.
I know, Lace.
Karen says she knows someone
who talked to Shelly
when she was going
through some stuff.
I guess she works
on a sliding scale, so...
Did you tell them
we were having money trouble?
(SIGHS, GRUNTING)
- Daniel, stop!
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
OK.
Let's just wait a few days, all right?
What do you keep scratching at?
Nothing.
It's, like, a bite or something.
(SIGHS)
(KIDS CHATTERING PLAYFULLY)
There they are. Go get 'em.
Hey, there he is.
Bobby, get up!
Get up. You're not hurt.
There you go!
Now get the ball!
Hey, so Karen says you guys are,
what, looking for a therapist for Sammy?
DANIEL: No.
(CHUCKLES)
No, no, it's nothing.
It's a rough spot.
Is everything all right at home?
- Yeah.
BOBBY: - Ew!
- He peed himself!
(LAUGHTER)
Sammy?
- Sammy?
- Ew, he peed himself!
Hey, buddy,
if you had to go to the bathroom,
you should've just told me.
Sammy, what's wrong?
Hey.
Sammy.
(HIGH-PITCHED SCREAMING)
No. It's OK.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Sammy, stop! Sammy!
Sammy, stop!
But you're sure he's OK now?
OK, just get home. I'm here.
Bye.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
(HOLLOW THUMP)
(LOUD BANG)
(SHRIEKS)
(LACY GASPING)
Oh, shit.
(CLICKS TONGUE) God.
(LOUD BANG)
(SHOUTS)
(BANGING)
(GASPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
They just hit the house,
hundreds of them.
Karen, I can't even
begin to describe it.
Yeah. No, there's...
We got an army of people
over here right now.
No, you guys, don't touch it!
They could be contaminated.
We're just looking at them.
OK, but just, both of you,
don't touch them.
Yeah.
Dude, this is awesome!
This is definitely
the start of an outbreak.
- Bitch, you're gonna get quarantined!
- Shut up.
If I am, so are you.
We'll run autopsies on a sample,
see if they're sick.
We haven't had any reports
of avian flu
in the local starling population,
but it could be something new.
Well, and if they weren't sick?
Then we'll look
for environmental causes...
...uh, hail storms, lightning.
We're coming up on the Fourth,
so you can't discount fireworks.
They'll disorient a flock pretty easily.
(SIGHS)
Look, uh, it'd be great if we get
some answers to what caused this.
(SIGHING)
We've been having some...
...uh, strange things
going on around here,
and it would just be really nice
if this wasn't adding to it.
Uh, we'll do our best, Mr. Barrett.
I'll give you a call.
OK. Thank you.
LACY: Sam, Dad said
you got scared in the park today?
You don't remember
screaming at the park, buddy?
What do you remember?
I remember going in the grass
to play with the other kids.
Yeah?
Then I wasn't me anymore.
Hey, uh, Sam, why don't you
head up and, uh, brush your teeth,
and I'll tuck you in, OK?
- OK.
I'll be right up.
Thanks, pal.
OK. OK. We'll call
the therapist in the morning.
I'll figure how
to pay for it somehow.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(WIND WHISTLING SOFTLY)
(STAIRS CREAKING)
(SIGHS)
(SAM CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
SAM: (QUIETLY) Can't hear any.
What do you mean?
Sam?
SAM: I promise,
I won't tell them anything.
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
DANIEL: - What's going on?!
- There was someone...
- I... I just turned on the light.
- What?
- There was someone in the room.
- What did you see?
The light, and there was someone...
- Sam?
- There was someone in here!
Sam?! Sam!
What happened?
DANIEL: - Sam?
- What going on?
LACY: Sam?
- Sammy?
- Sam!
LACY: Sam?
(LACY SHRIEKS)
(ALARM WAILING)
- Oh, shit!
- Sam!
(KEYPAD BEEPS)
- Hey, what the hell are you doing? Sam.
(ALARM STOPS)
Sam.
Mom?
It's OK.
Sam! Wake up.
- Why are we outside?
(DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(SIGHS)
Shh.
(QUIETLY) They don't know how he got out
without setting off the alarm.
They're gonna send someone to check
the system again in the morning.
(WHISPERING) Daniel...
...I saw someone in Sam's room.
The window was locked, Lacy.
You were standing by the door.
If somebody was there,
where'd he go?
I don't know. I can't explain it.
But I saw someone
standing over Sam's bed.
And when I turned on the lights,
both of them were gone.
You didn't see Sammy in his room.
You couldn't have.
He was already outside.
So you think I imagined it?
Lace...
...what is this?
What are we talking about?
I don't know.
(STAMMERS) I'm...
I'm just saying,
something's going on.
This is me now. It's not Sam.
Look, I hear you.I do.
But we've got enough to handle right now
without getting crazy.
It's not gonna help anything.
(WHISPERS) What the fuck?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Light her up!
(RATNER MAKING ENGINE NOISES)
Butt in your face! Butt in your face!
(LAUGHS)
(RATNER CONTINUES
MAKING ENGINE NOISES)
Listen, you can't tell
your mom about this place.
What, you think
I'm gonna get you in trouble?
Promise?
What are you gonna do for me?
You've... been a bad girl.
What are you doing? Stop it!
Dude, what is wrong with you?
Sorry, I...
Have you ever even
kissed a girl before?
Come here.
Pucker your lips.
Close your eyes.
(PLAYING THE DRUMS: "DAYS")
(STREETLIGHTS CRACKLING)
(PANTING SOFTLY)
DANIEL: If someone's
coming into this house,
we'll see him on this.
This isn't some kind of twisted way
for you to spice up our sex life, is it?
That wasn't the idea.
But I like the way you think.
This is gonna solve it, Lace.
SAM: Do you think he's watching us?
(JESSE OVER WALKIE-TALKIE)
You mean Dad?
Yeah.
Probably.
Do you think there's somebody here?
No.
Then why did Dad
put up the cameras?
JESSE: 'Cause he's just making sure.
SAM: - Command Control?
- Yes, Lunar Base?
I'm scared.
Don't worry, Sammy.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I promise.
(CRICKETS CHIRRING)
(DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS, SNIFFS)
(MOUSE CLICKS)
(STATIC CRACKLES)
- What the...?
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(STATIC CONTINUES CRACKLING)
(KEYS JINGLING)
So, three bedroom, two bath.
It needs a bit of updating,
but that's really a chance
to make it your own,
get exactly what you want.
WOMAN: - Hm.
(SIGHING)
What do you think, honey?
It looks like a lot of work.
I have to say, you know,
I know this area pretty well now,
and you're not gonna do
much better for this price.
Um, how flexible do you think
the sellers will be on the terms?
They are highly motivated.
I mean, I think
we can be very... (STUTTERS)
(GRUNTS)
- Are you OK?
Lacy?
(LACY GRUNTING) (MUFFLED) Lacy?
(BANGING LOUDLY)
- Lacy!
- Oh, my God!
(GASPS, PANTING)
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
(GROANS)
(RING-TONE PLAYING)
- Hello?
MAN: - Hey, it's Pete.
What the hell happened to you?
I've been calling for hours.
I got a message from a very distressed
client saying you had
some kind of a breakdown in the middle
of the walk-through this morning.
They were about to call 911,
for Christ's sakes,
- but you walked out of the house.
- Oh, my God.
Look, I know it's been
rough out there,
but maybe you should
take a break for a little while.
No, Pete, I can't do that.
OK, well, the thing is
I'm not asking, Lacy.
Your clients took their business
over to Sunshine Realty.
I'm sorry, kiddo. Just call me
when you're feeling better.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(PANTING)
- Oh, God. (GASPS)
(RING-TONE PLAYS)
- Pete, please let me explain, OK?
WOMAN: - Mrs. Barrett?
This is Janice Rhodes
from the National Wildlife Center.
I got your husband's voice mail,
so I thought I'd try you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes, go ahead.
I have some new information
about the incident,
but I'm afraid it raises
more questions than it answers.
Oh, w... what kind of questions?
The birds were negative for avian flu.
But what we did determine
is that the impact trajectories
indicate the birds were
part of three different flocks
and not one,
as we originally assumed.
I don't understand.
So what does that mean?
What it means is
that three different migrations
coming from three different directions
flew into your house, Mrs. Barrett.
It's as if something was
drawing them to your home.
(WHIRRING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Have you been working on
anything since leaving Jacobson?
You know, I've been tinkering
with a few personal projects,
but pretty much enjoying
just being a stay-at-home dad.
Oh, really?
Oh, man, what I wouldn't give
for a little time
like that with my family.
Yeah. No, it's... it's been great.
You guys got big plans
for the Fourth, or...?
My kids got me running all over
town looking for fireworks.
No, I think we'll probably
stick close to home.
Well, listen, Daniel,
I'm really glad you came in.
I loved what you did
on the Bay Cities project.
- Thank you.
- All the other partners
are very supportive,
so I say we do it.
- Really?
- Really.
- What do you say?
- I... Yes! (CHUCKLES)
- It's yours. All right?
- Fantastic.
- Absolutely. I'll be in touch, OK?
- Great.
- OK.
- Have a good Fourth.
Thank you very much.
Hello?
Hi.
I've got news.
- Me, too.
- I got it, Lace.
I got the job.
Are you serious, Daniel?
They want me to start on the 15th.
Daniel, that's... that's amazing!
(LAUGHING)
(BOTH SIGH)
Let's see if Karen and Mike
will take Sammy tonight.
(LAUGHS)
Jesse can stay at the Ratners'.
We need to celebrate,
for a change.
Oh, shit, I'm sorry.
What was your news?
Uh... nothing.
Let's celebrate. (SIGHS)
(LAUGHS)
(LACY LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
(DOGS BARKING OUTSIDE IN DISTANCE)
Daniel?
(DOGS CONTINUE BARKING OUTSIDE)
(GASPING)
Daniel?
(DOGS CONTINUE BARKING)
Why aren't you answering me?
Daniel.
Daniel, wake up. Daniel!
Wake up. Wake up.
(GASPING)
Daniel.
What am I doing in the kitchen?
LACY:
I found you in the backyard.
You don't remember
getting out of bed?
(KEYPAD BEEPING OVER MONITOR)
(SNIFFS)
No.
That is so... weird.
It's more than weird.
I'm ready to tell you my news.
I lost six hours today.
I mean, the last thing I remember,
I was in the middle
of this walk-through.
The clients told Pete that they thought
I was having some kind of breakdown.
And I woke up in bed, and I had this.
Jesus, Lace.
Daniel, I've got to show you something.
So I started with the birds.
And the best they can
understand it is that
something is interfering
with the Earth's geomagnetic field,
and... and that's causing
the birds to veer off course.
Some people say that it has something
to do with the government,
that they're testing some kind of
super-secret weapons technology.
And other people...
...think it's something else,
something...
...not from here.
What does that mean, "not from here"?
Not from... this planet.
- Lacy.
- I know this is so hard to believe.
- Just trust me. I've been research...
- No, it's more than hard to believe.
I mean... aliens?
That's...
That's insane. Right?
You know this is the reason
we don't self-diagnose on the Internet.
Stop. Hear me out on this.
There are people
who have reported experiencing
the same things
that we have been experiencing,
in these communities where these
other bird deaths have taken place.
This picture was drawn
by a five-year-old
in Chesapeake Bay in 2007,
shortly before he vanished.
Vanished, Daniel.
His family claims
he was taken by aliens
and that they had been
entering their home for weeks.
Sam drew this yesterday.
Yeah, well, maybe Sammy saw
this drawing online and copied it.
And maybe he made
800 birds hit our house?
I found a guy in the city who claims
to be an expert on this stuff.
- I think we gotta go talk to him. Yes.
- No. No, no, no, no.
Well, what other explanation
do you have?
Just because I can't explain something,
doesn't mean aliens are responsible.
Why can't you understand that
some things defy normal explanations?
We're not those people
who believe in crazy things!
Maybe those people
aren't the crazy ones!
- Who are you? Who...
- Don't do this.
- Where is my wife?
- Don't do that!
- You always...
- My sane wife!
Crazy stuff is happening right now!
Stop it! I'm not saying
nothing is going on.
But this, this is...
this is too much.
There's got to be another answer.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(LIVELY CHATTERING)
Right there.
You can go. Go ahead.
- Jump in.
- Cannonball!
Hey, shirt off, string bean.
Can't swim with your clothes on.
Come on, dork,
I know you want to swim.
Sammy, come here.
Let me take a look at you.
It's OK, baby.
I'm just gonna take a look, OK?
Put your arms up.
(GASPS)
Sammy, tell me who did this to you.
Sammy, I need you to tell me
who did this to you.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Hey, you know that girl Jennifer?
- Yeah.
- That bitch was on my jock.
- Really?
- Yeah.
What about you?
You get any?
I saw you with Shelly.
Did you kiss her?
- Yeah.
- Did you feel her titties?
Kind of, I guess.
Shit, dawg!
That's nothing!
You got to go downtown.
That's what I do with all my ladies.
(GUN COCKS)
Hey, Barrett.
(GUN POPS)
- Ow!
- Dude, stop.
- Better run, bitch!
Stop being a dick! Stop!
(GUN POPS)
(LAUGHS)
I'm gonna pop a cap in your ass!
(GUN POPS)
(GUN COCKS)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING
GROWS LOUDER)
(GUN POPS)
- Man down!
Oh, come on,
it didn't hurt that bad, you pussy.
Jesse?
(SHOUTS) Jesse!
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA)
How is he?
Well, I didn't find
anything physically wrong with Jesse
that would cause a blackout or seizure.
And the MRI was clear.
So, as I said, I don't think
what we're dealing with here
is a neurological problem.
So what do you think it is?
Well, I believe this episode was
the result of some emotional trauma.
Now, I need you to listen to me
very carefully, Mr. and Mrs. Barrett.
During my examination, I found some
unusual marks on your son's body.
What... I'm sorry.
What kind of marks?
Well, they look like
small geometric shapes.
Uh, squares, rectangles, circles.
But the troubling part is
that they appear to have been
applied with a brand.
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Now, Mr. and Mrs. Barrett,
it's my opinion
that he did not do this to himself.
Jesse says he doesn't know
how he got them.
Do you have any idea
how he got them?
Uh, no.
Well, I have to inform you
that because of his age,
I'm required to refer this information
to Child Protective Services
for further investigation.
This is standard procedure.
They're gonna follow up
with some questions.
Do you understand
what I've just told you?
(WHISPERS) Yes... (CLEARS THROAT) Yes.
Now, Mr. Barrett, the incident report
says that Jesse was playing
in the woods with his friend
at the time of his blackout.
Yeah.
Uh, a boy named Kevin Ratner.
He's a few years older than Jesse.
Well, do you have any reason
to believe that your son
and this boy
were into anything strange?
JESSE: - Dad, what are you doing?
- Daniel, stop!
- Daniel, stop right now.
- Hey, Mr. Barrett.
- Jesse, are you OK? What?
- What'd you do to my son?
- Stop, Daniel!
- Huh? What did you do?
- Nothing! What the fuck?
- Stop it right now!
Tell me, you little freak!
He's only 13 years old!
- He didn't do anything!
- Hey!
(GRUNTS)
- Daniel! Whoa, whoa!
- You guys, stop it!
- Ask your son what he did!
There's something wrong
with you people!
Just leave it on.
You have to.
(SIGHS) Jesse.
- Hey...
- Leave me alone.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hi.
(SIGHS)
Don't touch me!
Tomorrow, we're gonna get a call
from Child Protective Services.
My best friend just
treated me like a criminal.
- Lacy...
- Karen said that Sammy
told her the Sandman did this.
You realize who she thinks
the Sandman is, right?
- I know.
- Did you do this?
- Did you put your hands on our son?!
- Jesus Christ!
Something is hurting our children,
Daniel, and you're too stubborn
- to believe what it is!
- I'm not listening to this shit!
Then tell me who did it!
Tell me.
Because it's not just
happening in their heads!
I don't know!
But when I find out,
I'm gonna deal with it.
Yeah, you really dealt
with things today, all right.
Daniel the hero!
(CRICKETS CHIRRING)
(ELECTRONIC HUMMING)
(STATIC CRACKLING SOFTLY)
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(SIGHS)
(PANTING)
Wake up, Sammy.
Sammy. Wake up.
(GASPS)
What's wrong, Daddy?
(GASPS, PANTING)
(WHISPERS) Oh, shit.
(STATIC CRACKLES)
(WHISPERS)
Come on, come on, come on.
(WHISPERS) What is it?
Do you remember right after Jesse
was born, and he was so sick?
The doctors didn't know what it was,
and they told us all we could do
was wait until morning
to see if he was gonna be OK.
That was the longest
night of my life.
I just felt... too helpless.
I didn't know if I was
gonna be kissing a child
or burying one in the morning.
It took me most of the night,
but I finally realized
something that allowed me
to watch the sun
come up without fear.
However it all turned out,
no matter what I had to face...
...I knew I would get through it,
because I had you.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(EXHALES)
I'm ready to believe.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER NEARBY)
(BABY CRYING NEARBY)
Mr. Pollard?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I had to run to the store.
That's OK. Um, I'm Lacy,
and this is my husband, Daniel.
(KEYS JINGLING)
You said on the phone
you have two children.
Yes, I...
We were just thinking
that it was better maybe
if we met you first, and then...
(KEYS JINGLING)
(LOCK CLICKS)
- Thank you.
- Have a seat in the living room.
I'll, uh, put on some tea.
(SILENT MOUTHING)
(FLOORBOARDS CREAKING)
(CATS MEOWING, PURRING)
(HISSES)
(CATS PURRING, MEOWING)
(WHISPERS) Of course
he would have cats.
POLLARD: Cats don't
seem to care about them.
(SIGHS) I used to live
in the suburbs, but...
...the dogs always barked at night
when they came around.
(SIGHS)
Dogs have a sense for them.
Kept me up at night, so, uh...
...so I moved here to a building
that doesn't allow dogs.
Helps me sleep
a little better at night.
I don't fight them anymore.
Them?
The Grays.
That's what they're called.
They, uh...
(GROANS)
There are three generally
accepted kinds of aliens:
the Grays, Insectoids
and the Reptilians.
But nine times out of ten, what people
report seeing are the Grays.
In fact, I'm... I'm dubious
about the other two altogether.
Especially the Reptilians.
I don't think
those accounts are credible.
Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
That would make anyone skeptical.
I'm sorry, uh...
I'm getting ahead of myself.
The... the first thing we need to do
is determine whether or not
you actually are
experiencing an encounter.
Is... is that a test?
Uh, just a series of questions.
Helps weed out the lunatics.
Well, good. Let's do it.
OK.
Have either of you seen
any bright lights in the sky
above your neighborhood
that moved in an unusual way?
(CLEARS THROAT) No.
Have you experienced any
severe headaches or migraines?
Nope.
Either of you heard
a ringing in your ears
that seems to be happening
only inside your head?
(SOFTLY) Yes
Have you experienced
any unexplained illnesses,
strange allergies or nosebleeds?
- Yes.
Have you witnessed any abnormal behavior
by animals in your neighborhood?
Three different flocks of birds
flew into our house the other day.
I would say that qualifies.
Have either of you
experienced any blackouts,
stretches of time
that you can't account for?
And have you experienced a feeling
that you might not be
in control of your own body?
How do you know all this?
You are not alone in this.
Others have experienced
what you're going through
and have struggled
the way you're struggling now.
Why are the Grays, or whatever they are,
so interested in us?
What makes us so special?
Nothing.
There's nothing special about you.
I'm sorry.
You were hoping
for a different answer.
But this is beyond
our comprehension.
What answer would a lab rat
understand from a scientist
in a white coat putting electrodes
in its brain, giving it cancer?
I've interviewed
literally thousands of people
who claim to have been
visited by the Grays.
They come from all walks of life.
The only thing they have in common
is that their lives have
become a living hell because of it.
People think of aliens
as these beings
invading our planet
in some great cataclysm,
destroying monuments,
stealing our natural resources.
But it's not like that at all.
The invasion... already happened.
No one knows exactly when, but...
...they're here.
They've been here.
The presence of the Grays
is now a fact of life.
Like death and taxes.
Do you know what they want?
They seem to be...
...studying us, experimenting on us.
One thing we know for sure is,
they use our fears against us.
It can start like a...
a childish prank...
...a mess in the kitchen
or things missing in the house.
And before you know it, you're walking
through a full-blown nightmare.
You probably already have implants.
Implants?
That's how they control you.
Make you do things
you can't remember,
make you see things
that aren't there.
(SCOFFS)
- Shall we have a look?
He has...
Let me see.
(SIGHS)
Yeah, there she is.
This one didn't take as well.
Skin's pretty irritated,
that happens sometimes.
It's a... it's a rash or a bite.
That's what they want you to think.
The Grays...
...hide what they do.
Disguise the implants
as something perfectly normal.
Most people don't even
know they have them.
Well, can we remove it?
No.
No. Believe me, I've tried.
Oh, my God.
Every time I think I'm getting it,
it seems to burrow in deeper.
(PANTING)
We'll move. Pack everything
in the car and just drive away.
These beings almost certainly
came millions of light-years
to get here.
Do you really think
moving to the next town
or checking into a motel
will stop them from finding you?
The events you've been experiencing,
the disturbances in your home,
the blackouts,
the marks on your bodies...
...they are not the beginning
of something, Daniel.
They are the end of something.
It's like a countdown.
The Grays will watch a family
for a long time
before they reveal themselves.
But once they do, it means they're
getting ready to take someone.
What are you talking about?
This is important.
Which member of your family did
the Grays first make contact with?
DANIEL:
My youngest son, Sam.
POLLARD:
Then Sam is in the most danger.
The Grays almost always abduct
the first family member
they showed an interest in.
So that's it?
- We just wait until they take our son?
- No.
You fight them
with everything you've got.
Your only hope is
to make it so difficult for them,
that they simply move on
to someone else.
Wait-wait-wait-wait, I'm sor...
That can work?
It has before, in some cases.
Yes. I've even heard of cases
where someone who's been taken
has eventually returned,
but you can't count on it.
Everything the Grays do is intended
to divide us from one another,
to isolate the one they've chosen.
Your greatest defense against them
is if your family is unified.
But you have to act quickly.
There isn't much time.
(EXHALING)
Protect your family, Mr. Barrett.
We'll go to the police.
We'll show them the surveillance video.
And say what, "We think aliens
have come into our house,
implanted some probes we can't see"?
The police will think we're crazy, Lace.
- Hell, I think we're crazy.
- They have to believe us.
- It's the truth!
- You realize what will happen
if we do that?
They won't just not believe us.
They'll take Jesse and Sam.
They'll say we're unfit to be parents.
Everybody's already suspicious.
We have to do something.
You heard what he said!
This only goes one way!
(SOBBING)
(REGISTER DINGS)
- I mean, you've got your Remington .17,
uh, your Ruger .204...
...uh, then there's
a Winchester .243 A-Bolt,
if you're looking to go
with a higher caliber. Uh...
I need something that packs
a lot of punch at close range.
What kind of hunting
you say you're doing?
- Mom, what's going on?
(DOGS BARKING)
Why are we getting a dog?
I thought Dad was allergic.
Dad can take medicine, and dogs
are good to have around the house.
- It's for protection, isn't it?
- We'll talk about it later.
- I want to talk about it now.
- What about this one?
(AGGRESSIVE BARKING)
Yeah.
(DRILL WHIRRING)
- Hey, pal.
- You're boarding up the windows?
We're keeping out the Sandman.
- Where's the dog?
- In a room in back with Mom.
We got a dog?
You want to give me a hand?
I could use some help.
No. This is bullshit!
(DOOR OPENING, CLOSING)
- Hey, Jesse, come on.
Jesse, stop!
- Let's talk about it.
- Talk about what?
How you beat up my best friend?
How everyone thinks we're freaks?
You've ruined everything.
Come... come inside.
Let me explain.
There's nothing to explain.
You can't keep treating me
like a little kid.
You can lie to Sammy,
but you can't lie to me.
Jesse!
I hear your dad's boarding up
all the windows.
What's he trying to keep out?
I think I know, but...
...if I told you, you'd probably
think I'm crazy like him.
Look, I've known your dad
since I was four.
And he's always been
totally weird, but...
...I don't think he's crazy.
(PANTING)
If the Sandman comes
to talk to you tonight,
I want you to promise me
you won't listen to him
or do anything that he says, all right?
- I promise.
- OK.
Maybe if I just gave him my eyes,
he would leave us alone.
No, baby, you can't.
The Sandman is never satisfied.
So we can't give him anything.
That's the only way
we can make him go away.
JESSE:
Something's coming, isn't it?
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Tonight?
Maybe.
I don't know.
But we've got to be prepared.
Do you think it's gonna hurt us?
That's what your mom and I are
gonna make sure doesn't happen.
Why don't you just call the police?
They wouldn't understand.
It's up to us.
(FIRECRACKERS POPPING)
(KIDS CHATTERING)
Look, whatever happens tonight...
...don't let your brother
out of your sight, OK?
I won't.
(KIDS LAUGHING,
CHATTERING DOWN STREET)
(FIREWORKS CRACKLE OUTSIDE)
(FIREWORKS CRACKLE LOUDLY)
(PLAYFUL CHATTER IN DISTANCE)
Do you guys want to watch fireworks?
How? We're stuck inside.
We can watch them on TV.
MAN ON TV: ...savory beef
grilled to perfection.
And with just the right
of Mr. Sunshine...
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING OVER TV)
(WHINES)
Sammy, do you remember
your first big Fourth of July,
when we went up to visit Aunt Maureen
and Uncle John in San Francisco?
When we went on the boat?
That's right, Uncle John's boat.
And do you remember
what you said the fireworks looked like?
Ice cream?
(CHUCKLES)
- That's right.
Ice cream.
What about you, Jess? You remember
your first big Fourth of July?
We were at the old house.
And you and Mom woke me up.
And you put me on your shoulders,
and you carried me
to the top of White's Hill.
And do you remember
what you said when we got there?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- I said I wanted to go home.
(LAUGHTER)
Yeah.
I carried you all the way up there
to see your first big fireworks,
and you couldn't care less.
(ELECTRONIC HUMMING,
STATIC OVER TV)
(GROWLING, BARKING)
(WOOD GROANING)
(ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
Lacy, take the boys upstairs.
No. We need to stick together.
No, no. We need to stick together.
- Jesse, upstairs now.
JESSE: - Dad. Come on...
(STAMMERS)
- Jesse, now.
- Lock yourself in Jesse's room.
- Go, go, go, go!
Don't open this door
under any circumstance, OK?
- Mommy! Mommy!
- Baby, I'm going to be right out here.
- I'm going to be right outside.
- Mommy!
Come on.
(DOG CONTINUES BARKING)
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
(BARKING CONTINUES)
(HIGH-PITCHED HUMMING)
(TV TURNS ON)
(PEOPLE SINGING
"AMERICA THE BEAUTIFUL" ON TV)
(SLAMMING)
(SCREAMS)
Daniel! Daniel!
Daniel!
(DOG BARKING)
(WOOD CREAKING)
(SCREWS CLATTERING ON FLOOR)
(BANGING, SCREWS CLATTERING)
(PANTING)
(SCREWS CLATTER ON FLOOR)
Leave us alone!
(DOG BARKING, WHIMPERING)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(WOOD CREAKING)
(SCREAMING)
- Come on!
- OK.
Daniel! Daniel!
(POUNDING ON DOOR) Daniel!
Stand back! Back! Back!
(LACY SCREAMS)
- In! In!
Sammy. Sammy!
Go, go, go.
(LOUD STATIC ON TV)
(HOUSE CREAKING)
(CREAKING INTENSIFIES)
(SCREAMING)
(YELLS)
(GUNSHOTS)
SAM: Mommy!
Sammy, no!
Sam?
(DEEP ELECTRICAL HUMMING)
(REPEATED BANGING IN DISTANCE)
(BANGING GROWS LOUDER)
You were right.
I ruined everything.
No!
(GUNSHOT)
(SAM GIGGLING)
Sammy.
Sammy!
(MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY ON TV)
(WOMAN MOANING ON TV)
MAN: You've been a bad girl.
WOMAN: I guess you'd better punish me.
(MOANS)  That feels so good.
(BOTH) Watch with us, Jesse.
(SAM GIGGLING)
Sammy?
(SOFTLY) Sam...
DANIEL: Jesse!
- No!
(HORNS HONKING)
(CAT MEOWS)
DANIEL: Right. Yeah.
No, I... I know
they don't believe us,
but, Marty, you're... you're...
you're our lawyer.
I need you to at least
act like you believe us.
Yeah.
So, when's the next court date?
Uh-huh.
Hey, brought up some more toys.
(DISTANT SIREN WAILING)
(SNIFFLES)
Have you experienced
any unexplained illnesses,
strange allergies or nosebleeds?
Do you remember right after Jesse
was born and he was so sick,
and the doctors
didn't know what it was?
My, uh, oldest, Jesse, was sick
all the time when he was little.
It was like he was allergic
to the entire world.
(BEEP, RADIO STATIC)
(MUFFLED VOICE)
(RADIO STATIC CONTINUES)
(STATIC AND WHIRRING)
(TONE EMERGES FROM STATIC)
Command Control?
(RADIO STATIC)
(JESSE OVER WALKIE-TALKIE) Sam!
(DISTORTED YELLING)
JESSE: Sammy!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org