Hold this!
Faster, faster!
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Get a compress!
Gotta shut down port diesel.
It's pulled loose!
Keep full speed!
Give it everything she's got!
What's he going to do?
Southern course...
...moving toward the African coast.
Damn!
Flood tanks!
All men to bow!
Down to 90 meters.
- Bow plane jammed!
- Use manual rudder!
Bow plane stuck
in full down position!
Both engines stop.
All men aft!
Hurry! Faster!
Trim all to stern!
Ballast pump down!
Trim with air!
Still sinking.
Load unchanged.
Gotta lose weight!
Pump 1000 litres!
Shut him up, medic!
Main pump down!
Blow tanks?
All back full!
Boat not responding.
Blow tanks!
Blow front.
Stop... now.
Why don't you stop!
Give it whatever she's got, Chief!
Blow 'em all!
Come on up.
Boat is beyond control.
200.
210.
220 meters.
Beyond 230.
240 meters.
250 meters.
My God!
Do not turn...
...Thy face away from me.
A shovelful of sand.
God threw a shovelful
of sand beneath our keel.
280 meters.
This boat's amazing!
Torpedo hatch taking water!
Taking water behind control panel!
Taking water in motor bilge!
Tube 5 taking water!
What you need?
- Leakage plugs.
- In the bow.
Exhaust valve?
Leakage plugs! Move!
Give me that lamp!
I need a wrench, damn it!
Where are my reports?
Taking water... at tower frame!
Where are the tools?
- Where is it?
- Bilge pump!
Motor control panels down!
Diesel's all busted!
I demand proper reports!
Where's it worst?
Shaft valves and housing.
Machinist, battery two...
...determine damages.
Don't strip the crankshafts!
Can't see a thing!
Push... harder!
I'm pushing!
Can't get the wedge in!
Give me that hammer!
Need more men aft?
I'll find out!
- Damn it!
- Can I help?
Hold the light!
Father, don't forsake us.
Stupid asshole!
Damn idiot!
I need the diesel room toolbox.
Hurry!
Where are the tools?
Bigger wrench!
Leakage in diesel bilge!
Tighten them carefully.
Don't break the bolts.
Cooling pipe leaking!
Get down there
and tighten those valves!
Give me that timber!
More plugs... hurry!
Gently, men.
Taking water fast in stern.
All hull valves burst.
Cooling system down.
Compressors dislodged.
Shaft valves taking water.
What about fuel leaks?
Can't tell yet.
- Anything else?
- Battery cells are cracked.
They can't take this!
Acid in the bilge.
Neutralize with lime wash.
Count drained cells.
Get battery connectors, hurry!
Over here!
I need plugs and a hammer!
- Here it is.
- Thanks, Lieutenant.
Calm down.
Tell the Chief!
Taking water in motor room.
Rising above torpedo tubes!
Careful!
24 cells drained.
24 cells. Holy shit!
We're way short of connectors!
He's got to bridge those damaged cells.
Or else we've had it.
Can't tighten it. Can't see.
Lieutenant, lights!
If we don't fix this, we're goners!
To the right, more to the right!
Wire!
I need wire for bridging!
Move it, we need wire!
Hurry up!
The Chief needs wire.
Look for wire!
Move it! Search for wire!
Incredible torpedoes in these tubes!
25,000 Marks apiece.
And we can't find...
...a piece of wire.
Some old wire worth 50 pennies!
Periscope hydraulics jammed.
Can't be moved manually, either.
Wire!
Finally, something!
Pliers!
Leaks stopped.
Good, Johann.
Really good.
Now, get out of those wet rags.
Now let's get it out...
...this water's got to go!
First, into the control room bilge...
...and then out.
Faster! Let's get rid of it!
And scoop... and scoop!
Get with it.
No falling asleep back there!
3 more cells... starboard.
Where do we stand?
Almost done. 3 cells to go.
Make way for the Chief.
Entire compass system is down...
...probably the sonar, too.
Radio is totally out.
Quite a mess.
Can we surface?
Any chance at all?
Good question.
Some air may be left
in the ballast tanks...
...from all that blowing.
That might help us.
With every last bit of air pressure...
...maybe...
We've got to reduce our weight.
That water has to get out.
Might work. It just might!
Aft is almost bailed.
It could work...
...by hand into tanks...
...then with main pump...
...and air pressure,
the water's pushed out!
Main pump?
Can do.
Then we go for broke.
Blow tanks, and...
We'll get only one try.
When?
Once everything's repaired.
In 6 to 8 hours.
- CO2 content?
- 1.8 percent.
We got enough oxygen?
No.
Pass out oxygen masks as needed...
...men off duty to their bunks.
How's he doing?
Hard to tell.
Doesn't look good.
So, Pilgrim...
...all okay?
Yes, Captain.
It's all okay.
How are things aft?
Moving along, Captain.
Guess I'll show my face then, huh?
Be careful.
All right here?
Okay. Doing fine.
Sure, Captain. It'll work out.
How's it going?
Got to change two more bearings.
Do you want some glucose?
Crazy idea...
...to ram us through this strait.
It was bound to go wrong.
He knew it.
That old fox knew it all along.
Since he got that radiogram...
...ordering us to break through.
That's why he wanted us off the boat...
...in Vigo.
There was no chance to get through.
He wanted to make us believe
it was possible...
...with a simple trick.
"Drop down and glide through"...
Not a bad trick...
...except that it had to work.
Will we ever surface, Chief?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Is it hopeless?
It's been 15 hours.
He's not going to pull it off.
I'm sorry.
I asked for it.
"To be heading into the inexorable...
...where no mother will care for us...
...no woman crosses our path...
...where only reality reigns...
with cruelty and grandeur."
I was drunk with those words.
Well, this is reality.
Reporting to the Captain.
Electric motor fixed.
Main pump fixed.
Water can be pumped into tanks...
...then blown out with compressed air.
Compass ready.
Sonar ready.
Good, Chief.
Take a rest now.
Still got a few small problems.
All you need is good people.
Good people.
Listen up.
We're going to blow tanks now...
...to see if we can lift our butt.
If we do...
...it might get uncomfortable again.
Lots of traffic up there.
So, all we can do...
...is pray those diesels start up.
Then full speed ahead and off we go...
...out of this crater...
...and back home.
If it works...
...half a bottle of beer for everyone!
We just might get lucky.
They're not expecting us.
Well, men...
...are we ready?
Contact bearings?
No contact.
Prepare to surface,
rescue gear ready.
Switch to red lights.
Man your diving stations.
Blow tanks.
Boat rising!
Quiet men! Calm down!
270 meters.
First watch, get ready.
260 meters.
250 meters.
240 meters.
230 meters.
220.
Hatch is open.
How about the engines?
Both diesels.
Now everything hinges on this.
I think...
...it's running!
Who says you can't make something
out of nothing?
They won't get us this time!
Not again!
Hang in there, damn it!
Hang in there!
3 degrees to starboard.
Course 320 degrees.
There he goes again!
They don't notice us.
They're all asleep in their bunks.
No, you know what?
They're at the casino,
celebrating our sinking!
Cheers, guys!
Here's to getting home!
As long as the diesels hold up...
...and with a little bit of luck...
...we'll make it home.
The 3rd Submarine Flotilla welcomes
our returning sailors.
All engines stop.
Let go aft line.
- Thanks, Hinrich.
- Don't mention it.
The sun's shining.
Lift it!
All right? Almost there.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/45zre
Help other users to choose the best subtitles