Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I'm in.
Alright ladies, twenty dollars.
What ya got Phil, are you in or not?
- I'm out.
Let me guess.
Raise?
Well, I wasn't going to, but now that you put
the idea in my head, sure, why not?
I've seen that look before. I'm out.
You don't wanna do that?
- I think you're bluffin'.
That's an awful lot.
- Could be.
It could also be that the cards in my hand
plus the cards already showing
give me an 86 percent chance of winning.
You know what, Tory,
you've got a 14 percent window to lose.
You're so full of shit.
- Am I?
This is so much fun, gentlemen. I fold.
- So what's next?
Shit, I didn't even need it.
Every single time.
One more round?
- I gotta go.
This sucks.
- What sucks?
This!
College is half over, no fun.
Alex's room.
- I'm not here, Buddy.
No, this is Ben, who's this?
Yeah, just a second.
Dude, it's Melissa.
What?
She says she's calling you back for like two weeks going.
I can't talk now.
Tell her I'm not there.
You can't? You've got the biggest
crush on this girl for the past six months.
You're gonna talk to her now.
Melissa, Hi.
No, I'm in the middle of something right now.
Can I call you back?... Right.
Who are you?
- I know.
What happens if he wins?
- Alex plays in a Poker
Stars tournament on TV.
What if he doesn't?
- He's making photocopies for a law firm.
Guys please, I've been up all night.
What do you need?
- A pair of ladies.
Hey, guys.
We're so proud of you.
- Definitely.
Magna cum laude, not bad.
But suma cum laude would have landed you
a full scholarship for law school.
Hello everyone, Mr. and Mrs. S.
- Hi, Ben.
How are you, son?
Where are all the girls wanted it?
Open your eyes kid.
You've haven't said anything?
- No.
Said what about what?
Alex?
I put in for a tournament.
- Sweet!
I got him.
- It's only for a couple days.
You promised it was just a hobby.
- It won't get out of hand.
'Get out of hand'.
Come on, I beat out hundreds of people.
I stuck my neck out to get you that job.
- And I'll still be there.
This is a big deal.
Thanks for being here with us at PokerStars.com,
a ten million dollar
I'm Greg 'Fossilman' Raymer
and working with me is Joseph Hachem.
So Greg, what've you got today?
- Well Joe, in case any of our players don't show up today...
I'm ready to jump in anytime they want.
These are our players.
Antonio 'Magician' Esfandiara.
The 'Unabomber' Phil Laak.
Tex Button, and of course the
very famous, Karen 'Razor' Jones.
Do you want a drink?
- No, no, I'm fine.
We will see if
to our newcomers.
You want to give me a hand in here?
Player's on third,
be right in.
Each player first are dealt two down cards.
And then they bet a round.
Then come the community
cards with the flop, the turn, and the river.
In the end the best five card combination
wins the hand and takes the pot.
Let's take a closer look at
one of their newest challengers.
I guess you could say I've
always been good with numbers.
Note that Alex Stillman, just 21 years old,
born and raised in Los Angeles,
learned to play poker
in just the last three years.
And when this whiz kid went
off to college in the east,
he realized that there might be a
little bit more to his poker hand.
Good luck all.
4,000.
You have to bet, Karen?
Too steep for me.
- Alex, who had by far the most chips...
but he has already lost the most
since the start of play.
Let but see then.
Have fun.
- Looks like I've scared everyone out.
10,000.
He may run into problems.
- Not really.
If you don't know how well the cards
of Razor, it's top pair.
He likes his hand.
Alright, I call.
It's all up to you.
Ten of clubs.
Interesting.
I'm all in.
- Should you see.
Hey, you're gonna wish
you'd paid more attention.
I tripped up
Razor keeps pace.
Once see what the river.
I think Alex
will be very disappointed.
Thus feels zero percent now.
You didn't get a card when you needed it,
but you were already reports.
See you around.
Go back to school.
He was lucky that he came extent.
Hopefully he learned
for the next time.
Alex, when you get a moment, I need you to get
Mr. Wallace the briefs for the Longhorn case.
By the way, today is pay day,
but they don't give you your first check
until the end of the next pay period.
Do you think you can make it two more weeks?
- I think I can manage.
OK, Good.
- OK
Oh, and Alex, be careful. That sorter
is almost at capacity.
Find anything better?
There's one cruise left
that leaves in July.
We can afford a third class cabin,
but that's about it.
We do get a lobster night right now
Really, lobster.
Why don't we go first class?
Oh, come on.
Honey,
what's the matter?
That's a lot of the money and we have to
make it last our whole lives.
Alright, for 400 dollars.
I even go to the casino.
You don't have to gamble,
I'll gonna go with you.
Oh, wait a minute.
- I just go to see it.
And what about Helen?
- I just saw Helen, she's doing fine.
You go watch your pledge.
- Not true. I look only.
That may not be a problem.
- I ain't takin' the rap for you.
As if you play against a baby.
- Of a baby who plays himself?
I understand him. I'm still young.
That's really funny.
To bad there's no minimum age
for making money.
Ok, that was fun.
But I must go,
otherwise I come home too late.
Pocket money for the next month.
Get that out for me.
You need to do this professionally.
Nice playin' in there.
- Thank you. That's nice.
What do you think, Tommy?
I think he could have done a lot better.
Are you talking about me?
If I saw you bluffing,
everybody at the table saw you bluffing.
What are you talking about, I flopped a set.
- You missed the flush.
Maybe you need to get your eyes checked.
- Maybe.
Listen, you have a lot of potential,
so if you ever want to talk about strategy...
I think he's ok.
You could do a whole lot worse.
Okay then.
Tommy Vinson.
What he was talking about?
- He is determined drunk.
Did you really flop a set?
No, I missed my flush.
I knew that you would show up.
No, I came to play cards.
No, just give me five minutes.
See that guy with the red hat?
What about him?
- What kind of hand has he got?
Good or bad?
Good.
- Wrong.
You know how I know?
- How?
When he has bad cards,
he scratches to his face.
He does this every time.
It's a tell. Watch.
In that way.
You were just lucky.
Pick somebody. Anybody.
That guy over there.
He has a good hand.
Ace-King maybe,
or an Ace-Queen.
You should be playing against them.
I don't play.
Can you give me that napkin please?
Nice accent. Is it German?
No, Russian.
Then you drink a lot of vodka then.
I hope you're better with cards
than you are with women.
Really I am. You know I won $22,000
in PokerStars last month?
The Razor, she's just so...
She ate you up.
- You saw it?
I had really bad cards.
It's not on the cards.
You don't play against cards,
you play against players.
What do you have in mind?
Million dollar pay outs.
I cover the buy-ins and we split
50-50 right down the middle.
Cash?
- Not yet, first you gotta win.
But you gotta listen to me,
every word.
Why should I do that?
Because by the time you're twenty-five,
you'll be set for life.
You set for life?
I could have been,
if I'd had someone to listen too.
You found it.
Nice house.
Would you like something cold to drink?
A coke, soft drink, beer?
Beer.
Is that you?
- Yes. Not to believe, eh?
The poker finale of 1979 in Reno.
What's this?
My wife put that up there.
That's the hand I was dealt
when I beat Doyle Bronson.
Oh, My God.
You beat Doyle Brunson
in the World Championship?
They didn't call it that back then.
Shit.
It was just called 'the game'.
Now it's for huge pots,
diamond bracelets.
You never won a Championship?
I was in the top ten.
It was great.
For five years I was the best there was.
And then I...
I lost my confidence.
You lose a lot of games...
you borrow a lot of money...
from friends...
family.
You keep on playing...
and you hate the world.
I mean... I lost everything.
I almost lost my wife.
She told me that if I'd quit...
well... she'd stay.
I quit and I haven't...
haven't picked up any cards in 20 years.
20 years?
You haven't played poker in 20 years?
Not even at home.
Do you miss it?
Not as much as I'd miss her.
If I...
If we are going to do,
should we sign something?
Will we see each other differently
just trust?
Are you sure your wife's not
going to come home and kill us?
- Don't worry.
She won't be home until tomorrow.
Concentrate.
Gus Hansen.
What's he doin'?
I don't know.
He's playing too fast.
He  shuffles the cards.
He knows what he has.
These guys know exactly what they have.
A false tell.
Alright, I think I got it.
Let's go try it out with the University guys.
Come on.
We've been through a 100 games.
You think you're ready?
- Tommy, please.
You want me to do this, the only way
I'm going to learn is making bets.
The casino is just 20 minutes away.
If we're gonna do this,
let's do it right.
Look who we have there.
God, it's been a long time.
How you doin', Barry?
- That your kid?
That's my kid.
- Well, have a seat.
Yo, son.
Are you sure you handle this?
We'll see.
I raise.
Call.
500.
I fold.
I raise with five.
- I fold.
I call.
Give me something good.
All in.
I'm all in.
I fold.
This is a little different than
playing on the Internet, huh son?
What'd ya say we take a break?
- I just got bad cards. They did.
Come on, Tom, let ATM stay.
- Yeah.
You bite your lower lip.
- What are you talking about?
Every time you get a bad hand,
you bite your lower lip.
No I don't.
- We continue.
Wait. Come, stay well.
- If I see it, everybody at the table sees it.
I'm here to learn.
Give me one more chance.
I'm all in.
Well then, cash.
What'd you think I otta buy?
A BMW?
Or a Vet?
I like BMW myself.
The kid has a straight.
It was OK?
- Yeah, it went good.
Yeah, I did.
You like the lip?
These guys have long memories.
Next time, don't try the same thing.
When was the last time you had any?
When was your last time?
- I'm doin' fine in that department, thank you.
Yeah.
Why do you care, anyway?
A young guy,
testosterone popping out every pore.
It seems like you should give it a run.
I just want you to be happy.
- I don't know. I'm...
for whatever reason
I've gone out with a girl, I...
I just wish they'd come up to me,
it's be a whole lot easier.
You know, some of these skills you
learn at the tables, people skills...
watching, observing, listening...
they come in handy
if you just apply them in other areas.
Like that tall drink of water over there.
Just go over to her
and say hello.
Everything will be fine.
Trust me.
I will do that.
Hi... I'm sorry, I don't normally do this, but...
- I'm a Virgo...
and before you ask,
no, I don't come here often.
I've never done that before.
The reason that I'm here...
see that old man behind me?
He thinks that I'm terrible with girls,
and that's probably true.
Would you even can giggle?
- I don't think so.
What should I do
so you could help me out here?
Tell me why you're so
terrible with women.
I... I don't know, uh...
probability?
I wasn't expecting that one.
- What I mean is...
Asking a girl out is very
simply a 50-50 proposition.
She either says yes or she says no.
I don't like to do anything where you only
have a 50 percent chance of succeeding.
Well, if 50 percent odds are not enough for you,
then you my friend are in the town.
No, that's not true.
Take poker for example.
In poker if you have bad
cards, it doesn't matter,
you still have the option of bluffing.
And you don't think
that applies to women too?
Good luck, honey.
Bye
Alright, let's start over.
Ask me out.
You see I don't even know your name.
- Michelle.
Hi, I'm Alex.
Would you like to go out
with me sometime?
I don't know Alex,
what do you do?
I just graduated college and I'm
working part time at a law firm.
No, thanks.
No, wait, wait, I make... I make unlimited
CEO for a Fortune 500 company,
we're in software development,
and I travel all over the whole world to exotic
countries which maybe you'd love to go?
Really?
So, I would love to go out with you.
Seven-two.
Could you just spot me a couple?
- I never do. It's all or nothing with me.
Of course you do.
I hope you're better at cards
than you are at air hockey.
- You know what?
This time I'm gonna win.
- Let's go.
Oh my god, are you OK?
Yeah.
What if I'm not?
Well I...
I'm fine.
- The bounce.
The bounce.
Good trip, huh?
Definitely.
You like that girl?
You have a good time last night?
And this morning.
You're a machine.
- Oh, I wouldn't say that.
You have to focus from now on.
I'm focused. We're going to make all the way.
- All the way.
To hear me.
Friday night there's a tournament
in New Orleans.
Next Friday?
- Yes. Is that a problem?
No, not a problem.
Hey Dad, a friend of mine
wants to go to Santa Barbara,
I was wondering if I could take a day?
I know, I know.  This is the last time.
I swear.
Thanks. Bye.
Bad news, baby,
I gotta to Cleveland.
I should be back by Monday.
I'll call you later this evening.
Well done. We are going to rest.
Tomorrow is a big day.
Rest? I've won.
Let us go a little drink, or something.
So far so good.
That's all you got to say?
Just calm down.
Maybe you'll feel better tomorrow
when I win $600,000.
What about Helen!
Do not answer the phone.
Why?
- Because...
Your opponents tomorrow
want to keep you up
Maybe it's important.
- Don't open the door,
I'm telling you for your own good.
What if it's important.
Hi, I'm Shaniqua
and this is my friend Alley.
I told you.
You can can beat everyone at this table,
with or without sleep.
Rough cards.
- False.
You know it's not the cards
and so do I.
There isn't anything I could do.
You're tired.
You're right back to your old bad habits.
You're in love with your money.
I can tell what everyone has.
- No, you can't.
Then why don't you go and play?
- Because I promised somebody I wouldn't.
You call lying to your wife a promise?
You'd better go home.
What's going on, Honey?
What?
Where were you, in Las Vegas?
Well, went to New Orleans.
-New Orleans?
Yeah, for a tournament.
- I knew it.
I'm not playing any cards at all.
I'm just teaching a kid...
How much did you lose?
-$10,000.
$10,000?
-Yeah.
Tommy.
- But in Vegas...
When were you in Vegas?
I want you to understand though,
we were in Vegas...
- I'm goin' to my sisters.
Hi, Michelle, it's me.
Can you call me back?
Three messages, and she won't call me back.
- Will you stop worrying about her.
Let's think of winning.
- What's first place, anyway?
$500,000.
Guess who?
- How many guesses do I get?
One. Did you have fun the other night?
- Oh my god, you're here.
How's it going so far?
- Really good, but it just got a whole lot better.
It's nice to see you again.
Yeah, you too.
Do you want some?
- No, thanks.
What?
Nothing.
There's just something about you.
You're a nice guy.
Is there something wrong?
I wish...
- What?
I wish I'd met you under
different circumstances.
What do you mean?
You know.
You live in LA, I live in Vegas.
So? That's only 300 miles away.
4.5 hours by car, one hour by plane.
Where are you going?
Well, my father's in town.
I've got to go.
And I need to rest.
- You can sleep here.
I'll call you later, okay?
Good luck tomorrow.
Is she there?
- Yeah, I'll call her, hold on.
How's it going?
Where are you?
- I'm in...
I'm in Vegas with that kid,
Alex.
The World Poker Tour Championship.
It starts in about two weeks.
I need to get him in shape
and then get him out of here.
Listen, this is it.
If it's over, then it's all over.
I never thought we'd have
this conversation again.
Listen, we got our money back,
all the money, a lot and some interest.
That's not the point.
- What do you mean it's not
the point, it is the point.
Goodbye, Tommy.
Sorry about those last few hands.
- You'll do fine.
And we made some money.
- And what we have earned.
A little money, come on.
60 grand each.
Well, minus expenses.
Bellagio.
Hold on.
Michelle.
Hey.
- Hi.
Is this your dad?
- Yeah, I'm her daddy.
At least for tonight.
Wait. What?
Go find you own girl.
Do you feel bad for me or something?
Look, you don't understand that at this point...
- Did anyone pay you?
It's Tommy.
I'm sorry about the girl.
It was a dumb idea.
Hello.
Hi, what are you doing?
Listen to me, I know this seems
like a hell of a lot of money.
When you think about it,
it's nothing compared to what we could do.
Don't walk away
over some girl.
Don't you mean a hooker?
I just thought I'd help.
- By fucking with my feelings?
Alex, listen.
- I'm done, we're through. It's over
Helping people is more than that.
Yeah...
Maybe you're right.
I'm home.
Jordy, let us alone.
- Just one more second.
Jordan.
I'll hear everything.
Where were you this weekend?
I told you, I was with Ben.
Alright, I was in Vegas...
Look, I came in third.
Alex, I didn't spend the last 20 years
of my life working my ass off
so you could play cards for a living!
- I had a partial scholarship.
And who do you think paid
the other half?
Ok fine.
Here. Here's the other half.
You won that?
- $62,000.
And in two weeks is the big one,
like eight million dollars.
Alex, listen to me.
You have a job.
Not anymore.
I'm quitting.
Oh, Alex... now...
Hello, this is Helen.
Please leave a message and I'll
get back to you as soon as possible.
In Las Vegas,
written history.
There will a battle
for the game's ultimate title.
It's for the 15 million dollar WPC Championship
here on the World Poker Tour.
Hi everyone, welcome to the
biggest week of the poker year,
the WPC World Championship.
I'm Mike Sexton along
with Vince Van Patten.
And Vince, this is going to
be an amazing week for poker.
Mike, we have five
exciting days of poker ahead of us.
Each player has to put up a $25,000 each
and the winner is gonna take home
over eight million dollars.
And what's really exciting about this,
is that everyone is playing today.
All superstars in the game
are playing this match.
Yeah, you're right Vince,
all the greats are here.
Razor Jones, Doyle Brunson,
Gus Hansen, Phil Ivey...
Daniel Negraneu, Mike 'Double
Diamond' Jackson, Tex Button...
and a rookie who's been making big noise
and just played his first WPC event
earlier this season... Alex Stillman.
Alex is a great player, he's a young a rookie.
They're all talking about him.
He finished tenth at a tournament
in New Orleans a couple weeks ago,
so everybody's talking about him.
But there is another great story,
and that is a fantastic player that is back.
A big comeback for the phenomenal
Tommy Vinson.
What a great moment this must be.
Tommy supposedly taught
one of our young entries,
Alex Stillman, a thing
or two about the game.
And Tommy hasn't played any
tournament poker in over 20 years.
I can tell you, that's a long time to
be away from poker at this level.
Doyle and Tommy bring a lot of
history to this tournament.
Should be a lot of fun.
If you ready participate in this rodeo?
It's gonna be a rough one now.
That's what I thought easy to go
home and take up playin' bridge,
you're gonna lose your ass
What you holdin' Tommy?
You want any of these chips?
You're all  goin' down.
Thank you.
- Nah, don't even mention it.
I can't believe that he is playing again, Johnny.
- I know.
Why now?
Is it me?
Oh, no.
What can possibly be in the cards now?
Dignity, respect.
He just wants to hit a home run.
Before the sun sets.
With you.
He wants the title that he never had.
Something that no one
can ever take away from him.
I'm all in.
I'm all in too.
Damn it. Well done, Tommy.
- Take care of yourself.
Ok...
Hi.
-Hi.
Can I come in?
How'd you find me?
- I've got my ways.
So, listen.
- No, you listen.
I love you.
And I know that you needed to do
this more than I needed you not to.
Therefore, I ask only one thing of you.
When you make it to the final table... win.
Win it all.
100,000.
- I raise to 200.
500,000.
- I'm all in.
I'm all in.
- Me too.
It's crunch time,
there's only nine people remaining.
400,000.
- But only six make it to the final table.
The pressure is mounting,
they're looking for the big money.
Two million.
- I'm out.
- We have already done.
What do you have? An Ace high?
I'm in.
I'll call.
I'm gone.
Nice hand, Tommy.
- And they call me a magician.
Tommy Vinson has knocked out
the 'Unabomber'.
500.
I raise to 1.5.
I'm all in.
Call.
If Razor gets a Jack,
an Ace or a spade she'll cripple Alex
and put him on the working trips.
Here we go with the river.
It's a three.
I could read you like a book.
Seven players left.
We're down to the wire.
Who's goin' home and
who will fulfill their dream?
200,000.
You got something?
Okay then.
I'd like to raise.
700,000.
All in.
- Tommy goes all in.
The 'Magician' really has an
important decision to make now.
You're sure about this?
- Oh, yeah.
I can't fold.
Well, I call.
- Antonio calls with the pocket Jacks.
Almost 50-50.
- Here comes the flop.
Keep it small.
Small.
No Ace, no King, please.
He gets his Ace on the river, Vince.
Nice hand, Tommy.
Good luck, guys.
Do good with my chips.
- I'll do my best.
And Antonio the 'Magician' disappears.
Abracadabra.
That's it. We are down to six.
We'll see you tomorrow at the final table.
Crazy, huh?
Look there. Alex.
Oh, my god. What are you doing here?
- Ben told us where to go.
This is great.
- We wanted to come.
Book a room.
I've checked us in.
Give me two seconds, ok. I need to do something.
Say that you're my parents.
Do you want some more?
- No.
Excuse me, Mr. Vinson.
There's a phone call for you at the Bar.
Hello.
Looks like you're doing pretty
well in the tournament.
I could say the same for you.
The final table.
Life is full of surprises.
Yes, that's right.
I just wanted to wish
you good luck tomorrow.
Good luck to you too, pal.
Second place is not bad
for someone of your age.
And you're not bad for a guy your age either.
My wife is here.
I've got just one thing I want to say.
I know your tell.
See you tomorrow.
Hello everyone. We are coming to you live
from the Bellagio in Las Vegas,
where have the largest prize pool in the
history of World Poker
Tour will be given out.
We've had a record number
of players entered in this years event,
but only six still have dreams
of capturing this coveted title
and taking home over
eight million dollars.
Mike, this is gonna be great.
Big money here this week and
let me tell you something,
all the big names in the game are here,
all of the Superstars players.
But they are gone,
we have dead men walking.
Let's go down to our finalists.
And what a final table.
We have the cowboy.
Yes, hear. Back in the saddle.
Wipe the dirt out of your hair,
because Tex Button's here..
Then the only lady in the final table,
She was WPC ladies champion,
from Montreal, Canada, Isabelle Mercier.
That's right. Oui, oui. And now
the youngest player at the table.
He is only 21 years old and
he looks like he just left a concert.
The very talented Alex Stillman.
The next player has already won titles in his day,
but not for any amount anything like tonight.
I'm talking about the man, the myth,
the 'Double Diamond', Mike Jackson.
And now a professional player who's made
many final tables in his day.
From Los Angeles, California, Scott 'Laser' Lazar.
What a player he is.
Now rounding out the field,
a very captivating story,
We have an old school
poker player who is for
the first time ever on the
World Poker Tour final table.
In fact, this man has not picked
up a card in over 20 years.
The very talented,
Tommy Vinson.
We have everything tonight,
men against women,
old school versus new school.
This is gonna be great.
- The cards are ready.
There's a millionaire among them.
Let's go down to the table.
Coming into todays final,
Tex Button is our chips leader,
with 12 million in chips.
An then, in second
place is the youngster,
the new kid on the block, Alex Stillman,
he's got about 10 million in chips.
And in the third place Mike 'Double Diamond'
Jackson with about 9.3 million.
600,000.
I'm out.
Call.
Check.
Another 600,000.
- Tex has just a pair of nines.
He bets another 600,000.
Call.
Tommy makes a flush draw hand.
- Check.
Check.
Tommy has made a flush
but Tex has made three nines
This can be a problem for Tex.
- Two million.
Ok, I call.
Tex keeps pace.
- What a disaster.
Tex looks like a chuck wagon
just ran over him.
Nice hand, Tommy.
Tommy Vinson becomes the chip leader,
well over five million.
Heart. Heart. Heart.
I'm in.
Give me a diamond Queen.
Give me something please.
Good luck.
I'm all in.
- Call.
This is our first loser. Tex Button.
He began with the largest number of chips,
and he is sixth.
Tommy Vinson has flopped three fours.
A fantastic flop.
Isabelle needed a ten,
and she did not get it. She is gone.
She ends on the fifth place
but she won $585,000.
Tommy is such a legend.
And to see him come back after 20 years
and to make the final table is
phenomenal and he's playing so well,
I think he's got a chance
to take this tournament.
Let's cross our fingers for Tommy.
Back to the game.
Call.
Mike 'Double Diamond' Jackson
out of this tournament in fourth tonight.
But he will taking home $878,000 winnings.
We're gonna take a short break.
We are down to three.
Stay tuned. We'll be right back with
more of the World Poker Tour.
Well baby, it's crunch time
and it's come down to this.
The third place winner will
take home 2.2 million dollars.
The runner up tonight will
win a meager 4.1 million.
And our champion tonight
capture a WPT championship title
as well as take home just
over eight million dollars.
Scott looks at his cards.
And he has a pair of Queens in the hole.
8.2 million.
Alex and Tommy have both identical hands,
Jack-King. This should be good.
Call.
Here comes the flop.
Oh, look at this. Nine, Ten, Queen.
Alex and Tommy have flopped
a nuts King high straight,
but 'Laser' Lazar has a flop,
so we're going to see fireworks here.
- A disaster for either one of these guys.
Three million.
- Lazar is committed.
Look at that.
Once here to see how Alex deals.
I'm all in.
- He's going all in, puts it over the top.
All in.
- Tommy's going all in as well.
I call.
- The showdown of the tournament.
Alex and Tommy will share the pot
unless Lazar pairs the board on the river.
Otherwise he is out and he is third.
Here comes the turn.
The five of clubs, no help for Lazar.
- Irrelevant.
No help for anybody.
It's a three.
That's going to do it for Scotty Lazar.
He is out in third place..
Incredibly then, the youngster
and the elder statesman
are gonna play heads up for the
title and the eight million bucks.
Great, but Scotty Lazar
has performed well.
He is out at three,
but he wins 2.2 million dollars.
It's tradition on the World Poker Tour,
we get down to heads up play,
we bring the trophy and
the cash out to the table.
I tell you what, this is
going to be a great story.
I mean, we have the youngest player,
21 years old, Alex Stillman.
What's so beautiful is that he was mentored
by the oldster, Tommy Vinson.
And now, they'll go up against each other
for the WPT World Championship.
So, the incredible match
of a teacher versus the pupil,
coming down to the title
and eight million bucks.
Well, the price of poker is going up now.
The opening is now with a $50,000 ante.
Blinds are 250 and 500 thousand dollars.
Action at the Bellagio.
Buckle up ladies and gentlemen.
Raise.
- Here we go.  Look at the action on hand number one.
Alex has the worst
starting hand possible,
but he's raising the pot,
trying to steal the first hand.
This is beautiful. He tries pull off a Winona.
He has absolutely zip in his hand.
Tommy knows he has nothing but junk,
but my god, I think he's gonna fold anyway.
I fold.
- You're right. Tommy does fold.
So Alex takes pot number one.
Raise to two million.
That's a two million dollar bet
and the kid is bettin' with a six and a four.
He thinks Tommy
bad cards.
I think you're right.
It looks like Alex has got it all figured out.
Unless Tommy changes
things around quickly,
his Championship hopes are dwindling.
One million.
- Look at this man go.
Tommy has bet a million dollars
without looking at his cards.
I've never seen anything like this.
This is a first on the World Poker Tour.
He's totally in the blind.
Is it gonna work or not?
Call.
Here comes the flop.
Check.
All in.
- Do you see this? Eight million on the line
and Tommy goes it all in
without looking at his cards.
Fold.
- Look, it's placing them on the table.
Alex folded, so the strategy
by Tommy has worked.
I don't believe this.
I bet one million.
Call.
- Here we go again.
Blind man's bluff.
Check.
I'll bet another million.
Call.
All in.
Absolutely incredible.
The question is, how long can he keep
playing those cards in the dark.
You can only so far sliding on barbed wire.
Now he looks finally looks at his cards.
- Yes, and he's got two jacks.
Let's see what he's gonna do now.
Does he push harder?
Check.
-2.5 Million.
I didn't quite see Alex's cards
when he bet the 2.5 million.
Tommy's got to love his hand,
will he be aggressive and go over the top?
Well, we shall see.
Call.
- He's just calling. That's some playing.
Okay, we're gonna see the flop,
here it is.
That's a dangerous flop right there.
Of course we don't know
what Alex has on his plate.
Check.
Here's the turn card.
They stare at each other.
Alex checks again.
- Yes, and now the river, Mike.
We have two pair on the board,
four's and three's and an Ace.
Very interesting,
but danger everywhere.
All in.
- This is it. Tommy Vinson has gone all in.
Now if Alex should call, and he's wrong,
Tommy Vinson will become our new Champion.
Call.
- And he's called!
Alex is gonna need a three,
a four, a pair of Queens...
a pair of Kings or an Ace to win this pot.
Tommy shows his Jacks.
Nice hand, Tommy.
That's it. Tommy Vinson,
after a 20 years hiatis...
has come back and captured the
World Poker Tour Championship title,
and has won 8.2 million dollars.
Vince, what a story.
The teacher teaches the students a lesson.
We will talk with the Champion.
You were top. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
You were great.
A second place finish is not bad, right.
- Are you crazy? Four million dollars.
I know.
- Easy to pay for law school
If you want to. Good job.
Thank you.
Let's drink to the new
WPC World Champion, Tommy Vinson.
Thanks for watching.
Until the next season.
May all your pots be enormous.
Wonderful. Thank you.
Not quite even.
Do you mind?
Great playing.
- Me? And what about you?
I got lucky with the cards.
I guess I should thank you.
Why?
You're a natural.
No, not about the cards.
You see that girl in there?
Sorry you didn't win.
I will, someday.
I bet you will.
I gotta go.
- Will I see you back next month?
Not a chance.
I'm going to Hawaii
first class.
This was so real.
You're ready.
I might come back in about
25 or 30 years.
Did you have a pair in your hands?
Nines? Tens?
Tens.
I knew it.
Goodbye, Tommy.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org