Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Occurs in the back of the machine
something horrible ?
Slowly. Repeat yet.
What is he talking about?
That the machine is on fire.
Warned the passengers?
I guess you did do.
People jumping out of the panic.
- It should fly business class.
That's right, go help
people with parachutes.
He has a vivid imagination.
Why did he tell crazy stories?
- He's trying to get your attention.
He said Juanita : " The washing machine
a cat. " Juanita was getting freaked.
We do not have a cat. - The economy -
the nurse must be kept alive.
What else to do in Sodom and
Gomorrah is in addition to the museums ?
Let's Melissa stripparikerhoon. and
he could smoke my first joint here.
I am just joking.
- Not funny.
Amsterdam is a mess.
I read about it and saw on TV.
The fault is 60 minutes.
Drugs on every corner.
Whores the window.
Amsterdam is a beautiful and
tolerant. Kids will love the place.
Why do not we have gone
Rome or Paris?
We have gone there. you wanted to
spend some time with Melissa.
I just want to be his best.
- As.
There has been great.
Showing him the night watch.
Let's go for a boat ride on the canals.
You will never forget this holiday.
The time now is 16:35 local time.
It is quite chilly 18 degrees.
It's cloudy
and rain is expected.
Royal Atlantic to welcome you
welcome to come again.
Are you interested in the drugs?
I'm at work in the pharmaceutical sector.
I do not think anything illegal ?
- I do not smuggle drugs.
Tranquilizers. Can I get you ?
- Are you trying to bribe me ?
They lower blood pressure. high
blood pressure to kill unnoticed.
What ?
No, the father did not go to jail.
Amsterdam, there are no laws.
Enjoy your stay ,
Dr. Richmond.
Dr. Richmond !
Hey, Chris.
My wife Cathryn.
Chris Amsterdam office.
And thou of Melissa.
Do you know sign language ?
- My uncle is deaf.
Farmer Uncle ? You said
Melissa is the most beautiful you see a goat.
I meant that...
That she is the most beautiful you see on
cow. That's what I always say.
My car 's outside.
If we hurry , we avoid the traffic jam.
How was your flight ?
- Melissa can not tell you.
Tulesa machine ? You gotta be kidding me.
Captain of hyppäisin Ekana.
We meet in the morning Hartman , right?
At 11 , Van der Molenin office.
Wednesday is perhaps the second meeting ,
but the rest of the week is free.
I'll introduce you around.
- My wife like it.
Have you been before in Amsterdam ?
- I do not. But I have heard of the place.
All is true.
- That's what I was afraid of.
Billy !
What is it?
Billy Boy Manson also live here.
Manson Five - yhtyeestäkö ?
He left the band only. he lives in
always here during a visit.
Hänellähän is the piercing ?
And the snake in your pants.
I do not think live in the next room ?
- He has reserved the entire upper deck.
Come on, Melissa.
He's not your type.
Should I reschedule the tickets?
- Are you kidding me ?
She plays the mother
three times a day. - The poor woman.
Richmond... - Booking may be the company
as Nelson Pharmaceuticals.
No.
- I have a reservation confirmation here.
Arrange this thing right now.
I'm going to ask the questions , my colleague.
Is there a problem , Chris?
- They do not find the reservation.
They are making a mess out. If this
clear , they will get an earful.
That's it.
Are you tired?
You should be.
You did not sleep on the plane.
At home I have for breakfast. but here
hardly get cereal for dinner.
I hope that call does not continue
throughout the night. Is wrong with the booking ?
It will be reviewed.
Are you all right , Princess ?
Come back !
Billy , we loved you!
Booking was found.
- It's about time.
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
New computer, do not...
Mistakes happen to everyone.
- Fill this out.
And passport?
- Cathryn ?
Melissalla is an emergency.
- Can not he wait?
No.
-I can take him.
You can go with Chris.
Is everything all right now?
I think so. Passports ?
Or is it already stolen ?
Just laugh. But I'm surprised
no matter what is lost.
Yes.
But they mean well.
Please call if you are bored. I'll show
you the real Amsterdam.
Here it is.
I'll wait here.
He looks like your room
and the wife gets a spare key.
You have a message.
Sorry still confusion.
Oh, hell.
Is something wrong?
Van der Molen wants to
to meet today.
Was not he supposed to meet in the morning?
How busy is that?
I do not know. I ask from Chris.
Get out of here ,
before I call the police!
I am pleased to
when Manson will fade.
Melissa.
Melissa ?
Are you all right , Melissa ?
Look at the girls.
There you are. Why Van der Molen
would like to see today ?
He played here. At 21 bar.
Is not this wait until morning?
Maybe he's talking about legal matters
before the meeting. Where's Melissa ?
Did not he come back?
- He was with you.
I went to buy cigarettes.
He was not going to the toilet.
- He 'll show up.
I'll still check it out.
Take it easy.
He looks around.
If anyone finds out , we deny
everything. I'm not doing it anymore.
Do not go.
- We do not have any more to talk about.
Excuse me.
- Lucas !
Sorry.
He is with me.
- You are crazy.
To accept the offer , and everything goes smoothly.
- Now you can stop , Rudolf.
This is incredible.
Drop it.
Hänetkö ?
No, you idiot. It's a weapon.
This is crazy !
Stop it.
I asked , you would not kill him.
- The gun just went off.
Do not yell at me.
What do we do now ?
You're the boss of you.
- You fucking...
He did not die.
I shoot again?
No! Yes !
Not sure ?
Decide now, the man is in pain.
Shoot , you...
- Will it shouting ?
No. Shoot him.
This is a nightmare.
Just another weapon.
Get it fast.
- Look elsewhere.
I thought you were a professional.
I have. Want to see your papers ?
Please help me.
Do something.
I fixed it. My gun.
Do we need it now?
- What a mess !
You need to talk with someone.
- Let's get out.
We can not leave him here.
- The body must be disposed of.
Where to?
- Why are hired you ?
This comes late,
but wages need to talk.
Do your job !
Unbelievable.
- At least he tried.
Who is that? Catch up.
What about the man ?
I'll take care. Go !
Stay behind the fence.
McDonald's is just around the corner.
I do not have time.
Your child is missing?
- After going to the bathroom.
Age ? -10.
Did he leave alone?
- No. But he just went away.
Have you been looking for ?
- Let's call the police.
We have been looking for.
Let's call the police.
It may be an exaggeration.
This is a big hotel.
He knows that we expect
him, and would be back soon.
I will send someone to look for him.
No one has seen him.
Send someone to look for him.
Look at the camera.
Speak with a bunch of Manson.
- Melissa is not a fan.
He can not just disappear.
- No. Call the police.
Maybe she's been kidnapped ?
Problems?
- The child is missing.
Reassures parents.
We are looking for him.
What about Manson's floor?
- The girl is not interested.
Cornelius Beaumont , Director.
-Walter Richmond.
I do not want to cause panic , but
our girl had been gone a quarter of an hour.
Is it stuck in the elevator ? Other problems ?
- I doubt it.
Maybe he got lost. I personally do not
always find a place to another.
Maybe it's because iästänne.
- Sir. There is no reason...
You got it. I'm so sorry.
We look forward to 10 minutes. If he does not
return , we will take further action.
Waiting is a waste of time. - Police
does not care about such things.
In general, missing children
are false alarms.
Your daughter is old enough to
ask for advice, right?
That's the problem.
Play out , girl.
Do not touch me.
What are you doing ?
Stick with it.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Cat got your tongue ?
What are you doing ?
Son of a bitch !
Who was that?
He was going to kill me.
If you wanted a car radio back,
had asked only.
Say something.
Are you hungry ? Same to you.
Can not you talk? It's too bad.
I encounter a let down when I'm talking about.
Talking is OK,
provided that the use of non- words.
What a mess.
I should clean up sometimes.
How old are you?
10 years? So young.
You can make it.
You seem harsh.
Is it a cold? Take my coat.
Amsterdam is a wonderful city ,
but damn cold at this time.
Where to now? I like the company,
but it would be busy.
Any plans ?
Is that a notebook ?
" L'Europe " ? It's an expensive hotel.
Do you live there?
Are you coming with me?
Again he. Is he someone to talk
the therapist to whom you paid ?
Where do they go?
Are you sure?
- He was here half an hour ago.
Was he alone ? -Ol. I thought
in such a Manson fan.
Where did he go ?
I do not know. We are in a hurry.
He came from the bathroom
and went in the wrong direction.
Where is he now?
- Somewhere here.
Hiding all etsijöiltä.
- The police came.
Ronnie... I'm sorry,
person was mistaken.
Parents are naturally
worried. But it is in vain.
How long your child has been
missing? - Half an hour.
You arguing about ?
No, he went to the bathroom.
Does she have a boyfriend ?
- We came to the counter.
Some become friends quickly.
There was no dispute and no boyfriends.
The loss is not a reason.
He can not use his voice
to ask for help.
He hears , but he can not talk.
He had an accident.
Please describe him , then we can
ask the services to monitor.
You have to look for him.
Police should help us.
The city is great. We can not look for
each reported lost.
Most of the day will appear on
period. This is ridiculous !
Please call after two hours ,
if need be. How does he look ?
He points out for a girl ,
who disappeared three weeks ago.
Did you find him ?
- Yes.
Most of it is.
I hope your parents
is money. Reward would be valid.
Probably seemed modest ,
but the boat is my home.
It is the same. But you'll thank me
all what I do for you, is not it?
Habit is not present
little girls real Amsterdam.
And the smell.
Remember to watch out for needles.
And let the tip your host.
Can you climb ?
Follow me on. Do not look down.
Hello!
-How are you , Simon?
Life stinks,
but this is something you do.
Where did you find him?
You should visit the
down more often.
Do not hoppuilko.
Do not you introduce us ?
Nice.
- But osaisiko to clean needles?
If I show where the hotel is ,
if you can get there yourself ?
Are you afraid of more and more of those guys ?
Sadly , I am busy.
Will you take him as a " L' Europeen " ?
Narkkariluola What is it?
- Hotel, stupid.
Is it money ?
-On. The purse is there in your pocket.
Here it is.
What I put my money ?
Have a nice life, asshole !
As well! There is no money. credit
cards and phone cards only.
Let's call the hotel
and tell where you are.
Soon, I'm a free man again.
Part numbers for all
five star hotels.
" Room 428, a suite ," I say.
" You have a package down there. "
They will come down, and I'll go up.
Please enter your last name, so that the job plays.
May I speak to
Mr. Richmond with ?
I do not know the room number.
Do you want them aboard ?
I'm not going.
Do not responding?
I'll try again.
Is everything all right ?
- Why not?
How old are you?
- He can not talk.
Do you know the man?
- Some types of...
Is there an ID card ?
- Yes, of course.
Stay here !
Is she okay?
-On. We are talking about with him.
He wrote his name and the hotel
name. Thus we found you.
Melissa !
What happened?
Take it easy.
I hope you'll understand him.
I am Lieutenant Winter.
What does he say ?
- He saw someone killed.
Close to the hotel.
She was chased. He fled.
Did he murder ?
So , it says here.
Armed man chased him.
Who was killed?
We have not received notice.
I do not think he came up with this ?
- No, look at him.
He was found
a known drug addict 's company.
Your daughter fled
one partioautoistamme.
He did not know how to drive.
No, he lost control of the car.
Car broke down completely. jacket found
seven stolen wallet.
It's not his jacket.
Look at the size.
He got it from a man
that helped him.
Who was chasing him ?
We do not know. There are no witnesses.
Do you not believe him?
We have not been informed of
murder or a shooting.
Please look into the matter.
We'll do so.
Thanks for the suggestion.
Can we go to the hotel ?
As long as you are
available for questioning.
They will stay here for a week and the rest
happy to help with investigations.
Glad to hear it. - We do not
want to seem ungrateful.
We are happy.
If only the rest of your stay
sujuisi a more comfortable marks.
Bluffing girl ?
The story is just amazing.
Sorry.
I should not have left him.
Do not blame yourself.
Did you call the Van der Molenille ?
He does not answer anything.
He's probably on the way.
- Did not I come?
I 'll be fine.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Is that blood ?
- Maybe. Or paint.
Anything? Not now ,
As with other periods of history.
No body, no sleeves.
Only shards of glass.
Please check anyway.
- Is this the right place?
This is the only access to the street.
- I call the technical guys?
He is now in order.
My wife takes her to bed.
So he did. Being investigated,
but none has been found.
I do not.
Quarter of an hour to get to meet him.
I know that it's important.
I do my best.
I'll tell you.
Have a nice day ,
Mr. MacKenzie.
Does he sleep ?
- Sleeping.
How many of you gave ?
- Just one.
You should have let the two.
- The pills do not solve everything.
That kind of thinking
the work would take me.
We can not stay here.
- Hotelliinko ?
Amsterdam!
Do not you exaggerating a little ?
He is afraid. Someone shot him,
because he witnessed the murder.
He exaggerates.
What do you think?
I believe in facts. There is no body, no
signs of fighting or shooting.
He did not invent this.
Maybe he saw the fight.
Maybe he heard the
stories from Amsterdam.
I believe him. - Calm down.
We can not do anything now.
He needs a father ,
who believes in him.
Right. But I do not think
everything he says.
You do not even speak the same language.
Give me time.
Four years.
I'm trying. But this is difficult.
It is more difficult to Melissa.
- He is not an invalid.
We should not
have come here.
No one wanted this.
Melissa is a strong girl.
Sleep, now. We will decide in the morning.
Maybe the police know more then.
If you want to go more and more ,
we're leaving.
Do not change your clothes ?
I'm coming down , then
when he is sleeping properly.
Take your time.
Things will , believe me.
I'll meet you down there.
Do I get another one ?
- Votkamartini.
I was supposed to meet with a little
less than fifty years old man.
Gray hair, glasses.
Have you seen her?
At least not here in the bar.
Want me to ask at the reception ?
- No need to.
Dr. Richmond ?
Hartman ?
Welcome to Amsterdam.
Late, due to traffic
does not work in this city.
Will van der Molen ?
- Is he not come?
I asked her to be on time.
Well, lawyers are always busy.
Do we sit ?
Why did we have
to meet tonight?
I have to go to Tokyo
tomorrow. It came as a surprise.
On the other hand , we would
transferred to a meeting -
I suggested that we meet today.
If it 's no trouble ?
Not at all.
- Do you want to order?
Whiskey. Do you?
No, thank you.
How was your trip?
- The flight went well.
The problems began
here at the hotel.
Your wife and kids are involved.
- My wife and one daughter.
Did they steal your credit card ?
- My daughter disappeared from the hotel.
He was lost hour.
Police found him -
and he told
the most incredible story.
I like the incredible stories.
He said he saw the murder and
that the armed man was chasing him.
Are you kidding?
- Police are investigating the matter.
Did you find anything?
- No. You'd be surprised if there was.
Kids can you
incredible stuff.
He certainly saw something.
But there is nothing so exciting.
Yeah, right. where
Richmond is a lovely lady ?
She will come soon.
- Great.
delay does not
Van der Molenin not like that.
I'll call the office.
Maybe something unexpected happened.
Excuse me.
I'll be back soon.
I have found the girl.
231 ?
Job done.
Did you hear anything?
He is certainly on the way.
I wish I would have. I would like to
agreement made ??before I left.
What happens in Tokyo ?
- Business Meeting.
" Kyoto Medical " with ?
- That is correct.
I know what you're thinking ,
but you are wrong.
I just business
I believe in honesty.
Lucas did not always agree ,
but I think a promise is a promise.
And we can take care of this
the case right now , without lawyers.
Just need to sign the papers.
Buy the size of Lucas champagne.
That sounds good.
- We can take care of it quickly.
We agree on the way, but
the first one to talk.
Our lawyers questioned whether the signature
amount, but to persuade them.
Lucas likes it. his
their conditions were pretty steep.
You agreeing.
- Hepatic that he is awkward.
But such an agreement to give you
's advantage over its rivals.
And it shows
to pay the sum.
Now we only need
the missing data.
What ? I thought that Lucas sent
them a week ago Friday.
We need the originals.
You know the lawyers in the United States.
Van der Molenin had to deal with it.
- They may be with him.
Most likely.
If I had known ,
I would have handled the case.
We have to wait
Van der Molenia.
What if he does not come?
- Why not come?
Maybe he forgot.
Or he's sitting in a traffic jam.
We need to
to postpone the signing.
But I have to be
Tokyo tomorrow night.
Unfortunate.
But my hands are tied.
Then we have a problem.
- Sorry.
Cathryn , this is Mr. Hartman.
We look forward to Van der Molenia.
Nice to meet you.
I guess I interrupted anything.
- We were finishing up.
How to Melissa ?
- Good. He sleeps.
I can call my boss
and ask for his opinion.
I would like to conclude the contract
which no one is satisfied.
I'm trying. lawyers make
work for us , not vice versa.
How can your daughter ?
Your husband told me what happened.
I wish she would recover the incident.
We put him to bed.
Sleep helps , yes.
Suzy , this Walter.
Not quite, but I will tell later.
May I speak with MacKenzie ?
Lunch? Ask him to call.
This is important.
The hotel , yes.
I'm sorry !
It is lunch time.
He'll call as soon as he gets back.
How long does it take?
-Hour.
So long?
We eat together? our
My wife and I had to eat here.
I do not know... - If you 're lucky ,
we can lift the basins trade.
Perhaps Van der Molen
time to desserts.
Yes for me would be nice.
If it indeed is.
The restaurant should be
the best in town. - Let's find out.
Have you heard of croquette ,
that exploded ? -Do not attempt.
The guy got
really severe burns.
Be called the bomb squad place
before you take a bite ?
As long as the alarm. - You sound like a
like my mother before my wedding.
Winter.
Was he sure?
Did you talk to yourself with her?
To the sounds.
We eat a little
and we will show up.
It was human blood.
And shots were heard.
The girl may have been right ?
- The body is missing.
Do you want to question him ?
Wake him up ?
You are sick. Tomorrow will be enough.
He's not going anywhere.
Table for three.
Thank you.
Follow me, please.
Can I get you something to drink?
- Wine.
Whiskey. And a bottle of
non-carbonated mineral water.
Not a bad idea.
What happened to Van der Molenille ?
- What do you mean ?
What happened to your lawyer ?
We do not know.
He did not come.
Mr. and Mrs. Richmond ?
Spare keys.
Thank you very much.
Do not you got a key?
- Some confusion.
We moved to another room.
- You moved ?
A suite for the same price.
The great thing about the service.
Excuse me.
You gave me the wrong number.
Mr. Peters ? How's it going ?
I've changed my mind.
- This is me. Bruno.
Let's talk briefly.
I'm having dinner with my friends.
Your offer was slightly
overestimated. You will understand.
What the fuck?
But I'm feeling generous
and I can accept...
Accept what?
Well...
45 500
-45 To 500 ? What are you talking about?
It 's my final offer.
Now I get it.
You can not talk.
You're so sharp.
45.5, and no more.
Room 455, does not it?
- That is correct.
Whether it's clever.
- You are responsible soon as possible.
I'm on my way.
Swimming pool building is difficult.
I should not have bothered.
What stateful ?
- I love the " Lobster Thermidor."
Looking for something? - Reading glasses.
I left them in a safe top.
Room?
I'll go get them.
I can read the menu to you.
They're important to me , anyway.
That's not only due to the lenses. he is
Melissa 's house. You know the mothers.
I'll go take a leak.
See you later , Henry.
One of Amsterdam 's oldest
churches is shown on the right.
DO NOT DISTURB
It's me , honey.
Wait a minute.
We eat dinner downstairs.
I came to get my glasses.
Go back to sleep. We will not be for long.
Can I get you something ?
Of course, I
not angry with you.
I love you too.
Get some rest.
Sweet dreams.
I'm so sorry.
Was everything all right?
It was. He woke up.
But you probably already fell asleep again.
Oh, great.
I cut myself shaving myself.
I am the last ;
who believes partaveitsiin.
Malaria is on the way to the north.
- " El Niño ".
Good evening.
One of the lifts froze up , Tom.
Little bitch !
Where do you think you're going ?
Ricky Mitch.
- Mitch here.
Pikutyttö slipped right through.
Behave properly.
And keep your mouth shut.
Do you see anything ? someone
probably set off the alarm.
That's it.
What is on the floor ?
Red wine , tomato juice.
I do not know. Call the cleaning.
The good you do not have them kirkujia.
Does not interfere with the beauty of Billy Boy's dreams.
Did you want him for the night ?
Carefully. I get mad easily.
My rave-up , right , Ricky ?
- She managed to get through it.
Wanted very much to see me, huh?
- He will be sought.
We show a little
hospitality.
Girls are freezing.
Will you take something warm ?
The rules prohibit this.
- Who will pay for hired?
She has the initiative.
Hormones are a rage across.
Ricky Mitch.
- Mitch here.
Come on. There was not a girl.
And Billy taken by girls in.
Come and sit by my side.
You do not like cartoons ?
I love cartoons.
We can look more
if you want to. My dear.
How's the donut ?
Is not it?
What are you doing ?
Do you write me a love letter ?
You smell good.
Like a pristine flower in morning dew.
Want to see my snake ?
Whether you themselves.
Do you want to wrestle first?
We can have pillow fights.
What is that? The list of wishes ?
" My name is Melissa Richmond
and I can not talk about. "
" I live in a hotel.
Call... the police ? "
What kind of crap is this?
I barely inches to you.
Do you want to have to back to jail ?
Who sent you ?
Are you on drugs the police?
This is an ambush.
I thought that this city
is tolerant.
Ricky , what is this?
What the...
More fans , huh?
Heavy - metal , right?
Here you have the metal.
Have you always lived in Amsterdam ?
- Born and raised here.
I go from the South of France.
I have a house in Saint-Tropez.
If you go up there in the...
Did you hear ? Maybe we are called.
Of course, I invite you to.
Do you think he play?
Who ?
Van der Molen.
Maybe.
I wonder if the lunch time over?
I'll call and ask.
Mr. Richmond,
you came to the guests.
No, at this time
not to do maintenance work.
We respect our guests
the right amount of sleep.
What was that?
- He heard something hakkausta.
Maybe Manson is back in the festivities.
The front desk.
Hello?
If this is a play...
Van der Molen is dead?
- He was supposed to meet with you.
We want to talk to you
with your daughter again.
Police found the van der Molenin.
- Discovered ?
Unfortunately, he is dead.
- Lucas is dead?
Who are you?
- Hartman. He was a lawyer.
Melissa saw someone in the fair
Van der Molenin attack.
Maybe. We need to talk
with your daughter. No, she 's asleep.
He has , unfortunately, be awakened.
Whether you're a real tough chick !
Give me the gun here,
so anyone not hurt.
He is not here.
- Where is he?
Gym.
- Fire.
What the...
That's Billy Boy Manson !
- Something has happened.
That's all they want.
Hit's a perfect fit.
Do not move!
Put the gun down.
Keep your hands visible.
Okay.
Not to worry.
He is strong and survives.
You saw Van der Molenin
Thus, the last in the afternoon.
Office.
This is terrible. I can not believe this.
If you need anything ,
applies for me.
How's he doing , Walter ?
- In case of unconsciousness. But he survives.
Good to hear.
Who would want to kill your daughter ?
Maybe it's that killed Van der Molenin.
Melissa was a witness.
What is this world coming to?
Determine whether the attacker more information ?
Will look into it.
We would have more questions.
Now? It can wait.
Demonstrate tact.
Not now.
Perhaps it is better to
wait until tomorrow.
Can I do something ?
You've been a great help.
You, too, experienced the loss.
Do not worry, I'll be fine.
Ajanko you to the hotel?
We have arranged
room here.
Oh, great. Now is not the time
talk about work , but...
Right now, I just think Melissa.
I understand.
I'd better get going.
Let's talk about tomorrow.
Call on earth...
Thank you.
Come with me.
His secretary found them.
- Let's see what Richmond said.
He was shocked. hopefully
This allowed him to convince.
Are these reports true ?
- Original.
How could he get away with faith ?
These do not resemble each other at all.
What if I signed ?
Hartman would have been a big bonus.
Did he kill lawyer
papers due ?
The results show that drugs
is fatal side effects.
Hartman wanted to keep them secret.
- He falsified them.
Van der Molen was found out ,
and did not want to hide it.
He came to tell me.
- But Hartman got to him first.
Who chased Melissa ?
Bruno Decker.
would kill his mother
a packet of cigarettes.
Decker recently played for Hartman.
Hartman is the culprit.
Since you arrest him?
Your daughter is the only witness.
He recognizes the man?
Thus, the evidence does not suffice.
- Not.
But I know a way how they can
get caught. If you just agree.
Hey.
- I'll meet you in the morning.
Melissa can not again
be imperiled.
The situation is completely under control.
- This is your fault.
That was unfair.
Nothing will happen to your daughter.
Trust us.
We're almost in position.
Gives son of a bitch to come.
He will come.
Good evening, Doctor.
Mike Larry.
- Larry here.
How's it going ?
- We are ready to go.
We'll be downstairs. The second
the hospital is 10 minutes away.
Are we ready ?
See you later.
Will everyone else, Doctor?
What the...
- Hartman took an ambulance.
Melissa...
- All of the units !
What are you doing ?
He drives towards the south of the Blauwbrug.
He can not escape.
I knew that this would happen.
He is the Vondelpark
and drive to the east.
Can you hear me , Hartman ?
Surrender.
You do not get anywhere.
We know that you are hearing.
Is this the right frequency?
It is for sure.
- It's over.
Stop the car and come out.
- I will show you.
There they are.
- Get him a bitch!
Is everything all right ?
- There he is.
Where are you going ?
- Stay in the car !
Where is Walter ?
Thanks !
Melissa !
Need help ?
- I do not. My daughter !
Walter !
Melissa !
What the...
Trying again are you ?
This can not be due to puheistasi.
Do you like it ?
Can I really boat ?
Be offended if you say no.
Thank you.
What do you think of Amsterdam
during the day ?
I hope that rehabilitation is successful.
- He seems dedicated family.
I do not think he will sell this boat
in order to buy drugs ?
You are always so pessimistic.
So go out tomorrow to Rome?
Yes, it is supposed to.
Crime figures in Rome
are the highest in Europe.
Even worse than Amsterdam.
What does that mean ?
New round of Amsterdam around.
After all, brings the beginning.
Does the idea of ??a
Amsterdam changed?
Subject to change.
The city is beautiful.
Melissa seems to thrive here.
Just out of curiosity just how much would
this boat fetch me on the open market, sir?
Professional Translation Services
www.gts-translation.com