Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Come on. Daddy! Let's go play
on the beach!
MAN:
I'm getting my shoes off. Hang on.
Come on!
MAN: Just run right in it.
Go on, run right in.
[SHRIEKING]
Yeah, it's cold, huh?
It's gonna be a big castle.
MAN:
Let me know if you strike oil, okay?
-Hi.
-Hi, how are you?
I've been waiting here forever.
Oh. Dad. The train was on time,
you're always early.
What, are you starting already?
-Why, you can't take it?
-Come on, let's go home.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[RETCHING]
You all right, honey?
You know, there's things
you can tell me.
I'm not as bad at communication,
and so on and so forth, as you might think.
I've lived in the world.
I'm not pregnant.
No. No. I wasn't saying that.
Yeah, you were.
[LAUGHING]
-You seeing someone?
-Yeah.
Someone with a name?
Nah, you wouldn't like him.
Well, how do you know that?
How do you know I wouldn't like him?
I wish you had someone.
Well, who says I don't have a honey
stashed away somewhere?
[LAUGHS]
You're my girl.
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
[POTS CLATTERING]
Hey, careful. Careful, it's hot.
[EMMA LAUGHS]
Yeah, well. I'm not really sure
how to cook it.
You finally got a vegetable,
and I don't know if I can eat it.
You all right? You been to the doctor,
yeah?
When's the last time you went?
I get a physical every year.
-That's right, they make you.
-Hey, careful.
So how'd you get time off work?
-You don't even know what I do.
-Of course I know what you do.
Dad. I'm a glorified intern.
I can get off when I want.
I wanted to come home.
I'm glad you did.
Maybe you'll tell me
what's bothering you.
I'm just tired, you know.
I think I got a bug.
Yeah? Wanna lie down? Go on.
Go upstairs, lie down.
I got your room all ready for you.
I know you do. Dad.
Or, ginger ale.
That'll settle your stomach. I'll get some.
Always keep some ginger ale on hand.
Uh....
Honey, hey.
Come on, honey. Come on.
-Okay.
EMMA: Dad?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God. Dad.
I have to go to a doctor!
I gotta tell you something!
I should have told you something!
What?
Okay. I gotcha.
MAN:
Craven!
[GASPING]
Oh. Jesus.
You're my girl.
I know.
[CRAVEN PANTING]
Holy anoint--
Love and mercy.
May the grace of--
May the-- May the--
[SOBBING]
MAN: Hey, there's Bill.
WOMAN: All right. I'll let him know.
About 5' 9''. 5' 10''.
Thinks white from what he could see
through the eyes of the mask.
Yelled out one word: ''Craven.''
And then he fired.
Jesus Christ.
JONES:
Hit Emma instead.
Then he ran.
Didn't pursue.
You want some water, coffee
or something?
Want something stronger?
I know somewhere in here there's a bottle
of Crown Royal with dust all over it.
You're gonna put the first foot forward.
Tommy. I don't care if it's now.
I'll sit with you, okay?
Get out. Get out of here.
he's not a basket case. Get out.
Somebody get him some coffee.
I want a glass of ginger ale.
Get him a ginger ale.
We'll get him. Tommy.
You know how we react
to things like this. Officer involved.
''Officer involved.''
Well, we ought to do that for everybody.
right?
Officer invo-- Who the fuck
do you think you are?
Well, if you wanna get philosophical.
I'll get philosophical with you.
Wanna get cleaned up?
No. I'm all right.
I want you to come stay
with Carol and me.
No.
You can't stay here.
It's where I live.
If you won't come--
Can't everybody just get out of here?
Just finish what they gotta do and go?
-This is someone armed and dangerous.
-What do you think I am?
Can everyone get out?
Don't like them gawking.
Can they just go? Finish what
they gotta do and go. Get out. Get out!
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Emma Craven's phone.
Hello?
[PHONE LINE CLICKS]
EMMA:
Are you all right?
Dad, are you all right?
Yeah. I'm fine.
CRAVEN [ON VIDEO]:
Who's my little girl?
Em.
-Who's my little sweetheart?
-Em.
[CRASH]
[GRUNTING]
[GARBAGE TRUCK WHIRRING]
[METAL CLANGING]
MAN [ON RADIO]:
A fatal shooting last night of the daughter...
...of a Boston police detective
leads our news.
Emma Craven, 24, an MlT graduate, was
killed in front of her home in Roslindale...
...by a man
thought to be targeting her father.
Kathy, from what l understand,
police don't have much to go on right now.
Lisa, there is still a lot of unanswered
questions when it comes to this case.
Twenty-four-year-old Emma Craven
was gunned down...
...outside this Roslindale home
on the porch behind me.
Now, sources tell me the suspect
in this case may be someone...
Turn that shit off.
...Detective Craven came across or had
a run-in with while he was working.
-You all right?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
None of your neighbors saw anything.
And the rain hasn't left much
for forensics.
We're gonna need to go through
your cases. Tommy.
You must have an instinct on this.
something.
Not off the top of my head, no.
All right, well, they wanna see you
upstairs first anyway, so....
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
This is off-subject.
This is my daughter's phone.
I need a list of her contacts. I gotta
talk to her friends, associates.
Yeah. Janet can do that.
Don't worry about it.
Blocked incomings too.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR
THEN DOOR OPENS]
Tom.
I am so sorry for your loss.
Anything you need from me and Mary.
And let us know about the arrangements.
It'll be in the Globe and the Herald.
I haven't been downst-- You know, to....
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
Bill Whitehouse is running things.
He has every resource
this department possesses.
Hey, this is a cop thing. Officer involved.
So will you take a leave of absence?
No.
Tom, we can't have you
on this investigation. It's a rule.
Well, since it's me that's gotta figure
out who would wanna kill me...
...for reasons only I'd know about,
then I'd rather get paid for it.
So the rules don't apply.
He's right, isn't he?
I think he is, yeah.
All right.
I gotta make a statement
to the media.
Is there anything you want in there?
You wanna stand with me?
CRAVEN: No, thank you.
-Well, they wanna see you. Tom. The media.
CRAVEN:
I don't want any part of it.
I'm not gonna sit in the murder room.
There's no point to it.
There's no physical evidence.
If you had a gun or something--
Jesus. I can't think.
It'll come to me.
It'll come to me,
but it's not gonna come to me here.
I gotta drive around. I gotta think.
Right. You do what you need to do.
You keep me informed. I'll punch in.
-I gotta go. Coroner wants to ID the body.
-Are you up to it?
Yeah. I want my case files brought up.
Nothing this year makes any sense to me
at all.
Tommy.
I'll have them sent to your house.
Sure.
MAN: Cause of death:
injuries arising from gunshot wounds.
Massive hemorrhage.
Heart seizure due to shock.
Tom, this is very difficult.
You may think you've done this before,
it's not the same.
Let's get it over with.
DOCTOR:
Is this your daughter...
...Emma Charlotte Craven?
Yes, it is.
Leave her alone.
Let me have some scissors.
What was that. Tom?
Scissors. I need some scissors.
EMMA:
Don't cry, Dad.
I'm not.
I don't know if I can make it.
You have to.
All right. All right.
And you're wasting two guys
here at my house. Bill.
If you want them in the neighborhood.
have them going door to door.
BILL [OVER PHONE]: Someone's
trying to kill you, Tom. They're staying.
I got nothing. Nothing.
I don't have enemies.
I never lived life or said what I thought
enough to have enemies.
Listen, you know l understand.
I'm not starting a personal conversation
with you. Bill, don't get nervous.
And tell the two uniforms in the cruiser
to stop pissing in the bushes.
They can come in the house.
[SIGHS]
This is your beach.
EMMA:
C'mon, Daddy! Come on!
Come on, Daddy! Come on!
Let's go play on the beach!
Come with me, Daddy!
Come on. Daddy!
Let's go play on the beach!
Okay, sweetheart. I'll be right there.
In a little while.
BILL:
Tom.
You ready for this?
Ski mask found in a hedge five doors
from you.
We got hair. Caucasian. It's in for DNA.
-Keep me posted.
-Where you going?
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[DOG BARKING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
Mr. Burnham. Mr. Burnham, yeah?
Yeah.
Settle down, all right?
I'm not gonna hurt you.
See? You know my daughter.
What are you, her boyfriend
or something?
-Yeah.
-All right. Okay.
I'm Emma's father.
I'm gonna let you go now.
You're gonna be all right. Okay?
-Yeah.
-Okay, be nice, okay?
Jesus Christ.
I'm sorry, but you gotta
get the fuck out of here now.
Give me a minute, all right?
I wanna ask you a couple of questions.
If you answer the door like everybody else--
What the hell are you so scared of?
Is this your handgun?
How did my daughter
get a goddamn handgun?
-Did you give it to her? Is this your--?
-I gave it to her.
All right. Why?
I didn't notice a shotgun
in your list of weapons. You own one?
-You think--?
-This is your pistol.
You licensed it in Vermont,
it's illegal in Massachusetts.
I tell the police you opened the door
with it, automatic year in jail.
Not that I don't have you by the balls
for trying to stick me in the doorway.
-You'd be lying.
-I don't care.
I know you. You're her dad.
You never came to visit her.
Didn't even bother.
Yeah.
You worked with her...
...and I need to know
what kind of trouble she was in.
I can't talk about that.
There're security strictures.
Clearance to work where we do.
I can understand you won't help me.
But I'm confused you won't help Emma.
Look, she's dead, man.
There's no way to help Emma.
There are probably two fucking guys
out there...
...watching and listening to us
right fucking now.
Now. I'm sorry,
but you gotta get the fuck out of here now.
Please. Or I'm dead.
There's something I need to give you.
Yeah? Yeah, sure, go ahead.
Here's the keys to her place.
And her personal things.
Thanks.
Look. I'm gonna leave you alone now until
you realize you gotta talk to me. All right?
Yeah.
I know you're a good guy, or Emma
wouldn't have had nothing to do with you.
Here's my card.
It's got my cell on it, okay? Call.
You were right. I don't like him.
Why did you have a gun, honey?
[DEVICE CRACKLES]
[CRACKLING]
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
Jesus.
So, what is it that I can do for you.
Millroy?
What do you do usually. Jedburgh?
If someone has a national security
problem...
...they dial a number in northern
Virginia.
And then I decide what happens next.
What's your problem?
You're a consultant in security.
I'm merely consulting.
So consult.
There's a company called Northmoor.
They own a number
of Defense Department contracts.
It's not an Agency front, if that's what
you think. It's a real private company.
That is unusual.
They have private security.
Autonomous security.
Well. I'm autonomous myself.
These are the facts:
One of their secure facilities
was penetrated.
Three people died making their escape.
A fourth, an employee who may have been
involved, has been killed.
-By Northmoor security?
-I didn't say that.
No one would.
The fact is we don't know.
She was shot dead five nights ago.
Her father's a Boston detective.
The Boston police are working on the
assumption that her father was the target.
And what assumption
are we working on?
That he wasn't.
-Who killed her?
-That's not the issue at this point.
National security is the issue.
I know your function. Jedburgh.
This has to be cleaned up.
Whatever it takes?
Yes.
Are you absolutely sure
you want me to look into this?
Because you have to be absolutely sure.
-She was killed. In Boston.
-Yeah.
But this isn't part of that.
-You think it's a funeral robbery?
-Yeah.
Look. I don't want this getting mixed up
in the other business.
I don't need the trouble, all right?
-You do me a solid in Boston sometime.
-Thanks.
[PHONE DIALING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Hello?
-Hello. My name is Tom Craven.
Your number
was in my daughter's phone records.
I'm Emma's father. I'm a policeman.
I just wanna know
what you were to Emma.
-Find out what happened.
-It says in the papers what happened.
Someone tried to kill you
and they got her.
Is that what you think happened?
MELISSA:
l run a shop. A luggage shop.
I wanna keep running a shop.
Look. I'd like to talk to you in person.
I-- Will you do that?
About Northmoor?
Yeah, sure, about anything
you want to talk about.
How do I know you're you?
Well, when you meet me you'll know that
I can't be anyone else but Emma's father.
Will you help me?
Look. I'm out of state.
I'm at my grandmother's.
I have your number. I'll call you.
I'm here to see John Bennett.
Detective Craven.
Jack Bennett.
-I'm sorry for your loss.
-Thank you.
Can I say how shocked we all were
to hear of Emma's death.
She was a valued member of our team.
I can't say I knew her very well personally,
but she is well thought of.
-She is missed.
-Thank you.
BENNETT:
In the '60s, this hill was excavated.
It was a site for Nike nuclear missiles...
...miles of tunnels and launch chambers.
I'm sure Emma told you.
No, she never talked about her work.
So Northmoor bought this
from the federal government?
Well, we lease it.
-For money?
-Coffee?
-I'll have a ginger ale.
-Certainly.
Get Detective Craven
a ginger ale, would you?
ANNIE: Of course.
-Please.
You have interesting friends.
Yes.
This facility. R & D in general...
...brings a great deal of money
to Massachusetts...
...as reflected in the tax breaks.
How can I help you?
I suppose I wanna know what my daughter
did here.
In what sense?
She didn't tell you about her work?
Perhaps because she was following
your security protocols.
And what are they,
in your understanding?
I don't understand anything.
She never talked about her work.
Right.
Well, you understand that most
of what we do here is classified.
Almost everything we do.
What she did, despite her qualifications,
your daughter was a trainee.
She was a full employee
and there's a benefit package...
...which I suppose you should see
personnel about.
I'm not interested in that just yet.
All our people are very well-insured.
I'll bet they are.
Well, what we do here:
Northmoor is essentially
a research facility.
We have a mandate from government to
develop a safe and clean energy source...
...based on fusion technology.
It's very green.
Weapons.
You make them.
Well, if we did, it would be classified.
I can tell you, you're a policeman...
...and have access to this information
anyway. Northmoor's an important part...
...of the nation's nuclear stockpile
and maintenance program.
We ensure that the nation's nuclear
stockpile...
...remains ready
for the president's order.
Not weapons, raw materials.
Emma was a part of this?
God, no. As an intern, she didn't have
any direct involvement whatsoever.
She worked on the research floor.
We all very, very much regret
Emma's death.
It must be especially painful for you
in the circumstances.
You mean
that she was shot instead of me.
As a parent. I can only guess
at your pain. I think.
Though I'm sure I cannot imagine
its full dimensions.
I've taken up enough of your time.
I'd like to talk to her friends, if any.
Yes, of course.
I'll see what I can do. I'll tell personnel.
Get you a list, contact numbers, so forth.
Can I ask you a question?
What does it feel like?
Thanks.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Craven.
BILL [OVER PHONE]: You ready for this?
-I'm ready for anything.
-We have a DNA match.
Oh, really? Give me the skinny.
[AGENTS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
AGENT 1 :
Clear right!
AGENT 2: Got a man down on the couch!
Got a man down on the couch! Give me one!
Contact! Move it!
You're awfully calm. Tom.
Doesn't do me much good
to be any other way.
No buzz off this guy, nothing?
This guy was a comer in his profession.
This guy was a hit man.
-What's the matter?
-Nothing.
Tell me what you were looking at.
Says in the evidence log
the hair was 2 and a half inches.
So he cut his hair.
Not as recently as a week ago.
-So, what are you saying?
-I'm not saying anything.
Hair can stick to a hat for a long time,
years.
Decades. And why would a pro
blow off two barrels of his shotgun...
...instead of saving one for his target?
Creeping up on a bereaved man
at a murder scene is not very bright.
Mr. Craven, we have things to talk about.
Like your name
and what you're doing here?
Like who shot your daughter.
You know who shot my daughter?
If I was looking for a man
who might have shot your daughter...
...and I had a limited imagination,
of which I do not...
...I might have looked
at the poor bastard you found today.
The known killer.
The unusually well-known killer.
Makes you think.
-What are you burning?
-None of your business.
Yeah, go ahead.
-Cigar?
-I'm not celebrating just now.
I know you don't smoke.
I saw your DARPA file.
That's my way of telling you
you got a DARPA file.
You gonna tell me what that is?
Defense Advanced Research Projects
Agency.
Their slogan is:
[SPEAKING IN LATIN]
And I know you know Latin.
You know what that means, yeah?
-Stand the fuck up.
-Please do so.
Well, it seems you're no one
in particular.
Just some English guy...
...standing on my lawn
with a District of Columbia driver's license.
Thank you.
-Is Northmoor part of DARPA?
-Well, that's hard to tell.
-Why are you here?
-Your daughter was flagged...
...as a possible terrorist threat
to the United States of America.
I said ''flagged.'' I didn't say she was.
Funny, the Boston Police Department
didn't come up with that one.
Funny if they had.
MAN:
What the fuck are you burning out there?
Fucking Christ.
My English friend. Mr. Davenport here...
...about 6 feet tall. 220 pounds...
...is enjoying his cigar.
WOMAN: Is he putting it out?
I can't sleep because of the smell.
CRAVEN:
You said my daughter was a terrorist.
I didn't. But someone did.
Who are you. Mr. Jedburgh?
I'm a friend of the court.
And I'm a bit fucking cold out here.
Pills, pills, pills.
Not like when we were kids...
...when it was pills, pills, pills
in a very different context.
You're not much of a partier,
are you. Craven?
I mean, what do you do for fun?
What do you mean, recently?
What's your interest
in my daughter's death?
Well. I don't like the look of it.
I mean, what do you think?
Do you recognize them?
Should I?
They broke into a U.S, classified
nuclear research facility.
Then they drowned in the Connecticut
River when they were making their escape.
Now. I know that sounds bollocks,
but it's not.
Northmoor isn't federal. I checked.
So if you're saying my daughter
was involved with these people...
...the most you could get her for
is trespassing.
Her apartment was tossed.
Her computer was stolen.
And do the police know
that you know that?
No.
Oh.
You're a smart fucker.
What does Northmoor do?
What have they done?
The people who drowned
belonged to Nightflower.
You know, tree-huggers, militants.
New Age fuckups....
Sometimes they blow shit up.
Infrequently, and not very well.
You can look them up.
The organization itself,
but not the dead guys.
They're classified.
She wasn't an activist.
Not the type.
My daughter was not a joiner.
She was more like me.
If she did anything, whatever she did.
she would have done it alone.
There's a point when anybody
can become an activist.
I mean, you see something happen
that's so wrong you have to act...
...even if it means the end of you.
Now, let's just say she was involved.
Her companions died,
and she came home.
She didn't say anything.
She meant to, she wanted to,
but she didn't make it.
I'm gonna advise my department
of one...
...which is me...
...to allow you to continue
your investigation.
Even though you sometimes
burn the evidence in your own back garden.
And you, an officer of the court.
I'm not gonna arrest anyone.
I never do.
You gonna try and stop me?
It depends.
I'll see you around.
You know.
sometimes I feel like Diogenes.
You know, the guy who walked around
with a lamp...
...looking for an honest man.
-How'd it turn out?
-What, for him?
I don't remember.
But you and I did pretty good.
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
I thought you were gonna wait
until I was a nice guy.
As a career move. I seriously need
to be seen telling you to fuck off.
You have no idea. You don't understand.
Go home. Go home. Go ho--
There's nothing you can do to me.
There are times when you don't have
a choice what kind of guy you are.
And you understand that
because you're doing it right fucking now.
May I?
You drinking the good stuff
because your job's going so well?
Is this an intervention?
If it is. I'd like to call people...
...who don't whack me around
because I'm afraid for my life.
I assumed you'd be
some kind of scientist.
Didn't think your daughter'd
go for a grease monkey?
Something like that, yeah.
If you wanna beat yourself up.
Well, what if I said
she said I reminded her of you?
Except drinky.
Something to do
with the absence of bullshit...
...and no patience
for Broadway musicals.
You're looking at me like I'm crazy.
Somebody shot my girlfriend.
Have you factored that in?
What do you know about Nightflower?
You see any granola or C-4
in my cabinets?
-Politics don't interest me.
-What did interest you?
Emma.
Look. I'm under contract.
I have a five-year contract.
I'm surveilled.
I'm gonna lose my fucking job
if I talk to you, no matter who's dead.
How did my daughter
get people through the security...
...at a classified nuclear R & D
facility?
There's a rumor she had help.
You.
No. I passed a polygraph at work.
What happened?
Come on, level with me here. I'm not a cop
now, it's just you and me. What happened?
You got somewhere else we can talk?
You didn't pass the polygraph, you know.
They just told you you did.
Emma was writing to Senator Pine.
At some point
she went to this greaseball local, a lawyer...
-...to see about getting out of her security--
-The name of the lawyer?
-Dampson or Danderman.
-Danderman.
Anyway, so nobody could help her.
And whistle-blowers always sound like
psychos, and Pine didn't get back to her.
And so all of a sudden
it was these Nightflower assholes.
She got them in
through the cooling tunnels.
I mean, she didn't go in herself.
But she was there.
How was Emma exposed to radiation?
She wasn't.
That's what I'm saying.
she didn't go in the tunnels. I mean....
They were exposed, but she couldn't have
been exposed, she wasn't in the tunnels.
-What happened to the people that went in?
-There's a protocol.
It's Bennett, he's insane.
In case of a breach,
they release irradiated steam.
Now. I can't prove this,
and you can't prove it.
I mean, these are clever.
clever fuckers, right?
You're a cop. You gotta help me.
Sure. Yeah. I will help you.
Come with me, tell me the truth.
-We'll get you deposed by a lawyer--
-No, no. No. I'm sorry, no.
I like you, you're Emma's dad.
But you have to go.
All right. You can always
change your mind.
In the meantime, here, this is yours.
It's loaded.
That's illegal in Massachusetts.
Everything's illegal in Massachusetts.
[SIREN WAILS]
[SIREN WAILING]
[GRUNTING]
What does it feel like? Hm?
[RINGING]
-Good evening, senator.
-Great to be here.
Two days ago, you gave a speech...
...in which you criticized your colleague,
Senator Stafford, for his position--
Well, we all have positions, Gordon.
l think the American people are asking,
with good reason...
...whether the price they have paid
for their security is too high.
INTERVIEWER [ON Tv]: With respect,
that's an answer one would expect.
But how does it jibe, senator...
...with your support of secret
research facilities in Massachusetts?
PINE: l am curious
about what you just asked me.
Now, if you're asking about...
...this administration's failed policy
with regards to--
INTERVIEWER: Senator,
what can you tell me about Northmoor?
PINE: l'm not familiar
with the business practices--
The parent company's one of your
biggest corporate donors.
PINE:
Well, all l can say about my donors is that...
...they're completely vetted
and aboveboard.
INTERVIEWER: Senator, there is a serious
and growing petition movement...
...to ban military research
and development in Massachusetts.
l understand that, l understand that.
But people have to realize
the importance of R & D of every kind...
...to the Massachusetts economy.
Now to hark back to your question
about Senator Stafford.
l fully agree with his desire
to expand oversight of R & D...
...but let's not throw out the baby
with the bathwater.
JEDBURGH:
I never had kids.
Maybe it's better not to have had one
than to see one die.
No.
It was worth everything to have her.
Public drinking is illegal
in Massachusetts.
Everything's illegal in Massachusetts.
Payback for the Tea Party.
You ever had wine before?
No, not with any pleasure.
Besides, with you. I think I'd have to
switch glasses when you weren't looking.
[JEDBURGH CHUCKLES]
My daughter was irradiated.
I don't know how exactly, but I think it
was our friends at Northmoor.
Later, she was gunned down
at my home.
And I want to know
what you think about that.
I had a source says
Nightflower people...
...were intentionally exposed
to radiation while in the tunnels.
But that source is dead now.
He wasn't a bad guy.
No.
Now, you know better than anyone.
cases like these are never solved.
They're simply too complicated,
too much hard work.
There's a lot going on out there
in this world.
And you just never can connect A to B.
How do you know that?
Because I'm usually the guy
that stops you connecting A to B.
It's part of what I do.
CRAVEN:
If I was an employee at Northmoor...
...and I wanted to blow the whistle
on something...
...what would I be blowing the whistle
on?
Well, let's take a walk
and we can talk about it.
I'm not walking into the dark with you.
You're a wise man.
Are you on my side?
Well, that's hard to tell.
You know that Fitzgerald thing...
...about an artist who's a man
who has two opposing ideas in his head...
...and, you know, he believes in them
both simultaneously?
I heard of it, yeah.
Well, that's sort of the beginning of it.
So, what's that like,
not being anyone in particular?
I don't know what it means
to have lost a child...
...but I know what it means
never to have had one.
Yeah.
You got nobody left to bury you.
Oh, by the way....
Thanks for not killing me.
Detective Craven, how do you feel
about a suspect being identified?
You're here later than everybody else.
Is that because you got a lousy boss?
I'm so sorry for you.
I'm sorry I have to be here.
It's all right, take it easy.
You got a business card or something?
Thanks.
Look, go on home, honey. It's too late
to be out here. I'll call you, huh?
I knew this would be the outcome.
Mr. Danderman?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to--
-I interrupt?
-No.
I'm Craven. Detective Thomas Craven.
Boston Police Department.
I know who you are.
I'm sorry for your troubles.
Thank you. I understand
my daughter was a client of yours.
Yes. I mean, no.
We had a consultation.
She never formally became my client.
Oh.
It says in her phone calendar that you and
she had dinner on the 18th of last month.
Yeah. I asked her on a date, yes.
Well, how'd it go?
Fine. Fine.
She was a nice girl. Smart as a--
-Sorry. I have to go.
-I'll come with you.
Can I ask you what this is about?
She came to your office. She wanted
to blow the whistle on something.
You know what that's from, when
cops used to blow their whistles?
DANDERMAN: I can't talk about that.
CRAVEN: I don't want you to.
But then later on that night,
you invited her out to dinner.
Gee, you're really nervous.
Mr. Danderman.
And you're about two seconds away from
telling me how inappropriate all this is.
Let me say. I know you couldn't
represent her in a non-disclosure contract.
But you probably suggested
further discussion...
...over a nice plate of spaghetti
and meatballs, huh?
You had two agendas.
One, you wanted to have sex with her.
Hey. I'm not passing judgment here,
okay?
And two, and really. Mr. Danderman...
...you wanted to know about
what security breach she represented.
I have to get to a deposition
in Springfield.
You represent Northmoor
in local matters.
My daughter came to you,
but you're Northmoor's attorney.
Let me add that you organized
western Mass, for Senator Pine...
...who's put your name before two different
governors for district court judge.
-You were about to say something?
-I don't have anything to say.
You are out of your depth.
far from your jurisdiction.
I'm going to the Globe, the Herald,
tell them...
...my daughter came to talk
about Northmoor.
You were Northmoor's attorney,
yet failed to disclose it.
You'll be in the middle of a story saying
how my daughter was the target, not me.
-Is that where you want to be, huh?
DANDERMAN: On what evidence?
I'll forge a fucking diary. I don't care.
Getting you in trouble's good enough.
Listen...
...this is not about police, okay?
This isn't about police, arresting,
all that nice shit.
This is about me knowing what I have to
and that you gotta tell me.
Now. I wanna see the senator.
See the senator? Who the fuck
do you think you are?
I'm the guy with nothing to lose
and doesn't give a shit.
You tell him that.
And fasten your fucking seat belt.
EMMA:
Look, Daddy. Lots of A-B-C's.
[KNOCKING ON GLASS]
Hi.
I wanna go to her apartment.
I wanna see her things.
That's not a good idea right now.
I'm sorry.
I am so scared.
Look. I would take you for a cup of coffee.
something to eat.
But we have to just talk now.
I'd like to ask you things about her...
...personal things maybe I never knew,
but there's no time for that--
[MELISSA CRYING]
Look. I can't take this, okay?
Talk to me, huh? Talk to me.
I introduced her to them.
Introduced her to who, honey?
Nightflower.
Fuck, you know?
-Corporations this, corporations that.
-Just keep it straight. Huh?
They had a little shack on the river.
Nightflower.
[BIRS CHIRPING]
[BIRD CHIRPING]
-I am so afraid.
-Who are you afraid of?
They came to my house.
These guys in black suits.
They were asking about Emma.
I lied my ass off.
What were they doing at Northmoor
that Emma wanted to expose?
Bennett's the motherfucker.
All right? It's Bennett.
That's all she wanted to say.
he was insane.
She realized he was completely fucking
insane.
Okay, whether he was this, that
or whatever....
What were they doing at Northmoor?
Why did Emma go to Nightflower?
She couldn't go to the papers
because of her contract.
And the senator wouldn't help.
And you are not hearing this from me.
All right? You are not.
I run a Iuggage store.
-I got a 3-year-old.
-I'm not hearing this from you.
What were they doing at Northmoor
that Emma wanted to expose?
MELISSA:
She had this for you.
In case.
I never wanted--
I'm just a person.
You know? I'm just a fucking person.
Okay, honey. I know.
Go back to your baby, okay?
I never saw you.
All right? Go on.
[SIGHS]
I gotta tell you something else first.
What?
She thought they poisoned her.
You know...
...I always liked this town.
When she moved out here...
...she said it reminded her
of Paris in the '20s, you know...
...because we got a very traditional home
in Boston and--
Maybe it wasn't what she wanted
out of life, you know?
What was the name of her contact
at Nightflower?
Tell me that and we're done.
No. I'm done now.
In her phone records,
there was a guy called Robinson.
Is that the guy?
Yeah. Now I'm done.
[GASPING]
We've stabilized her.
She's in a coma,
although we weren't able to save her leg.
-She has a child. Is anybody coming to--?
-Her parents just arrived.
-Thanks.
DETECTIVE: Thanks, doc.
Go ahead. I'll keep you posted.
Thanks.
[DOOR OPENS]
[WOMAN CRYING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
WOMAN [ON VIDEO]:
Okay.
My name is Emma Charlotte Craven.
l work at Northmoor Massachusetts
as a research assistant.
l know that l am violating
the security conditions of my workplace...
...and l know l am committing a crime.
But l'm doing this because l've exhausted
every legal avenue that is available to me...
...and no one would listen.
So now l have to do what's right.
Northmoor is breaking the law.
They are making nuclear weapons.
But these are not American nuclear
weapons.
They are weapons
designed to foreign specifications...
...and built with foreign materials.
So, obviously, if these bombs
were ever to be used...
...they would be traced directly back to
another country and not the United States.
l've stolen documents, images,
blueprints...
...but we need proof of the weapons
themselves.
So l'm showing a team of people...
...how to get into the Northmoor facility
to video the evidence.
l'm recording all this
because l'm very scared.
l'm under constant surveillance.
My phone is tapped,
and l'm being followed.
So chances are that if you're watching this,
l'll already be dead.
l--
l love you, Dad.
Fuck.
[BIRD FLUTTERS]
The next time a contractor asks to run
his own security, what should I say?
I suppose that would be up to you.
This is called a containment situation.
I wonder why.
The problem is
that there are things uncontained...
...and some of them will never go back
in the box.
You're scared about Craven.
wisely so...
...but here's the damage control
analysis:
Apart from Craven, three sets of parents
have lost their kids.
And now you have an employee
who tries to run over a single mother...
...only to be shot in the head
by the same cop you previously bereaved.
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-You know the thing about the dead?
They have got lovers, friends, relatives,
a billion loose ends, estimated.
Let's start at the beginning
of this debacle.
Nightflower is a pack of paranoid,
anti-corporate, hubristic freaks.
They think you're the devil
if you give them ice cream.
Do you think three of their people reading
as drowned is gonna read as an accident?
It was an accident. And the man involved
in the other incident was a Bosnian...
...who, as far as paperwork is concerned, is
alive and well in London at this moment.
I can do my job.
It seems I can also do yours.
What you're doing is not my job.
-Isn't it?
-Even if the drownings were accidental...
...the bodies were recovered by
a radiation team and disposed of secretly.
By your people, not mine.
You said they were
contaminated terrorists.
Not American citizens,
and you had contaminated them.
One of them is the only child
of a mom with multiple sclerosis.
When she's on TV saying. ''Last thing
I knew they were breaking into Northmoor.''
Do you know what I'm saying to you?
Do you understand what you have done?
What's worse: me doing it, if anything
has been done or you covering it up?
I'm just a private individual, a citizen,
a man.
You, on the other hand,
are the United States government.
What I am is the guy whose only fuck-up is
letting you have your own security fiefdom.
BENNETT: Whatever they say,
there was never a break-in.
Northmoor's never had a security breach,
never had an accident...
...and Northmoor
does not make weapons.
Least of all, things supposed in certain
contingencies best known to you...
...to look like Jihadist dirty bombs.
I wouldn't worry about it more.
''Fuck you, it's classified''
still works as I'm far as I'm concerned.
Are you even here. Mr. Bennett?
Are we even talking?
I'm at my house in Virginia.
I've got food poisoning. Where are you?
Oh. I'm not here.
Is Robinson keeping
his part of the bargain?
-Mr. Robinson?
-Yes.
-Mr. Allan C. Robinson. Jr.?
Could you remove your glasses.
please, sir?
[GRUNTING]
My daughter was Emma Craven.
She wasn't killed in your amphibious little
operation against the corporate satan.
No, she was killed later.
On my front porch. Come here.
I wanna know why you.
with your concerns about the planet...
...and human race, stayed silent about
the deaths of your people. Why's that?
People with families.
All of them had kids.
And one of them was my daughter.
Nah. I'm not gonna hit you again.
She wouldn't want me to.
Then again, she's not here
because of you, you son of a bitch.
Now, we got a serious situation here.
Mr. Robinson.
They know who you are,
and you're not dead. Not dead, shot, hurt...
...poisoned, nothing.
Now. I figure that's because
you cut a deal.
But you're gonna cut another deal
with me.
You're gonna tell me everything.
Come on, you son of a bitch.
[DEVICE CRACKLING]
MILLROY:
I need to know about the properties...
...of the substance
you gave Emma Craven.
I'd rather not discuss it in those terms.
Is it something
she could've encountered in her work?
BENNETT:
Any exposure, if there were an exposure...
...would be consistent with a documentable
procedural failure on her part.
Is it something that could've remained
in her effects...
...and been transferred to her father
without much collateral contamination?
Do you mean.
could it have poisoned her father as well?
Yes.
What, in your opinion, would be the
consequences if Craven opens his mouth?
It's unsurvivable.
So be it, then.
Do you see a soul in there?
I beg your pardon?
You can button your shirt.
Now, as we discussed yesterday,
there will be some erratic behavior.
I regret to say that this probably means
that you'll have less time--
I know what it means.
I've been having aural hallucinations.
My father's voice calling my name
as I start to sleep.
Bastard's been dead for 40 years,
and suddenly he's yelling at me again.
I come awake.
You're not sleeping?
No. I'm not sleeping.
I start to sleep and then I jolt awake.
There's something about the darkness.
I don't like it.
I'm not a counselor.
I know you wanna banter with me.
I don't do that.
I can only give you the facts.
Well, we all know what the facts are.
We live a while...
...and then we die
sooner than we planned.
-Standard procedure with the senator.
-Yeah. I get it.
You know, you didn't really let the side
stand with you.
-You got a lot of brothers out there.
-Yeah. I know. I like a private funeral.
The senator gets in his moods.
Not too good today.
Oh, that's too bad.
I was jumping for joy.
Are you hungry? We have some
sandwiches, a cup of tea.
No, thank you, sir.
Well, it's always a pleasure
to meet a combat veteran.
You left as a master sergeant
of a heavy weapons platoon.
-Yes, sir.
-How'd you do that at 20?
Everybody else was dead.
Did you have trouble adjusting
when you came home?
-No.
-Really?
No. People talk about trauma
and so forth.
I figure you pretty much come out
of combat the same way you went in.
I know that's not a very kind thing to say,
but that's my observation.
And I know there's a lot of big bucks
in this post-traumatic stress thing...
...but combat's pretty much
like anything else:
It can help put perspective on things
when you're scared shitless.
What is the nature of our appointment.
Detective Craven?
I was hoping that you could tell me that.
How am I supposed to tell you
what you want to see me about?
Well, because you're seeing me in less than
48 hours after I talked to your attorney.
Your daughter did come to me
with allegations about Northmoor.
She sent me a letter.
What'd the letter contain?
It touched on national security matters
that are classified.
-What happened to the letter?
-That's also classified.
But protocol would be
to turn it over to the committee...
...that does oversight on the area
your daughter's letter touched upon.
Prompting an investigation
on my daughter.
Opening up a DARPA file on her,
treating her like a terrorist?
I'm not involved in security matters.
I did write to your daughter advising her
that she might be in breach of security.
Oh.
So you didn't help her?
I'm very glad to see you, detective...
...as both a veteran and as a police officer
of your many years of service.
But I have to tell you
that your daughter...
...and we have to say this
despite her terrible accident...
...was in violation of almost everything
of which she could be in violation.
-What did she allege?
-That's classified.
Detective, a very important part
of the Massachusetts economy...
...is research and development.
Senator. I think you're in a position.
senator, regarding Northmoor...
...where you had better decide
whether you're on the cross...
...or banging in the nails.
Here.
These deaths
are the result of a conspiracy...
...by one of your major
campaign contributors.
You incIude your daughter?
Her death was an accident.
No, she was poisoned with thallium
by Mr. Bennett.
I think I'm scaring you. There's probably
not too much upside to scaring a senator...
...except to provide some perspective.
I'm gonna go,
but I'm gonna leave you these.
And I want you to call
everybody involved.
Tell them I know everything I need...
...to throw a box of tarantulas
into this situation.
Shut up. I'm not interested
in talking any more shit.
You investigate this
at a national level.
You do that, maybe you'll come out
of this all right. I don't know.
I don't think you knew that the people you
are in business with killed my daughter.
But now that you do know.
what are you gonna do about it?
Good afternoon, senator.
CRAVEN:
Get out of the vehicle.
What the fuck do you think you just did?
You just rear-ended an unmarked cruiser.
I made an observation that you're armed.
-Through smoked glass and our coats?
-Yeah. I'm funny that way.
Get out of the car now
or you're gonna make a move...
...for something on the inside
of your jackets, you understand me?
Get out of the car.
CRAVEN: All right, on your knees.
Hands on your heads.
What do you got?
These guys are armed.
They were following me, rear-ended my car.
You got some ID there? Thanks.
They're not law enforcement.
Imagine that.
What are you?
Don't think this is gonna
get straightened out?
-Not for a while.
-These fuckers got automatic weapons.
You just made a serious mistake.
Did you shoot my daughter?
I'm the supposed target of the killer.
So you're gonna follow me, armed, with
no credentials, into the city of Boston?
You're out of your fucking mind.
Welcome to hell.
A strange new twist
in the Emma Craven case.
As you know, a suspect has been
identified in her murder.
But there are new developments today
involving her father.
Two men have been arrested in Boston.
Police say the men were taken
into custody after their car crashed...
...in the back of an unmarked police
car...
...driven by Boston Police Detective
Thomas Craven.
The father of Emma Craven.
This all happened on Arlington Street.
Robert Down of Dover, Maryland...
[ON Tv] ...and Thomas Hannaham
of Washington, D.C...
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
...were also found armed
with automatic weapons.
-Bennett.
-We need to abort right now.
[OVER PHONE]
We can't risk dealing with Craven yet.
BENNETT:
It's too late.
It's already been done.
WOMAN: --and would not explain why
they had automatic weapons in their car.
What, you wanna try?
Mm-hm.
Hold your hair back. Your mother will kill
me if I get it all messed up. There you go.
Also on your chin.
Little moustache.
[GIGGLES]
Perfect. Now you need your razor.
Here you go.
Don't cut yourself.
-Comb.
-That'll work.
All right, now watch.
Painless.
Wash it off.
And one more.
[LAUGHING]
[COUGHING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Can I come in. Tom?
-You all right?
-Yeah.
BILL: Remember that trooper
out at the airport, busted Whitey...
...and got demoted and transferred?
He knew what was going on.
But he couldn't prove it,
and nobody wanted to know about it.
And finally he shot himself.
You remember that?
I don't think you'd shoot yourself.
But what's coming is worse than that.
It isn't what it is. Tommy.
It is never what it is.
It is what it can be made to look like.
There's a DA in Hampshire County...
...gonna charge you with the death
of your daughter's boyfriend.
He don't have a case.
That doesn't matter.
It'll be five years of people thinking
you did it.
You'll go broke, you'll lose the house.
Then they'll go after your pension.
If you win the case,
then there'll be a civil suit...
...and by that point you won't be able
to afford a lawyer.
What are they offering you?
I got kids. Tommy.
I don't.
But even if you did, right?
-Even if you did?
-Yep, even if I did.
[VOMITING]
You know. Bill...
...no one expects you to be perfect.
But there's just a few basic things
you gotta get right.
Always do the best you can
by your family.
Go to work every day.
Always speak your mind.
Never hurt anyone
that doesn't deserve it.
And never take anything
from the bad guys.
That's all.
It's not much to ask.
[FLOOR CREAKS AND GUN COCKS]
Hello. Craven.
[GRUNTS]
[METAL CLANKING]
[GRUNTING]
[DOOR RATTLES]
[COUGHING]
[GRUNTING]
I need your car.
Not yet.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Go ahead.
Hold on.
Hey. I'll call you back.
Derek. Derek.
You're all fucked up. Craven.
You're all done. Sit down.
Lie down. Be dead.
[GRUNTING]
Oh, you fuck.
-Say. ''Craven.''
-Fuck you.
Aah! You fuck.
''Craven.'' Say it.
Fuck. Craven.
-Louder!
-Craven!
I'm sorry you had to see that, honey.
[GRUNTING]
Bennett.
[COUGHING]
Thank God.
Deep down...
...you know you deserve this.
[GRUNTING]
MOORE: Got a cop of almost 30 years.
spotless service...
...and there's not one person who can
explain his instability without lying.
Who has executed the director
of the nuclear research facility...
...where his daughter was employed.
Okay. Ideas.
JEDBURGH:
Your scenario is this:
He was accidentally poisoned
by his own daughter.
-But he blamed Bennett.
-How do we know that?
Testimony of an altercation that happened
at Northmoor while he was there.
Testimony from the senator.
I can easily testify that he was unstable.
he came to my house--
JEDBURGH:
That's right.
He made wild allegations, he was armed.
You know, you was really Iucky to live.
That's true. That's very true.
Now the real story here, gentlemen, is:
''United States Senator
Escapes Assassination.''
Right. That's the lead story.
That'll wipe the rest out of the media.
Anyone who looks at the rest of this
is gonna see that something happened...
...but no one's gonna be able
to figure it out.
That's your objective.
To make it so convoluted
that anyone can have a theory.
-But no one's got the facts.
-That's quite good. Jedburgh.
Senator. I've been making things
unintelligible for the past 30 years.
Oh, and by the way,
it's Captain Jedburgh to you.
Captain? Of what?
Very little he can tell you about.
[SCOFFS]
Right. Well, it seems
we have a good starting point.
What's the prognosis on Craven?
Well, you know he's terminal.
We're all terminal. Millroy.
Even middle management.
But how fast is he being terminal?
-He's incapable of speech.
-Thank God for that.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I understand you had a chance to terminate
Detective Craven and did not do so.
You come to me. I look at things.
I decide.
Jedburgh, we've got to get the senator
out to the press.
I've decided what this country is.
What?
People who deserve better.
Yeah, we all appreciate
Captain Jedburgh.
Yet we would have not got to this extremity
had he done what the situation dictated.
JEDBURGH:
Senator.
I don't think you really understand
what side of the situation you're on.
Well. I think we've had
a successful meeting.
[PINE GASPING]
I am a United States senator.
By what standard?
-You got a family?
-Yeah.
-Kids?
[FOOTSTEPS]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[ENGLISH SSH]
What's the theory?
You know Craven.
He's completely straight up.
He's arrested everyone that needed it
because it said so in the book.
Yeah. All my officers do that.
Oh, yeah.
The thing is he hadn't been on Gangs.
He hadn't been on Organized
for 15 years.
If I had to pick a cop who had enemies,
it wouldn't be Craven.
They could put you away for life,
you'd agree he had a point.
But he's been all political. Towelheads.
That guy that jumped the freighter
in Eastie...
...with the drawings of the gas yards.
Yeah, there's that.
[SIGHS]
How's he dealing with it personally?
You tell me.
There's a situation.
There's a girl. Emma Charlotte Craven...
...MIT graduate, nuclear science...
...unusually good at mathematics,
but was bored with the career implications.
-I like her already.
-She was extremely bright...
...but apparently disinterested
in outward distinctions, not a careerist.
Diplomacy's for the scarecrow. Millroy.
Because he didn't have a brain.
[CHUCKLES]
I know you find me middle-class--
No, not middle class.
Middle management.
Can we make this
about national security?
At this stage in my life,
it's about whatever the fuck I say it is.
You want the definition
of discretionary powers...
...all you gotta do is take a good look
at my smiling features.
JEDBURGH: So you're suggesting
this girl penetrated a secure facility?
MILLROY:
We're not ruling out anything.
Information is still coming in,
yet the Northmoor facility was penetrated.
She was probably involved.
We're working backwards.
Where is Northmoor exactly?
It's an American-based
research and development subsidiary...
...of Hollander North.
It has two sites.
One of them, a particle accelerator...
...the other one even more hush-hush.
That's where she worked.
Northmoor has no less than 24
Defense Department contracts and licenses.
My oversight capacity is not official.
Oh. I see.
Are we even having this conversation?
We've never had a conversation.
You see the problem--
The situation is that Northmoor...
...has its own security infrastructure.
Autonomous security.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Things may have been done.
Are you absolutely sure
you want me to look into this?
Because you have to be absolutely sure.
So, what's her position,
this Emma Charlotte Craven?
She may have penetrated the facility.
She may have just had a job there.
As I said, we're not sure which side
she batted for.
She a sister fister?
I don't believe so.
But if she was.
she's a dead sister whatever now.
-Oh.
-She was shot dead five nights ago.
Boston police are working
on the assumption that her father...
...a Boston police detective.
was the target.
And what assumption
are we working on?
That he wasn't.
[SIGHS]
You were never afraid of the dark.
You're a brave girl.
If you'd been more afraid.
more like other people...
...maybe I'd still have you.
But I'd love you less.
Good night.
Next time, tell your old man, huh?
If you wanted me. I would've made time.
You're a little unstable right now.
If you dare think that you're safe...
...just because I can't prove anything,
you're very wrong.
I don't know what you're talking about,
and neither do you.
My driver is armed,
and you're a man distracted by grief...
-...in a state of paranoid confusion.
-You're probably right.
If he takes his hands off the wheel.
I'll kill him then you.
-What if I file a police report?
-Don't fuck with me. I'm a cop.
I'm gonna let you go now.
All you need to know is
I'm gonna get you.
Go ahead.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/td57
Help other users to choose the best subtitles