Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
DAVID: There was a girl.
A beautiful girl
surrounded by people.
Yet utterly alone.
Her brother, Chris,
died sophomore year.
She spent all of her time
secluded with her family,
or in the comfort of books.
I watched her for
all of high school,
waiting for that perfect
moment to talk to her,
but that moment never came.
(INAUDIBLE)
I watched as people
gradually forgot about her.
And she seemed content
to disappear.
But not to me.
And although she didn't know it,
I saw the possibility of us.
Jade Butterfield. Mmm.
Four years, and you
never talked to her.
Well, in my defense, no one did.
There is a reason for that.
She's an ice queen.
Girl can't be real.
You don't think she's real?
"You don't think..."
Girl looks like that, has that much
dough, can't be real, all right?
I know these things.
(CHUCKLES)
Ah, it's stupid, I know.
No, it's not.
Come on. Dad wants a photo
of the happy family.
Oh, whose family are we
taking a picture of?
Come on.
Jade, come take a picture.
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Will you take two?
Just to be safe.
Okay.
(SHUTTER CLICKING)
- There.
- Thank you.
- Congrats, honey.
- Thanks.
GIRL 1: That one's going online.
GIRL 2: Yeah.
I barely know those girls.
I didn't expect to
be in the picture.
Take a seat. Come on.
Mom and Dad's happy
family photo can wait.
(CHUCKLES)
Promise me you won't do in
college what you did here.
Chris was an amazing brother,
and we all miss him,
but you can't stop living.
He'd want us to live
more, not less.
How's anyone ever gonna know how
ridiculous and funny you are
if all you ever do is hang
out with Mom and Dad?
- I don't just hang out with Mom and Dad.
- Oh, really?
How many kids signed this?
And, uh, you can't
include teachers.
Don't.
Thanks, Dad.
You're welcome, son.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you. It means a lot.
Maybe you should buy
a blowtorch, huh?
- To melt the ice off your girl.
- Mace...
- Your son's got a crush.
- No, I don't.
- Does he?
- Is she here?
- Yeah.
Which one is it?
- Jade Butterfield. Mmm-hmm.
- HARRY: That blonde over there?
- Don't you dare. No.
- Hey, Jade!
Hey, Jade!
MACE: Jade!
Jade, I want you to meet my son!
- Come on! Come on!
- The greatest kid here!
DAVID: Hey, you guys. Come on, man!
Whoo-hoo. My son, the
high school graduate!
(GROANING)
Oh, wow. Mr. Schwartz,
thank you. This is too much.
Mrs. Schwartz. You guys take
care now, all right? Okay.
Ah. (CHUCKLES)
Balling!
Dude, you going to
Jenny's Saturday night?
Really? Again?
- Come on.
- Don't do this.
Do you have any idea how your
constant break-ups affect my life?
I'm so sorry.
The energy, man, it gets all
awkward and shit, all right?
Just get back together
with her so I can
go back to the life
I'm accustomed to.
Can you act like a
respectable human being?
You're the first
face the guests see.
And yet they keep coming back.
(CHUCKLES)
Welcome to the Inn.
How are you doing?
HUGH: Can you just, uh,
give me a nice spot?
MACE: Absolutely.
Will do, sir. Take care.
(CHUCKLES)
You're Jade Butterfield.
We go to school... I mean,
we went to school together.
David, right?
Yeah.
HUGH: Hey, Jade.
I should go.
Okay.
Would you sign this?
Sure.
MACE: Jade Butterfield
Come back to me
I'm David and I love you
(CHUCKLES)
HUGH: My wife will have a mixed salad
to start and your pasta special.
My daughter's gonna have the
steak, medium, and soup to start.
Good?
- Yeah.
- WAITER: And for you?
I think I can handle this myself.
I'm gonna go for the burger and
fries. Medium rare, please.
And a Crown and Coke. Better
make it a double, actually.
You're here from ASU
for two short months.
Let's just try and
keep it pleasant.
That's why I got the double, Dad.
Um...
We've been going back and forth over
what to get you for graduation.
We know we haven't done very
well with the holidays and so on
and that's not been
fair to you or Keith.
I don't need anything.
We could go shopping. We could
get a new wardrobe for Brown.
Yeah, you should
think of something,
or else you'll end up
with a photo of this guy.
(ALL CHUCKLE)
There is one thing.
What? Anything.
- A party.
- A party? Wow.
Out of all the things
you could ask for?
Well, I was looking at all
the kids at school today
and high school's where you're supposed
to make friends you'll keep forever.
I don't know any of them.
They don't know me.
A party. I think that
that is a great idea.
Well...
Sure.
- Yeah, sure. Okay.
- (ALL CHUCKLE)
HUGH: It's been a long time since
we've celebrated anything.
Thank you very much, Mr. Abbey.
(CHUCKLES)
- Hi.
Do you want me to get your car?
No. Um...
I'm having a graduation party.
(CHUCKLES)
- I'm inviting the entire class.
- Really?
Is it that hard to believe?
Uh, no. I've just
never seen you out.
I didn't know that you, uh...
- Mingled with the masses.
- (CHUCKLES)
I just spent the last
four years of high school
trying to get into another
four years of college.
(CHUCKLING)
- You don't have to come.
- No, I want to.
(STAMMERING) I mean, we want to.
- We wanna come.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Could you just give me one second?
- MACE: Welcome.
- Welcome to the Inn.
Keep it close. Don't park me in.
- Oh, sure, no...
- (COINS CLATTER)
No, he didn't. Hey, man.
Now, I'll take them, but you gotta
hand them to me, all right?
I don't pick up shit off the floor.
It's time to learn.
- Hey. Hey. Hey.
- (CHUCKLES)
You boys best earn your
three minutes in my car.
- Yeah, thanks, man.
- MACE: "Boys"?
DAVID: Give me the keys. Come on.
Give me the keys.
I guess we should definitely earn
our three minutes, don't you think?
Why limit ourselves to three?
I mean, why?
- Are you coming?
- You're stealing his car?
- Whoa.
- I mean, I wouldn't say "stealing."
Technically, borrowing.
What about your job?
Jade, get in the car.
- What?
- (ENGINE STARTS)
Get in the car.
- What is she doing?
- I don't know. Come on!
MACE: Get in the car!
Jade Butterfield, get in
the car this instant.
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoo-hoo!
(SQUEALS)
Whoo!
Yeah!
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(BOTH CHEERING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Where the hell have you been?
We've got guests freaking out.
- You stole my car.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
Sorry. We just wanted to make
sure it wasn't parked in.
You ate Fatburger in my Maserati.
It's over. You're done, mister.
That's actually my fault.
You should blame me.
All right, I want him fired.
- Now.
- No, it was my...
- I want him fired, too.
- It was my fault!
- Him and him fired, and I'm having your job.
- I ate Fatburger!
It was me. It was me. I ate it.
No. It was me.
- I ate the Fatburger.
- (ALL SNICKERING)
(CHUCKLING)
- Oh, is this a joke to you?
- No, I mean...
You trying to impress your hot
little girlfriend over there?
Now, watch what you're saying.
Everyone, cool down.
Why don't we go inside?
It's gonna take a lot
more than stealing
my car to get her
to spread her legs.
MACE: Oh, shit. Damn!
- That was self-defense.
- Get out of here, David! Now!
- MACE: What was that?
- That kid, he hit me!
Jade. Are you all right?
MAN: I swear to God, I'll sue.
That was self-defense.
MAN: God, I'll sue him.
I'll sue him, I'll sue you. I'll sue
everybody! I'll sue this whole place!
He's out of here, sir.
Is my Fatburger evidence?
'Cause I'd like to
finish eating it.
- Just get out of here, Mace.
- All right, yep.
- Sorry, sir. Sorry.
- (WHIRRING)
HARRY:
I hope this isn't happening again.
'Cause Judge Dean called.
Word travels fast.
It was no big deal.
I lost it for one sec, that's it.
Well, one second is
all it's gonna take
and I don't wanna have to
worry about you again, David.
Now, why would I wanna be a valet
when I can be here with you?
Plus, I am gonna own the
shop one day, right?
Ah, easy.
I'm still breathing, partner.
Right.
- This guy deserve it?
- Yeah.
Let me guess, you
were protecting Mace.
(CHUCKLES)
And a girl, too.
(INAUDIBLE)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- No, no, no. Come on, come on.
- (CHUCKLES)
Answer it.
- Go on. Go, go, go.
- I'm going.
There she is!
- Congratulations, sweetheart!
- Thank you.
- Oh, my God, you look gorgeous tonight.
Your dad tells me that you'll be
leaving on your internship soon.
Two weeks. I'm really excited.
How exciting.
- Yeah, come in. I'll go get him.
- JOE: Thanks.
Dad?
- Oh.
- There are people here.
I lost track of time.
Ah, okay.
(SIGHS)
Oh, you're beautiful.
Thank you.
Are you coming down?
Yeah, I'll be there in a second.
- See you, Dad.
- (MICROWAVE ALARM BEEPS)
You want me to heat you up a piece?
Ah, no, thanks. I'm on my way out.
Nice suit.
Got a job interview or something?
7:30 on a Saturday? (CHUCKLES)
I did it already.
Yeah, that's why I'm redoing it.
You know, your mom
bought me this suit.
What for?
Get married in.
I can change if you want.
No, no, no.
Looks better on you.
This thing you're going to tonight,
is it a dance or something?
Mmm, sort of.
- Well, embarrass yourself.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Builds character.
- Sure, sure.
DAWN: Hugh.
- Dawn, Joe, nice to see you.
- DAWN: Hi.
- Thanks for coming.
- Of course.
Hi, Joe. Oh, you shouldn't have!
Since you did, how come only one?
(JOE CHUCKLES)
Raymond, Tracy, thanks for coming.
The Mayo Clinic's so
lucky to have you.
(INAUDIBLE)
Excuse me for a second.
This is what you wanted, right?
Yeah. It's great.
- Everything's great.
- JOE: Hugh!
Come over here and settle a bet.
Go.
A, uh, friend of yours is here.
WOMAN: Jade.
- Hi.
- Congratulations.
I'm so embarrassed. This isn't
exactly what I had in mind.
You run with a
slightly older crowd.
(CHUCKLING)
It's a complete failure.
I thought if I reached
out to our class,
they'd wanna be here as much
as I wanted them to, but...
There's another graduation party.
That's probably where everyone is.
Oh, right, yeah.
You know what?
I'm gonna be a little creative.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- (LINE RINGING)
MALE OPERATOR:
Atlanta Police Department.
Hi, I'm calling about a very loud
party at 44 Seawall Road. Um...
And I've asked the next-door neighbor,
Jenny, to turn down the music,
and it just seems to be
getting louder and louder.
And now... Oh, God!
There seems to be someone
pissing on my Mini Cooper.
I need this shut down
straightaway. Thank you.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Hi.
Is David here?
Yeah, he's inside. Come in.
- Shit. Is this your party?
- Yeah.
(CHUCKLING) It's about time!
- Hi.
- Come on.
Hey. Hi.
(MUMBLING)
Hi.
- Should I take off my shoes or something?
- No.
- No?
- Come in.
(CHUCKLES)
(MOUTHING) The ice has melted!
Come on.
(CHUCKLES)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Thanks for getting
everyone here, man.
Yeah, man. Ah, about that. Uh...
(WOMEN CHUCKLING)
- You invited Jenny?
- "Invite" is a strong word.
Come on, man.
Dude. She cheated,
she's sorry. Let it go.
You did ruin her party.
Oh, shit. She's coming.
Later.
Wow. (CHUCKLES)
You certainly got everyone
here, didn't you?
Maybe that's because the
cops busted my party.
See, I think what happened, my
neighbor, who's in Florida,
sensed that there was a party
happening and called the cops.
Now all my friends are at
Jade Butterfield's party.
A girl who acted like we
didn't exist in high school.
Does that make sense to you, David?
You have a party every weekend.
What difference does it make?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
What's going on now?
Who are these kids?
David made it all happen.
Isn't it wonderful?
Who's David?
He's the friend of Jade's.
He's there.
- That's the valet!
- What?
That's the kid I was telling
you about at the restaurant.
Jade is happy.
The party is a great idea.
- Hugh, please.
- (MUTTERING)
Hey! Quiet! Quiet!
Right. So, uh, we're all
having a great time,
and, uh, it's gonna get
even better because
I have a really good
game we're gonna play
where each couple has to
pick a song out of a hat
and you all have half an hour
to choreograph a routine. Okay?
Hey. What do you
mean "choreograph"?
It's fine. You'll love it. Uh...
My beautiful date, Sabine, please.
Our song is romantic and big
so we should probably do a
lot of figure skating moves.
- Figure skating?
- Mmm-hmm.
Show me.
Like this.
Wow.
- You don't wanna do this?
- Mmm-mmm.
- Not even a little bit?
Will you give me your hand?
- No.
- Come on.
Really?
Give me your hand.
Come on.
I did it for my third-grade
ballet recital.
It goes over really well.
(DOOR OPENS)
Ten more minutes.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Uh...
Is she running?
You're stalling, aren't you?
No.
I just like cars. I promise.
My dad's been trying to
fix the carburetor forever.
So far, no luck.
Is it his?
No.
It's my brother Chris'.
My mom wants to sell it.
It makes her sad, just
sitting in the driveway.
All right.
Maybe I am stalling. (CHUCKLES)
Maybe we should, uh,
(CHUCKLING)
- rehearse.
- (ALL CHEERING)
It takes a certain type of confidence to
dance in the footsteps of Salt-N-Pepa.
I mean, a very brave person.
But we have two brave souls
coming up to do just that.
Mace and Gwen. Come on.
- (ALL CHEERING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
Get hype!
- Get hype!
- Whoo!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHUCKLES)
(CHEERING)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHISTLING)
Thank you for this.
Now, someone named Jade
Butterfield and her new friend.
Give him a hand but not
your car keys. David!
MACE: Yeah, David!
I see you!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL CHEERING)
MACE: Oh, man! What is this?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
DAVID: Shh, follow me.
(JADE CHUCKLES)
Where are we going?
MAN: Whoo!
HUGH: All right, everyone,
calm down. It's just a blackout.
I've wanted to kiss you
since the 10th grade.
I couldn't go another minute
without telling you that.
All right!
First off, I'd like to
apologize for the power.
It seems even our home is objecting
- to the number of people here tonight.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
Ah, but, more importantly,
I wanna make a toast.
We're all here tonight because
of our daughter, Jade,
a girl that brings so
much light to our life,
and as you can tell, if there's
one thing we need, it's light.
So, uh, Jade, where are you?
Shit.
HUGH: Jade. Come on.
Maybe he'll give up.
Come on, Jade.
GIRL: Busted!
Oh, shit.
Come on.
Get up here.
I'm so lucky
to be your father.
And everything you've
worked so hard for...
MAN: She's working hard, all right.
It's all coming true.
So here's to Jade.
- ALL: To Jade.
- (CHUCKLES)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Oh-oh.
GIRL: Seriously?
Okay. It's been quite an evening.
But all good things must
come to an end, so, uh...
And that would be the sign.
We'll get you cabs,
or, uh, Hulu, or...
- Uber.
- HUGH: Yeah, Uber.
Those of you who are driving,
please drive safely, but drive.
- Party's over.
- Party is over.
MACE: Deuces.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You must be David.
Yes, sir. Uh, it's
nice to meet you.
Can I show you out?
Sure.
I hear you're trying to get
your car running again.
Are you gonna steal it if I do?
(CHUCKLES)
Right, the valet.
No, that was just a
one-time thing, I promise.
Did you have a good night tonight?
Well, let's just say I
prefer how it started.
You know, I really respect
your daughter, sir.
And the truth is, I just
wanted to make her happy.
I think she's amazing.
Good night.
It was a fun party, huh?
I'm just going to my room.
I have to go.
(HORN HONKING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(WHOOPING)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
- Hi.
Last bay over there.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Hi.
- Oh.
- Whoa.
Are you okay?
(CHUCKLES) Not cool.
I got your text.
I was trying to think of things
I could do for your dad,
seeing as I feel like he didn't
love the closet as much as I did.
You don't need to do that, David.
I do.
I got something in
the box over there.
HUGH: Jade.
Sorry.
So, I spoke with Dr. Fitzgerald.
- Mmm-hmm.
- And we set a breakfast
for the morning you start.
You know, just so you can spend
that little extra time with her.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
And the dorm's all arranged?
I move in not this
Sunday, but next.
(CHUCKLES)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
(ENGINE STARTS)
What are you doing here?
- Get away from that car.
- Stop.
Look, it's working.
It was the old carburetor.
It was shot.
I had the right one
laying around the shop,
so I thought you might
wanna hear her run again.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
That's amazing! What did you do?
- It's no big deal.
- JADE: Thank you.
I never thought I'd
hear that sound again.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Look, Jade told me how much
this car meant to you.
And I tried to rack my brain
around something I could do,
seeing as, you know, we got off on
the wrong foot the other night.
The other night.
(CHUCKLING)
When you emerged from a
closet with my daughter.
Dad, he did this for us.
ANNE:
It's a very kind gesture, David.
Would you maybe, um,
join us for dinner?
I wasn't looking for an invite.
I should go home and shower.
You could wash up here.
I have to get changed.
I don't wanna intrude.
No, you wouldn't be
intruding, honestly.
Dad, please.
Yeah, okay. Sure, sure, yeah.
- ANNE: Great.
- Come on.
You might not know this, David,
but, uh, Jade is following
in her father's footsteps,
enrolling pre-med in the fall.
And since I'm kind of hoping
for a specialty in cardiology,
I just thought there was no better way to
celebrate than with a family heirloom.
No more gifts, Dad.
You've gotten me enough.
It was your grandfather's.
It was mine.
And it was gonna be Chris',
and now it's yours.
(JADE GASPS)
Oh, it's too much. Thank you.
Well, I think pre-med
at Brown earns it.
Not to mention your internship
with Dr. Fitzgerald.
Internship? You never
mentioned that.
It's not a big deal, that's why.
Very big deal.
I mean, she'll be leaving and
spending, I don't know, most of...
Um, I, uh, had to
declare my major, too.
It's not as fancy as Jade's, but I
had to major in something, so...
Communications.
Always wondered what that meant.
It's the study of
how we communicate.
Well, you know, you can always change
it later if it doesn't make sense.
All right, David. Your turn.
Ah, here it comes, the inquisition.
(CHUCKLES)
It's okay. If I can
pass, you can pass.
Keith, did she pass? He still
doesn't call you his girlfriend.
Okay, David, look, we know your
act of generosity with the car
wasn't really about anything
other than my daughter, so...
(LAUGHING)
I'd just love to know a
little more about you,
other than the fact you
can fix an old car.
I'm sure that's not your
most noteworthy quality.
I mean, it might be.
What about your future plans?
Where are you going to college?
Uh, I'm not going to college.
- Oh.
- Mmm.
Don't feel you need it?
No, I'm not saying that.
I took my SATs.
Well, I mean...
No, I wouldn't let
that discourage you.
I mean, not everybody tests well.
Ah, I got a 2090.
(LAUGHING) Well done.
SABINE:
That's an amazing score, David.
You could get into
UGA with that score.
Maybe. But I like working
in my dad's shop.
And so does he.
And there's nothing
wrong with that.
Yeah, I don't need much.
Warm bed, clean socks,
milk in the fridge.
- A nice girl to come home to.
- (HUGH CHUCKLES)
Modern-day romantic. I see.
- Can I just give you a piece of advice?
- Oh, no, Hugh.
Speaking as someone who's been
married for over two decades.
I mean, love is wonderful,
but it's not all you need.
You also need things
like life insurance
and PPOs and unromantic
things, like mortgages.
I get that.
I mean, I'm sure
I'll have all those things one day,
but I do think
that love comes first, you know?
At the end of the day,
what's more important than that?
KEITH: Oxygen.
Shut up, Keith.
(CHUCKLES)
You know, I've seen it firsthand.
I know what it's like
when it's there,
and I know what it's
like when it's not.
So you've been in love before.
No, no. (CHUCKLES)
But my parents were.
They met when they were in high
school, and it made sense.
That's what I wanna find.
True love.
The kind that you fight for,
that you always put first.
That makes you wanna
be good and do better.
And not just with any girl.
But "the" girl.
And when I find that,
that's all I need.
HUGH: Homeless and in love.
Sounds great.
Maybe I should have said
I was going to college.
- (CHUCKLING)
- Yeah.
I hope that you find that, David.
Thank you.
I mean, you and Hugh did.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh.
To love.
(ANNE CHUCKLES)
HUGH: Yes, to love.
- To love.
- DAVID: To love.
- JADE: To love.
- (GLASSES CLINKING)
I found what you said inspiring.
And inspiration has been in
short supply these days.
Uh, Jade tells me you're a writer.
Oh, I was a writer.
I wrote one book, but then, um,
life got in the way, so...
I've never met an author before.
If I got one of your books,
would you sign it for me?
(CHUCKLING)
Sure.
- Thanks. (CHUCKLES)
- Thank you.
Good night, David.
Thank you, sir.
- Good night.
- ANNE: Good night.
(CHUCKLES)
JADE: David!
She's leaving in two weeks. What
do you think he wants with her?
He's falling in love with her.
Well, she's not ready for that.
(CHUCKLES) Of course she is.
She's 17. It's her time.
She's never expressed any interest.
Oh, you haven't exactly let her.
So what should I do?
I should just encourage her to fall
in love and have her heart broken?
Yes, you should.
I think she'd be great at it.
I was.
Don't make this about us.
(FLOOR CREAKS)
Careful.
(SHUSHING)
You're shaking.
Good shaking.
We don't have to do this.
As much as I want to,
I can wait.
I don't wanna wait.
I wanna feel this with you.
Fast.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Who are you texting?
That's unbelievably rude,
after what we just did.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(CHUCKLES)
(JADE CHUCKLES)
So...
Don't you have to be at
your dad's shop soon?
I should probably go
before everyone wakes up.
(CHUCKLES)
It's mine now.
Your first present to me.
(CHUCKLES)
I remember him.
You do?
Yeah.
We were in seventh grade
when he was a senior.
(CHUCKLES)
He was good. I remember that.
He was good.
What's it like to have lost him?
My dad, he saved us all.
After Chris got cancer, he stopped
working to take care of him.
We wouldn't have got
through it without him.
And we're doing so
much better, really.
I'm lucky that way.
Some families never heal,
and we're doing so well.
It's okay if none of that is true.
But it is.
I know. I'm just saying
it's okay if it's not.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
JADE: Enlarged ventricles.
Cardiomegaly.
Course of treatment?
Check the patient's kidneys.
Could be in renal failure.
That's good.
So you can stay for
the next surgery.
I've got an angioplasty
starting at 2:00.
Oh. I actually have plans.
I'm sorry.
Does he know that this thing is gonna
be ending in a couple of weeks?
'Cause the kid at dinner last
night didn't really seem to know.
Of course he does.
I thought we had the summer.
I know, but it's too competitive.
I can't turn it down.
Say something.
I don't care.
I don't.
I don't care if we have 10
days, or one week or one day.
I want you to spend it with me.
(CHUCKLES)
And if I do?
(INHALES)
I promise you
they'll be the best
10 days of your life.
(CHUCKLES)
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
Have a snack!
(SCREAMING)
There's two more days.
You better have something
amazing planned.
Maybe.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(LAUGHING)
(CHEERING)
I love you, too.
(BEEPING)
I don't wanna leave.
Tell me to stay.
I want to, but...
I don't care about the internship.
I want to be with
you for the summer.
- You mean that?
- Yeah.
- Then stay.
- (CHUCKLES)
Stay.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- Stay.
- (CHUCKLING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Oh, you're home late.
I'm tired, Dad. Please.
Can I just ask you why
you're unpacking?
I called Dr. Fitzgerald.
I'm not taking the internship.
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
So David put you up to this?
No. It was my decision.
The internship is your
ticket into medical school.
It's not something you
can just walk away from.
I know. But I'm an
incoming freshman
and I have four years
to find another ticket.
I went out on a limb with
Dr. Fitzgerald for you.
I'm sorry. But I'm allowed
to change my mind.
So, this has nothing
to do with David?
No.
Then what's going on?
We used to talk.
This doesn't make sense.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Maybe I do want more
time with David.
Honey.
- You must have felt this way once.
- (SIGHS)
With Mom?
Yeah. But we hadn't just
graduated high school.
I was through medical school by the
time your mom and I got serious.
That's not where I am.
- Well...
- I'm here now,
and I've never felt
this way about anyone.
I thought about it,
and I dreamt about it.
I just never thought it
would actually happen.
And now that it has,
I need more time.
(SIGHS)
You know, of all the reasons
to sacrifice something that
you've worked so hard for,
a boy.
It's very unlike you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
What's going on?
Ah, we're going to the lake house.
Get dressed. Your bathing
suit's still in the dryer.
For the weekend?
- Hi, Jade.
- Hi.
Um, I don't know.
Uh, pack enough for
a couple of weeks.
Your sentence begins now.
Heard about the internship.
Nice to know I'm not the
only one disappointing Dad.
You didn't tell me we were
going to the lake house.
Well, I think we need it, Jade.
I think we need to spend
time together as a family.
I think we're drifting.
I don't wanna go! You know that!
I can't leave David now!
You're going to the lake
house with your family,
and I'm not gonna hear any
more complaints about it.
Get your stuff.
Hey, man. Where you been?
(CHUCKLES)
I was with Jade. Why, you miss me?
Sure, yeah. Most nights I've
been crying myself to sleep.
(CHUCKLES)
UGA?
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
I didn't know you were thinking
about going to college.
Uh, I wasn't until recently.
College boy.
Yeah, I could see that.
Think you got a shot?
Jade's mom's gonna write a
letter of recommendation.
Plus, she used to work there, so...
I'm still gonna work in the shop.
Oh...
I like the idea.
I was wondering how I'd
afford early retirement.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
ANNE: Wait, wait a minute.
I have the key.
Anyone wanna take a swim?
No, we're starving. I'm gonna
take Sabine into town.
Can we bring something back?
HUGH: No, I'm fine.
- Sense of humor? Jagermeister, maybe?
- (CHUCKLING)
Do you want anything?
No.
I'll take a swim with you.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
JADE: I'll get it.
- Hey.
- Thank God you're here.
- ANNE: Hey.
- These are for you.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much for having me.
You have a beautiful house.
- JADE: Amazing, isn't it?
- What are you doing here, David?
Uh, Jade invited me.
Keith invited Sabine. I don't
see what the problem is.
The problem is this is
meant to be a family trip.
I'm sorry, but inviting David
was never part of the plan.
(SIGHS)
He didn't know?
It's fine, David.
- The more the merrier.
- HUGH: No, it's not fine.
ANNE: Hugh, please.
Well, he's here now, and I
don't want him to leave.
Well, that's not up to you.
Actually, it is.
He's my guest and he's staying.
(EXHALES)
Jade just became a woman.
You didn't tell your dad?
He's never gonna forgive me now.
He'll get over it, I promise.
Now you have the perfect chance to
show him how wonderful you are.
What are you doing?
Come on. (CHUCKLES)
Come on!
Really?
Take it off.
Come on.
Hurry up!
- (SCREAMING)
- Whoo!
I don't even recognize her.
And you know, she would never
act this way before him.
I think she's right on track.
Giving up the internship
is right on track?
Didn't it ever worry you that
she wasn't out in the world
experiencing life?
She spent the past two years either by
our sides or with her nose in a book.
She deserves to have
fun this summer.
Well, she was mourning her brother.
You can't expect her to go to a
slumber party every weekend.
I know very well who
she was mourning.
She just lost her teenage years
and now she's finding them.
HUGH: Yeah, with a total stranger.
We don't know anything about him.
(SIGHS)
She is falling in love, Hugh.
When did you last see her
this happy? Hmm? When?
I don't know.
That's something you wanna end?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
HUGH: (STAMMERING)
I gotta say something.
I need to apologize to David.
I might have overreacted
slightly when you arrived,
and, uh, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
So, maybe, clean slate?
Yeah, that would be great.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
Nice. Cheers.
Thanks, Dad.
ANNE: Aw, that was beautiful.
Berries, anyone?
Mom, David finished your book.
- I loved it.
- She's an amazing writer, right?
Yeah, maybe you'll feel
ready to write again soon.
- You should.
- Yeah, maybe.
You reminded me how
much I love reading
and how much more I need to do.
Well, you'll have more
books than you know
what to do with at the
University of Georgia.
You think I have a chance?
Of course. With your SATs?
And Mom's letter.
They love her there.
So, you're applying to college?
Yeah. Yeah.
Second semester. Hopefully.
DAWN: Knock, knock.
- Hi.
- ANNE: Oh.
I didn't know Dawn was here.
No, neither did I.
- HUGH: Hey.
- Hi.
- HUGH: How are you?
It's a work colleague of Hugh's.
I think I met her at the party.
You know what?
I'm feeling inspired.
I'm gonna go inside and write
that letter. (CHUCKLES)
Hey.
- Hey.
- Do you wanna do something fun?
- Yeah.
(SCREAMING)
Whoo!
Yeah!
ALL: One, two, three!
(ALL CHEERING)
(JADE CHUCKLES)
We need more sparklers!
- What?
- We need more sparklers.
Okay. I'll go get some.
KEITH:
Yeah. Top shelf in the garage.
(DOOR LOCK CLICKS)
What?
- What?
- Did you hear something?
- JADE: David, did you find them?
- What?
- Uh, no, we're all out.
- We can't be.
I said we're all out, okay?
Okay. Jeez.
(EXHALES)
(FIREWORKS EXPLODING)
(DOOR OPENS)
HUGH: David, you're up early.
Uh...
Good morning.
Yeah. Yeah, it is, isn't it?
Listen, I was thinking about taking
the boat out for a little spin.
Ah, I'm just gonna get some coffee.
I'll make you one to go.
I'm gonna wait for Jade.
She's not gonna be up for hours.
Gets that from her mother.
Come on, it'll be fun.
(ENGINE REVVING)
(SIGHS)
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah, we bought the place in
'96, and the kids were just...
A little poison ivy, a few too many
mosquitoes, but I just love it.
And you know, no matter what
was happening in our lives,
we could come out here because
nothing would seem as bad.
At least that was the idea.
There's no need for any of this.
You can just get to the point where
you ask me about last night.
Last night?
You and that woman you work with.
I don't know what
you think you saw.
I do.
I know exactly what I saw.
I'd be very careful, David.
That's a serious accusation
you're about to make.
If you think I'm gonna
tell Jade, I'm not.
If that's the reason why
you brought me out here.
But I'll tell you this.
If she found out,
it would kill her.
There's nothing to tell.
But if you continue down this
road, you will regret it.
You understand?
You've been quiet all day.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm all right.
I'm just tired.
Our dad's finally getting
to you, isn't he?
Does he compare you to
Chris, or is it just me?
It's all right. Your dad's
just having a hard time.
(CHUCKLES)
No, he's been having a
hard time for a while now.
He's an asshole.
He just can't hide it anymore.
"And Chris wouldn't even
know what a frat party was!
"Communications? Isn't
that for yoga instructors?
"Arizona State?
Why not major in alcoholism?
"I mean, Jesus Christ, Keith!
"Could you just be better?
"Could you just do something?"
(CHUCKLES)
It's fine. I don't...
I don't really care.
It doesn't matter.
I'll never be anything like him.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
Hey. The kids went into town.
You up for a movie?
- I'm returning a bunch of calls.
- Okay.
This is Dr. Butterfield
for Detective Sutton.
He's a patient.
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
- (ALL SCREAMING)
Hey. What's up?
I missed all this.
(LAUGHING)
Let's be young and dumb,
just for tonight.
Done.
- Come on.
- Okay.
(GIRL CHEERING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Ah! Hey! What are you doing here?
Oh, you'd know if
you ever called me.
Listen, we all went
in on a houseboat.
We've been partying for the
last five days straight.
- I miss you, man.
- I miss you, too.
(CHUCKLES)
And what about me? Hey.
It's good to see you, too.
Yeah, this party's done.
We're gonna take off.
You two should join.
- Where to?
- We're gonna go to the zoo.
We're gonna sneak in after it closes,
we're gonna get a little high,
and then we're gonna hang out
with the wildlife. Huh? Huh?
All right, we're gonna
get a lot high.
Trust me, there's nothing like it.
I think we're just
gonna stay here, man.
No, I wanna go. Can we go?
No. We're gonna stay here.
What? Let's go. Come on.
She wants to go.
ANNE: Dear Helen,
this letter may come off
slightly unconventional,
but that seems to fit David.
It's difficult to put into words,
but his presence has affected
not only my daughter,
but our entire family.
You know, we don't have to do this.
I'm fine. I want to.
Charlie!
- (LAUGHS) What up?
- What up, dawg?
Hey, this is my boy, Charlie.
Turns his head every
time, all right?
Hey.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ooh, welcome to my zoo.
ANNE: He is filled with so
much light and so much love
that I can't believe this won't
translate into a very bright future.
KEITH: Fifty!
ANNE: Quite simply...
Ready or not, here I come.
ANNE: ...he's sparked
something in all of us.
A laughter in my son.
MACE: Run, run!
ANNE: An awakening in my daughter.
(CHUCKLES)
No!
(JADE CHUCKLING)
(KISSING)
(GROWLING)
Hey-ya! Okay-ya!
(ALL SCREAMING)
ANNE: A desire in me.
(SIGHS)
A desire for what?
ANNE: To be in love again.
Jade's about to leave.
We could go anywhere, start over.
I remember who you are.
Oh.
Who we were.
Are you in love with him, too?
(HUFFS)
Of course I'm not.
I love the way that he
loves our daughter.
I'm still in love with you.
It's a good letter.
I can mail it tomorrow
after my swim.
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CHUCKLING)
SABINE: Nice!
- DAVID: Let's go, come on.
- (MACE WHOOPING)
- (LAUGHING)
- DAVID: This is amazing.
- Wow.
- (TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Wow.
SABINE: I want this one.
- MACE: This is crazy.
- KEITH: This is amazing.
- MACE: Gwen. Get over here.
- DAVID: This is awesome.
MACE: Whoo!
I'm coming to get you.
WOMAN OPERATOR:
911. What is your emergency?
Hey. Um...
I just saw some kids break
into the zoo down on Lakeview.
Mmm-hmm.
MACE: Yes!
Love is in the air, Davey.
What's that smile for?
I'm thinking of asking
Sabine to marry me.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Does Jade know?
No one does.
I didn't even really
know until an hour ago.
Congratulations.
My dad, he'll, uh, most likely
try and talk me out of it,
and he'll probably
win, but for now...
For now, you're proposing.
For now, I'm proposing.
And hopefully eloping.
You know, man,
I'm really glad you came.
Thank you.
And I'm glad you're with my sister.
I haven't seen her this happy
since Chris was alive.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, Mace! What is that?
Oh, shoot, it's the cops.
Come on, we gotta go.
(SIREN WAILING)
KEITH: Come on, go, go, go!
DAVID: We gotta get out of here.
- JADE: Hurry.
- MACE: Move, move, move!
- KEITH: Jade! Sabine, let's go.
- Mace.
- What?
- Mace, take them.
- MACE: What?
- She can't get caught. Take them!
- JADE: No!
- Jade. Jade, come on!
- Come with us, David!
- Go! Go!
Go, go, go!
MACE: Like, today! Come on!
POLICE: There he is!
Hey! Over here!
KEITH: Come on, Sabine.
You, stop!
MACE: Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Hurry up!
- Get over here!
- (PANTING)
POLICE: Stop!
- (SIRENS WAILING)
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
Put your hands up in the air!
(PANTING)
Mom. Mom, wake up.
(GASPS) Jade.
- Jade. What's wrong?
- (SHUSHING)
- Shh.
- What's happened?
There was a reason I didn't
invite David on this trip.
I know, but it's because of David
that I'm not in jail, too.
No, it's because of David
that you've changed.
And not for the better.
Hugh, are you not
gonna go and get him?
I've learned a few
things about David.
It's not gonna be his
first night in jail.
We never really knew him
or what he's capable of.
You've been digging into his past?
Oh, rightfully so. He didn't think
to share this with you, did he?
I'm sure there's a perfectly
good explanation.
Well, yeah, he's a criminal.
And that's why he's
behind bars as we speak.
This could cost him his
college, his future.
He doesn't have a future, Jade.
And he's gonna make sure that
you don't have one either.
This is the kind of guy you
really want to fight for?
Yes! I don't care about his past.
There's nothing you can say that will
change the way I feel about him.
- Mom, please!
- Look, this is ridiculous!
I'm calling the station. Stop it.
Anne.
Please, Dad.
Get him out.
I love him.
On one condition.
Anything.
(SIREN WAILING)
As happy as I am to see you, I was
hoping it wasn't gonna be you.
Ah.
I'm sorry. Uh...
I'll pay you back. I promise.
I'm not concerned about the money.
Where's Jade?
She's at home.
She just knew it would make
things harder if she came.
I'm taking you to your car, David.
You're not coming back to
the lake house with us.
Hey, hang on. What do you mean?
Your relationship with
my daughter is over.
It's time to let her go. Let her
have the success she deserves.
Is that what she wants or
is that what you want?
She is not here to
pick you up, is she?
I'll ask her myself.
She's taking the internship.
Yeah, she decided this morning.
This is just a summer fling.
It's not real love.
(SCOFFS)
You're in no position to lecture
me on what real love is.
You have no idea what
goes on in my marriage.
No.
No, I don't.
But I know you have
this incredible family.
I see how you treat them. I would
never treat Jade that way.
Oh. Oh.
Tell me, how would you
treat her, David?
Go ahead, tell me.
Like that kid in the police report?
I did a little research.
Is that the kind of person you
think I want for my daughter?
That was a long time ago.
That's not me.
I would've thought you would have
learned more from your past.
I'm sure your father must have.
Don't you talk about my dad.
No, I mean, everything I hear,
he sounds like a great guy.
Works hard, puts a roof over
your head, does the best he can.
It was never quite enough for
your mother, though, was it?
You have nothing.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
One day you get home early from
school, there's another man there.
And what do you do, David?
You beat him.
You beat him so badly he has to
be taken away in an ambulance.
So he goes to the hospital, you go
to juvie, and your mom takes off.
You know that love that you
talked about at dinner?
You're never gonna have that.
It doesn't exist.
Your story isn't gonna end any
differently than your parents' did.
Jade will get bored with you.
Just like your mom got bored.
And how are you going
to handle yourself when
that happens again, David? Huh?
Because it will.
It doesn't matter how hard you try.
You're not gonna be
able to hang on to her.
She is gonna get to Brown.
She is gonna meet somebody like
her, smart, with a future,
and she's gonna leave.
And she won't look back.
You know why?
Because you're not good enough.
You're just like your father.
(GROANS)
Oh.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, thank you, David.
You had my entire family fooled.
Never me.
This is the real you.
This is exactly who you are.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Oh, my God!
What happened?
What do you think? David lost it.
I tried to fend him off, and he...
I don't believe you.
Look at me.
He completely lost control.
I told him you were leaving...
You told him?
Why would you tell him that?
Because you wouldn't have.
And it's time he knows the truth.
Jade, what...
No.
He peppers him with a right,
he peppers him with a left.
He's got Hugh Butterfield
in the corner.
(CHUCKLING) What's he up to?
Damn, did you hit her dad?
That's messed up, even for you.
You should've never taken
us there last night.
Whoa.
It sucks that you got caught,
but it's not my fault.
It was stupid, Mace,
and you know it.
It was fun.
Until it got stupid.
But it was fun.
Come on, man, we used to do
shit like that all the time.
Yeah, but back then I didn't
have anything to lose.
So, what, you're going
to Brown now, too?
Oh, great. You invited Jenny.
How big do you think
our houseboat is?
(SIGHS)
She still cares about you,
okay? We all do.
I know you've been lost
in this whole Jade world.
But you had a whole
life before her.
You might want to remember that.
Hey.
Sounds like you had quite a night.
Yeah.
Where's Jade?
I don't want to talk about it.
What, she didn't
come to pick you up?
Just let it go, okay?
Hey, I'm here as a friend.
Nothing else.
Now, come on.
Move over.
David, come on, you had
to see this coming.
Girls like Jade Butterfield,
they just think they're
settling for guys like you.
(SIGHS)
But funny,
smart girls like me,
they know how lucky they are.
Jade.
(BELL DINGS)
Jade, stop.
- That didn't take long, did it?
- Listen to me.
Mace called Jenny, okay?
- Not me.
- What?
It's true. You hit him.
You don't know what he's like.
What does that mean?
That he deserved to be hit?
What did he do?
Tell me.
Wait, wait, Jade, please.
You have to trust me.
How? He told me what
happened with your mom.
Why would you keep that a secret?
I wouldn't have cared if
you had just told me.
I was ashamed, okay?
I was ashamed.
I hate what my mom did to my dad.
And I hated what I did.
If you thought I was such an angel,
maybe you should never
have bothered with me.
So that's it? You're
just gonna walk away?
I know I'm not good enough for you.
But I'm not gonna spend my
entire life proving that I am.
You're a coward, you know that?
You don't fight for love.
You're terrified of it!
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
Jade!
Jade.
Jade Butterfield? Where is she?
Room 376.
KEITH: Mom.
- Hey.
Sweetie.
What happened?
(SNIFFLES) Honey, you were in a
car accident, but you're okay.
Where's David?
HARRY: David.
Dad.
Thanks for coming.
Any word?
No, they won't let me in.
Who's...
How is she?
Hugh Butterfield.
Harry. Harry Elliot.
You got a minute?
HARRY: Is she gonna be all right?
She's got a broken wrist,
among other things.
Thank God it wasn't worse.
Look. Uh...
We'd appreciate it if you
would show this to David.
And once we've seen
a judge on Monday,
he's a close personal
friend of family,
it will no longer be temporary.
Now, wait a minute.
I know how you must feel,
but they're just kids.
David, he's only 18. He's got
his whole life ahead of him.
My daughter made a
choice to move on.
He didn't respect that and
he knew the conditions.
That he couldn't get in a
fight with his girlfriend?
That he couldn't sneak into a zoo?
David's not a criminal, he's
just a kid with shit luck.
That doesn't warrant
a restraining order.
Your son hit me in the face!
And if you think I'm gonna let my
daughter get anywhere near him,
you're out of your mind.
She could've died
out on that street.
He can behave like
a reckless idiot,
he can screw up his
future all he wants...
You say one more unkind
word about my son
and I'll make sure you
can't say another.
50! 50 feet!
If he comes within 50 feet of
her, he's gonna be arrested,
and I'll sue you for everything
you've got. I've lost a child.
I'm not losing another.
Not for you
or your lowlife son.
You shouldn't be here, Jade.
I know, but I just
wanted to say goodbye
and his cell phone isn't working.
That's 'cause I took
it away from him.
Last thing I need is a
cop showing up here
'cause your daddy sees our
number on the phone bill.
Now, I'm sorry, honey.
I won't say anything, I promise.
That's not how it works.
I got to protect my son now
and talking to you ain't
gonna do him any favors.
Can you at least tell
him that I love him?
Don't ask that, Jade.
That's not fair.
You go to college,
you start your life.
That's the best thing you
can do for David now.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What's up, Big D?
What's going on, man?
NESBITT: So why don't you
tell me why you're here.
I guess my dad wanted
me to talk to someone.
I've been going to your
dad's shop for a long time,
and he's never made
this call, so...
I guess he wants me to feel better.
To move on.
NESBITT:
And you don't think you can?
DAVID: I don't think I should.
Maybe for some people,
they find the one that they're meant
to spend the rest of their lives with.
Right when their lives
are starting out.
What if Jade's the one
and I let her go?
I would regret that for
the rest of my life.
I just... I love it here.
I'm sorry. Do you want
me to leave you alone?
No. I'm just missing home.
NESBITT: Time helps.
It's slow and it's
painful, but it works.
Talking helps.
Going out with other
people, seeing friends.
And she'll be like a
book you read long ago.
I always wanted a Porsche.
You know? It's the life...
You think that's possible?
If you trust that if it's meant
to be, then it will be again.
And if it's not, you
will wake up one day
and realize that you haven't
even thought of her once.
And then you'll be free.
Are you all right, son?
No.
What do you want, David?
I want her.
I don't know why you
don't understand that.
Yeah, maybe I just didn't wanna.
What happened with your
mom, that was my fault.
I worked too hard.
I didn't make her happy.
Maybe she never loved me.
I don't know.
I never fought for her.
But I saw you and Jade together.
She loved you.
She believed in you.
I'm not letting you make
the same mistake I did.
Fight for her.
He'll take the shop
and he'll sue you.
You let that asshole try.
You love this girl?
Yeah, I love her.
You really love her?
Yeah.
Then you fight for her and I'll
be proud of you if you do.
I always wondered who did that.
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Shameful but necessary.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Do you want to get a coffee?
You didn't know Hugh
before all this.
I haven't lost all hope.
If we can get through
losing a child,
we can get through anything.
I know what's been done, David.
Don't judge me, you've
never been married.
How is she?
Uh...
She has a boyfriend.
His name is Miles.
He's pre-med, too.
You didn't want to
hear that, sorry.
It doesn't change anything.
I didn't think so.
Is she coming home for Christmas?
She is, but Hugh's never gonna
let her out of his sight.
He has his daughter back and
he's not gonna let her go now.
Just tell me where she'll be.
I'll meet her anywhere,
anywhere you would arrange.
I can't, David. I'm so sorry.
Anne, please.
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PA)
(SIGHS)
David didn't get into UGA.
Did you know that?
Uh, no, I didn't.
Although I'm not surprised.
I am.
It's why I called Helen and she
said she never got my letter.
You told me it went
out with the mail.
It did.
Oh, Hugh.
How could you have fallen this far?
You've ruined this kid's future.
He's barely keeping afloat.
How do you know how
he's keeping afloat?
Because I saw him, Hugh.
It wasn't fair of you.
It's not right.
You saw him?
Yes, I did.
And did he ask about Jade?
(CHUCKLES) Of course he did.
Did you tell him that
she's arriving today?
Hugh?
Hugh.
Hugh, this is it.
How you act right now determines
the rest of our lives.
Let this go.
Stop persecuting the poor kid
and look at who you've become.
No.
(WOMAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PA)
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
- Sir.
- I got to get back there.
- You got to get back in line.
- Listen, my daughter may be in danger.
We have a restraining order...
Do you have a ticket for
a departing flight?
Please slow down, sir. Walk.
- WOMAN: Oh.
- Sorry.
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- No, David, I can't.
- I'm sorry.
I had to see you.
I know it's crazy.
You could be arrested, David.
- My dad's here. You could go to jail.
- I know.
Just hear me out, okay?
Two tickets.
We can leave tonight.
We could go anywhere.
This isn't over, Jade.
I refuse to believe it's over.
I haven't moved on.
And I don't think you have either.
Do you love this other guy?
Do you love him like you love me?
Do you?
(EXHALES)
Of course not.
I won't love anyone
like I love you.
- We're leaving tonight.
- Okay.
- Okay. We'll figure it out.
And we'll leave this place behind.
You promise?
- I promise.
- Okay.
Go.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I got a restraining
order against a guy
who may have just gone
through security.
She's on a flight from Providence.
- She's at Gate 11 and I got to get back there.
- Dad.
- Hi.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah, it's fine.
- Yeah.
- We're fine.
- Okay. Have a nice day.
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
Were you driving the MG?
No, it must have been Keith.
KEITH: This is the one.
When the CD player blew, we had to
bring all the records downstairs.
- SABINE: It's awesome.
- (KEITH CHUCKLES)
What are you doing in here?
We were just listening.
He always had the best records.
This is not supposed to...
Oh, look at this. You scratched it.
You're supposed to put them back
in the sleeves immediately.
Dad, they're just records.
These are just things.
He'd want us to play them.
He's not here to ask, is he?
- No, I guess he's not.
- (SIGHS)
Keith.
- Where are you going?
- Sabine's.
Keith, what happened?
We disturbed the museum. I can't...
Every time I try to make
any kind of effort,
he just lashes out at me,
and I won't do it anymore.
I'm so sorry.
He has no respect
for Chris' things.
He knows better.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
- Where are you going?
- I'm going with my son.
- (CAR DOOR CLOSES)
- (ENGINE STARTS)
HUGH: I'm sorry, honey.
(SIGHS)
You can't make the
rules for us anymore.
- We're adults.
- Well, then act like one.
You have wanted me to
choose this entire time.
Well, finally, I have.
I choose to live my own life.
I choose David.
Jade. Jade.
Jade.
Jade!
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
- (CELL PHONE BEEPS)
- Hi.
(WHISPERING) I'll be right out.
DAVID: Okay.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(EXHALES)
JADE: What are you doing?
Dad! Dad!
Dad, stop!
Whoa.
I warned you, David. You are
not taking my daughter.
- Whoa.
- JADE: Dad!
Get back in your car.
- Get the hell off my property.
- Dad, don't! Dad!
I told you to stay
away from my family!
Hey, she wants to go with me!
- Please! Dad!
- Get back in your fucking car!
Dad, stop! You're gonna kill him!
She wants to be with me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Let's go. Come on.
(SIGHING DEEPLY)
(SNIFFLES)
(FIRE ALARM BEEPING)
Oh, no, no.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Dad!
Oh, no, no.
Oh.
Hugh?
DAVID: Hugh? Keith?
(COUGHING)
Hugh?
Hugh, come on. We got to go.
Help me get his things!
There's too much smoke. Come on.
Don't open the window!
(GROANS)
(HORN BLARING)
My dad and my boyfriend are inside!
- Inside? Upstairs? Downstairs?
- I don't know!
David!
We gotta go!
(GRUNTING)
Here. (GRUNTS)
You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
- (GRUNTING)
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
David!
(DAVID COUGHING)
I'm okay.
Wait! Wait, where's Anne? Keith!
They're gone!
(COUGHING)
Hugh!
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GROANING)
Hugh! (COUGHS)
Hugh.
(COUGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, my God.
(SOBBING)
Dad!
(COUGHING)
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
David!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PA)
Anne's on her way.
(SIGHS)
I couldn't save him.
I tried.
I just...
I just couldn't.
And what I've done...
The people I've hurt.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how this happened.
(EXHALES)
It's okay.
It's not too late.
I think he's been punished enough.
Let him take you to the airport.
He wants to. He told me so.
Hmm?
Yeah?
- Okay.
- Good.
Let's go.
JADE:
How are you, Mom? Will you be okay?
ANNE: I don't know. (CHUCKLES)
This is something that your
father and I need to do.
It doesn't mean that a part
of me won't always love him,
and maybe we'll find our way
back to each other, one day.
I don't want to leave
you like this.
I need you to.
It's your love that inspires me, Jade.
(CHUCKLES)
Inspire me every day.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
(SEATBELT CLICKS)
I'm here if you need me.
And even if you don't,
that's okay, too.
(SQUEALS)
California? That's a
long way back to Brown.
- Mmm-hmm.
- What exactly do you have planned?
I'm sworn to secrecy, sorry.
But we've got two days before
we go back to Rhode Island,
so I thought I'd make
them the best two days.
- Tell me.
- I can't.
Surprise!
- What?
- KEITH: Yeah.
My God.
- (CHUCKLING) Hey.
- Hi.
Oh, my God.
- Hey.
Mom's gonna kill you,
you know that, right?
Then we'll just have
to do it twice, then.
I, Keith, take you,
Sabine, to be my wife.
JADE: My first love was
everything all at once.
The kind you never fall back from.
Never try to.
Never want to.
A love so big, so strong,
it never dies, never fades,
never loses its electricity.
The kind of love you fight for.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org