Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Uh, what about,
"The Big One only gets bigger"?
"Everyone wants a Big One."
I got a big one. Sorry.
How about just, like, "Eat me."
Okay, okay. There's no shortage
of future slogans. Phil, what have you got?
Well, um, same-store sales
are up 8.4% this quarter...
which is just... amazing.
And the increase extends
across every demographic.
It's "tweens," heavy users,
minivan dads, even seniors.
So, clearly, the Big One
is not only a big hit...
it is quickly becoming
the flagship of our brand.
Which we'll be building on, both in
the upcoming second half of our campaign...
and in merchandising.
Terrific. Don, what about
those Little Big Ones?
Well, uh, last week, you know,
we did a pretty extensive focus group...
with some of the kids
from Martin Luther King Elementary.
- Yeah?
- And it went great.
Tested 91% in the top three boxes.
They loved 'em.
What is it now, eight to a bag?
- No, no, no. You're thinking
about the Itty Bittys.
- Oh.
No, no. We figure three Little Big Ones
for each kid's meal...
is gonna work out about right.
But we wanna do a little more
testing on that as well.
- How about Disney?
- No word yet.
Also, the PBS deal
doesn't seem to be happening.
Uh, apparently Burger King and McDonald's
have the Teletubbies all locked up.
Fuck 'em.
That's wonderful.
Yeah? You like that?
That's the Barbecue Big One.
Wow. Tastes like it's
right off the grill.
You don't think it needs liquid smoke
or any other kind of flavorings?
No. No, no, no.
I think it's perfect.
- Let's test that.
- Okay. Try this one.
- I don't know.
- Yeah. These Caribbean seasonings
are kind of tricky.
We're calling 'em
Calypso Chicken Tenders.
I think people are gonna
have an expectation for, uh...
maybe a touch of lime.
Oh, lime? Lime's easy.
I just held back on the terpinoline on this
to keep the flavorings subtle.
But I can always go back
and add more.
- Yeah. Why don't you try that?
- I'll keep working on it.
I really, really enjoyed it. You were wonderful.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay. Look, I gotta go.
I'll talk to you later.
Yeah, bye.
Thanks, Louise.
Donny boy. Have a seat.
Thanks for stopping by.
So, what do you think of everything?
It's good, good.
I'm glad to see the Big One doin' so well.
Hmm. Listen, you ever
run into a guy named Harry Rydell...
executive V.P.
out of the Chicago office?
I don't think so.
He works closely with our suppliers.
A little too closely, if you ask me.
What do you mean?
I have a friend that teaches food science
over at A&M- microbiology.
And this semester,
a couple of his grad students...
decided to culture some patties
from a bunch of fast-food chains.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well-
They got ahold of a couple
of Big Ones- frozen patties.
Don't ask me how.
And the fecal coliform counts
were just off the charts.
I'm concerned that this
could be a problem for us.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Uh- Not exactly.
I'm saying there's shit in the meat.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm.
"The drawbridge was down.
The great gate stood wide.
"I entered without challenge...
my own heels making
the only sounds I heard."
- Keep going.
- No.
- It's bedtime.
- Just one more.
- Please.
- No. That's it.
Good night, Stevie.
Hey.
- I think I may have to miss
your history exhibit on Thursday.
- Why?
Well, you know how Daddy has to go
out of town for work every now and then?
- Yeah, but I thought you didn't have to.
- Well, not as much.
But I gotta go to Colorado
for a couple of days.
All right? I'll be home
for the weekend though.
Okay.
I love you guys.
Too much E. coli in stuff. People could get sick.
Is that the one that can kill kids?
I don't know. I don't think so.
I mean,
nobody's gotten sick or anything.
But Jack says too much cow manure
is somehow getting into the meat.
That's disgusting.
That's my new job. Same office-
still dealing with bullshit.
Well, I guess it is a marketing issue after all.
If the kids die
from eating your burgers...
it makes them much harder to sell.
That's right. Marketing 101.
Don't kill the customer.
Bad for repeat business.
Mm-hmm.
¿Coco?
Hi.
No.
I sent that form in. I paid it.
Hey, you tell that coach
and that whole fucking league...
if he doesn't play,
I'm gonna kick all their asses.
Sí. Yeah, yeah.
I just did a pickup.
I'll talk to you later.
Gracias.
No.
- Sí.
Oh, God! Yeah!
You like the way that feels?
Oh, my gosh!
That's right, bitch.
- Do you like it when I pull your hair?
- Yes! Yes, pull my hair!
- That's right, slut.
- I love it when you call me "slut."
Let's go. Stand up.
Yo. Stand up.
Come on. Stand up.
Hey!
Stand up.
What the fuck you doin'?
Fuckin' people on vacation.
Go.
Hang on a second.
Welcome to Mickeys.
Can I take your order?
Yeah. I'm thinkin' about a Big One.
Okay. Would you like
some large fries with that?
No. No, thanks. Not tonight.
- Our supervalue drink?
- I'll have a chocolate shake and a water.
All right. Would you like
any dessert with that?
- A brownie pie or a turnover?
- No, not tonight.
Okay. Uh, that'll be 4.98.
Okay. Here you go.
So, what's your favorite thing
on the menu?
I like everything.
Well, I know that's not true.
But you did give me
the correct answer.
I was just testing you. I'm actually
a vice president of marketing for Mickeys.
- Really?
- Yeah. It's true.
Just here in town for a couple of days
seein' where the Big Ones come from.
- Here?
- Oh, no, not here.
But at Uni-Globe Meat Packing
just outside of town.
That's where every single Big One patty
in the entire country gets made.
- No way.
- Yeah.
- It's amazing.
- Wow.
Lettuce.
Pickles and cheese.
Special-
I think I burned the meat.
Amber. Order up.
- There you go.
- Okay. Thank you.
- What's your name?
- Amber.
Right. Don Anderson.
- It's nice to meet you.
- You too.
- Maybe I'll see you around.
- All right. I'm always here.
Bye.
Brian, can I get a Coffee Freezer?
Bring it over to the scalding tank.
Amber, hon,
electric is 131 for last month.
Mom, I gotta pay my car insurance.
Well, anything helps.
So how's your day lookin'?
I have band practice after school,
then work at 6:00.
Well, don't let them
keep you past 10:00.
I'll try to get out of there. Tony's been
pretty cool about letting me out early.
Good.
Hey.
- Hey, Amber.
- Hey, David.
- Hola.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
And right over here, Don...
we mix our product
with a low-fat product...
from about a half a dozen
other plants.
The liquefied gas in the cylinder...
takes 'em down
to 40 degrees below zero!
Wow. That's a lot of Big Ones.
Yeah. Well, somewhere
in Kansas City...
someone will be eating these
tomorrow night.
...can be used to explain
how accidents happen to other people.
But accidents don't just
happen to other people.
Accident prevention
is each individual's responsibility.
This program is designed to make you
think more about accident causes...
and how you can prevent injuries.
If you eliminate
the cause of accidents...
you're on your way to an accident-free
workplace and lifetime.
Safety works in your home also.
It works when you're-
Yo. You heard about
the robbery last night?
- No. Where?
- At the McDonald's over on Cayenne.
They came in at closing time
and put everyone in the basement.
Said they'd get shot
if they came out.
- And boom- 6,000 bucks.
- No way.
- Yeah. 6,000 in cash.
- In cash?
Hell's yeah. How many times you seen somebody
buy their McNuggets with a credit card?
- Good point.
- They said it was the third
fast-food place in Cody...
to get robbed in the last few weeks.
They hit Fuddruckers on Thursday night.
We're probably next.
All the more reason
for you guys to quit.
I mean, why do you even work there?
Not all of us can get hired
at the Banana Republic.
Yo! Fuck y'all doin' in my truck?
Mike.
Yeah, the Big One's been great.
Really great.
Sales keep creepin' up.
There's been no drop off.
That's what we're hearin'.
- I've had this location 12 years.
- Yeah?
And you'd have to go way back-
maybe even to the original Teeny-Weenys
promotion- to see anything like this.
- You guys hit a home run.
- Well, hey, we all did.
Definitely.
Hey, Tony, have you ever-
Have you ever been out to the U.M.P. plant?
Uh, no, I haven't.
I've been hearin' some mixed things
about the place.
I've heard all sorts
of nasty stuff goes on there.
You have? Like what?
I don't know. Um-
I used to have a friend
who used to work there...
and he used to tell me
all sorts of things.
Did you know that's where
the Big Ones come from?
This was a long time back.
I mean-
Look, my friend could have
been full of shit.
Yeah, 'cause I was out there.
I mean, the place is-
It's spotless.
- Yeah?
- Oh, yeah. It's high-tech, state-of-the-art stuff.
Stainless steel everywhere.
People wearin' gloves and clean white coats.
I mean-
Well, might be a lot different now.
So, um, the friend-You think I might
be able to give him a call?
I don't know.
He split a long time ago.
I haven't really talked to him.
Well- Right.
My wife's got an uncle.
He can tell you all about that place.
- Does he work out there?
- Oh, no, no. He used to sell 'em cattle.
But he's a real... character.
You know, been on the ranch
a little too long.
You think he'd talk to me?
Oh, he'll talk to you.
Might scare you though.
He's a little intense.
I'll give you his number.
His name is Rudy.
Hey. Hey!
What the fuck you doin'?
What the fuck-
Are you fuckin' retarded?
Say it. "Grade 'A'." Say it.
- Grade "A."
- Thank you.
Fuckin' know you understand me.
You people act like I'm a fuckin' retard.
- Sí.
- Get back to work.
Coco.
Yeah, like that. Like that.
Like that.
You know, if that safe in McDonald's
was holding six grand...
Tony must have at least five or six
locked away in there.
Maybe more. You think he goes
to the bank every day?
That's a good question.
Tim says that over where he works...
that they don't even have a safe.
That's 'cause nobody ever eats there.
That chicken fajita I had the other night
was some slimy shit.
Yeah, well, there's a reason
why it only costs 99 cents.
There may be five or six grand
in Tony's safe every night...
just sittin' in there, while we're out here
gettin' paid dick to mess with this shit.
Yeah, no kidding.
And Tony's a real prick too,
you know?
I always catch him
checkin' out Amber's ass...
and he's, like, five times her age.
Hey, the cops must have these places
totally staked out at night.
'Cause they're just waitin' for another robbery.
The best time to do it would be
first thing in the morning...
around opening time.
Okay. Here's how it goes down.
We come in here
first thing in the morning.
- It's still dark, no traffic.
- Uh-huh.
Everybody's feelin' calm and sleepy.
We'll be taking this order to go,
motherfucker.
If you got the balls, bitch.
I'm supposed to go out to some ranch.
Maybe that'll be worth something.
I don't know.
Well, I'm meetin' with Harry
on Friday.
So I should be back on Saturday.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Put-Put him on.
- ...but the disease that spreads-
- Who's this?
Hello, Stevie.
Couple of guys invited me to a party
at the "U" on Saturday night.
You wanna come?
Do they know you go to Cody?
For some reason,
they think I'm a freshman in college.
Oh, I wonder why.
One of them is really hot.
Oh, I gotta work that night.
You work way too much.
You the one that called?
Yeah. Hi there. I'm Don.
Climb on over.
- Ever been out here before?
- Nope.
It's beautiful.
You ever been on a ranch before?
Yeah, when I was a kid, at camp.
How, uh- How many acres
do you have, Rudy?
Well, you wouldn't want to have to walk
your way outta here. That's for sure.
Come on up
and meet my new neighbors.
Aw. No.
Aw, geez.
- When did all this happen?
- Last couple of years.
Local rancher lost control
of the land.
Banks took it and sold it
to real estate speculators.
What the hell happened over there?
- Meth freaks.
- Out here?
They find a quiet little place,
start cookin'-
till somethin' blows up
or burns down.
Wow.
Past year and a half,
I've had two bodies dumped on my land.
Dead bodies?
One of 'em was rolled up
in this nice-lookin' carpet.
Scared the shit out of my foreman.
They dump dead dogs and cats...
and all other sorts of garbage
on my land.
Seems like I spend half my time
just defendin' the place.
I gotta go to court next week...
to fight off some private
corporation from Denver...
wants to build a toll road
across my land.
Eminent domain, my ass.
They got another word for it-
robbery.
You wanna open that up for me?
You should get a clicker.
Hey, Rudy. You know anybody
over at Uni-Globe Meat Packing?
- Sure.
- What do you think of 'em?
I think they're a fine bunch.
Really?
They'll slit your throat
for a nickel.
Nothin' personal.
They just want the extra nickel.
- Well, who do you know over there?
- I know all of 'em.
- I sold cattle to 'em for years.
- Oh.
More important, I know their type.
They are the meanest, toughest sons of bitches,
and they're proud of it.
But that's nothin' new.
My granddad went up
against the meat packers in 1919.
Testified in Congress
about their price-fixing.
And after that, none of them
would buy his cattle.
U.M.P. and all the rest
tried to run him out of the business.
- Okay, but that was a long time ago.
- Yeah.
And the big packers are even worse today.
They're even bigger today.
- Really?
- And meaner.
Hell, old Dwight D. Eisenhower
would've shut 'em down.
He wouldn't have stood
for their crap.
Do you think they would knowingly
sell us contaminated meat?
Oh, come on.
Workers are gettin'
their arms cut off over there.
You don't know
who you're dealin' with.
No. No, I don't.
Please, help me.
I- I was at the plant.
It seemed clean to me.
They show you the kill floor?
I don't know.
I saw a lot of things.
You'd remember.
You see any cattle
gettin' their heads cut off?
Were you walkin' ankle-deep in blood?
No.
So they didn't show you a damn thing.
Okay, but how-
How... would cow manure
get into the meat?
Rita.
- No, no. Thanks, I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yes, thank you.
- I'll have some.
Hey, Rita, is your brother
still workin' over at U.M.P.?
How's he doin'?
Oh, he has a good job now.
He's a supervisor in Trim.
- Hmm.
- Mr. Anderson here would like to know...
if the meat over there is clean.
He wants to know how cow manure...
could ever possibly wind up
in his hamburger.
Well, there's lots of ways.
My brother used to work
at the gut table.
And, you know, they have
to pull out the intestines and the stomachs.
And they just don't have enough time
to do it right.
The line is moving too fast.
So when they're pulling the guts out-
and they make a mistake-
all the poop and stuff
just pours out all over the meat.
Okay, okay, okay.
All right.
But, really,
how often does that happen?
Every day.
- We got any cookies back there?
- I'll bring a plate of them.
Anything else you want to know?
No. No, that's, uh, plenty. Thanks.
This isn't about good people
versus bad people.
It's about the machine
that's taking over this country.
It's like somethin'
out of science fiction.
The land, the cattle, human beings.
This machine don't give a shit.
Pennies a pound.
That's all it cares about.
A few more pennies a pound.
Sounds pretty bleak.
By the way, Don,
you seem like a nice fella.
But the food
your company sells is crap-
total crap-
even when there isn't manure in it.
Eh?
Sí.
Bueno.
Ándale.
Thank God old Mr. Nathan come in.
He took one look at me.
Said, "Harry...
"you are the scariest
fucking clown I've ever seen.
Take that off immediately."
And that was that.
I came about that close
to becoming the first Mickey.
Which would have been a disaster,
because I'd have probably killed somebody.
Mmm. What do you think?
I know it's not Mickeys.
- Mmm.
- But it's good, right? Good burger.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's-It's great.
- Harry, what's goin' on out at U.M.P.?
- Beg your pardon?
Yeah, what's really goin' on out there-
with the meat?
You're supposed to be
our conduit to that place.
- They didn't give you the tour?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Who took you through there?
Uh, Terry?
- Oh, boy.
- No, no, no.
He was- Listen, he was great.
He was fine.
I just-
I've been talkin'
to a lot of people around town...
and I've been hearing
some bad things about that plant.
You know, things
they don't show you on the tour.
Sounds like they might be running
the production line too fast, you know?
- Hmm.
- People are gettin' hurt out there every day.
They're gettin' cut up.
One guy lost his entire arm.
These poor Mexicans,
they come over here...
and U.M.P. treats 'em like shit.
And the meat-
I gotta tell you somethin'.
Harry, the meat is filthy.
Do you know they got untrained people
workin' at the gut table?
- Really? The gut table?
- Yeah. I mean-
- Harry, there's shit in our meat.
- Harry.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I heard you were here today.
- How are you doin', huh?
- Ah, can't complain.
- Good. Lisa, I want you to meet Don Anderson.
- He just came to the company from CNN.
- ESPN actually.
- Don is the inventor of the Big One.
- Really?
No. My team came up with the name.
You're just being humble.
It was pure genius, Don.
- It's a good name for a burger, isn't it?
- It sure is.
It's very nice to meet you.
Can I get you another Fat Tire?
I would love another Fat Tire.
You want a beer, Don?
- No, thanks.
- Just one.
- All right.
- Just one. All right.
Mmm!
You know...
I think there might be a little bit of shit
right here in this meat.
Just a teeny little bit.
Microscopic.
Your tests say that the meat
we're getting from U.M.P. is clean.
It's not. I've seen independent tests
that say that it's not.
There's always been
a little shit in the meat.
You've probably been
eatin' it your whole life.
Yeah? Well, I prefer not to, Harry.
Well, I don't know
who you been talkin' to, Don...
but there is absolutely nothing illegal
goin' on here, okay?
Meat is supposed to be cooked.
And the grills at Mickeys
are calibrated carefully...
to make sure it kills every little bit
of the bad stuff that's in there.
- That might be kinda tough
to explain to our customers.
- Explain what?
Listen, there is cow shit in our meat
because we're running the line too fast.
Just cook it.
That's all you need to do.
You see? That's one of the things
that's just buggin' me about this country.
Really buggin' me.
Americans have become
these-these great big fraidy cats.
Afraid of everything.
Everything's gotta be sterile and germfree.
Well, everybody needs to grow up.
That's what they need.
You wanna be safe?
Huh? Perfectly safe?
Well, forget about it.
That's not gonna happen. Okay?
Everybody just needs
to get that through their head.
Just cook the meat,
and you'll be fine.
I can't believe I'm hearing this.
You've known all about this?
I'm shocked.
Donny boy, you just gotta try and step back
and look at the big picture.
40,000 people die
in automobile accidents every year.
Does that mean Detroit
should stop making cars?
Does it?
Of course not.
You ever been down to Mexico?
- What's that have to do with anything?
- It's beautiful down there.
Really beautiful.
Great beaches. Gorgeous.
But poor. Poor.
Poorest fuckin' place
I ever been, I think.
Guy down there makes three,
maybe four dollars a day.
A day, Don.
Now, that same guy,
he comes up here...
he gets a job workin' for U.M.P.-
makin' $10 an hour.
That's more money in one day
than he makes back home in a whole month.
So, frankly, I don't see the problem.
Nobody's makin' these people
come up here. Right?
Nobody's tellin' them
to come work for U.M.P.
- Okay, okay. But that's not the point.
- And you know what?
I admire these people. Okay?
I really do.
They're hard workers.
They're workin' hard, and they're trying
to improve their lives. Okay?
Now, isn't that
what our ancestors did?
Isn't that what made this country
the great country that it is today? Huh?
And you wanna try and stop 'em?
You wanna tell 'em
that you know what's best for 'em?
Well, most people don't like
to be told what's best for 'em.
Well, what's goin' on
at U.M.P. is unacceptable.
And I'm gonna have
to tell Jack about all this.
Oh. Gonna tell Jack, huh?
I've been workin' for this company
almost 30 years.
Hell, I grew up right down the street
from the Nathans...
when we were all back in Muncie.
So, here's my little piece
of friendly advice to you, Donny boy.
I'd be careful
how close I got to Jack.
See, your boy Jack
is about this close...
to gettin' his tit
caught in the ringer.
He's under investigation, okay?
Cookin' the books,
paddin' his expense account.
Not to mention
bonin' his own secretary, okay?
- And that is not the kind of
company that we want to run.
- Louise?
That's right.
Your buddy Jack's got two,
maybe three months before he's out the door.
- Could be sooner.
- He's sleeping with Louise?
And you know what, Don?
You should be thankin' me
instead of doin' all this complainin'.
I negotiated a hell
of a good price with U.M.P.
Okay? I negotiated a great price
for your fuckin' meat.
Hell, if it weren't for me,
there wouldn't be no Big One, Don.
I'd like to see you find a supplier...
that will sell you Grade "A" chuck
at 40 cents a pound.
I'd like to see that.
Have-Have you ever met Louise?
Have I ever met her?
Twenty years ago,
I gave her that job.
She was a good-lookin' woman
back then too.
It is a sad fact of life, Don.
But the truth is...
we all have to eat a little shit
from time to time.
But just for the record, I want you to know
that I'm with you on this.
Okay? I really am.
I'm gonna go down there.
I'm gonna see
what the hell's goin' on.
If I have to,
I'm gonna kick some ass.
You know what, Harry?
I don't think
that's gonna be good enough.
You seem like
a real bright guy, Don.
I'd hate to see you get caught up
in something you couldn't get out of.
Give it some thought.
Why don't you take
some of these fries home with you?
I'm not gonna finish 'em.
No. No, it's not that simple.
There is something definitely weird
going on between Jack and Harry...
and, either way,
I can lose this job.
Either way.
No. No, we're not gonna move again.
That's-
That's not gonna happen.
Well, just tell Jay
to wait a moment.
This is important.
Well, have him wait!
Yeah.
I'll- I'll talk to you later.
No, no. Look, Jack, it's gone great.
I, uh- I've been out to the plant.
I spoke to some workers.
I even tracked down
this old rancher...
who's dealt with these guys for years.
So, there's a lot of things, but-
Yeah. No, of course
I met with Harry.
Yeah. He's-He's a- interesting guy.
You were right.
But I- I don't think that he's...
a crook.
Well, I don't know.
All right.
Then, uh...
I would probably recommend...
we do some additional testing...
in the near future.
See what that shows.
Yeah.
- Will you be keeping this
on your American Express?
- Sure.
- I have three pay-per-view movies at 7.95 each.
- Uh-huh.
- Would you like to join
our Executive Guest Advantage program?
- No.
- Did you enjoy your stay with us?
- Not really.
- Were you here on business or pleasure?
- Business.
Is there anything we can do in the future
to make your stay with us more enjoyable?
You can give me my bill.
Bye-bye, Mr. Anderson.
Have a great day.
Want sharper video quality? Want
clearer audio? Try GOM Player now!