Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
This is the police!
Open up!
Police! Anyone here?
Hey, fella.
Anybody home?
Ma'am, turn around slowly.
Unit 507,
we got a possible homicide.
Requesting backup.
Copy that, 507. Backup is
en route. ETA 10 minutes.
Adrian?
Adrian!
Adrian.
Cobbs.
Cobbs!
This is Unit 507.
I've got an officer down.
Repeat, officer down.
Copy, 507.
EMS is being notified.
Backup to your location
in five minutes.
It's gonna be so much better
than the city, honey.
You're gonna have sidewalks
to ride your bike on and a yard.
You're gonna love it.
I miss Daddy.
I know, honey.
But you're gonna be
so much happier here.
I promise. You'll see.
There they are!
- Hi.
You must be Claire.
Your mommy's told me
a lot about you,
so I brought you something
very special from our office
Ta-da!
I'm sorry. She's still not 100%
about this whole moving thing.
That's all right. She will be
when she sees her new room.
Come on. Let's go inside.
Welcome home.
What do you think, hmm?
I mean, I know it's not perfect,
but I think with a little bit
of work, it'll be great.
Well, you know, there was
a lot of interest in this house,
mostly from
real estate speculators,
but I felt that
it needed a family.
You like it?
Did something happen here?
What?
Well, it's an old house.
It's got a lot of history,
but nothing too bad.
- There you go.
- Oh, thanks.
Those are for the front door,
the back door, and the garage.
I'm right in town.
Call me if you need
anything at all.
- What is this?
- That's for the keys.
Oh, okay.
You keep that.
Thank you.
Oh.
"Lilith."
What's that?
What's what?
Claire.
Please, Mommy, can I keep her?
But you have so many other dolls
already, honey.
But I want this one.
I think that one probably
belongs to somebody else.
Finders keepers.
Fine, but you have
to let me wash it first.
Come on.
All right, keep unpacking.
Okay.
Everything's going pretty well.
I mean, she's not
super excited, but...
What's going on with you?
Same-old, same-old.
Grading papers.
Everything okay with the move?
Yeah. You know what?
Thanks so much for helping me
with that article.
It's hard to imagine
there's actually people
who believe this stuff is real.
Sometimes it's easier to rely on
a supernatural explanation
rather than confronting
the truth.
So what are you gonna do now?
Well, I'm gonna talk
to some of the local papers,
but I really just want
to take some time
and work on my book
and focus on Claire.
Good.
It's much bigger
than our old apartment.
- Claire?
- Everything okay?
You know what? I'm gonna go.
I'll call you later?
Okay, honey.
Good luck with the unpacking.
Thanks.
And I have some friends for you
in one of these boxes.
Tomorrow I have to go
to a new school with new kids.
I'm scared.
I hope they're nice,
not mean like some kids.
What if they don't like me?
What if they don't need
any new friends?
Hey.
I know it's hard.
You're gonna do great.
I promise.
Can I sleep with the light on?
Aren't you forgetting something?
Mom.
Come on.
Okay.
Now I lay me down to sleep,
I pray the Lord
my soul to keep.
If I should die before I wake,
I pray the Lord
my soul to take.
- 3 times 3?
- Nine.
- 3 times 4?
- 12.
- 3 times 5?
- 15.
3 times 6?
Claire?
Are you paying attention?
18.
Very good.
- 3 times 7?
- 21.
Hey, did you really move
into the bad house?
I heard it's haunted.
Stop it.
You moved into the bad house?
It's gonna get you.
♪ It's gonna get you ♪
- ♪ It's gonna get you ♪
- Hey!
Stop it!
Hello?
Oh, my God!
- The door was open.
- Can I help you?
I'm Janine, your new neighbor.
Alyson.
I thought this place
was gonna... Oh!
Whoops!
They kept
all the original fixtures.
It's lovely.
Oh, where are my manners?
Sorry they're a bit smushed,
but my cats were
walking on them.
Thank you.
Oh, look.
There's one of them now.
Smokey!
He's my oldest.
You have a little girl.
Yeah. Claire. She's nine.
My cats simply adore children.
Oh, that's great.
So if Claire ever wants to come
and play with the kitties,
just send her over.
They would love it.
And if you need anything,
just holler.
- Okay, thank you.
- Bye!
It's nice to meet you.
Wow.
Mommy said
it would be better here,
that I'd be happy.
She promised.
I thought things
would be different,
that people would be nicer.
But they're not.
They pick on me.
I hate them.
I wish they were dead.
- I won't go back there!
- Claire, you have to!
- Stop it.
- No.
- Yes.
- I want to go home.
- We are home.
- No!
You don't scream at me.
No!
Let me go!
♪ They put you in
a wooden box ♪
Claire, honey, I know
you don't want to go to school,
but you need to eat.
♪ Cover you up
with dirt and rocks ♪
♪ Don't you laugh
as the hearse goes by ♪
♪ For you may be
the next to die ♪
Claire, honey, didn't you
hear me calling your name?
Claire.
♪ The worms crawl out ♪
♪ They crawl all over
your dirty snout ♪
♪ Your chest caves in ♪
Honey, where did you
learn that song?
♪ Your brain turns into
sauerkraut ♪
Sluggo!
Smokey!
Din-dins!
No! No! No! No!
No! No, no, no, no!
Separation and divorce can be
very stressful for a child.
An entire support system's
been torn out from under her.
The future suddenly appears
very uncertain.
The hardest thing is that you're
having to go through this alone.
I just... I don't know what
I'm supposed to do anymore.
I mean, she won't go to school,
and she'll barely eat anything.
Her father still lives
in the city?
Yeah.
Returning to the dynamics
of that environment
might be a helpful thing
for her,
even just for a visit.
I'd strongly consider
letting her go back.
Thank you for your time, Doctor.
The subject exhibits traits
I've seen in similar cases
of callous,
unemotional children.
Distinctive lack of remorse
and empathy.
Further study will be required
before I can determine
the presence of psychopathy.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You're not even gonna touch
your ice cream?
Fine. Then I will.
I wanna go home.
Honey, this is our home now.
Why? 'Cause you and Daddy
can't get along?
It's a lot more complicated
than that, sweetie.
It's your fault.
Claire...
You're always so busy
with your stupid writing.
No wonder he hates you.
I'm gonna go take care
of the check.
What have you got there?
Give her back.
A pretty girl like you
should have a nice, new doll,
not an ugly, old one
like this.
- She's not ugly.
- Well, look at her.
She's practically falling apart.
I tell you what.
I bet I have a new one
in the back room.
Why don't we throw this one
away, and I'll go get her?
Give her back!
Claire!
I am so sorry.
What is wrong... Claire!
I'm sorry.
I think we should
talk about this, don't you?
She's a murderer!
- What are you talking about?
- Your daughter!
I don't... What?
A child trampled through
my garden last night.
Janine...
I saw the way
she looked at them.
My babies wouldn't hurt anybody,
and now they're dead,
and she killed them!
Okay, well, I'm sorry,
but I can assure you
that my daughter had absolutely
nothing to do with your cats.
Excuse me.
Good night, Rose.
Good night, Hank.
Someone there?
- Hey, Daddy.
- It's Daddy's little girl.
Oh, my God, I've missed you.
Bedtime is at 8:30
and no sugar after 6:00.
Yeah, I know.
I've done this before.
Just keep an eye on her, okay?
Ready to go, sweetheart?
Okay, you keep warm, all right?
I love you.
Well, that's a nice house.
How much did you put down?
Don't.
I bet you could get some
good money if you flipped it.
Jonathan, please.
There's a unit that opened up
two floors down from me.
Earl even said
he'd waive the deposit.
Look, just take care of her,
okay?
Okay.
Looks like there's a leak
in one of your fittings.
There's something else.
- What's that?
- You know these people?
No.
No, they must be the people
that used to live here.
That looks like
a muñeca quitapena.
A what?
Muñeca quitapena.
The doll.
You don't see them here
in the States much.
They're not usually that big.
My daughter actually
found this in the house.
She's gotten
pretty attached to it.
Bad luck to find
someone else's muñeca.
"Local family found slain."
Zachary, this nice lady is gonna
ask you some questions, okay?
Hi.
I'll be right outside.
Do you mind if I sit down?
I'm Alyson Simon.
I recently moved into
your old house.
And I have a little girl
who's nine,
just about the same age you were
when you lived there.
She found your doll.
Do you remember your doll?
She's grown
really attached to it.
Can you tell me why you did it,
Zachary?
Why'd you kill your family?
Was it...
Was it the house?
Was it something in the house?
Zachary.
Zachary!
It's time to go.
No, I just need one more minute.
He's not gonna tell you
anything.
♪ Don't you let
the hearse by ♪
♪ For you may be
the next to die ♪
- Where did you hear that song?
- Ma'am?
Where did you hear that song?
Tell me where you heard
that song!
The kid killed his whole family
and two cops in my house!
We found his picture
under my daughter's floor!
Mrs. Simon, the state civil code
is very clear.
A death in the home
is only a material defect
if it occurs within
three years of the sale.
Material defect?
This isn't a cracked shingle.
It's a multiple homicide!
What do you want me to do?
Tell the bank
that you misrepresented
the condition of the property
and get me my damn money back.
There's no cooling-off period.
This is a done deal.
Then list it. You said there was
a lot of competition.
Sell it to one of the others.
Yeah, well, um...
- There was no one else.
- Listen...
I'm gonna be honest with you.
With the history of this house,
selling it is not gonna be easy,
believe me.
No. You know what?
I'm calling my lawyer.
There's no reason to get...
Damn it.
You knew this would happen.
You were my friend.
And I always will be.
Why?
It's her turn.
She needs me.
You understand, don't you?
Why you have to go?
I'm scared.
Don't be. You're going
to be happy again.
You're going to be free.
You can play forever.
With you?
Come find us, Zachary.
We'll be waiting.
You know,
sometimes your mother and I,
we act like mean children
on a schoolyard.
We say things to each other
that we don't really mean,
and you have to listen to it,
and it's not fair.
But both of us want you to know
that we love you
more than you can ever imagine.
Well, what about Mommy?
What about Mommy?
Do you love her?
I do.
Well, I just don't understand
why we can't live together
and things can be
like they used to.
Okay.
Because sometimes
people who love each other
need a little time apart
to remember why they loved
each other in the first place.
But I promise you
I'm working on it.
No, you're lying.
No, sweetie.
Yeah, you don't love her.
- Yes, I do.
- You don't love me either.
Claire...
And I don't love you.
Why doesn't anyone listen?
We don't want a new mommy.
We want our mommy to come back
so that things can be
like it used to be.
You're the only one
that listens to me.
I will never stop
loving you, ever.
I promise.
Cross your heart?
Cross my heart.
Hope to die?
Come on, let's go home.
Your favorite pizza.
Here you go.
And...
some funny movies
to make you laugh.
Thought I'd come by
and surprise you.
No, no, no, I told you that
tonight is not a good night.
Is she here?
Can I meet her?
Oh.
She is just adorable.
Who are you?
My name is Kathy.
I'm a friend of your father's.
He never talks about you.
- Kathy's a friend from work.
- Yeah.
So what grade are you in,
Claire?
Sweetheart,
someone asked you a question.
- So?
- So why don't you answer her?
- I don't want to.
- Jonathan...
Claire's in third grade.
Well, your father told me
that you like dolls.
I brought you one.
Isn't that nice?
What do you say?
It's ugly.
No, it's not ugly.
Yes, it is. It's ugly.
I don't want it.
It's okay. I'm sure she'll
open up when she's ready.
But until then, maybe she can
play with Sally, huh?
Hey! That's crossing the line.
You pick that up right now.
- It's just a little thing.
- Claire, now!
That didn't go
as well as I expected.
She just moved to Monterey,
and she left all of her friends,
she's in a new school,
and the separation
between Alyson and me
is really hard on her.
- I didn't mean to...
- Kathy...
I told you that I needed to be
alone with my daughter tonight.
I'm sorry. I just...
I wanted to be with you.
Tell you what.
I could use a drink.
Why don't you let me
finish up these dishes?
You go down the corner
and get us a bottle of wine.
I really don't think
that's a good idea.
Oh, come on.
You really don't take no
for an answer, do you?
Listen, you deserve
a chance to relax.
Okay.
And I'm gonna get some
chocolate chip ice cream
because that's
Claire's favorite.
- I'll be right back.
- Sure.
♪ One quiet night ♪
♪ I've been waiting
oh, so long ♪
Claire?
Claire, is that you?
Jon?
Jon, is that you?
911, help me.
- 911. What's your emergency?
- Oh, my God.
What's your emergency, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Do you need
medical assistance?
- They're here.
- Ma'am, are you there?
Ma'am?
- Hi.
- Hey.
Do they know what happened?
Said it looks like
someone broke in.
Signs of a struggle.
I was gone 10 minutes.
Were you guys serious?
No.
She was just a friend
from work,
but we've gone out
a couple of times.
That's it.
Why don't you come back with us?
I gotta stay here
and deal with the police.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Why don't you and Claire
go back?
I don't want you
anywhere around this.
Okay. Call us
if you hear anything.
Thanks.
Come on, honey,
let's go get your stuff.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
You've reached Ken Stevens.
Please leave a message.
Hi, this is Alyson Simon.
I was just calling to see
if you had put any more thought
into the house situation.
Could you give me a call back,
please?
Ms. Simon?
It's Ken Stevens.
It's Ken.
I wanted to come by and clear
the air a little bit, Ms. Simon.
I thought, uh...
I thought we could talk about
the house's history.
Claire?
Is that you, honey?
Okay, yeah.
You know what?
What do you want me to say?
You want me to say I made
a mistake? Fine, I did.
I made a mistake. You know,
I didn't call you to argue.
We gotta figure out what we're
gonna do about our daughter.
The therapy isn't working and
I don't know what else to do.
When she came over, she had this
spooky-looking doll with her.
Yeah, and she won't
go anywhere without it.
She happened to mention that
Kathy brought her a new one?
What do you mean?
She brought her a new doll.
I found it underneath her bed
torn apart.
I'm talking violently.
- Wow.
- I know it's just a doll,
but I can't help but think
it might better if it were gone.
I'll be right back.
Lily?
Where's Lily?
Oh, God, honey, you scared me.
Where is she?!
Claire!
Where is she?
Come on, honey.
Claire, it is too late.
Put it... Claire!
- Claire!
- Where's Lily?
- Stop it!
- How could you do that to her?
She was my friend!
My only friend!
Stop it!
She did not belong to you!
She belonged to someone else.
- Ow.
- What? What?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Claire, honey,
where is this from?
Who did this to you?
I don't know!
Claire!
No!
- Good morning.
- Hi.
Are they real?
You come on in,
I'll tell you all about them.
See you in a bit.
How many of you have
ever heard the expression
"giving someone
the evil eye?"
One of the best known and
perhaps the most frightening
Latin American superstitions
is called Mal de Ojo.
Ophelia?
The belief is that the evil
spirit can direct bad luck
or even injury at someone with
nothing more than a simple look.
Children, particularly the ones
that are not baptized,
are believed to be more
susceptible to this curse.
Next.
Oftentimes in Central America,
you'll see children wearing
something red
or even having a simple red
thread tied around the wrist
to ward off Mal de Ojo.
Lights, please.
Okay, well, finish the readings
on superstition for next time.
Alyson, hi.
I'm sorry to hear things
aren't going well with the move.
- Oh, yeah.
- Did you bring it?
I did.
And it's from Guatemala?
- Tecal.
- Hmm. It's a worry doll.
Some people believe that when
a child has trouble sleeping,
it's because a large amount
of stress has built up,
but a worry doll
worries in the child's place
so the child sleeps better.
Does it work?
Sometimes, but the question is
does it work because
the doll has magical powers,
or because the child
believes it does?
Okay, assuming
that it does work,
and this doll can transfer
the child's worries to itself,
could it work
the other way around?
I mean, could the doll transfer
something to the child?
Look, Alyson, if your
daughter's having issues,
I'm really not the right person.
Okay, just look at something.
This happened the other night.
I picked it up.
I was trying to get rid of it,
and now Claire has a bruise in
the exact same place on her arm.
- It's not a voodoo doll.
- I know it's not.
But I took this doll that night
and put it in a Dumpster,
and the very next morning,
it was back.
This doll.
Yeah.
Can you help me?
If you don't mind leaving it,
I can take a closer look at it
for you.
You can keep it
as long as you like.
I want this doll as far away
from my daughter as possible.
Okay.
Thanks.
I want you to realize
that as a professional who
works regularly with children,
I have a responsibility
to report...
suspicious behavior...
to the authorities.
What... What do you mean,
um, suspicious behavior?
Tell me about her arm.
Wait a minute. Are you...
Is that what this is about?
Are you...
Are you accusing me
of abusing my daughter?
I'm giving you a chance
to explain it.
What? Are you...
Of course not!
Absolutely not!
Come sit down for a second.
It's very important
that you help me understand
how this happened.
Understand what?
She's a kid. Kids play hard.
Why don't you ask her?
I did. She told me
that you grabbed her.
- You lost your temper.
- I don't believe it.
That's crazy.
I mean, that's crazy.
Why would she tell you that?
Do you lose your temper?
No, I don't lose my temper!
You're raising your voice
right now.
Yeah, because you're making
ridiculous accusations!
You're saying
I'm abusing my daughter.
It's difficult
to be a single mom,
and I can't imagine how much
stress you must be under.
Don't you dare make this
about that.
We'll give this one more chance,
all right?
But if I see as much as
one bruise...
or one scrape,
I'll call protective services,
am I clear?
Yeah.
Jon, I feel like
I'm losing her,
and I don't know
what else to do.
That's it.
I'll see you in a couple hours.
No, I can't ask you to do that.
You're not doing this alone
anymore, Alyson.
I'll see you by 10:00.
Okay, thank you.
- Hey.
- Oh!
You scared me.
Where's Lily?
Why don't I take you to the
store and buy you a new doll?
I don't want a new doll.
I want Lily!
Claire!
Why do you always hurt me,
Mommy? Why?
Oh, my God.
Okay, let's see what we got.
Ophelia?
Would you like me to start
with the abdomen?
Sounds good.
Want me to check it out?
No, no, I'll go.
Call maintenance and stay here.
Hmm. Strange.
Hello?
Is there someone there?
We need to get out of here.
Ophelia?
There's Daddy's little princess.
I know what you want.
Daddy's world-famous...
flapjacks.
- Morning.
Breakfast is almost ready.
Can you get the juice?
Yeah, sure.
The campus
has been on lockdown,
as officers question anybody...
- Here you go, sweetie.
- who might have information
helpful to this case.
The classroom
where the student was found
belonged to Latin American
studies professor
Elena Carranza.
Oh, my God.
What?
What, you knew her?
She's the one I gave it to.
The professor was not
at her apartment.
Efforts to reach her by phone
have failed.
Her colleagues and students
are among those being
questioned this hour...
I gotta go.
- Bill, back to you.
- Thanks, Valerie.
More from this breaking story
later in our broadcast.
Did your mother
do that to you?
Hurt your arm?
Yes.
How, Claire?
How did she hurt you?
I was in the kitchen,
and I spilled my milk,
and she just...
she just finished cleaning up,
and...
and she got mad.
Claire, I'm going to go
and get a special report
so I can write this down.
I'm in the middle of something.
I know, but someone left this
in the front door.
It's the Simon girl's doll,
isn't it?
- Who left it?
- Don't know.
I went to put the mail out,
and it was just sitting there.
Just keep it up front
for me, okay?
Sure.
And there's another thing.
It's about Zachary Orcutt.
That's a lot of blood.
Yeah, looks like our victim
was killed up here,
then dragged down to the desk.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm sorry,
but Professor Carranza
was a friend of mine,
and I'm wondering
if anyone has found a doll.
A doll?
Yeah, I came by, I dropped it
off with her yesterday.
She was looking into
something for me.
I'm gonna need you to leave.
There's a detective outside
that'll take your statement.
Danny, can you please
escort this woman out?
Okay, but it's really important
that you find this doll.
- I need you to come with me.
- Yeah, but...
- Get her out of here.
- Yeah, okay, I'm...
Right this way.
Sorry.
Anyway, they dragged her
from here to there.
Right.
And down the steps.
Hello?
I really need to talk to you
about Claire.
How soon can you get here?
Halfway to the city is gonna
be like another hour or two.
I know you went to see
Zachary Orcutt.
You know I evaluated him
for the court five years ago
after he murdered his family.
Okay. Why are you
telling me this?
Shortly after
you spoke with him,
Zachary Orcutt
disappeared from his ward
and hasn't been seen since.
Are you telling me
that Claire is in danger?
Just get here
as soon as you can.
Jane, I need you to
reschedule my next...
Claire?
Claire.
Sweetheart?
Sweetheart!
Daddy?
Just checking.
Claire?
Sweetheart?
Claire, open the door!
Claire!
Hello?
Hello!
Claire?
Sweetheart?
Claire!
Anybody here?
Oh, my God!
Claire?
Claire!
Claire, you open this door
right now.
Do you hear me?
Claire, Daddy says
open this door right now!
Sweetheart?
There's something else in here.
Claire, give me the doll,
sweetie.
No.
- Claire.
- That's it.
No!
Daddy!
Jonathan!
Stop it, stop it!
They're connected!
Look.
♪ Don't do you look
as the hearse goes by ♪
- Where'd it go?
- Where is it? Where is she?
Where is it?
It's downstairs.
Stay here. Stay here!
I'd run if I were you.
Claire?
Claire!
Claire! Oh, my God.
No sign of it.
We're going now!
Don't just stand there.
Move. Move!
It's a prayer.
It's not getting out anymore.
- No! No!
- Claire!
You've got to get her
out of here!
Let me go! Let me go!
- Where are we going?
- Anywhere! Far from here!
How's she doing?
Fever still hasn't broken.
- May I see her?
- Yeah.
You were right.
There's a strong connection
between Claire and the doll.
Exactly what kind of connection
are we talking about here?
There are three stages.
The first stage, the doll
and the subject are introduced.
In the second stage,
the doll actually gets
into the host's mind.
It influences
his or her thoughts,
starts to change
the way they behave.
And the third and final stage,
the doll and the host will meld.
They'll become one.
- Are we too late?
- I don't think so.
But I don't think
we have much time either.
Well, how about
if we get her to a doctor?
There's gotta be someone
who could do something.
It's very important that we
handle this in a specific way.
So it is possible
to break the bond.
I don't know. I thought if we
got your daughter far away
that it would free her,
but I was wrong.
The doll still has
a hold on her.
Then I'll destroy it.
I'll go back to the house,
and I'll destroy it.
Jonathan...
This time of night,
I can be there in two hours.
You can't. You can't!
- Do you have any children?
- No.
Then you couldn't possibly know
what it's like to sit there
and watch your daughter suffer
and do nothing about it.
You're right, I can't,
but what I do know
is that if you don't dispose
of this doll properly,
whatever happens to that doll
will happen to your daughter.
If the doll dies,
Claire dies.
What is it that we need to do?
What is the proper way?
You have to remove
the eyes first.
If you remove the eyes
from the doll,
the connection with Claire
should be severed.
What do you mean, should?
How many times do you think
I've done this?
Okay, then that's what we'll do.
And when were done, I'm gonna
burn the frickin' thing.
No!
- Come here, Claire.
- Jonathan, be careful.
- What?
- Don't let her have it!
You let her live!
Jonathan!
Oh, my God.
Where is she?
She's outside.
Claire!
- Claire!
- Where is she?
- I'll check over here.
- Okay. We'll go this way.
Claire!
Claire?
Stop! Claire, stop!
Elena!
Oh, my God.
Get the tarp!
Okay.
Claire.
Elena.
Elena?
We're gonna be okay.
Hold on!
Everybody okay?
We have to find it.
- I'll go get it.
- You're not getting anything!
- Claire.
- Claire!
Claire.
Oh, my...
Sweetheart.
Just give Daddy the doll.
There is no doll, Daddy.
Claire, give Daddy the doll.
No!
Your daughter
doesn't need you anymore,
and neither do I.
Alyson!
Claire!
Claire...
Alyson!
Goodbye, Mommy.
No!
- No!
- The eyes!
Can I help?
Go upstairs and bring your
mother's dresser down here.
- You think you can handle that?
- You're funny.
No, there's some picture frames
in the living room.
You can grab those.
Okay.
- She doesn't remember anything?
- Nothing.
I mean, she remembers moving
in here, but that's about it.
Good.
Let's keep it that way.
You sure about this?
About what?
About us.
Yeah.
I'm sure.
I love you.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Okay.
♪ Don't you laugh
as the hearse goes by ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org