Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Are you OK?
Yeah. God, I don't know
what's wrong with me.
I might just be coming down
with the flu, or something.
Don't tell me
you're pregnant.
I'm not pregnant.
No express service
between 34th and 14th Street.
We apologize
for the inconvenience.
Parker!
Parker, no!
Hi, honey.
Hey, what are you
still doing up?
I've been waiting for you.
Ah.
You know,
I think your man
might make partner.
What does your wife
get out of this partnership?
Oh, wow.
God, you look beautiful.
More beautiful than usual?
Maybe.
I'm pregnant.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I have four pregnancy tests
that say I am.
Oh my God.
I love you.
I really think it's time
we consider moving
out of the city.
You know?
Just like we always wanted.
You mean
like you've always wanted.
Wait, you said,
"l will never raise kids
in this city."
I know. I know.
But, I feel different now
that I'm actually having one.
Well anyway,
we should look
at a couple of places.
Yeah? I've got the name
of a good real estate agent.
Will you think about it?
Maybe.
I'll think about it.
OK.
Ugh.
Get out of here now!
Get out! Go! Leave!
I've saved this property
for last
because I think
it's really special.
Now, as you can see
it's very private
but just as commutable
as the other homes
we've looked at.
Wow.
It's really big.
It's spacious
but don't let that put you off
until you've seen it.
Wow.
It's beautiful.
This home was built
with children in mind.
Do you plan
on having any children?
Actually I'm pregnant
right now.
That's wonderful.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
You have to admit
this would make
a perfect nursery.
Yeah.
With this much land
so close to the city,
I'm sure
it's out of our price range.
Isn't it?
No.
Actually the owners
are anxious
to get the place off their hands
as soon as possible.
Really?
Their daughter
went off to college,
so they decided to move
into the city.
I guess they felt
like this was too much house
for the two of them.
Come on.
We spoke about it.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
OK, it's finished.
Is it gonna work?
Yeah.
Y eah?
Go see for yourself.
Well?
Does it work?
It works.
Oh!
No, no!
What are you doing?
It's a mouse.
There's a mouse.
It's a what?
It's a mouse.
All right.
OK, I've got it.
Where is it?
He went
under the dresser.
Under here?
Yeah.
OK.
OK, mousy,
come on.
What are you doing
with that?
He's probably
next door by now.
Can I write you
a check?
Yeah.
Yeah, you can write me
a check.
Oh, good.
You moved
into Jenny's old house?
1 620 Woodland Lane.
Oh.
Yeah, I guess I did.
That's Jenny's house.
She used to work here.
We were pretty decent friends.
Thanks.
Thank you very much.
Let me tell you,
they didn't have
the drugs back then
that they do now.
I'm sure.
But Mom,
I don't want
the drugs.
I'm planning on having
a natural birth.
You don't want
the drugs?
Nope.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Are you crazy?
Who wouldn't want
the drugs?
Mom, you know
the drugs are actually
bad for the baby.
They aren't bad
for the baby.
Y es, they are.
You'll be singing
a different tune
when the baby comes.
Trust me.
Yoga and all that breathing
doesn't mean shit
with a ten pound parasite
coming out
from between your legs.
It's true.
Why do you think
you're an only child?
Mom, you're scaring me.
Well, you should be scared.
You should be horrified.
I'd come but I don't even
want to be reminded.
Thanks for the support, Mom.
Could you just hold on
for one second?
I want to put
Parker downstairs.
He's been driving me
up the wall lately.
OK.
Come here.
Oh God.
There you go.
Hi.
Mom, I need to go.
I'm actually cooking
dinner for Steven tonight.
Cook?
Did you move to a farm?
What?
They don't have delivery
out there?
I like cooking.
And Steven's been working
really hard lately
and he comes home
like ten o'clock at night
and I think
he'd like a meal.
Well, I hope he doesn't plan
on working these kind of hours
when the baby comes.
He's going to take some time
off when the baby comes.
OK.
Good.
It's great to talk to you.
You too, sweetie.
O K.
T ake care
of yourself, OK?
You take care of yourself.
Bye.
Parker!
Come here, boy!
Come on!
It's time to eat!
Come here!
Come on!
Parker!
Parker.
How you doing?
Oh God!
No! Oh God!
I am so sorry.
I had a nightmare
of a phone call
just as I was leaving.
You OK?
I killed Parker.
What?
I'm sorry.
How?
Does this mean
I'll be a horrible mother?
Laura... it wasn't your fault.
It was an accident.
Why didn't I close
the door to the laundry room?
Why didn't I do that?
Let's get some sleep, eh?
I'm sorry.
I know.
Oh!
Oh no!
Is there something wrong?
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be
all right.
She's fine.
Everything's fine.
Laura.
Actually, she's asleep
right now but, uhm,
they're just gonna keep her
in for a few more days
because of the c-section.
You OK?
Yeah, I'm,
I'm a little tired.
You'll be able to rest
as soon as you feed her.
We advise our mothers
who've had a c-section
to breastfeed on their sides
because your abdominals
are going to be sore
for awhile.
It takes some practice.
You can do it.
I don't think
she wants it.
No, oh, you've got to be really--
careful to make sure
that her mouth
is on it.
You don't want to starve
your baby to death,
thinking she's feeding
when she's not.
I've seen it happen.
Ah.
See?
Now, from here on out
everything's pretty
much downhill.
There you go.
Oh God.
Hey.
Hi.
Hello.
Hello, little one.
Hello, my little one.
No.
Oh-oh-oh.
How long you been up?
Uh, I don't know.
What time is it?
It's about six thirty.
I don't even think
I slept.
I heard those mice again.
Oh Jesus.
Look, I'll call the exterminator.
I'll make sure
someone gets out here
today. OK?
OK.
I've got to go.
I've got to go,
sweetheart.
Oh. Here we go.
There we go.
See you.
When are you coming home?
I'll call.
God!
Is there something wrong?
I assure you
it's perfectly normal.
I, I,
it's just that--
Just use the ointment
I prescribed
and you should be fine.
Really.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've really got to go.
O K, bye.
You got a rodent problem?
Hello?
Hi.
Why'd you call
so early?
I didn't.
Yeah.
Like around four
I got your message.
Oh, oh.
Are you OK?
Mom, how did you feel
after you gave birth
to me?
How did I feel?
I felt like shit.
You did?
How else
are you supposed to feel
after you've just had a baby?
So, what,
you've got the blues
or something?
It's like I have
so much anxiety.
I'm just worried
about every little stupid thing.
Yeah well, don't worry.
It goes away.
You'll be fine.
It does?
It's one of those aspects
of having a baby
that people fail to mention.
Hormones,
they're horrible.
It's weird.
I feel like I 'm going crazy.
You're not going crazy.
Excuse me.
Basement?
There's only room
for one crazy person
in this family
and I already
got the job.
I promise you,
it'll get better soon.
You just need to get
some sleep.
At least five hours.
How am l
supposed to do that?
The baby eats
like every two hours.
I 'm not going to do that.
He has a really stressful job.
OK?
He can't get up like ten times
in the middle of the night.
And you can?
You guys
should take turns.
So he has a job.
He goes and does his job.
Then he comes home
and he has another job.
He's the father.
The mother isn't the only one
who's responsible
for the child.
Mom...
can I call you back?
OK.
I'm sorry.
No problem.
I'm just glad
you were around.
I laid some traps
even though
I didn't see any droppings.
But you never know.
They say if you got one mouse
you got forty.
Like I said,
mice like to run up and down
the pipes.
So if I were you,
I wouldn't leave your diary
in the utility closet.
Mice like to eat
that kind of stuff.
What diary?
I just assumed it was yours.
It looked kind of girlie.
If you'll just sign there,
Ma'am.
Thank you.
And you call me
if you hear anything else.
OK, I will.
Oh God!
Help!
Help!!
What are you talking about?
You are kidding me?
Don't tell me that.
Why is he springing this shit
on us now?
This is meant to be finished.
This is meant to be a deal.
I can't believe this.
Look John,
It's a little bit late
in the day for this.
Y eah.
Sorry to interrupt, John.
I 'm gonna have to call you back.
OK?
Bye-bye.
Hey, darling, hey.
Where's mommy?
Sh, sh, sh.
All right, all right.
Laura!
Laura!!
Laura!!!
Laura!
Laura!!
Steven, I'm in the basement!
Open the door!
Jesus. What happened?
O K. All right.
I have to feed her!
I practically abandoned her.
Laura, she's fine.
She's never
gonna forgive me.
There's nothing to forgive.
Anyway, she's a baby.
She forgave you
the moment you fed her.
I think she thinks
I'm a bad mother.
Listen to me.
Listen.
You're a great mother.
I'm not.
I'm a terrible mother.
Can I help you?
Are you Mrs. Davis?
Yes.
I am Mrs. Kasperian.
Your husband sent me.
He said you need helper.
Steven...called you?
He's very good man.
He knows it's not easy
to be a mother.
I'm not looking
for any help right now.
Well, he sent me.
Maybe you would like
to telephone him. I wait.
All right,
I'll call him.
You can come in.
Thank you.
Is your mother coming?
No.
Thank God
she doesn't want to fly.
Where is she?
She's in Los Angeles.
Are you from there?
Yes.
When I had my first baby,
I wanted to go home to Mother.
I was very scared.
But she convinced me
to stay here.
Outside this country,
many mothers and babies
don't make it.
Here, very few women
have troubles.
Oh, look.
She's sound asleep.
Would you like me
to put her in the crib
for you?
No.
She's very beautiful.
Shall I go on folding?
Sure.
Always so much laundry.
Mrs. Davis?
Baby is sleeping upstairs.
You should get some rest too.
I will.
I'm going now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You get some rest.
Did you remember to call
Mrs. Kasperian
about baby sitting tonight?
You didn't forget
about the party tonight,
did you?
I didn't.
I called her.
She's coming.
Good.
It's all right.
You had me scared there
for a minute.
Oh, can you make sure
that you show up on time?
It's just that we're considered
to be one of the hosts
and I want to make sure
that we greet everyone
as they come in.
Oh my God.
How's your mouse problem?
They're doing great.
They are so good.
Hey, do you remember
that girl that you
told me about?
I think
I found something
of hers
and I was wondering
if I could reach her.
Uhm, I don't have a number
but she went to NYU.
I'm sure you can just call
their directory.
What was her name again?
Jenny.
Ugh.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
Oh my God! Jesus Christ!
All right. Where is she?
Where is she?
Oh my God.
Oh my God!!
Oh my God!
I'm sorry.
Mrs. Davis?
What you do
to your hair?
Oh no.
Oh no!
Will you take her?
Yes. Of course.
She'll be fine.
It's all right.
Little one.
She's fine.
Oh, little one.
Is everything all right,
Mrs. Davis?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm--
I'm fine.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm glad
I could help.
You are not happy,
Mrs. Davis.
Why do you say that?
You remind me
a little of myself.
When I had my first baby,
I wasn't happy either.
I didn't feel the way
I thought
a mother should feel.
Really?
I had first baby
here in the States.
I was
too far from home.
I was very lonely.
And I had no one
to help me.
I couldn't eat,
I couldn't sleep,
I worried about the baby
all the time.
I had many thoughts
of death,
I had terrible dreams,
even more terrible thoughts.
My mother thought
someone put evil curse
on me.
What did you do?
I prayed a lot.
Did it help?
No.
I went to someone
people said was good
at removing evil curses.
She told me
that when a mother has a baby,
she's cut in two pieces.
One piece is baby,
one piece is mother.
But sometimes
baby takes too much.
Baby steals mother's soul
and mother begins to die.
How did you overcome
those feelings?
I got my soul back.
Hello?
Hi.
Hi!
I was wondering
if you'd left yet.
Uh, uh, where?
Oh, Lord,
tell me you didn't forget,
you promised.
Oh God,
yes, I know, I know.
I'll be there!
Well, did you call
Mrs. Kasperian?
Uhm, yeah,
she's here.
OK, can you hurry?
Oh.
I really--
I really don't feel
like I'm up for it, though.
Look, all I asked you to do
was to come on time,
and to look nice, and smile.
And now what?
You're telling me
you can't even do that?
All right.
I'll be there.
You know
I wouldn't ask--
I'll be there
in an hour.
Good. Great.
Thanks.
Bye.
I'll see you soon.
Oh no.
Is that Steven's wife?
Yes.
She just had a baby.
I mean, it changes you.
There's no question but...
we're really happy.
I'm sorry,
excuse me.
Why didn't you tell me
it was black tie?
What did you do
to your hair?
I know. OK?
I had a really hard day.
All right?
You've no idea what--
Steven.
Hey.
I'm glad to see you let
the little lady out of the house.
It wouldn't be a party
without Laura.
I just love what you've done
with your hair.
So vanguard.
Thank you.
How's the kid?
We hear she is
the most beautiful child
in company history.
Yes, where is she?
She's at home
with the babysitter.
Oh! Well, we're all dying
to see her.
You should've
brought her along.
I can't believe
you left her at home.
I'm gonna call her
right now.
Do you have a phone?
Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
Thank you.
It's so great
to see you guys.
Glad you made it.
I love your dress.
Thanks.
She'll be right back.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, good.
What is she doing?!
Hey!
I was looking
for you.
I want to go home.
What are you
talking about?
I'm just gonna go home.
Laura.
Laura!
Laura!!
Hi.
Where's the baby?
She's upstairs sleeping.
Why didn't you answer
the phone?
I didn't hear it.
I must have been upstairs.
I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna go check on her.
Is everything OK?
Everything's fine.
Didn't you hear everybody
talking about me?
No.
What are you
talking about?
At the party.
All the coworkers.
You didn't hear
all the awful things
they were saying about me?
Right. So is that
why you stormed out?
No. I went and I called
and no one picked
up the phone.
Well, I think,
I think you owe me
an apology.
You knew how important
this was to me.
But no,
you show up late.
And you look a mess.
And then,
you're there for ten minutes
before you storm out.
I'm sorry.
I was worried
about the baby.
Oh no!
Steven! Don't take the baby
without telling me!
Oh my God,
you're bleeding.
Oh God.
Have you had
excessive vaginal bleeding?
No.
Have you started having
sex again?
No.
How often
do you bathe?
I take showers.
Sometimes more than once.
Well, your stitching
seems to have gotten infected.
I don't want to take
anything 'cause, uhm,
I'm still breastfeeding
and I don't want to hurt
the baby.
This won't hurt the baby.
It's just antibiotics.
Take them three times a day
and everything should be fine.
And you're also
having problems sleeping?
Yeah. I'm having
a lot of anxiety
and I'm feeling--
Take two of these
right before you want to go
to sleep.
Oh, the breastfeeding.
Here.
This will be better.
Maybe start out taking half,
see how it does.
H uh.
Hello, Mrs. Davis.
I can't get her to stop crying.
I don't know
what's wrong with her.
I fed her
and then I changed her.
And she just won't stop!
Maybe I could try.
Sometimes all you need
is a different person.
How did you do that?
How did you stop
her crying?
I, I don't know.
Maybe you could go up,
take a little rest.
Yeah.
Oh. Oh.
Oh little one.
Here we go.
No!
No! No!
What are you doing?
I find this knife
in baby's crib.
I don't believe you.
I protect your baby.
Step away
from the crib!
No.
Get away from the crib!!!
You need help!
Get the hell out of my house!
I'm going to kill you!
It's OK.
Thank God
the baby's OK.
Did she say anything
when you confronted her?
I asked her to step away
from the crib
and she wouldn't move.
I have to tell you,
Mrs. Davis,
I've known Mrs. Kasperian
for a long time
and I just can't imagine
she'd harm a baby.
Well, then why
did she have a knife
in the baby's room?
I don't know.
We're going to go
and talk to her.
Hey, how are you?
Hi.
Cigarettes?
I'm sorry,
it's none of my business.
Did you ever get in contact
with Jenny?
You said she left something
at the house.
So I was just wondering
how she was doing.
I gotta call her.
I'm gonna call her tomorrow.
Thanks.
Good to see you.
OK.
Bye.
New York University
student directory.
I'm looking
for a Jenny Foster.
Uh, she goes
to school there.
OK,
one moment please.
I'm sorry,
we have no record
of a Jennifer Foster
attending school here.
Hello?
The earth, the dirt,
the blackness inside.
Nothing in this room
makes me feel welcome.
How am I ever
going to tell them about this?
I hear voices.
Desperate.
Are they my voices
or someone else's?
I feel so cold in here.
I 'll be right back.
O K? I 'll be right back.
Police.
Someone is breaking
into my house!
Ah! Ah!
I called the police!!
They're gonna be here
any second!!
Ahh!!
I want my baby!!
Ah!
I don't know
what she looked like.
What's going on?
Your wife called
about an intruder.
Someone tried to break in?
Yes.
Jesus.
What happened?
There was a woman
and she was outside
and then she came inside
and then she was coming upstairs
and--
She was gonna take
the baby.
Was it Mrs. Kasperian?
I don't think
it was Mrs. Kasperian.
You know
she threatened Laura
with a knife.
No, she didn't threaten me
You know
what I mean.
We talked
to her earlier.
You talked to her?
You just talked to her?
You didn't arrest her?
It wasn't
Mrs. Kasperian.
Are you sure?
Yeah. No.
I mean, it wasn't
it didn't look
like her but--
I don't know.
she looked
more like me then,
I don't know.
I want to put
the baby to bed.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Look, I know
your wife's really upset.
But I'm going to be honest
with you.
Her story doesn't add up.
Maybe she's a little lonely
out here by herself
and worked herself
up into a frenzy.
I've seen it before.
Are you telling me you think
my wife called you
just to get some attention?
Are you
out of your mind?
I'm just saying
that I don't see anything
that leads me to believe
that anyone
other than your wife
was here.
I talked
to Mrs. Kasperian.
She said she found the knife
already in the baby's crib.
And you believe that?
M r. Davis,
I don't know what to believe.
That's my point.
Well, gentlemen,
thanks for coming out.
Now look,
I am not saying--
Good night, gentlemen.
Call us
if you need us.
Are you O K?
I don't know
what's going on.
It's OK.
Everything's going to be
all right.
But l... I saw her.
I know.
I believe you.
Let's get some sleep.
Shhhh.
Yeah, look,
I just need a few days.
OK?
I mean,
Jake can take care of things.
I mean, he can always call me
if he needs me, anyway.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I know. I know.
Well, uh,
look, I'll deal
with that on Monday--
Oh my God!
Ah!
Oh.
Excuse me,
do you have
any books on curses?
You mean
like witchcraft?
Yeah.
My personal favorite.
Get off!
Get off!!
No! No!
Get off!
Laura!
I gave her something
that will help her sleep.
Well, what's wrong
with her?
It's too early to tell.
We're going to keep her here
and monitor her behavior.
She may be suffering
from Postpartum Psychosis.
You're starting to look
like yourself again.
The doctors say
it's time to come home.
Where's the baby?
She's fine.
Your mother's with her
right now.
I'm sorry.
Don't say sorry.
I ' m sorry.
I didn't really mean--
I didn't want to hurt her.
I don't want to hear you
say "sorry" anymore.
OK? It's over.
It happened.
It doesn't matter.
You know?
Yeah, I'm happy
you're here.
Good.
I miss you.
I'm right here, sweetheart.
I'm right here.
OK?
We just got to get you better.
Hi, Mom.
Hi, sweetie.
She's beautiful.
Yes, she is,
isn't she?
How are you feeling?
I feel better.
Thank you for coming.
I didn't realize
how much I could use your help.
Well, if you told me
how cute she was
I would have been
on the first plane here.
Well you know,
now that Steven
is taking a month off,
and you're going to be here
for a while,
I thought maybe
I would start dancing again.
Well, that's a great idea.
That's a girl.
It's great to see you
dancing again.
You look beautiful.
Where's the baby?
Uh, I think
she's still sleeping.
Hm.
I'll go check on her.
Good morning, sweetheart.
Good morning.
Where's Jessica?
Who's Jessica?
Laura, where's the baby?
What baby?
Jessica!
Jessica!!
Jessica!!!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org