Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
It's the big house on the left.
"Casa de Porter"!
Hello?
See ya, Porter!
Just the one.
It's not five o'clock yet.
I beg your pardon, little pig.
What d'ya say?
Sandy? - Yep.
- Thought you were comin' Thursday.
It is Thursday.
- Looks like I missed your boat.
Oon't worry, buddy,
Uncle Paul will make it up to you.
What is this place anyway?
- It was an abandoned fishing camp.
It was a real dump when I got here.
Come aboard, I'll show you around.
Hey! Heel!
Here, boy.
We're in the poo, mate.
You like spaghetti this much?
- I'm quite a bargain hunter.
When the cruise ships are in the area,
you can do some terrific deals.
Any passengers that want Spaghetti-os
are out of luck.
I'm sure.
They're not exactly Omaha steaks,
but you won't go hungry.
There's gotta be some mistake.
You cannot be my uncle.
You know they say: You can choose
your friends, but not your relatives.
Why don't you unpack?
I'll rustle us up some grub.
How much did she pay you
to take me off her hands?
I resent that. When your mother
called, I didn't hesitate.
If anyone
knows about divorce, it's me.
I mean, family's very important.
You guys are all I've got.
How much?
A hundred dollars a week.
Just for the summer.
Oh boy, she really low-balled ya.
Story of my life, kid.
This concert's history.
All aboard!
Come on, sailor! Shake a leg!
You don't get up, you don't eat.
Time to rock and roll!
Spaghetti-os with or without?
- Without what? - Pee-wee franks.
Suit yourself.
But out on the ocean,
you can't order a pizza.
You ever been fishing?
What d'ya catch? - A whale.
But I threw it back.
Most people think fishing's
a bamboo pole and a 6-pack of suds.
But it's tougher than that.
- Oh really.
What about seasickness?
Look, I can handle it.
Sure ya can.
Where's the bait, sailor?
Bait my butt!
You okay?
At least it floats!
Funny. Buck-faced wombat!
Just keep your eyes on the horizon.
- For how long?
As long as it takes to keep it down.
Oamn dolphins stealing all the bait.
- They're scaring the fish away.
That's not fishing, kid.
That's murder.
It's pathetic.
Hey, kid!
You see where that dolphin went?
Yeah.
That way.
You sure?
Alright, Oirk!
Come on!
Go on, get outta here!
Go on. Go!
Go!
You gonna be at this concert?
- The Chili Peppers are mine!
You're splitting?
- Am I splitting!
Hey, Tommy.
You returning to the mainland?
I can't make it with no fish.
Fish are gone, I'm gone.
What, you givin' up the good life?
Good life's ancient history. I can't
feed a cat with what I catch.
Oon't worry.
I'm on the 5 A.M. Ferry.
Pick me up, we'll be at the concert.
Gotta go, it's the hippy!
Thought you might
like a change. - Why?
I dunno.
Yo, Marvin!
Aren't you a bit warm?
What's with him?
- Marvin's a little shy.
Give him a spring and a wire,
he'll make an outboard motor.
I don't want to hurt him.
- But sweetheart...
Okay, we'll put him back
in with his friends,
and we'll use this guy.
He won't mind at all.
Have fun fishing!
- Okay.
Become a marine biologist
and you can bait hooks too...
In Boston you wouldn't get to see me.
Just my luck.
This must be Sandy.
Hi, I'm Cathy.
He probably told you about me.
No.
Can you get my stuff?
So, how's he doing?
- Like a pizza, but upside down.
I'll straighten him out.
You cooking dinner tonight?
Why? You tired of Spaghetti-o's?
You heard Tommy's leaving the island.
We haven't had a decent catch
since spring. - I know why.
The fish are loaded with dioxin.
What's dioxin?
- It's a by-product of herbicide.
How's that getting in our water?
Careful!
Will he ever take off that raincoat?
Maybe we could get it cleaned
with him still inside.
You never take me seriously!
That's not fair!
Hit me with your best shot.
When are we getting married?
Gotta go fix the net.
- Porter Ricks!
Think he'll ever grow up?
What are you doing?
Hey, Sandy. Oo I look cool or what?
Or what.
It's the shirt. It was given to me
by Brian Wilson. - Who?
Brian Wilson. Beach Boys.
What are they teaching you kids?
I'm tired. Gonna hit the hay early.
Good. Cathy's number's on the wall.
There's spaghetti if you're hungry...
- Yeah.
I'm late. See ya in the A.M., kid.
See ya in the A. M... not!
FERRY OEPARTURES
Hello?
Is that you?
Come on!
Cool!
Sorry. Gotta jet. See ya!
Shake a leg, sailor!
You don't get up, you don't eat.
Sandy?
Earthquake!
Jeez!
Storm's comin'. Board up the windows.
I can't, Russ.
Looking for a runaway nephew.
Call off the search.
He took the first ferry out.
By the way, I'll need $22.50.
He put it on your tab.
He's so cute!
Sandy?
I am by nature a gentle soul.
However, I can crush a coconut...
with my bare hands.
Hold that thought
as we make our exit...
with dignity.
Get that rope!
Sandy! Get the line!
Oamn! Nice going, kid!
- You know what you just did?
I probably saved your life.
- You made me blow Chili Peppers.
Next concert's in Orlando.
I don't have tickets. - I don't give...
Great! Bloody great.
"Yeah, I'd love to see Sandy.
Send him down. It'll be great."
Lt'll cost me
my house and my boat, but...
I should give up
and join Tommy on the mainland.
Why didn't you just let me go?
- I'm not finished with you yet.
Oon't talk like my father.
I'm not looking for another father.
Good.
Make's us even.
'Cause I'm not looking for a son.
Especially
a screw-up teenager like you.
You don't know me.
You know nothing about me.
Tell you what I do know, kid.
This here is the earth.
This is the great big ocean.
Here's our tiny island. Your mum
is way over there.
No matter how you scream,
she can't hear ya.
You got no friends, no money,
no malls to hang around. You're stuck.
All you have is me.
So get used to it.
And relax. Got a long, ugly
day ahead of us... and night.
Gonna use that pillow?
Thanks.
He snored all bloody night!
Oh man!
Is nothing sacred?
Jeez!
Get off there!
Look...
Since I know you love being here,
I'll make a deal.
You work for me,
help clean this mess up,
and I'll get you
to that concert in Orlando.
How?
I don't even have tickets.
Kid, this is Porter Ricks.
If it exists, I can get it.
We'll make that show.
We?
- Think I'd let you go alone?
Besides, I can dig the Chili Peppers.
Not the Beach Boys, but who is?
Is it a deal?
Haul her in!
Start with the fish pan netting. Mast
and stuff's in the shed or in town.
I'm gonna have to stay
with the boat on the mainland.
You gonna be alright?
- I'll be fine.
Cathy will drop in on you.
You can reach me through
the coastguard station.
But nothing's gonna happen, right?
- Right.
Right.
You...
Like my dolphin?
- Your dolphin?
That's right. I found him.
What's his name?
His name's Flipper.
Never seen one alone like this.
Alone he'd be no match for Scar.
- Who's Scar?
The hammerhead that stalks
these waters. Big and ugly.
They say he took out a tourist boat.
He likes those out-of-towners.
That jerk tried to kill Flipper.
He was shooting at him.
That's Oirk Moran, a bottom-feeder.
What are you doing?
- I'm hypnotizing him.
It's not working.
You make him do something.
Okay. Sure.
Alright.
Alright, Flipper...
What do you wanna do today?
Jump!
Awesome!
You know...
- Where did he go?
I'm Kim.
- Sandy.
He's hungry.
- Really?
Where d'you get fish to feed him?
- Feed him?
He's your dolphin.
- Well, yeah...
Come on, I got an idea.
Lookin' good, Porter.
- Thanks.
Oid most of it myself.
Most of it.
Now I just have to pay for it.
Take a lesson from your nephew.
He's becoming quite a businessman.
What's he been up to?
- You'll see!
Fish go in the bucket. One dollar
to see Flipper, the Wonder Oolphin.
FLIPPER THE WONOER OOLPHIN
One dollar. Oid you put your fish in?
One dollar. In there. Wow!
TOSS A QUARTER. FLIPPER RETURNS.
OROP 25 CENTS HERE
PENNIES
Oon't ask me,
I can't explain how he does it.
What's this, a penny?
It's a Lincoln penny!
Vintage, man! Enjoy!
Marvin! Come on in. No charge!
1 dollar, thanks. Fish in the bucket.
1 dollar, thanks.
Fish go in the bucket. Excuse me!
You need a fish to get in.
I don't have to pay, Kim.
I own this circus.
What's going on here?
- Oh, hi!
My best havanas! - It's the
Flipper Show! - Who's Flipper?
Alright, the Flipper Show is over.
All you kids go home, now!
Come on.
- Sorry.
You can have your fish back.
Give me my fish!
- Now!
See ya, Sandy.
Go easy on him, Mr. Ricks.
You were gonna fix the house!
- I did it so Flipper could eat.
Who do you think you're dealing with?
You did it to turn some coin.
I didn't do too bad
for myself either. Hey!
Half cut!
As for you, you oversized guppy...
I'll have to bring out the heavy guns.
We're gonna try a new approach.
It's called "Oealing with your crap."
This is how it works. Number 1:
You're gonna take responsibility for
your actions and the consequences.
Number 2: You're
gonna start getting up on time.
And at work,
you're gonna hump, not gripe.
You'll have to use your brain,
the weakest muscle in your body.
And as fo the dolphin:
If the damn thing won't go away,
you'll feed it. In your own time.
And stand up straight!
Oh, and you wanna be
a big man with a cigar, right?
Fire up that puppy!
Keep it stoked! From now on,
when I smoke, you smoke.
Washed your hands? Sit down.
Stogies down.
Let's eat.
Mom, when are you picking me up?
- In 2 weeks. What's in your mouth?
Cigar.
- A what?
I've been smokin' up a storm.
Uncle Porter lets me drink beer.
He also knows a lot of
loose women. - Put your uncle on!
Yeah, Porter.
- He can't smoke. He's just a kid!
Hang on a sec, love...
It's OK,
he' s about to kick the habit.
Ready for another?
Oh, please,
I'll never smoke again!
Good. Now go and
take care of that poor little fish.
Good boy. Thanks.
Bring it to Sandy. Go on!
Porter!
I can't find Marvin anywhere.
I'm really worried. - Jump in.
1 minute 20.
Hey, Sandy!
Marvin, what's up?
Cool, huh?
Come on down.
Careful on the dock, Marv.
It's kinda slippery!
Alright, Marv. Meet Flipper!
Marvin!
- Flipper!
Way to go, Marv!
Are you guys telling secrets?
We were wondering what the deal
is with you two? - What d'ya mean?
You in for the long haul,
or is it just a fling?
Sorry, is that the wrong question?
Not at all, Sandy.
I'd be interested in the answer.
Eat up, it's getting cold.
Well, the gang's all here.
Word has it you have a pet dolphin.
I wouldn't call it a pet, Oirk.
No? The way fishing's been,
we don't need a dolphin...
to tear holes in nets and steal bait.
But you know that, don't you?
We're talking about one dolphin.
- You stay out of this.
One dolphin is one too many.
Bad smell around here.
What's his problem? - He resents
anything smarter than he is.
That includes about everything,
even these clams.
Get him!
- Out of the way!
What are you doing?
You're hurting him!
That's enough!
You've had your fun. Let him go.
- It's the Greenpeace Warrior!
The animal means something
to the kid. - It does?
Well, isn't that sweet?
Isn't that sweet, boys?
The kid and the fish are pals.
I'd watch how I make friends.
- Enough!
You got no right to do that.
I should teach you a lesson.
Yeah, I'd like that.
I have a thirst for knowledge.
Teach me.
School's out, is it?
Thought so.
Maybe next time.
You can count on it, Ricks!
Good boy.
Come here, let me see those teeth.
Here you go.
- That'll fit.
Slow down!
Hey, Buck, How are ya?
- Fine, and you?
Pretty good. Bit of storm damage,
nothing we can't handle.
Lucky dolphin! Gets the pro treatment.
- How are ya?
Fine, except a little bird told me
you found yourselves this animal.
Porter, you can't keep a dolphin.
Here's the funny part: We're not
keeping it. He just stays.
I tried to chase him away,
but he's taken a fancy to us.
He's also harassing the fish.
- What? - We can't allow that.
Who told you that?
- It doesn't matter.
The law says, unless an animal's in
licensed captivity, he must be at sea.
You're here to take him?
- You can't! He's used to being fed.
That animal
can't fend for itself anymore.
Help me out here, old buddy.
They'll stick him in some
aquarium and revoke your license.
Good boy. Easy now.
Slow down, guys.
You wanna come, or wait here?
All set, Porter!
Wait!
It's okay.
Good boy.
Let him down slowly.
Easy, easy!
Almost out of gas.
It's cold.
Here.
- Thanks.
Jeez!
Let's get outta here!
Another day in paradise.
You sleep here all night?
I know you miss him.
He belongs out there.
Things seem to mess up
when you care about them.
It's like they say:
"To live is to love.
All reason's against it,
all instinct's for it."
What does that mean?
- I dunno. Read it on a calendar.
It's good to care. People who don't
wind up drooling cream spinach.
How come you don't have any kids?
Kids require commitment.
That's not one of my strengths.
If had a kid,
he'd might turn out like me.
Might not be bad.
He could turn out like you.
- Now that'd be a nightmare!
Special delivery.
I got us front and center.
You're really going
to the concert? - Why not?
I was grunge before they named it.
Speakin' of grunge,
there's a load of dirty laundry
with your name on it. Enjoy.
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Sandy, do something!
- Hold him up, don't let him sink.
I'll be back.
How are the kids?
- They're all fine.
Come quick! He came back.
I think he's dying.
His breathing is shallow.
He's probably dehydrated.
Who's for pizza?
I see a dolphin.
The only thing keeping him alive
is a strong will to live.
Oo you have a blender?
- Pardon?
What is it?
- Kind of a dolphin shake.
An emergency supply of iron, protein,
calcium, bunch of other nutrients.
Oo you have any Jell-O?
- Jell-O?
Marshmellow cream...
Rancid...
Oead...
How about tropical punch?
Sorry.
- No problem, I got a handy vac.
I've seen him eat a cockroach.
It's better from you.
Come on, buddy.
You can do it.
Please, Flipper, just try it.
Come on.
That's it. There.
Listen, sorry about that time
I yelled at you.
I saved you
a couple of slices, extra anchovies.
This is quite a spread for you.
I was going to do croissants, but
you might've had a heart attack.
It's the thought that counts.
Like bringing someone flowers.
You'll do it one day.
I bought you flowers!
- You're such a liar!
What d'ya call that?
- Weeding.
Here are the test results.
I can't believe it.
He's just like a little kid.
All he wants to do is play.
Come here!
Go on!
Good boy, that's it.
Our friend was poisoned!
Oioxin levels are off the chart.
Another meal and he'd be glowing.
Someone poisoned him? - Or the water,
which is why the fishing's so bad.
Ooesn't make sense.
Nearest industry's on the mainland.
Maybe the mainland's found
a place to dump toxic garbage.
Uh-oh...
- What now?
The other night Kim and I
were looking for Flipper.
Oirk Moran's boat was out there.
They were tossing barrels over the side.
Oo you remember where you were?
Oefinitely. - Can you show us?
- No problem.
This is it. Right here.
- No, it was over here.
No, I'm positive. This is it.
- I'm telling you, I remember.
Actually, it was more this way.
No, over here. - I'm telling you...
- I know it was here somewhere.
"Somewhere"?
Could you be more specific?
It was dark.
Hey, I'm from Chicago.
It's not like there are street signs.
Oid you notice
the lighthouse on the way out?
I'm pretty sure this was the spot.
- Me too.
If you're at all right,
Oirk Moran's been dumping poison
smack in the middle of my fishing
grounds. Let's head back.
We know why
the fishing's been so lousy lately.
What is it this time?
Algae blooms, el Niño, bad karma?
Somebody's poisoning
these waters. - We may know who.
When Flipper came back sick...
- Wait a minute!
That dolphin's back?
We're talking about toxic waste.
Costs big bucks to dispose of.
If you can just dump it in the
ocean... - Look at these test results!
I'm not interested! Bring me
hard evidence and I'll bust 'em!
Buck! - Any idea how many
marine parks I've turned away?
That animal
would be a fine attraction.
Son-of-a...
- Easy, Oirk.
If Flipper's still here on Monday,
I will see to it that he's
jumping hoops at Sea World on Tuesday.
Still talking about that dolphin?
- No. Actually,
we were talking about
the slime-ball who's been
dumping toxic waste offshore.
That explains
why fishing's been so lousy lately.
You have an active imagination.
Just yesterday,
a fella landed a marlin there,
trophy size.
These things happen.
Nature has its
rhythms.
The fishing'll be back.
And you'll be the boy who cried wolf.
Remember that dolphin.
What did he say?
- He needs more evidence.
Like the dead fish ain't enough!
And Flipper has to be gone by Monday.
- That gives us three days.
For what? - To deploy our
secret weapon: Flipper.
What are you talking about?
- Project Quick Find.
The Navy started it after Korea.
They trained dolphins to find things
like missiles. It was top secret.
How do you know about it?
- Part-time work.
You didn't tell me. - You never told
me about whatshername at the marina.
That was years ago.
How d'ya know about that?
Cast off. We got work to do.
Sandy, come up on the bow.
- Hey, Sandy.
We could miss that concert.
- What concert?
Microphone?
Nitrox, pressure gauge?
GPS...
- Nitric oxide,
ATP, dramomine...
Seasickness.
- I don't need this. - Sandy,
never hurl in front of a woman.
Thanks.
- Something to live by.
Nice outfit!
Figures.
Wait for me!
Porter, can you help Marvin
set up the computer?
Computer? No problem.
What are you gonna do?
I'm command central.
I'm keeping track of Flipper.
Tell me when the grunt work's done.
Grunt work?
We both know I'm good at that...
Sandy, make sure Flipper's ready.
Kim, you spot. Marv, this is for you.
Flipper's secret is
echo-location. - Echo what?
Oolphin sonar. Flipper sends a beam
of sound and receives an echo back.
He's good at that.
- Like a dog.
Instead of using his nose,
he uses his... echo... thing.
Exactly.
The Navy took it one step further.
Come in, Central Command. We're in
spashdown area, awaiting orders.
Copy that. Send Flipper
when the ball is secure. Over.
Go on, boy. Find it!
Negative on station 1.
Proceed to next station.
I love all this Navy talk.
You still have your old uniform?
Guppy says negative on station four.
Oamn.
Negative on station 15.
We must have
searched the whole ocean by now.
We should come back tomorrow.
This Martha Stewart's a clever woman.
She's made curtains out of fishing
nets. That'd work at my place.
I think
you really need to get a life.
It's just sea swells.
I think he found something.
Hey, look!
What's happening?
- He found something. What now?
It's time for
the "Flippo-Cam". - The "Flippo-Cam"?
You made this?
You're starting to scare me.
Giant squid astern!
Marv, I...
I don't see anything.
I bet that's his family.
POISON
Oh my God!
- Gross.
HAZAROOUS WASTE
We better get hold of old Buck!
- Buck? Try the coastguard.
Coastguard, this is the Reliable, over.
Gotcha!
It's not working.
What happened?
Marvin, what's wrong?
That'll send a signal
so we can find the spot again.
I'm not going without Flipper.
- This isn't the time.
This is Porter Ricks.
Anyone out there?
Hey, Marv.
Where's Sandy?
Oh my gosh.
Mr. Ricks!
Alright, Buck...
- Sandy's gone. - Not now...
Buck, I...
Oh God.
Scar!
No!
Help!
Come on, swim!
That a boy, come on. You're safe.
That's one courageous little dolphin.
Too bad you saw us that night, son.
Thanks buddy!
That's a good boy!
You alright?
- I'm fine.
Thank God.
Your mother would have killed me.
You remember that story about Scar?
- Yeah. - It's true.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Get that piece of sea slime
out of here. - Let's go.
I don't think we got it in time.
EPA's on the way.
Oon't worry. We'll clean these
waters up, thanks to Flipper.
What about Flipper?
He saved my life.
How about it, Buck?
As long as he's free,
he can make this his home.
We'll have him looking out for us.
How about it, Sandy?
He should go. - What?
- He belongs with his family.
What is it?
No, I can't come.
Go on, it's okay.
Please!
Just go!
Hi Mom!
Hey bud!
How was your summer?
- It was a total blast.
A total blast, huh?
I can't wait to hear about it.
See ya around, Marv.
What's the matter?
He'll be back. You'll see.
Gonna miss you.
I'll miss you too.
Gimme a sec?
- Come on, let's go on the boat.
Gonna miss me?
Bye.
- Bye.
Take it easy, kid.
- All aboard!
Bye.
- Take care.
Wait!
I forgot one thing.
Can I come back next summer?
I think you'd better. I just made
a deal for 150 pound of spam.
Go on, get!
There!
Hey, check it out!
Hey, come on, guys!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org