The formally attired gentleman
is Edward Van Sloan,
who plays Doctor Waldman
in Frankenstein.
Here he is out of character
to introduce the film.
Van Sloan had closed the Bela Lugosi
Dracula film in a similar manner.
This was an added scene, photographed
long after the film completed production,
in anticipation of objections
from religious groups
over the theme of divine presumption.
Staff Universal screenwriter at the time,
John Huston, wrote earlier drafts
that included lines such as "Frightful,
supremely frightful, would be the effect
of any human endeavour to mock the
stupendous mechanism of the creator."
Scenario editor Richard Schayer
wrote another version,
which includes material used
in the speech now being given:
"Here we unfold the portentous record
of Frankenstein, man of science,
who sought to create a man in
his own image, not reckoning upon God."
This is Rudy Behlmer speaking.
The main title is presented
in a properly misterioso manner.
The music is an original composition
written for the picture
by film composer Bernhard Kaun.
Other than the end-title music,
it is the only scoring used in the picture.
This was typical for 1931.
Background scoring throughout a film did
not become accepted practice until later.
The writing credits
may seem a bit complicated:
"Based upon the composition", "From
the novel", "Adapted from the play",
"Screen Play", "Scenario Editor"...
All this will be sorted out.
Then, of course, a single card
for director James Whale.
Notice "The Monster" is only identified
by a question mark in the cast list.
This was reminiscent of the very first
stage production of Frankenstein in 1823.
The character of the monster was billed
only with a question mark at that time.
Originally, this opening sequence
began with a distant shot in profile
of the funeral procession going up the hill.
This was dropped during editing,
but appeared briefly during the flashback
sequence in The Bride of Frankenstein.
The panning shot of mourners
ends by a statue...
and the statue is of the Grim Reaper.
Here we are introduced to Henry
Frankenstein, played by Colin Clive,
and his assistant, played by Dwight Frye.
This sequence does not derive
from the novel,
nor does it derive from any of
the play adaptations that followed.
But the novel that spawned
the Frankenstein phenomenon
was radically different in many ways
from the countless dramatisations
that followed on stage and screen.
When did this saga
of Frankenstein begin?
It started on a stormy night, June 1816,
with a 19-year-old woman
who was lying half-awake in a villa
on the shores of Lake Léman
in Switzerland.
Mary Wollstonecraft Godwin was staying
there with her lover, later her husband,
the poet Shelley.
Together with their neighbour Lord Byron,
his physician, Doctor Polidori,
and Mary's stepsister Claire,
they would often gather on chilly, wet
evenings and read ghost stories aloud.
One evening Byron suggested
they each try their hand at writing a story,
a story of the supernatural.
On another night, Mary heard an intense
conversation between Shelley and Byron
concerning the nature
of the principle of life,
and whether it might ever be
discovered and communicated.
According to Mary,
the talk went on to include speculation
that perhaps a corpse
could be reanimated,
perhaps the component parts
of a creature might be manufactured,
brought together
and imbued with vital warmth.
After going to bed, she later wrote
"I did not sleep,
nor could I be said to think."
"I saw - with shut eyes,
but acute mental vision -
I saw the pale student of unhallowed arts
kneeling beside the thing
he had put together."
And here's Frankenstein literally
throwing dirt on the face of death.
"I saw the hideous phantasm
of a man stretched out,
and then, on the working of some
powerful engine, show signs of life
and stir with an uneasy, half-vital motion."
"His success would terrify the artist."
"He would rush away from
his odious handiwork horror-stricken."
"I could not so easily get rid of my
hideous phantom - still it haunted me."
"On the morrow, I announced
that I had thought of a story."
Shelley encouraged her
to develop and expand the material.
He also helped her to edit
the manuscript as it evolved.
21 months later, in March 1818,
Frankenstein was published.
In 1831, Mary Shelley
revised her novel for a new edition.
She also added an introduction,
which tells the story of its origin
and ends with Mary bidding her
"hideous progeny go forth and prosper."
And indeed it did.
Frankenstein is one of
the most often-reprinted novels
in the history of literature.
The adaptability of the story to the theatre
was recognised immediately.
In 1823, there were at least five
stage versions, both serious and comic.
One, Presumption; or, the Fate
of Frankenstein by Richard Peake,
was to serve as a basic transcription
of the novel for the stage
and a source for further elaboration.
Action and melodrama were
the keynotes of Peake's play,
and Frankenstein the creator
and his creature
were presented as instant antagonists.
There is a major creation sequence -
not in the novel -
an assistant to Frankenstein named Fritz -
and a non-talking monster.
In the book, Frankenstein's creature
eventually becomes absolutely verbose,
with an impressive vocabulary
and masterful syntax.
His monologues run on for pages
and, on occasion, entire chapters.
Here at the medical college we are going
to meet again actor Edward Van Sloan,
this time in character
as Doctor Waldman -
a variation on his Van Helsing role
in Universal's Dracula with Bela Lugosi
that was released earlier in 1931.
Van Sloan also played Van Helsing in the
New York stage production of Dracula,
with Lugosi, in 1927.
Later he played Van Helsing again
in Universal's 1936 sequel
Dracula's Daughter,
and a similar role, Professor Muller,
in The Mummy in 1932.
Van Sloan began his professional
acting career on the stage in 1910.
He worked with stock companies
in Montreal, Canada,
and in Boston, Newark and Cleveland,
finally reaching the New York stage
in 1923.
All in all, he was in
approximately 150 plays.
His film career began with Dracula, but
he soon became a victim of typecasting:
The Death Kiss, Death Takes a Holiday,
The Black Room, The Phantom Creeps,
Before I Hang, The Monster and the Girl,
and so on and so on.
He died in 1964.
The technical advisor for Waldman's
lecture was Doctor Cecil Miller,
a brain specialist.
The character of Fritz, played by
Dwight Frye, was not in the novel,
but was introduced in the 1823
Richard Peake stage dramatisation.
In early drafts of the film scripts
the character was mute,
but it made sense to give him speech
so that Frankenstein could have dialogue
rather than talking to himself
or resorting to pantomime
during the rather nefarious
preparatory work for the experiments.
The about-to-be-dropped-and-shattered
"normal brain",
followed by Fritz
taking the "criminal brain",
was a later addition to the script
by Francis Edwards Faragoh.
This element had never been used before
in novel or plays,
and indeed took away from
the basic innocence of the monster.
Perhaps it was felt, because of the severe
time compression necessary in the film,
that the criminal brain would justify
the monster's early acts of violence,
in addition to his being tormented.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Close-up of Henry Frankenstein's
photograph.
Close-up of a maid.
Close-up of guest, Victor Moritz.
Close-up of Henry's fiancée Elizabeth.
Then cut back to the establishing shot,
with the top half, including chandelier,
being a matte painting.
A rather unusual way to introduce
a new sequence and new characters.
The room in Elizabeth's home
is a set left over from Universal's
The Cat and the Canary from 1927.
Leading man John Boles
was given the thankless part
of Henry's friend and Elizabeth's friend -
although he would like to be
much more than friend to Elizabeth.
Boles acted and sang on Broadway,
then came to Hollywood
and starred in several musicals,
such as The Desert Song,
Rio Rita and King of Jazz,
revealing a rich baritone voice.
Later he became a leading man
in screen soap operas,
such as the 1932 Back Street, Only
Yesterday, and the 1937 Stella Dallas.
And he was a father or father figure
to Shirley Temple
in The Littlest Rebel and Curly Top.
Here it is planted that Victor has strong
romantic feelings toward Elizabeth,
but, being a gentleman,
he doesn't overplay his hand,
and for the most part stays
in control with regard to his feelings.
Henry Henigson, a Universal executive,
early in the preparation of Frankenstein
complained to screenwriter Garrett Fort
that the implied frustrated love affair
between Elizabeth and Victor
was "insufficient"
as relief from the horror plot.
Fort responded "The girl is not deeply
in love with Henry and does love Victor."
"Her wedding to Henry is the result of a
childhood arrangement between families,
quite in keeping with the continental
conception of such matters."
"She is fond of Henry, she admires him."
"Her emotions, when she finds him
in trouble, are not those of love, but pity."
"She has given up Victor
because of obligations
she feels she cannot sidestep."
"Henry is an abnormal character.
The Victor and girl character are normal."
"The audience will be rooting for them,
although, at the same time, sympathetic
to Henry because of his ill-starred love,
wrecked because of
his absorption in science."
"The girl, in her scenes with Henry,
will receive all the sympathy
because we realise
she is making the best of a bad bargain,
but doing it like a thoroughbred."
Mae Clarke,
director James Whale's leading lady
in the recently completed
Waterloo Bridge, whom he liked,
was a natural choice
for Frankenstein's fiancée.
She had been in film since 1929, and
before that was a dancer, actress, singer,
appearing primarily in nightclubs,
Broadway musicals, vaudeville.
In 1974, author Anita Loos
revealed that Clarke
was the inspiration for her Lorelei Lee
in Gentlemen Prefer Blondes in 1926.
"I patterned her on a cute, little blonde
HL Mencken was escorting at the time."
"Her name was Mae Clarke.
Mencken was a beau of mine."
In The Public Enemy, also made in 1931,
Clarke was the memorable recipient
of a half-grapefruit slapped and twisted
on her face by James Cagney.
She was Cagney's leading lady in
two other films after The Public Enemy -
Lady Killer and Great Guy.
Mae had a stand-out and showy role
as Molly the prostitute
in the 1931 version of The Front Page.
But her starring role in Waterloo Bridge,
in which she played a woman forced to
turn to prostitution by her circumstances,
was Clarke's favourite part -
and she is excellent in it,
delivering a performance
of extraordinary delicacy.
Because of legal complications regarding
two remakes, one with Vivien Leigh,
it was unavailable for viewing
for decades.
James Whale said that on Frankenstein
"I asked for Mae Clarke for Elizabeth
because of her intelligence, fervour
and sincere belief that Frankenstein
would claim the public interest."
The only other actress of record
considered for the part was Bette Davis,
under contract to Universal
for six months.
But apparently producer Carl Laemmle Jr
did not think too highly of her sex appeal.
After Frankenstein,
James Whale immediately cast Mae
in the leading role
in The lmpatient Maiden.
Here is the miniature exterior
of the old watchtower set
and the full-scale portion of the exterior.
The interiors were built
on a Universal sound stage.
Back in 1927, English theatrical
producer and actor Hamilton Deane
decided to try out
another subject for his company,
to alternate with his version
of Bram Stoker's novel Dracula,
on his tour of the English provinces.
This was to be a new adaptation
of Frankenstein by Peggy Webling.
The initial presentation of this
Frankenstein took place late in 1927
in Preston, England.
It continued to alternate
in the provinces with Dracula,
and it finally opened in London,
considerably revised, in February 1930.
Peggy Webling retained some basic ideas
from the novel and the previous plays,
but she made substantial changes
in time, locale, incidents and characters.
Mary Shelley's narrative took place
over a considerable period of time.
In the novel, Frankenstein vows
to destroy his creation
and pursues him to the Arctic,
where the scientist dies
and his foe goes off into the ice and mist,
presumably to his death.
Shortly after the play opened in London,
the London Times announced
that it would be produced on Broadway.
As with Deane's Dracula,
playwright and newspaper correspondent
John L Balderston -
who had recently written
the hit play Berkeley Square -
was engaged to revise and brush up
the material for American consumption.
He kept, for the most part, Peggy
Webling's modifications and structure,
but he added several touches of his own.
For example, Fritz, the hunchback who
assists Frankenstein in his experiments,
was added - although he is mute
in Balderston's version.
With the release of Dracula in early 1931,
Universal Pictures had a major success.
Even before it was in theatres, there had
been discussions regarding a follow-up.
Frankenstein was a logical choice.
The film Dracula was based more on the
Hamilton Deane play than on the novel.
This stage version had been exceptionally
well received in England and in America.
Since Universal bought the play version
of Dracula from Deane and Balderston,
they decided to do the same
with Frankenstein.
The original novel, of course,
was in the public domain.
In May 1931, the screen rights for the play
were purchased for $20,000,
At Universal's stipulation, the play wasn't
produced in America - never has been -
contrary to the original plan.
Notice the lateral move here.
James Whale liked moving from one area
to another, as on a stage, with a cutaway.
Rex Ingram's 1926 film The Magician
has various aspects that were
later used in Frankenstein.
The dwarf assistant in The Magician
hobbled down a staircase
similar to the one in this film
when he was going
to open the tower door.
Also, there is a comic porter scene
from Shakespeare's Macbeth,
and that's often been cited
as an influence.
In a letter, Florey said that he and Schayer
"worked with Garrett Fort" -
who wrote Universal's Dracula -
"on the first screenplay, following
the lines of my synopsis treatment."
"Fort wrote the dialogue."
"My contribution was as continuity
of action and development."
Florey directed a test, shot on
the castle set left over from Dracula,
with Bela - Dracula - Lugosi
in the role of the monster.
As early as April, Lugosi had been
announced for Frankenstein.
Florey claims he had thought of him
for the role of Frankenstein,
but that Universal executives
insisted he play the monster.
According to Florey, the edited test ran for
20 minutes, which seems extremely long.
It was photographed by Paul lvano,
and it started with a short conversation
between Victor Moritz and Waldman,
leading to both going
into the Frankenstein laboratory.
Following a scene with
Frankenstein and Fritz in the lab,
there was the arrival
of Waldman and Victor.
According to Florey,
the test lasted up to and including
the initial awakening of the monster.
The actors involved were
Edward Van Sloan, Dwight Frye, Lugosi -
all of whom from the film Dracula -
and two stock players.
From all indications,
Lugosi's test make-up and garb
were reminiscent of
Paul Wegener in The Golem,
the 1920 German film about
a legendary figure of clay
brought to life by Rabbi Loew
in the 15th century.
According to Forrest J Ackerman's
interview with Edward Van Sloan -
who later played the major role of
Doctor Waldman in Frankenstein -
Lugosi arrived for the test
with a head "about four times normal size,
with a broad wig on it."
"He had a polished clay-like skin."
Lugosi claimed he did not want to play
a speechless brute laden with make-up.
Mary Shelley's and Webling
and Balderston's talking monster
had been relieved of speech,
but he did speak in Universal's first
sequel, The Bride of Frankenstein,
for which Balderston received
co-adaptation credit.
The evolving script at the time presented
the monster as totally unsympathetic,
devoid of any pathos.
Who could blame Lugosi?
In an interview Carl Laemmle Jr gave
within six months of his death,
he states that the sight of Lugosi
in the test make-up
made the studio head
"laugh like a hyena".
Florey claimed
the test make-up was virtually identical
to the final make-up worn by Karloff,
but obviously Laemmle didn't regard
the Karloff version as funny in any way.
Karloff himself recalled that
he had been told the Lugosi make-up
was "a horrid, hairy thing.
Not at all like our monster."
Make-up artist Jack Pierce
told an interviewer
that Lugosi himself influenced
the test make-up negatively,
thinking "his ideas
were better than anyone's."
Though not followed to the letter,
the general structure of the first half
of the Webling/Balderston play
was at least in evidence in
the evolving film script for Frankenstein.
But the last part of the play was not used
until Universal made
Bride of Frankenstein four years later.
The final act of the play was concerned
with Frankenstein's preparations
for the making of a mate for the creature.
This originated in the novel.
But the monster kills Frankenstein
in the play
after his creator decides at the last
moment not to provide him with a mate.
Then the monster stumbles into
the electrical apparatus
and dies as a result of a flash of lightning
and the machine that brought him to life.
Between the time the play premiered
in Preston, England, in 1927
and its London opening in 1930,
there were considerable changes
in the script.
In the early version, the monster
leaps from a cliff and destroys himself.
Frankenstein and his fiancée, whom
the monster had wanted to possess,
are then happily reunited.
There is no material regarding the plan
to create a mate for the monster.
By the end of June, a director
was confirmed for Frankenstein:
Britisher James Whale.
Whale was relatively new to Universal.
He'd just finished directing an extremely
well-received screen adaptation
of Robert Sherwood's play
Waterloo Bridge for that studio.
His previous film-directing credits
were the dialogue scenes in Howard
Hughes' aviation epic, Hell's Angels,
and all of Journey's End -
the screen version of the exceptionally
popular RC Sherriff World War I play
that Whale had directed on the stage
in London and then in New York.
All of the elaborate electrical apparatus,
full of sound and fury,
but signifying and actually doing nothing,
was built by Kenneth Strickfaden,
who began his film career
as an electrician in 1921.
The first film to use some of
his electrical pyrotechnics
was the 1929 Return of Sherlock Holmes.
The devices that, as a hobby, he had
collected over the years and stored,
came from discarded industrial parts,
old aeroplanes, sections of automobiles,
radio-broadcast transmitters and
odds and ends of electrical equipment.
In 1981, he said "I'd put something
together, then sit back and marvel at it."
"Then I found there was a market."
"The styling all depended upon
what kind of junk I had at hand."
The apparatus was leased by the studio
and Ray Lindsay operated it.
In 1981, the Academy of Motion Picture
Arts and Sciences sponsored a gala affair
in Strickfaden's honour.
Above the ceiling-opening of the lab set
electricians operated
large lightning-arc machines,
which gave off bright flashes of
intermittent light and showers of sparks.
Boris Karloff recalled years later "The
scene made me as uneasy as anyone,
for while I lay half-naked and strapped
to Doctor Frankenstein's table,
I could see directly above me
the special-effects men
brandishing the white-hot, scissors-like
carbons that made the lightning."
"I hoped that no one up there
had butterfingers."
Director James Whale later commented
on the importance of the creation scene:
"I consider the creation of the monster
to be the high spot of the film,
because if the audience did not believe
the thing had been really made,
they would not be bothered with
what it was supposed to do afterward."
"By this time, the audience must at least
believe something is going to happen."
"It might be disaster, but at least
they will settle down to see the show."
The lines "In the name of God" and
"Now I know what it feels like to be God"
were deleted by some local and regional
censor groups at the time.
And in 1937,
the Production Code Office required
that the lines, among other aspects,
definitely be eliminated
for reissue approval.
Throughout this film, scenes of
incredible intensity and dramatic impact
are relieved by relatively mild scenes.
Here we are introduced to
Henry's father, Baron Frankenstein,
portrayed by
British stage actor Frederick Kerr,
who had recently worked with
director Whale on Waterloo Bridge.
Incidentally, the baron here refers to
"an old ruined windmill" where his son is.
In early drafts of the script, Frankenstein's
laboratory was in an old ruined windmill.
This was changed to a watchtower,
but somehow this reference
in the script wasn't changed.
Frederick Kerr was on the stage
almost continuously for 50 years
in both England and America.
In 1930, he commenced his film career
and appeared in Raffles with
Ronald Colman, among other films.
Whale requested Kerr for both
Waterloo Bridge and Frankenstein
and said that
"He is an asset to any picture."
Kerr died in 1933 at the age of 74.
Enter the burgomaster,
played by Lionel Belmore.
The British actor arrived in America
in 1907 after being on the London stage.
For a long time he was with
the old Vitagraph Studio in New York City.
Belmore appeared in a great range
of parts over the years,
in such films as the 1922
Oliver Twist, the 1924 Sea Hawk,
The King of Kings, The Count of Monte
Cristo, Cleopatra, Mutiny on the Bounty,
Little Lord Fauntleroy and
The Adventures of Robin Hood in 1938.
His so-called horror pictures are
The Vampire Bat, Son of Frankenstein,
Tower of London
and The Ghost of Frankenstein.
Apparently, producer Carl Laemmle Jr
wanted Whale to do Frankenstein.
He was now the fair-haired boy
around the lot.
But Whale wasn't sure.
Dracula and Frankenstein
were both pushed through to production
by junior Laemmle's efforts.
He was enthusiastic
about this tale of the macabre,
but his father, Carl Senior, founder and
president of Universal, was apprehensive.
Frankenstein was even
stronger stuff than Dracula.
But young Laemmle, who had been
made head of production in 1929
as a 21st-birthday present from his father,
had been right about the very successful
All Quiet on the Western Front in 1930,
and, of course, he was right
about the recent Dracula.
Whale, after giving the subject some
thought, decided to do Frankenstein -
partly, perhaps, because it wasn't
yet another World War I subject.
Here is another relatively
calm and quiet scene.
But we are gradually building up
to the revealment of the creature,
better known as "the monster",
although so far he has done
nothing to deserve that title.
Remember, in 1931 no one had seen
what the character had looked like,
other than advertisements, posters.
His visage was hardly that of the icon
we have known through the decades.
Also, we weren't sure what he would do,
how he would react, what would happen.
This speech of Henry Frankenstein,
not in the final shooting script,
gives us an added dimension
to Henry's character and psyche.
Colin Clive plays it extremely well.
It is a telling counterpoint to his utterly
believable theatrics in the creation scene.
Here is the intelligent,
enquiring and sensitive human side
of the obsessed and passionate
man of science.
Although Universal wanted Leslie Howard
for the role of Henry Frankenstein,
Whale insisted on Colin Clive,
the British leading player of the stage
and screen versions of Journey's End,
both directed by Whale.
Universal went along with Whale,
and Clive sailed from England.
Even assuming that Fritz replaced the jar
marked "abnormal brain"
before handing it to Frankenstein,
it would seem, with all his training, the
doctor would have spotted the differences
between a criminal brain
and a normal brain,
as outlined and demonstrated
by Doctor Waldman.
Well, let's call it dramatic licence.
The monster's criminal brain became
a thread in many Universal follow-ups.
The first son of Frankenstein wanted to
provide the monster with a healthy brain.
The second son did replace the brain,
but with one not exactly normal -
that of lgor, played by Bela Lugosi.
Then, in 1948, Count Dracula - Lugosi -
would try to give the monster
the brain of Lou Costello
in Abbott and Costello Meet Frankenstein.
And so it goes, or so it went.
And now, after much anticipation, surely
one of the great theatrical entrances.
Whale chose to direct this
in an unusual, but very effective manner.
First, we heard the sound of
the monster in the hall: Suspense.
Then, when the door opens,
he walks in backwards: More suspense.
And the dramatic turn, followed by
a series of progressively closer shots,
which allow us to be startled,
and yet able to observe in detail that face.
Whale certainly was involved in
the concept of the monster's look.
He made several sketches and consulted
with make-up artist Jack Pierce,
but Pierce was the man
who executed the work.
He and Karloff worked for several hours
each evening over a three-week period
to evolve the make-up
prior to the start of production.
Over a bald cap, the head was built up
with layers of cotton and collodion.
The scars were painted on, and
careful shadow-definitions were applied.
Pierce would then hand-lay the hair.
Karloff had a bridge of molars
on his right side that were removed
and he sucked in his cheek.
Pierce shaded this for accent.
Karloff's lean, gaunt face and features
were necessary for the perfect realisation.
A top layer of blue-green greasepaint
gave the skin a grey look
on black-and-white film.
Karloff, according to some accounts,
suggested his eyelids be heavily caked,
giving the creature a look
of only partial awareness.
Pierce accomplished this
with mortician's wax.
The metal studs that protruded
from the sides of the monster's neck
were inlets for electricity.
Significantly, the creative make-up always
allowed Karloff's expressions full play,
accounting to a considerable degree for
the effectiveness of his characterisation.
His legs were stiffened by steel struts.
To add to the bulk, he wore a built-up
and padded double-quilted suit
and raised heavy boots.
These were weighted in such a way as to
enable him to lean considerably forward.
The ill-fitting black suit
was made up with shortened sleeves
to make his arms appear longer.
Years later,
Pierce stated that the monster's
final visage was "a compromise"
between his own ideas
and those of Whale.
The overall look of the monster
in all of the subsequent Universal sequels
was never as effective as it was
in the original production -
at least, in my opinion.
Karloff's test convinced
Whale and Universal executives
that he was perfect for the part.
In the August 12th script
this scene is handled quite differently.
I quote from that script:
"The dwarf drops on the floor on all fours,
fumbles in his pocket,
takes out a dirty package of cigarettes,
strikes a match and lights a cigarette."
"The moment the monster sees the fire,
it lets out an unearthly shriek."
"Lts mouth widens to a hideous grin,
its awful hands beat the air,
it starts to rise from the chair,
moves toward the dwarf."
"Frankenstein and Waldman shout.
The monster takes no notice, however."
"So Frankenstein, now frightened,
seizes a box of matches
and strikes match after match
in the monster's face until it is cowed."
"He grovels on the floor, shrieking."
"Frankenstein again
approaches the monster."
"This time he holds a single lighted match
in front of the latter's eyes a long while."
"The monster shrinks from the fire."
"During this, the dwarf
has maliciously crept up."
"Stealthily, he kicks the monster."
"Just at this moment, Frankenstein's
last match flares up, then dies out."
Obviously, changing the matches to
a torch made much more dramatic sense
and was a precursor for things to come.
Fritz is played by
Kansas-born Dwight Frye -
neither a dwarf nor a hunchback,
but another victim of typecasting
after his role in the 1931 Dracula
as the crazed Renfield.
After Frankenstein, he was the village
lunatic in The Vampire Bat, and so on.
But, before coming to Hollywood in 1930,
he had an impressive career on the stage.
After touring in stock,
vaudeville and musical comedy,
he then had leading roles
in a variety of Broadway plays,
and in 1929 the critics voted him one of
the ten best actors of the legitimate stage.
He died in 1943, aged 44,
from a heart attack,
which could have been brought on
by the strain of working nights
at Lockheed Aircraft Company in World
War II in order to support his family,
while playing some bit roles by day
and acting in local theatrical productions.
His death certificate listed his occupation
as "tool designer".
In the play,
especially in Balderston's version,
Frankenstein's relationship to the monster
is decreed, in Frankenstein's words,
as "Only command, blind obedience,
no discussion."
He treats the creature cruelly,
and in Balderston's adaptations makes
considerable use of a whip and a hot iron.
He also finds satisfaction in having
the monster perform tricks like a puppy,
literally commanding him to "lie down,
roll over", and he refers to him as a slave.
Frankenstein announces that the creature
"must be afraid of me. He must obey me."
This cruelty is transferred in the final
screen version to the character of Fritz,
who continually provokes Frankenstein's
creation with whip and torch,
thereby making Frankenstein
more sympathetic.
Incidentally, many people refer to
the monster by the name of Frankenstein.
In fact, in Peggy Webling's 1927 play,
the revised 1930 presentation,
and Balderston's version of the play,
the monster is called Frankenstein
after its creator,
on many occasions
by some of the characters.
Whale was quoted, when asked why
he decided to do Frankenstein:
"Of 30 available stories,
it was the strongest meat,
and gave me a chance
to dabble in the macabre."
"I thought it would be amusing to try
and make a physical impossibility
seem believable."
"Also it offered fine pictorial chances,
had two grand characterisations,
and had a subject matter
that might go anywhere -
and that's part of the fun
of making pictures."
Among the changes made in the script by
the new writer, Francis Edwards Faragoh,
was giving dialogue to Fritz,
Frankenstein's assistant,
who in the previous Universal scripts
had been a mute.
Also, Frankenstein's laboratory
was now located in an old watchtower,
rather than the deserted mill.
The mill, however, was retained
for the final scene.
Most importantly, both Frankenstein
and the monster were modified
into basically more sympathetic
characters, given more dimension.
Certainly now
we feel sorry for the monster,
as in the novel and the Webling play.
In the novel
Frankenstein is a student of science,
not a doctor, not the son of a baron.
The scene in which
the monster is given life
takes place in the upstairs room
of Frankenstein's house,
not, as in this film, an old watchtower.
There is no apparatus giving forth
a pyrotechnic display during the creation,
no raging electrical storm outside.
In the Webling/Balderston play,
Frankenstein's study, in an old house
at Goldstadt in Switzerland,
has been fashioned into a laboratory, and
there's a storm during the creation scene.
In the early versions of the screenplay
an abandoned windmill is used for the lab
and a storm is raging.
A description of the setting in a
preliminary script draft in the studio files
mentions "something suggestive
of the laboratory in Metropolis."
The 1926 German silent film
had a mad scientist
involved in a laboratory creation scene
amidst considerable
electrical paraphernalia.
In Mary Shelley's book,
the description of the procedures
by which Frankenstein gave
his creation life is vague.
Indeed, this major sequence
of the creation, a high point in this film,
is presented in one
not-very-detailed paragraph in the book:
"It was on a dreary night of November that
I beheld the accomplishment of my toils."
"With an anxiety
that almost amounted to agony,
I collected the instruments of life
around me,
that I might infuse a spark of being
into the lifeless thing that lay at my feet."
"It was already one in the morning;
the rain pattered dismally
outside the panes,
and my candle was
nearly burnt out, when,
by the glimmer of
the half-extinguished light,
I saw the dull, yellow eye
of the creature open."
"It breathed hard and
a convulsive motion agitated its limbs."
Then in another paragraph she wrote:
"I had worked hard for nearly two years
for the sole purpose of infusing life
into an inanimate body."
"For this I had deprived myself
of rest and health."
"I had desired it with an ardour
that far exceeded moderation,
but now, now that I had finished,
the beauty of the dream vanished,
and breathless horror and disgust
filled my heart."
The monster has been described
as a projection
of Mary Shelley's feeling
of isolation and hatred,
which stem from the death of her mother
when she was only ten days old.
Mary was barely tolerated
by her cruel father and was driven inward,
spending her childhood in solitary
pastimes: Reading, writing, daydreaming.
In a letter sent to Colin Clive
before production,
director James Whale described how he
perceived the character of Frankenstein:
"An intensely sane person,
at times rather fanatical, and
in one or two scenes, a little hysterical."
"And a little reminiscent of
the breakdown in Journey's End."
"Frankenstein's nerves are all to pieces."
"All the time I should feel Frankenstein
is normally an extremely intelligent,
a sane and lovable person, never
unsympathetic, even to the monster."
Shortly after talking over Frankenstein,
James Whale did not have an actor
in mind to play the monster.
Whale's companion, David Lewis,
had been impressed
with Boris Karloff's performance
as the rather ungainly and odd convict
in the stage and screen versions
of The Criminal Code.
He recommended that Whale meet
the actor to see for himself the potential.
Whale and Karloff arranged a meeting and
Whale decided to test him for the role.
Whale said later on
that he was fascinated by Karloff's face:
"His physique was weaker
than I could wish,
but that queer, penetrating personality,
I felt, was more important than his shape,
which could easily be altered."
Although Karloff had been
in American films since 1919,
he was hardly a well-known performer.
Most of his parts in silent films
were small or not particularly significant,
but just before Frankenstein
things were looking somewhat better,
with showy parts in
The Criminal Code and Five Star Final.
Karloff's real name
was William Henry Pratt.
Born in a London suburb,
he emigrated to Canada in 1909
and eventually joined
various theatrical touring companies,
playing supporting roles in plays
all over Canada and the United States.
By 1919, he was in Hollywood
playing extra and bit parts in films.
He also alternated as a truck driver
until the mid-'20s to support himself.
Frankenstein, of course, made him a star
in a myriad of horror films,
but he also played character parts
in a variety of other films.
But the public identified him with horror.
Once again, as relief and counterpoint to
all of the preceding high-intensity drama,
or melodrama, if you will,
and the mayhem,
we have a tranquil and idyllic interlude.
A romantic scene, yet.
Colin Clive gets an opportunity
to shift gears
now that he is away from
graveyards and old watchtowers.
Clive was from a military family,
a descendant of the famous Clive of India.
His father was a distinguished colonel
in the British army.
Young Colin's horse fell
in cavalry training,
fracturing the young man's knee
and ending his military future.
The leg never fully healed.
He was forced to resign from
Sandhurst Royal Military College
and went into the theatre, training
at the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art.
He made his London bow in 1919
and toured in many plays,
including repertory companies.
James Whale hired him to play
the doomed Captain Stanhope
in the extremely successful
World War I drama Journey's End.
He starred in the play and film version,
which was also directed by Whale.
Other film roles following Frankenstein
include One More River, from
the last of The Forsyte Saga novels,
also directed by Whale,
Clive of India, about his ancestor,
Mad Love, based on The Hands of Orlac,
The Man Who Broke the Bank
at Monte Carlo,
and, of course,
The Bride of Frankenstein in 1935,
in which he reprised his role
for director Whale.
Mae Clarke said in 1971
"Oh, how I remember that voice."
"Jim Whale would say about Colin
'His voice is like a pipe organ."'
"'You just arrange him, pull out the stops
and his voice comes out like music."'
But Clive in his personal life
was tormented and anguished,
fraught with his private demons -
a kind of Jekyll and Hyde.
He also drank heavily.
In 1937, at the age of 37,
Colin Clive died as a result of alcoholism.
Prior to the 1931 Frankenstein there were
three silent-film productions of the story,
the first going back to 1910.
The Edison Company's
approximately 15-minute-long version,
according to the script, was a liberal
adaptation of Mrs Shelley's famous story.
It featured a hunchbacked
and shaggy-chested monster
suggestive of Quasimodo,
with a stark, kabuki-like white face
and a mass of matted hair.
The monster was formed
in a "cauldron of blazing chemical"
rather than with the aid of electricity.
The climax of the film introduced
some aspects of the Jekyll-Hyde theme -
the monster was defeated
by the power of love.
This, presumably the world's
first horror film, was filmed
at the Edison Manufacturing Company
Studio at Bedford Park, the Bronx,
under the direction of J Searle Dawley,
and was colour-tinted and/or toned
for daylight and night scenes.
Then there was the feature-length
Life Without Soul in 1915.
In this adaptation the monster had
no bizarre trappings or unusual make-up.
He was "awe-inspiring,
but never grotesque".
One character was established by being
shown reading the story from a book.
When Frankenstein died
after killing the monster,
the book was closed and each of the
characters revealed to be alive and well.
The third filming was done in Italy in 1920
and called The Monster of Frankenstein.
No known negatives or prints
survive of the silent productions,
with the exception of the 1910 version.
With the exception of this sequence,
Frankenstein was filmed on the Universal
lot and the immediate surrounding terrain.
But now the production moved to what
was almost certainly Lake Sherwood
in the Santa Monica Mountains
near Westlake Village
and close to the dividing line between
Los Angeles County and Ventura County.
Lake Sherwood and its immediate
neighbour, Sherwood Forest,
had been used for many years as a choice
location for all kinds of outdoor pictures.
The name, according to various sources,
derived from its use
in Douglas Fairbanks's
1922 production of Robin Hood,
and it was ideal for jungle epics,
Westerns, you name it.
Seven-year-old Marilyn Harris
was chosen to befriend the monster
in this delicate portrayal.
The monster, for the first and only time,
finds a human who is unafraid of him -
an innocent peasant child.
Karloff later said
"Whale and I both saw the character
of the monster as an innocent one."
"This was a pathetic creature
who, like us all,
had neither wish nor say in his creation,
and certainly did not wish upon itself
the hideous image
which automatically terrified humans
whom it tried to befriend."
"What astonished us was
the fantastic number of ordinary people
that got this general air of sympathy."
"I found all my letters heavy with it."
In the Peggy Webling play the monster
accidentally crushes a dove in his hands
and throws it into the lake,
where, much to his delight, it floats.
Then he takes Frankenstein's crippled
sister, a character not in the novel or film,
out in a boat and tries to make her
float like the dove - but she drowns.
His remorse at this act
is one of the motivations
that leads to his flinging himself
off the cliff in the 1927 play version.
The monster, as portrayed by Hamilton
Deane in this play, was sympathetic.
In a variant version from the same play,
at the side of a river the creature, unaware
that death can be caused by drowning,
placed the girl's head beneath the water
to see her lovely face
through the glassy surface.
Marilyn Harris, years later, recalled that
"After the monster threw me into the lake
I was supposed to swim underwater,
but I had only three swimming lessons.
I didn't even know how to go underwater."
"They had rowboats in a semicircle
outside of camera range,
but the first time the monster threw me in
I couldn't go underwater,
I had too many clothes on."
"I had to get all my clothes dry
and my hair redone", says Marilyn.
"The second shot went fine.
Boris Karloff threw me in again
and I went underwater
out of camera range."
Touched and excited
with his first encounter with beauty,
the monster tries to float the little girl
and feels intense pain and confusion
when she sinks.
Later the scene was considerably cut
and modified from what you see now,
but more about that anon.
This European village
was built on the back lot at Universal
for All Quiet on the Western Front in 1930.
It was used through the years
for a great many films,
including subsequent
Frankenstein productions.
The village was destroyed by fire
many years later.
The present European street
was then constructed on the same site.
The dances are authentically performed
by Austrian musicians and dancers.
Incidentally, where exactly are we?
In Austria, Germany, Switzerland?
And what is the time period?
The wardrobe varies from 1931 fashions
to Doctor Waldman's frock coat
of an earlier vintage.
There is never any indication of
an automobile, a telephone, a radio,
to say nothing of the practice of hanging
bodies on gibbets for public viewing.
This was abandoned in Europe
before the 20th century.
And, being somewhere in Europe, they all
speak with a British or American accent.
In another exchange between
Universal executive Henry Henigson
and screenwriter Garrett Fort
during the script-development stage,
Henigson wrote "I think everyone in the
production should speak perfect English
and we should take away
the jas, the Herrs, the Frauleins
and twists in the language's construction
which give it a Teutonic distinction."
"We're not trying to place the picture
geographically in any particular spot,
and I think that we can attend to this
by taking the Teutonic element out of it."
Garrett Fort replied
"In a story laid in and around Goldstadt,
with names like Frankenstein,
Waldman, Moritz, Fritz, etc,
it seems that a Teutonic element
is inescapable."
"If we lay it elsewhere it will be necessary
to change every name in the cast,
probably even that of Frankenstein, which
certainly has Teutonic connotations."
"This might lead to titles such as
'The Monster', 'Garibaldi',
or 'Love and Murder in Norway', etc."
"I have an idea that there is nothing
offensive about the Teutonic slant."
"And it is a particularly pertinent angle
when we consider that
the Teutonic type of mind is certainly
foremost in the scientific world, etc."
Another scene between
Elizabeth and Henry.
This time Elizabeth's premonition
of danger and death
is about to become a reality.
In the novel, Frankenstein reluctantly
agrees to create a female for the monster,
but he changes his mind and
the outraged monster tells Frankenstein
that "I will be with you
on your wedding night."
After Frankenstein and Elizabeth marry,
the monster keeps his word
and kills the bride.
In Edison's 1910 film version, the monster
returns on Frankenstein's wedding night
and, hearing his bride scream,
Frankenstein interrupts the attack
and the monster flees.
In Peggy Webling's 1927 British play,
the monster falls in love
with Frankenstein's fiancée.
She is captured by him,
but finally escapes.
Lewis Klein, the general manager of
Horace Liveright Theatrical Productions,
the potential producer of the
Webling/Balderston US play version,
added some ingredients of the
bodice-ripping school of sensationalism
to John Balderston's adaptation.
The monster confronts
Frankenstein's bride and seizes her.
In the struggle he tears off her bridal veil
and the top of her wedding gown -
"Which gown", Klein explained,
"is a breakaway affair,
and leaves her as nude
as the censor will allow."
"Then he is about to mount her in a rape."
This production, as we know,
was never presented on the stage.
The staging of this scene
resembles a similar scene
in the 1919 film
The Cabinet of Dr Caligari,
whereby the character
portrayed by Conrad Veidt
has been sent to kill a lovely girl
in her bedroom.
The suspense here is well orchestrated
and both players do not go over the top
in the realisation of the scene.
Although Mae Clarke remembers tea
breaks each mid-afternoon during filming,
she never had an opportunity
to get to know Karloff very well.
"He would arrive at 4am
and spend four hours in make-up."
"He didn't have lunch with us because
it was easier for him, due to the make-up,
to eat alone
in his dressing-room bungalow,
where he could remove
some of his body padding."
"Then a couple of hours would be spent
removing his make-up at the day's end,
and he would require a rubdown
after stomping around all day
with those weights on his shoes."
The woodcutter is carrying his drowned
daughter to the burgomaster's office.
The scripts had Maria
being carried by her mother,
who was also established earlier
at their cottage.
This particularly long tracking shot -
actually two tracking shots -
apparently was difficult for both players.
Marilyn Harris recalled "And did that
ever hurt. It was the longest walk."
"All I can remember is
'Stay limp, don't move,
just let your arms flop,
just let your hands flop."'
"Oh, my back hurt so bad."
Michael Mark, playing the father,
appeared later in Son of Frankenstein,
The Ghost of Frankenstein
and The House of Frankenstein,
with different roles in each.
Going back to the drowning at the lake,
this scene was cut entirely or in part
by many local state and city censors
and in foreign countries
before the film's initial release.
But when the studio applied to
the Production Code Administration
for a reissue seal of approval in 1937,
various cuts were demanded.
This scene was modified in a manner that
paradoxically compounded the problem.
The action played as photographed
up to the point where the monster
had thrown his last daisy into the water.
He watched it, then looked at his empty
hands and held them out toward the child.
The rest of the scene was deleted,
and it stayed deleted for decades
until Universal's restoration.
The motivation to destroy the monster
is gaining momentum.
Maria's father, the townspeople,
the burgomaster,
and certainly Frankenstein, were ready.
Incidentally, has anyone
noticed the disappearance
of the old baron, Henry's father?
He wasn't around before, during and after
the monster was loose in the household,
and he's not around now.
The original plan,
as we know from scripts and memos,
was to keep Victor Moritz on the scene,
quietly longing for Elizabeth,
so he and Elizabeth would be with each
other after the forthcoming tragic events.
Hence the emphasis on
"I leave her in your care."
Obviously, it is clearly understood
that neither Victor nor Elizabeth
are joining the hunting party.
There seems to be no question about
the durability of the Frankenstein theme,
with its innumerable interpretations.
The cosmic theme of the limits of man
and the power of God,
which extends to man emulating God.
The disturbing idea that science could
create life, possibly even eternal life.
The fascination with dolls,
mechanical puppets and robots
that effectively simulate life.
The Faustian concept of the overreacher,
who momentarily commands divine
power, only to be destroyed because of it.
The father creator
who abandons his child.
Frankenstein's crime
was that he abandoned his creature.
The theme of the divided self,
in this instance creator and creature,
that is part of the human psyche
and derives from ancient legend.
The dumb innocent,
craving love and understanding,
but forced to become violent
and exercise hatred
because of the lack of compassion
and the fear of others.
Frustration and overwhelming rejection
were the cause of the monster's brutality.
Frankenstein, then, is a mixture
of fascination and horror,
dream and nightmare.
Mary Shelley succeeded in
creating a tale that would, she said,
"Speak to the mysterious fears
of our nature and awaken thrilling horror."
The enraged, driven villagers,
frequently carrying torches,
became a staple in Universal's cavalcade
of Frankenstein films.
In Bride of Frankenstein, villagers seek
the monster with lanterns and weapons.
In Son of Frankenstein, the villagers
storm Castle Frankenstein's gate.
In The Ghost of Frankenstein,
villagers storm the castle to dynamite it.
In Frankenstein Meets the Wolf Man,
the townspeople are in pursuit
with guns and howling dogs.
In House of Frankenstein,
there is a band of torch-bearing villagers.
In House of Dracula, the mob
chases the murderer through the town,
up the hills and through the cemetery.
The exterior chase scenes were shot
on portions of the Universal back lot,
including Pollard Lake,
and around the nearby hills.
Lifted footage of the search party
from Frankenstein was later inserted
in The Bride of Frankenstein, The
Mummy's Tomb and House of Dracula.
If Frankenstein had been made
just a year or two later,
at this point we would be listening
to rousing music underscoring.
We're no longer on the back lot,
but on one of Universal's sound stages
with plaster rocks and a cyclorama in the
background representing an ominous sky.
A cyclorama, incidentally, that had
some problems, as you will soon notice.
Incidentally, director James Whale
described this chase
as "the pagan sport
of a mountain manhunt".
Note that the wounded man
is character actor Francis Ford,
who earlier had been a Universal
writer, director and leading player.
He was director John Ford's older brother.
During the First World War,
in the British army,
Whale was in
a prisoner-of-war camp in Germany,
where he directed and acted
in plays for his fellow prisoners.
Later he abandoned his job
as a cartoonist for a London newspaper
to become a full-time theatre person -
actor, director, set and costume designer
and stage manager.
According to Whale biographer
James Curtis,
the genesis of the look and interpretation
of Karloff in Frankenstein
goes back to Whale's
highly praised performance
as the demented son of Charles Laughton
in the London stage production
of A Man With Red Hair in 1928.
Following Frankenstein,
Karloff worked with Whale again
in The Old Dark House
and The Bride of Frankenstein.
But after Son of Frankenstein
in 1939 with another director,
he vowed never
to play the monster again,
since he felt that the character
was becoming a clown or merely a prop.
Despite the horror genre
going in and out of fashion,
Karloff continued to make films, work
in television and appear in popular plays,
such as Arsenic and Old Lace in 1941,
and Peter Pan, as Captain Hook, in 1950.
Near the end of his life,
Boris Karloff continued to work
with half a lung,
crippling arthritis and a bad heart.
He died in 1969 of respiratory problems.
Unlike many actors
who played in horror films,
Karloff was always grateful for the
monster characters that built his career.
He once said of Frankenstein's monster
"God bless the old boy."
"Without him,
I would have been nowhere."
Here is the confrontation scene
between creator and creature.
The obligatory scene.
When the Laemmles
lost control of Universal in 1936,
Whale's golden years at the studio
came to an end,
following the release that year
of the extremely popular Show Boat,
Whale's last major success.
A few years later he retired from films
and started painting
in his Pacific Palisades home.
In 1957, his maid discovered Whale's fully
dressed body in the pool out in the back.
There was an ugly gash on Whale's
forehead, and many suspected foul play,
but ultimately it was revealed
that Whale committed suicide.
It wasn't easy for Karloff in take after take
to carry Clive to the windmill
and then up to the second level with all
that heavy paraphernalia that he had on.
And certainly his physical conflicts
were difficult for the same reason.
The exteriors of the windmill,
built on the back lot at Universal,
were a combination of a full-scale lower
structure of 12ft and an upper miniature.
The Williams travelling matte process
was used to effect overlapping elements.
The original plan was
to have the monster seek the mill,
the only refuge it knew
from the time its life began.
This was before the laboratory in the mill
was switched to the old watchtower.
Budgeted at $262,000
and given a 30-day shooting schedule,
Frankenstein had been laid out to film
in continuity for the most part,
starting on August 24th.
The schedule ran over by five days and
shooting was completed on October 3rd.
Final cost: $291,000.
The film was previewed at the Granada
Theatre, Santa Barbara, on October 29th.
When it started playing
in theatres in late 1931,
Frankenstein did sensational business
and garnered generally excellent reviews.
The New York Times called it
"Far and away the best thing of its kind."
The New York American
told how it held its audience
"in hypnotic thrill
through every sequence".
And the World-Telegram
referred to it as "a singularly fine picture".
Several local censor boards ordered cuts
to be made before it was shown,
even though
the Production Code Administration,
the film industry's self-regulatory body,
had passed it.
Czechoslovakia, Italy, Sweden,
Belfast and South Australia
rejected the film outright,
and England made
a considerable number of cuts.
But Frankenstein was breaking
house-attendance records all over the US.
It made the New York Times
ten-best list for the year.
Exploitation gimmicks that go back
to Grand Guignol presentations
in the 1920s and perhaps earlier
were resurrected -
ambulances stationed at the front
of theatres, nurses on duty in the lobby,
free nerve tonic, and so on.
Motion Picture Herald
stated that the film had arrived
"if the psychologists can be believed,
at the familiar psychological moment".
"People like the tragic best at those times
when their own spirits are depressed,
and the economists tell us that even
more than their spirits are at a low ebb."
Motion Picture Herald
stated that the film had arrived
"if the psychologists can be believed,
at the familiar psychological moment".
"People like the tragic best at those times
when their own spirits are depressed,
and the economists tell us that even
more than their spirits are at a low ebb."
The reference to the economists was
referring to 1931-32 being the worst years
of the Great Depression.
In 1937, when Universal
submitted Frankenstein
to the considerably tougher Production
Code Administration for reissue approval,
a number of deletions were ordered.
The official letter to the studio said:
"Remove 'ln the name of God' and
'Now I know what it feels like to be God."'
"Shorten views of Fritz with lighted torch
rousing the fear and fury of the creature."
"Eliminate view of doctor jabbing
hypodermic into back of creature."
"Eliminate scene in which the creature
throws the child into the water."
The ending of the film was changed at
the last moment before its opening dates.
Up to this time it was intended
that both Frankenstein and his creation
would die at the conclusion of the film,
as in the Webling/Balderston play.
Reaction at the previews
caused Universal executives
to decide on a new ending,
which necessitated the filming
of a short epilogue
depicting Henry Frankenstein
recovering from his injuries
and reunited with Elizabeth,
while his father, the baron,
and the maids drink a toast
to "a son of the house of Frankenstein".
The ending was written by Whale
and scenario editor Richard Schayer.
Colin Clive was on his way to Europe,
so another actor was used instead.
And Mae Clarke
could have been substituted,
based upon the staging of the single shot.
Frederick Kerr, as the baron,
reappeared from his prolonged absence
from the footage.
The prologue with Edward Van Sloan
was also a late addition.
The closing music is "Grand
Appassionato" by Giuseppe Becce.
He was a composer of short orchestral
mood pieces for motion pictures.
In fact, he was the innovator of
the library of mood music for orchestra.
And this selection goes back to the '20s.
This is Rudy Behlmer.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/556b5
Help other users to choose the best subtitles