Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
It's Mojo Radio back on the air.
Slammin'Sammy here.
Football time in Texas.
Let's go to the phone.
We got, uh, Butch on the line with us.
Butch, what about it?
We'll have a great year, or what?
How you doin'?
Good, Butch.
Tell me about this season.
We're gonna
have a hell of a season this year.!
Winchell's gonna take us all the way.
- Deep slant tripps stacked right?
- Primary receiver's inside flanker.
- "Z" burst.
- "My linemen are an 80 pass block."
- How deep is your drop?
- Five steps.
Five steps.
Tripps stacked left?
Inside eight-yard curl.
You gonna get a scholarship?
Yes, Mom.
"Z"receiver.
It's Mojo Radio, Slammin'Sammy,
and I've gotJerry on the line with us
from the Sonic down there.
Jerry, there's a lot of talk
that Coach Gaines,
"with that $60,000 a year salary"...
I know where we're goin'with this.
He makes a little bit more
than the principal of the school.
"I read the book"..."Just last week,"
I was readin'this book about Babe Ruth,
and they asked him
ifhe deserved his salary...
"way back in 1910"... "04, whatever it was,"
"and he said, "Hey, you know"...""
They said, " You make more than
the president. "He says," Well, you know,
can the president hit a baseball?"
I'm tellin'you right now, you know,
Coach Gary Gaines, they could give him
$ 100,000 a year,
and if these boys go undefeated,
it's worth every single dollar.
I tell you what, the principal,
uh, of Permian
"don't get 28,000 people"...
I got two
to three seconds of rotation and
my linemen are an 80 pass block.
Wide receiver?
He runs the... burst route.
If he sees cover two, he...
he bends outside, eight to 12 yards.
20 yards, and runs
straight to the sideline.
Are you ready for this, Mike?
- Yo. Ivory!
Ready to work?
'Sup, Boobie? State.
State? State?
State. State.
State.
Where your girlfriend at, Water Bug?
"Well"...
We ain't got a girlfriend yet?
- Come on. Let's go. Snap it up.
- "You wanna know why"
you ain't got a girl yet, Water Bug?
- Why?
- You got the wrong shoes on, man.
You got on white Adidas.
Everybody know the shoe is Nikes.
Nothin' holds a nickel next to Nike.
Ask Ivory. Ask Preacher Man.
- What kind of shoes
on your feet don't matter.
- Come on, Preacher. Bullshit!
- Don't matter at all.
- "You know God made black beautiful."
God made Boobie beautiful,
black and strong.
His mouth keeps gettin'
bigger and bigger and bigger.
And when Boobie knocks some fools out,
Boobie gonna knock 'em out with
black Nikes on his feet. Ain't that right?
I could knock you out
in a pair of flip-flops.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna knock 'em out
with Nikes on my feet,
and I'm gonna smile when I do.
Let's go. Five minutes. Let's go.
Get up. Let's go.
How y'all doin' up there?
Y'all doin' all right?
"45, Boobie"...
That's my nephew out there.
The boy can play some football.
I'm telling you.
I think he'll win
the Heisman Trophy someday.
The Heisman, really?
- Oh, yes sir. You can bet on it.
- "I got it.! I got it.!"
Who's you guys'favorite player?
- Boobie Miles.
He can spin left. He can spin right.
Don't make no difference.
He can block, tackle,
score the touchdown, snap the ball,
hold the snap
and kick the extra point.
Hell, the boy will fill up
the Gatorade cooler, walk the dog,
and paint your back porch.
I'm telling you, that boy
can flat out play football.
Ow! And he can pass!
Should we believe the hype?
What hype?
- The hype about Boobie Miles.
- "No, hype is something"
that's not for real.
"I'm all real."
I'm Chris Comer. I'm a running back.
So that means you're Boobie's backup?
I'm actually Boobie's backup backup.
I'm third string right now.
- "You know which way"
you're supposed to run?
- "Yeah, with strong right"...
I ain't talkin' about the play.
I know what the play was, okay?
Odessa's a small town, and, uh,
if you screw up,
everybody knows about it.
Your dad played at Permian.
What's it like to be the son
of a local legend?
Hold on to the damn ball, Donnie!
Next question.
There it goes.! There it is.!
How are your grades, Boobie?
I get straight A's.
I'm an athlete.
In what subject?
There's only one subject.
It's football.
- Ain't no other subject,
you know?
- Hut!
"Hang on to the ball.! The ball.!"
You sure he's part of
your gene pool, Charlie?
Shit.
Red alert.
Red alert, everybody.
What about the expectations
of coaching a team like this
in a community like this?
Well, I guess there's always
a surprise or two in every community.
Ball. Just concentrate on
hangin' on the ball. Both hands.
Hey, Donnie. Hey.
- Come here. Come here.
What's the problem?
- "Get off the field, Dad."
Why can't you hold on to the football?
What's so goddamn hard
about holdin' on to it?
- I'm sorry.
- All you gotta do is hold on to the
goddamn football, and you can't do it.
Tell me why you can't do it.
Just tell me. That's all I wanna know.
I'll try better next time.
Come on.
Hey!
Charlie.!
Don't you walk away from me.
- Leave him alone.
- "Don't you walk away from me"
when I'm talkin'to you, you hear me?
Tell me why you can't
hold on to the ball.!
Enough.!
Tell me. Answer a question.
Mr. Billingsley.
- It's the first day of practice.
- This is practice. Seriously.
Enough. Charlie!
Embarrassin' me out here.
Jesus Christ.
It's all right, Don.
It's all right.
Don't worry about it. Here we go.
Slot right. 38...
Billingsley, you ain't gotta worry
about holdin' on to the ball, man.
- Why's that?
- 'Cause you ain't gonna get the ball.
Your job is to be blockin' for Boobie.
I don't care if your daddy
is over there cryin'.
- You can...
- You never shut up, do you?
Our team's been playin'with each other
for a long time and, uh,
we got the brotherhood
part of it down pretty much.
People here at Permian are already
predicting a state championship.
Is there any pressure to that
for you guys?
Well, any time they start predictin'
the state championships,
there's always pressure, believe me.
You guys don't have a lot of size.
How can you make up for that?
We're gonna rely on our speed,
discipline.
Come on, Ivory.
You're in the game now.
You're in the game.
Do football players
get special treatment here?
What do you have to do
to be a better football player this year?
Do you enjoy playing football?
You quit reading
your press clippings, all right?
Because you're smaller,
and you're gonna be smaller every week.
- Yo, Boobie Miles!
- It is hard to be humble.
Ain't gonna be no growth spurt
between now and the first game.
Where does all that anger
come from?
- They're gonna underestimate you
every single week.
- We teach you this technique
for a reason.
We do not do this
to make our heads rattle.
You're gonna use your mind.
You're gonna play with your heart.
Come on.!
That's what you're gonna use
to win the state championship.
Get up, Ivory. Get up.
Get up! Get up.
It's a good day, gentlemen.
It's a good day to think
about responsibility.
It's a good day to ask yourself
if on a personal level you're willing
to accept that...
if you're willing to accept
the responsibility that you have...
to protect this team
and this school and this town.
And make no mistake
about it, gentlemen,
we are in the business
of protecting this town.
We're in the business
of winning.
The expectations
couldn't be any higher.
We will win state.
Can you be perfect?
Mojo.!
No, I'm all right.
Come on, Mike. Live a little.
He's not going out, either.
Yeah, he is.
Mike, you're going out tonight.
If I have anything to say about it,
you're gonna get laid too.
Billingsley.! Billingsley.!
"Party at Taylor's house" now, "Billingsley.!"
You better be there. Gonna get wasted.!
Party at Taylor's house.!
Billingsley!
Isn't that guy, like, 35?
Mike. Here's your mom's food.
How much?
No, no. Don't worry about it.
It's on us. It's on us.
How's she doin', by the way?
You never give me free food, David.
- "I just gave you free food."
- Oh yeah. Oh yeah, I forgot about that.
- Say hi to your mom, huh?
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Stay out of jail, Billingsley.
- We're not goin' home, Mike.
- I ain't goin' out drunk foolin'.
How 'bout I bring
your mom some dinner
so you can come out with us?
Because we're gonna get laid,
and we're gonna get drunk, and
we're gonna win state, but not tonight.
All right?
You been blessed, Mike,
'cause we got a runner.
He's gonna make us all look good.
So I'm telling you to lighten up.
All you gotta do is exist in those
two seconds between snap
and you givin' Boobie the ball.
So lighten up, Mike.
Mike.
How you doin'?
Hey, Brian.
How's old Gaines treatin' you?
Got you all perfect?
We gettin' there.
All right.
How's your mama?
Fine, sir.
- All right. You mind if we get a shot
real quick with the kid, little picture?
- Shot?
Yeah, little picture.
Yeah, sure.
Here. All right, sweetie.
Just take a picture.
My baby girl and the next Texas
state championship quarterback, huh?
Where's the damn camera?
Winchell, boy, you remember
every minute of this.
I'm tellin'you right now.
You're 17, but it goes fast.
Don't sleep. Don't waste a second of it.
'Cause before you know it,
it's done.
Nothin' but babies and memories.
You hear me?
Babies and memories.
Smile, sweetheart. Give us a smile.
Say "Mojo." Say "Mojo."
I tell you what, why don't
you hold on to her for a little while?
Babysit her for us for a couple hours.
We're gonna go get a drink.
We'll be back in a little bit.
All right. I'm kiddin' with ya.
Come here. Come here, sweet...
Come here, sweetie.
Let's go back over to Mama.
All right.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hey, hey. Bring it home, huh?
Bring one of these home.
Get you one of these.
Christian, get you one of these.
Boys? Right here.
Come up here a second.
Got some change for you.
Wanna go to that party?
Just for a little bit?
*It's tricky to rock a rhyme
To rock a rhyme that's right on time *
*It's tricky
It's tricky, tricky *
*Tricky, tricky *
*It's tricky to rock a rhyme
To rock a rhyme that's right on time *
*It's tricky *
* T-t-t-tricky, tricky *
*I met this little girlie
"Her hair was"..."*
What I saw was speed out there,
but uh, where's the beef, Coach?
I saw me some small boys.
They're small.
- I think we're gonna be okay.
- On defense?
Yes, ma'am. I firmly believe that.
We got some backs.
We're about, what, 180?
* Tricky, tricky, tricky *
*It's tricky to rock a rhyme
To rock a rhyme that's right on time
It's tricky *
Hi, Mike.
I'm Melissa.
I know who you are.
You do?
Everybody knows
who you are, Melissa.
who you are, Mike.
Is that right?
- Whole lot of... Arab oil embargo.
- " Oh, God."
- Don't talk about that.
- Midland Lee likes to bust it
up the middle, too.
You're right about that.
You know what you should do?
You should play Boobie Miles defense.
Work him both ways.
The problem with that is
I don't want to get him hurt.
We need him to score touchdowns.
Bullshit. That big nigger
ain't gonna break.
You wanna beat Midland Lee,
you play him middle linebacker.
- Break some heads out there.
- Are you ready for Midland Lee, coach?
*I got a letter from the government
The other day
I opened and read it *
This is not about Boobie. This is
about the fact that we're sittin'here
in the stairwell while they're up there.
- I wanna be with a ball carrier.
- Baby, Boobie is...
Don't you "Baby, Boobie" me.
I wanna see somethin'.
Can I get a touchdown?
How 'bout that?
Why don't you have a girlfriend?
I don't know.
Why doesn't he have a girlfriend?
Is that a rule or somethin'?
No, not really.
Well, then,
why don't you have a girlfriend?
Just don't.
Are you gay?
- What?
- Is he gay?
- "I'm not gay."
- Can you prove it?
Coach, here's to the start of
your second season as our head coach.
- We're here,
we believe in you and Sharon.
- Thank you.
To sittin' here in December
as the state champions ofTexas.
- Let's bring 'em hell. Go Mojo!
- Go Mojo!
Bring us some glory, Coach.
- "* That's what I say"
Don't need nothin'but a good time *
- Go! Go! Go!
Why isn't anyone allowed
at your house?
People come over.
When?
Is your mother really crazy?
No.
Are you crazy?
Do I look crazy?
Look like someone who's gonna get
the hell out of Odessa, Texas one day
and never look back.
Seriously works for me.
See ya.
Get in here, boy.
Come on. Get this off.
Ow.
That's good.
Ow!
Take my shoes...
Don't get so prude.
Stop. We're on your couch.
Something for everybody. Oh.
Let's go to your room.
Let's go to your bedroom.
Dad, can you just go
back to bed, please?
Who's this? This Melissa?
Yes.
Maria.
How you doin', Maria?
Damn, girl. You have grown up.
Dad, please.
Can you just go back to bed?
What happened to my lamp?
- "Hey, y'all. What's goin'on?"
- Hey, Flippy.
Hi, Maria.
What happened to my lamp?
I dropped it.
Yeah, you dropped it.
That makes perfect sense, huh?
He dropped it. Can't hold on to
the lamp, can't hold on to the football.
- I can hold on to the football, Dad,
now get the hell out of here!
Little fumble,
can't hold on to the football.
Since when can you hold
on to the football?
I haven't seen it.
Y'all don't do it today?
How about yesterday? You hold on
to the football yesterday? Have you
seen him hold on to the football?
How 'bout tomorrow?
You gonna hold on to it tomorrow?
How 'bout now?
Can you hold on...
Hold on to the football.
Goddamn it, Dad.
- "Dad."
- Maybe this'll help.
What are you doing?
Hold... on... to... the football!
Dad! Goddamn it, Dad!
Knock it off!
"That's enough.!"
I don't think we've felt this kind of
expectation in years.
If Winchell shows up
like we know he can,
even a short passing game
to give Boobie Miles
"a couple of feet of cushion"...
You boys all right?
Yes, sir.
Gonna win state?
Undefeated?
Yes, sir.
Get it done.
Take this opportunity
"to support the Permian Panthers"...
"The Southern California lifestyle
is but one of the bonus features...
"of playing for"...""
What's that word?
Uh, "distinguished."
- Who's that one from, UCLA?
- No, this is USC.
That's UCLA right there.
Hey, Mike. You gonna come visit
my distinguished ass in California?
See if I can put the damn smile
on your face.
You know I'm fittin'
to be rich, right?
I'm thinkin'about hiring,
uh, Eddie Murphy
to lay some ofhis shit on you...
till you crack a damn smile.
No? Well, what about
Richard Pryor?
Bill Cosby?
I know you like Bill Cosby.
Mike Winchell, you got
a natural ability...
for throwing Boobie Miles the ball.
Any every once in a while
you throw a pretty good pass,
so you're going to eat
yourJell-O Pudding Pops.
Wah!
Yo, Mike Winchell. You gonna move
out of Odessa, Texas one day, baby,
and you gonna come visit
Boobie Miles in California,
and you gonna smile,
or I'm gonna stick
about four pudding pops
up your white ass.
- "Now, now"... "Oh, my God.!"
I got Mike Winchell to smile.!
Look at this! Wah!
Did y'all see it? Wah.!
That's probably the only smile
y'all gonna see from Mike
all season.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm distinguished now.
Hey, Boobie.
- What?
- You didn't lift.
Come on, man.
This is God-given.
Only thing I gotta do
is just show up.
Now, people call this monument out here,
the Ratliff Stadium,
the monument to football of Odessa.
They say some of that money
should have gone to the school.
What's your feelings on that, D.U.?
You played ball.
Ain't that stadium
part of the school?
So I say that money did go to the school.
What's everybody whinin'about?
This is football country, folks.
Come on. Get your heads out.
Hi, Don.
Hey, Karen.
- It's you. Do you like it?
Do you like it?
- Think so. What is it?
Rice Krispy.
You like it, right?
Yeah, I love it.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
- "Hey, Gary?"
- Hey, John. How you doin'?
Good. Um, you real busy?
I got a minute or two.
What you got up?
- Well, I got some characters out here.
- Well, who you got with you?
Wilkins.
Well, hey.
Hey, Jim. How you doin'?
- How's that pretty wife of yours?
- She's good.
Ready for Friday night?
Sure hope so.
Seems pretty good.
I feel pretty good about it.
I really do.
" We'rejust, uh"...
Wanted to come by and visit,
maybe talk about defense
a little bit, if you got a second.
You got a second?
We got a dog named Mojo.
We got a cat named Panther.
You got season tickets?
You kiddin'?
We don't miss anything.
- Instead of the cover 2 zone.
- "Get the D-line in as many gaps"
and stack gaps as possible.
Double dent, type of technique.
- " Hey, Boobie."
- Hey.
- How you doin'?
- "All right."
Strong "B"slide force.
"Hell, we can look at"...
- He'll still be a robber...
- Get Ivory out of the board...
- And go!
- Go, go, go, go.
- "Go by the speed and make up"
"for the size differential"...
- What do you think, Coach?
Now, obviously we're not Division I,
but we got a good program.
You play well enough,
we'll find you a spot at Kansas Wesleyan.
- How far is the drive?
- What drive?
To your school. How far is it
from Odessa to your school?
I don't know. 10 or 12 hours.
Are you offering?
Ma'am?
Right now. Are you offering?
If you are, we're in.
Mom.
He'll sign his intent right now.
Well, obviously we're interested,
Miss Winchell, otherwise
we wouldn't be here, Mike.
- But right now, that's all we are, is...
- Interested.
Now, you go get at 'em,
you throw some touchdowns,
you win some football games,
maybe a state championship, huh?
We'll see if we can't find you a home
at Kansas Wesleyan.
Yes, sir.
Do you like playin' football, Mike?
Is it fun for you?
- Lots of fun, sir.
- He loves the game.
That's good. It's important.
It's... legitimate love of the game.
Supposed to be fun,
you know?
Greatest game in the world.
I'm not that good at toastin;
but, uh, I'll give it a try.
Um, fact is I don't know if I've ever
done a toast myself before.
Been involved in a few, but uh...
"Uh, well, here's to Boobie Miles, who"...
"Well, everything"... "everything you get"
this year, you deserve it,
because you... you work hard,
and you... I'm real proud of you.
"And, um, L. V., to you l"... "I can't"
even tell you how proud of you I am,
the way you've raised this kid
"and what you do for him, and uh"...
Here's to a great season,
and uh, God bless us.
- God bless us.
- God bless.
We been thinkin'about this
for four months now.
You seniors have been
thinkin'about it for 17 years.
Well, it's here now.
It's time.
If any of you have any doubt
in your mind,
I don't want you to walk
through that door over there.
You shouldn't have any doubt
in your mind about what
you're supposed to do tonight,
and about how
you're supposed to do it.
So let's take care of it!
*Don't know we can do this
'Cause we always knew this *
*Ha, ha
Yeah, boy *
*Bass
How low can you go *
- "*Death row"
What a brother know *
- Way to go.
- Do you understand?
- Hut!
Boobie Miles.
You can't turn it back
to Boobie Miles!
All Boobie, all the time here.
"A Mojo first down."
Boobie around one more.!
- Yeah! That's my boy!
- "Boobie Miles for 45 yards"...
"Score for Mojo. Touchdown."
Billingsley takes it right.
Boobie. Here we go again.
Into the end zone.
Touchdown, Mojo.
Boobie Miles has it all,
"all in one great package"...
the speed, the size, the athleticism.
Let me tell you, folks, Boobie Miles
is worth the price of admission.
Yeah!
Yeah, all right!
- "Boobie Miles breakin'loose"
one more time.
- Yes, sir!
- Broke the line.
Chavez.!
Chavez is playin'like a man possessed.
Whoo!
- God damn, I'm so proud of ya!
- Calm down, son.
- Chavez will eat you...
Billingsley. Hey, Billingsley.
Whoo!
Go sit...
Go get on the bench.
Get on the bench.
Boy, crazy.
I like enthusiasm, but my goodness.
He's gonna throw it.
"What an arm.! Did you see"...
Boobie Miles, from 35 yards out,
scores a Mojo touchdown.
You're doin' a great job.
Give me a smile. Give me a smile.
Thank you, Coach.
Boobie Miles is about as solid
as you can ask for.
He ain't gonna smile.
He's more internal.
Why not? Why didn't he ever smile?
Mojo.! Mojo.!
Keep watchin'out.
- Let me kick that extra point.
- Not this time. You did enough.
- " Come on."
- Chris Comer! Come in.
Comer! You're in the game.
Come on.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, son. Come here!
Come here! Where you goin'?
- You don't want me to go in, Coach?
- You don't want a helmet?
Where's your helmet?
Go get it!
Yes, sir!
- "You see my helmet, man?"
- Find your helmet, son.
- What you lookin' for, Water Bug?
- Let me get this real quick.
Let me get your helmet, man.
Come on, come on.
My goodness gracious.
Boobie.
Water Bug, you can't come out here
with no helmet, man.
You seen my helmet right here?
I can't believe it.
28 sweep. 28 sweep.
You don't know where your helmet is?
What are you thinkin'?
Where did you put your helmet?
- Right there a second ago.
- Well, it ain't there!
Do you not know that you
play the game with a helmet on?
- "Put your tail end right there.!"
- Hut!
He throws back to Miles.
Miles cuts to his right.
Bailey takes him down.
Was that a knee?
Could have been.
Hold on. Hold on.
Winchell
was still in there. Billingsley was
still in there. Unfortunately...
the running back's been taken down hard
"and it looks like a knee could possibly"...
Just gonna touch the kneecap here.
Does it hurt over here, son?
Get up, Boobie.
Let me take a look at this.
Let me look at it.
It's definitely his A.C.L.
I mean, it's a legitimate tear.
Do you think he tore any cartilage?
Maybe. I could feel the knee catching.
What do you think?
This kid, it's all about
how he responds mentally.
I don't know.
All right, everybody.
Listen up.
He's gonna be fine.
It's not serious. There's no tear.
He'll be back in a week.
That's the good news.
Even better news, y'all played
a great football game tonight.
A real good football game.
I'm real proud of ya.
And Mike...
Where's Mike Winchell?
Mike, I'm proud of you, son.
You showed discipline.
You showed leadership.
You played your butt off, son.
I'm proud of you.
All of you. Proud of all of you.
And, uh, Wilson...
Now that's body tackle.
That's what I been tellin'you about.
Did y'all see him tonight?
Anyway, I'm proud of every one of you.
I'm proud of the coaches, all of y'all,
each and every player.
I want you to go celebrate.
Feel good about yourselves
tonight, okay? Come on!
We only got
a minute and a halfleft in the game,
we're leadin'by a good lead.
He leaves the boy in there like that.
That makes no sense.!
You gotta protect your best asset.!
What's the matter with this man?
He could have ruined
the whole season for us right there.
We were up. We were winnin'big,
and the boy stays in the game.
"Yeah.! What's"... "You don't need any more."
You don't need to accomplish any more.
I think Coach Gaines
"is a stupid f"..."in'idiot."
Hey.
" Well, he sh"... "You know,"
he shouldn't have put him in.
I mean, we had a big lead
and everything.
I don't understand
what that was all about.
We can't do anything without Boobie.
"We had the game won"...
I'm feelin'some damage
on the right side here.
- "Well, can I play on Friday?"
- I think you got a slight tear.
Can he play?
Yeah, can I play?
Can he play football?
Can I?
You need to get up to Midland,
get an M.R.I.
Can a M.R.I. fix your knee?
Is he the one player
you can't do without?
Well, l... I never looked at it
that way. A football team is not
about one player or two players.
A football team is about the team.
This is a unit, and that's
the way we have to play.
"Uh, it's gonna be a"...
It's gonna be a challenge.
You are makin'
some bad decisions!
You're playin'like the village idiot.
You want people to think you're
the village idiot? Is that what you want?
The Eagles take down
the Panthers, 49-6,
and for Coach Gary Gaines,
it's gotta be back to the drawing board.
That's gonna be the word
around town all week.
Coach Gaines, what are you gonna do?
The loss of Boobie Miles can not
result in the loss of this season.
Hell of a game.
Gimme the keys.
Way to take care ofbusiness.
Gimme the keys, Dad.
We, uh... We just need
a few more days, Coach,
and we be back.
You go into Midland,
get that M.R.I.?
I don't need nothin'in Midland.
Those rich hillbillies ain't never seen
nothin'as pretty as Boobie Miles.
Them M.R.I. machines
wouldn't know what to do with it.
He gonna be just fine, Coach Gaines.
Uh, we gonna go back to the clinic
but they already said ain't no tears.
No tears?
Ain't no tear.
Is that what they said?
Yes, sir. Uh, we gonna go back
for some double confirmation,
but when it come time
to play Midland Lee,
we be good to go, Coach.
That's good, then.
He designed his offense
around one player.
We're dead.
We're not dead.
- We just need to start
throwin' the football.
- We're dead.
Dead. Pull it.
We gotta lighten up. We're 17.
Do you feel 17?
I don't feel 17. Pull it.
We will win state.
Chavo, you're like a human pinata.
You get your ass all beat on
more than anybody I know,
and you just sit there and spit out candy.
That's 'cause he's out ofhere.
He's got the grades.
No matter what, if we win or lose,
he knows he's gettin' out.
- "He's like the one foot"
out the door man.
- "It's true, Chavo."
You're gonna be
drinkin'martinis,
Gimme the gun.
eatin'lamb chops,
gettin'manicures.
You're just jealous.
Removin' your freakin' shoes.
What's it like being the quarterback?
I mean, this is a big responsibility
for a 17-year-old kid.
No.! That is not acceptable.!
Uh... It's sort of... I mean, uh...
It's not too bad. I know, uh...
- " You are playin'like a fool.!"
- " Do you think"
you can handle it?
If you got a receiver
gettin'jammed inside,
what will you do with your brain?
Yeah, I hope so.
What will your brain do?
- You'll throw outside!
- Throw it outside.
You'll throw outside!
Now you think you can do that?
- Yes, sir.
- Well, show me.
Show me!
Hey.
Yeah, well, I thought
maybe if you came home
it would help out a little bit.
She's sick.
She's not doin' so good.
It's just kinda hard.
Football's startin' and this is a lot.
Well, I thought if maybe you could
come home, it'd help out a little bit,
'cause she's your mother, too.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Can you get the job done, Mike?
We're pretty small.
I didn't ask you
if you think we're small.
I asked you if you think
we can get the job done.
Think so.
Well, you're gonna have to do better
than "I think so."Is that clear?
It's clear.
Now I'm gonna assume
that by now you've learned
that the world's not fair...
and sometimes
you get the short end.
That's all you get.
And if you don't do
something personally to fix it,
that's all you're ever gonna get.
Yes, sir.
Mike.
Do you wanna play college ball?
Do you wanna get out of this town?
Think so.
Well, why aren't you
doin' something about it?
My mind's not right.
One of these days you're gonna
have to get out of this house.
You're gonna have to leave her.
Yes, sir.
You gotta accept the fact that
people have to take care of themselves,
and that includes you.
You understand that?
Yes, sir.
Okay. The truth is,
against some
pretty overwhelming odds,
if... if you do decide to accept that...
Look at me, Mike.
If you decide to accept that,
you're gonna seriously fly, son.
Same song, different
verse. Middle of the second quarter,
Cooper has a 14-nothing lead.
Things are really going south
in a hurry.
But when you got an offense play
built around one player, that's great,
as long as the player's there.
When he gets hurt,
in this case like Boobie Miles did,
what do you do?
I don't know, but Gaines
better come up with a plan quick...
'cause the unthinkable's
gonna happen.
The Panthers are gonna lose
two consecutive district games.
Wilson gets the hand-off and he's
got room to run on the left-hand side.
Across the line. Clotheslined.!
- "And he's down.!"
- Gimme a running back!
We got a running back?
Permian has lost Boobie Miles,
now Wilson,
Comer! Comer!
Yeah, come on!
leaving him with third-string
running back Chris Comer.
- Hut!
- "Comer around the right side,"
has some room to run and...
runs out ofbounds.
What is that?
- I didn't have a block.
- You are so dumb! Are you scared?
I didn't have no block.
Football is a contact sport!
I think he's a sophomore.
May be lookin'for
a badminton scholarship or something.
That's not gonna cut it.
"Blue 40.! Hut.!"
The snap. Lookin'to throw.
Here comes the rush.
Winchell avoids the rush,
throws the ball,
Comer turns from blocker to receiver.
Has the ball, crosses the 20-yard line,
crosses the 30.
Comer to the 40.! Comer to the 50.!
- "Where did this speed come from?"
- Go, go, go!
- "Who was that?"
- It was Comer.
- Our Comer?
- It was Comer. It was Comer!
Comer has a Mojo touchdown.!
Chris Comer with his first varsity T.D.
Not letting go of that ball.
Gimme the ball.
- "85 yards, the second-longest"
power play in Permian history.
- Gimme the ball. Gimme the ball!
Interception, Brian Chavez.!
Abilene Cooper back to punt.
It's blocked.!
Touchdown, Permian.!
- "That's a Mojo touchdown."
- Jesus!
- "Billingsley up the middle,"
picks up a great block from Comer.
- Run, Donnie!
Forearm shove behind him,
in for the Mojo touchdown.
There's your old school football.
* Oh yeah *
* Got my Mojo working, baby *
Where did this guy come from?
Chris Comer afforded
a couple of fantastic runs
and one fantastic pass reception,
leading Mojo from a 14-nothing deficit.
Hello?
I'm feelin'great. How are you?
I feel much better than I did
before the hit.
This team has a swagger. They're
walkin'tall. They're playin'tough.
I love these kids.
I love the way Winchell's playin;
Real good. They came
"together after Boobie went out"...
He's got him.
Touchdown in the corner.!
You know,
we just have to dig deep...
Comer's amazing. You know,
he's stepping in just nicely.
My concern is that he doesn't
have the experience in the long run.
If they can just stay strong,
not get overconfident,
and take out Midland Lee
I think we're goin; man.
I think we're gonna go all the way,
but I'm a little worried.
Oh no, sir.
It's just a small sprain.
It was just, uh, a precaution.
We're on a roll.
Don't get started
on the celebration dance.
We got Midland comin'up.
Midland Lee is the real deal.
You don't need to be slackin'right now.
You gotta be playin'and practicin;
Permian zips past
North Shore Galena 17-3.
Come on. We're five and one.
The team is winning now.
They all win, but who we playin'?
Come on. Mediocre teams.
Two losses could shut the door
on the Permian Panthers.
Let's not start tootin'the horns
just yet, you know what I mean?
You lose two division games
in this football climate,
and you're done, Sammy. You're done.
Midland.
Boobie.
This the best damn hospital
in Texas.
The very best.
My son, Andrew, played for Midland,
and ended up back East at Penn.
Oh, he playin' with,
uh, Joe Paterno.
University of Pennsylvania.
Uh, premed.
Oh.
Just let it relax.
You have any pain?
Not at all.
Does this hurt?
Nope.
None of that hurts?
Okay. Go ahead and sit up and
just let your legs hang over the side.
In fact, why don't you
go ahead and get dressed
and let me look at the scan.
l-I'm sorry.
You'reJames' dad?
No, I'm his uncle.
"Come over and let me"...
let me look at the scan with you.
Uh, this is the scan
wejust did today ofhis knee...
and this is looking right
through the middle of the knee.
What we're looking at
right through here is... is the A.C.L.,
and what this shows is that
he's had a fairly significant,
fairly serious injury.
James, let me show you.
Right through here
is where the injury is,
and it looks like you've had
a pretty serious injury
to that part of your knee.
Significant enough that...
that I have concerns about
what you can do from here on.
So when can I suit up?
Well, let me just say with how
your knee felt when I examined it
and what I see on the scan...
"With"... "with the"...
"the things that you do well"...
The reason that you're great
is that you can run and cut
and hammer people...
and you don't hesitate
because you've got a solid knee.
When you don't have this ligament,
you can't do that,
so it's really out of the question.
What? No, no, no. That's...
That's not what Dr. Spencer said.
He said three weeks.
Three weeks is up,
and I'm ready to play.
I understand. I understand,
but again, when l...
Based on what I see
when I feel your knee, examine
your knee... What I see here...
You... You really can't play
with this kind of knee.
What are you talkin'
about, I can't play?
I'm gonna play.
I'm ready to play.
My team needs me.
Listen to me.
I am listenin' to you.
"l- I want"...
I want what's best for you.
You and I
are on the same page...
We ain't on the same page.!
How you gonna want
what's best for me?
Hold on. Hold on.
How you gonna want
what's best for me?
You from Midland, right?
You from Midland? Huh?
This is bull, man.
You just jealous
'cause you from Midland.
What I recommend...
You jealous 'cause you from Midland.
Who paying you?
- Who paying you?
- Come on, Boobie. That's okay.
You tryin' to take
my football career!
You tryin'to take
my football career.!
Boobie, let's get out ofhere.
Tryin'to take my football career.!
Whatever you're sayin' to me,
listen to me.
Come on!
Pig!
Here back on Mojo Radio,
it's Slammin'Sammy Stands.
I knew tonight's game was gonna
be a big game, but itjust got bigger.
Earlier today, Cooper beat Woodland,
which means that if Permian wins tonight,
they're in the play-offs.
"If they" lose", though, they fall back"
into a three-way tie for first place,
and that means the tie-breaker
is a coin toss.
So what'd the doctor say?
'Cause, see, if you go out there
before your knee's ready...
Coach, my knee's fine.
You okay with this, L.V.?
Yeah, I'm good with it.
Hundred percent.
Go get dressed.
The most storied rivalry
in the state of Texas...
is Permian hosting
the Midland Lee Rebels
at Ratliff Stadium.
Tonight one of these teams
could take a step toward the play-offs.
Permian has one district loss,
both Cooper and Midland Lee have two.
There's no doubt about that.
A win tonight puts
Permian in the play-offs,
no coin flip needed,
plus it'll send the Lee Rebels
home for the season.
Well, what
do you know, folks. Look at this
coming out of the locker room.
Number 45 has emerged
from the locker room.
Boobie doesn't look like
he's limping at all.
He looks good to me.
He looks like he's ready to go.
Now the question is, decoy or player?
He ain't gonna play.
I don't think so either.
From what I know
about Coach Gary Gaines, nobody
holds his cards closer than Gary does.
- Come on, guys. Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
- "Hut.!"
Winchell pitches to Comer.
Flipped on his head.!
Winchell, pressured by Olivera,
"swings a pass out to Billingsley"...
Picked off!
It's Dominguez.
Dominguez will take it in
from 25 yards away.
And Lee brings home points.
Hang on to the ball, son!
Don't worry about it.
Shake it off. Shake it off.
Don't worry about it, Coach.
Let me spin. Let me spin, Coach.
Y'all wanna win, put Boobie in.
Set. Hut.! Hut.!
- " Winchell"
will swing it out to Billingsley.
- Come on, Donnie.
And the ball is tripped
by Dominguez.
- "Kevin Lane, and a blatant"
body slam by Billingsley.
- Donnie! Donnie!
What's up?
My goodness. Son, is there
something wrong with you?
Are you mentally okay?
What are you
puttin' your helmet on for?
Take your helmet off, son.
You're gonna sit on the bench
for a little while.
You don't need that helmet.
Third down, with less than
two minutes to play in the half.
Strandler over the left side,
uncontested. 32 yards down to T.D.
Permian came in
with a four-game win streak
but they haven't been tested all year.
Coach Gaines is gonna have to find
a way to get his offense on track...
or start feeling his season
slipping through his fingers.
- "Do you think you're playin'football?"
Do you think you're playin'football?
You are showing me nothing.!
Do you understand me?
Do you think you got it made?
Because if that's what you think,
you're gonna find out what
it feels like to sit on your asses...
and watch Midland Lee
take your season!
No offense tonight for Mojo, and still
no sign ofJames "Boobie"Miles.
Y'all wanna win? Put Boobie in.
I'm about to spin.
Come on, Coach. Come on, Coach.
Let me get this for you.
Under five minutes to play
and Lee still leads 14-7.
Weak defense, weak offense
and no Boobie. If you're
Coach Gaines, what do you do?
Right now Mike Winchell
can't get this offense going,
and the Midland coach
has seen Boobie on the sidelines.
If you don't put him in,
he knows you're bluffing.
I'd put him in.
All right. Move out!
Come on!
Boobie! You're in.
Let's go! Let's go!
What you want, yo?
Well, we apparently are all
gonna get what we wished for,
because here comes Boobie Miles,
and this is certainly
what the fans came to see.
That's number 45
back in the Permian backfield.
Back slam, 37 stretch...
Break!
Now Boobie the senior,
Number 45, lining up behind
quarterback Mike Winchell,
and offensive line is rarin'to go
with room to run.
Three, 12, hut.!
Miles going left.
Hesitates just a bit.
Get off! Get off!
- Let's go with 60-Cheetah.
- 60-Cheetah!
Let's go! Let's go!
They're gonna cheat up close
to the line again and see if they're
gonna run Boobie one more time.
He will go to the right.
There is a hole.
He gets a block.
The Dominguez brothers take him down.
He spins and he's down.
Take it easy. Stay down.
Don't touch it.
Try to relax.
Let me take a look at it.
I'm gonna get up on my own.
I can get up on my own.
Folks, the utterjoy of watching
Boobie Miles trot back on to the field...
has been replaced by the sheer misery
of watching him being carried off of it.
We unfortunately may have seen
the last of Boobie Miles
in the black and white of Permian.
Let me see.
He's done.
We're gonna go jet fire, Coach.
Well, you better go somethin'!
One minute 35 seconds
left to play in this one.
Panthers move immediately
to the hurry-up offense.
Boobie
no longer a factor. Comer, following
the tackle, will dig up near midfield.
The clock now inside of 1:20.
It'll be second down, Permian.
Lee clinging to that seven-point lead
and time becomes a factor.
- 60 Cheetah.
- 60 Cheetah! 60 Cheetah! Hut!
Again, Winchell to Payne,
beating Preston.
Only 40 seconds left.
Mike Winchell trying to keep
Permian's play-offhopes alive.
- "Completes the pass."
- He's got it. He's got it.
Winchell was drilled,
but he seems to be okay.
- Back it off!
- "Winchell, past time, he's lookin;"
Again, Winchell to Payne.
The clock continues to run.
- "25 seconds left."
- Go, go!
Let's go! We got four up!
Hold it.! Hut.!
Mike Winchell trying to keep
the play-offhopes alive. Complete.!
We gotta go with...
This is for the ball game.
The clock is still moving.
Come on, front line!
- "Mike Winchell will go for the shotgun,"
steps back and he drops the ball.!
- Pick it up! Pick it up!
Picks it up, steps into the pocket,
looking for Allen Wyles, he's open.
Here's the pass, and it's... too tall.!
Midland Lee wins the ball game.
It's all right.
No, man.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Thanks for nothing, Permian.
Go home, cowards.
I don't understand
what's gonna happen
"at this point. How do we"...
Another loss, and
that's thrown us into a three-way tie.
They're going to have a coin toss.
You gonna be all right?
I'm okay.
You're serious?
That's right. We're gonna get the three
coaches, they're all gonna toss a coin.
I love you.
What the hell kind of way
is that to make a decision?
When you assemble
the kind of talent that we have here,
and then you just
throw it away like that.
It started with him playin'Boobie
when we had a big lead.
"And now"... "This is a once in a lifetime"
"thing to be able to see these people"...
I mean, we could have
been in the history books.
"And now? Ain't no way."
I mean, that's it.
What about Winchell's play tonight?
"Well, what do" you "think?"
"And that Billingsley couldn't hold on"...
They all suck.!
And I think it
just goes to the coachin;
That's what it is.
You know what else it is, too?
They been doin'too much
learnin'in the schools.
My daddy used to take a bullwhip,
and he'd cut it up...
And he'd tie 13 knots in it.
Then he'd beat me
and beat me in my gut...
till I got a sick feeling in my stomach.
Well,
that's how I feel...
when I watch "you..."
play... football.
Sick at my stomach.
Oh, I need some fresh air!
- " Aah.!"
- "What the hell are you doing?"
Get this sickness
out of my stomach.
- Yeah.
- Goddamn it, Dad.
You were sent down here
to learn how to play football.
And you haven't.
You have not!
And I gotta take that
as a personal... failure!
Nobody in Mojo football
wants to win in a coin toss.
But that's the way
it is. That's the way
the tiebreaker is.
Well, they oughta
change that.
They ought to change
"coaches"... "Make a lot"
of changes in executing.
I was supposed to
make a man outta you.
Shit.
You know what that is?
Do you know what that is?
That's a state championship.
I won a state championship.
Just calm down, Dad.
Can you touch that?
Can you... touch... that?
Can you... touch... that!
Hell with it.
What the hell are you doing?
You drunk bastard!
You ever feel cursed, Coach?
Like, no matter what,
inside your heart you feel
that you're gonna lose.
Like something's
hanging over you,
following you like a witch
"or a demon thatjust"...
What is wrong with you?
Why you gotta be
so messed up?
You can't win.
I feel like that all the time.
Even when things
are going good.
When we're winnin',
it's there.
And when we're losin',
What is wrong with you?
It took me a long time
to realize that, uh,
there ain't much difference
between winnin' and losin',
except for how
the outside world treats you.
But inside you,
it's about all the same.
It really is.
Fact of the matter is,
I believe that, uh,
our only curses are the ones
that are self-imposed.
You know what I'm sayin'?
We, all of us,
dig our own holes.
God, Dad.
*Breaks somebody's back **
What is wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is truly unbelievable.
A three-way tie for first place.
So, in less than an hour,
this truck stop,
which we're not allowed
to reveal the identity of,
will serve as host for a coin toss...
that will send two of these teams
to the state play-offs...
and one of them home
empty-handed.
Okay, Skip. We're on
in three, two, one.
Folks, we're here with
the three winning coaches.
Now, we've all agreed on
the rules. Two out of three
here, odd man out.
If you got one tails, they're out.
If you got one heads, they're out.
It's a tough way after a great
season for these coaches, but
this is the way it's gonna be.
When I give the word,
we're gonna toss our coins.
And then the district's gonna
have its two representatives.
Let's see the coins, guys.
All right, uh,
Coach Doug McCutcheon
"from Abilene Cooper's got"...
What is it, Coach?
A 1922 silver dollar.
'22 silver dollar, all right.
Coach Gary Gaines
from Permian, you got a...
'69 nickel.
And from Midland Lee,
"Coach Earl Miller's got a"... "Well,"
that's just your basic U.S. quarter.
Okay. Coaches ready?
One.
Ain't no curses.
Two.
Three. Toss 'em.
"Coins are down."
This one looks like it's heads.
Okay, that's heads
for Abilene Cooper.
That's mine.
It's heads.
Okay. Midland Lee
is also heads.
Hey, we got a third one
over here, Skip.
Coach, that's you.
- Come on, Gaines.
- Come on.
Don't touch that.
Just leave it alone.
- Well, that's heads.
- Yup. That's heads too.
Permian is also heads. Man.
- Yeah.
- "Well, that figures."
The way you guys'teams
played each other this year,
it'd take more than one toss, so...
Hang on a second.
You know, this coin's pretty worn.
Does this look like heads
to you, Doug?
I can't tell the difference.
It might be tails.
Folks, there might be
some controversy here
regarding Cooper's coin.
It's tails.
So, the good news is that life
continues for both Midland Lee
and Permian high schools.
At least for another
couple of weeks.
That's the good news.
The not-so-good news is
that it looks like all roads are
eventually leading to Dallas Carter.
And what a monster of a team
Dallas Carter is.
This Dallas Carter team
appears to be completely
unstoppable.
I mean, the rumor is they've got
nine players that have already signed
Division I letters of intent.
Damn, them boys big.
They are a very, very good
football team, people.
I'll get that car fixed today.
Yeah.
I don't want this to sound
like an apology,
but, uh, I didn't mean
"half the things I said la"...
I know.
You just...
You ain't gettin' it.
You don't understand.
This is the only thing
you're ever gonna have.
Forever,
it carries you forever.
It's an ugly fact of life.
Donnie, hell.
It's the "only" fact of life.
You got one year,
one stinkin'year to make
yourself some memories, son.
That's all.
It's gone after that.
And I'll be damned
if you're not gonna miss it.
No guts.
What's up, Water Bug?
What's up, Boobie?
Water Bug!
Play-offs belong to you, baby.
I'll make you proud.
What you all lookin' at?
Play your ass off!
Win state.
Be perfect, all that shit.
This is a gift for you.
It's gonna be worth
a lot of money.
I bet it will.
You be perfect,
Preacher Man.
What's up?
Now what we gonna do?
I can't do nothin' else
but play football.
Hey, hey.
Don't worry about that.
Don't worry about it?
I can't be doin' nothin' else.
You'll be all right, son.
I can't do nothin' else
but play football.
Why? We practiced
and we practiced.
It'll be okay.
You told me we were
gonna go to the pros.
What the hell am I gonna do
without my knee?
You'll find somebody else.
Don't worry about it, son.
No! I wanted to buy you a house!
They won't
let me play, though.!
It's play-off time in Texas.!
And who cares if Permian
snuck in on a coin toss?
You know
there's been a lot of expectations
for this Permian football team.
"And you" gotta "love"
this play-off atmosphere.!
They call this
the thinning of the herd,
the survival of the fittest.
Win, you go home.
Lose, you play basketball.
Quarterback Mike Winchell.
Runs back, pulls right, throws long.
- "Caught.! Touchdown.!"
- Whoo!
The Panthers defeated Dallas Jesuit
to advance to round 16.
They're goin'to the 20,
to the ten, to the five.!
It's Comer, folks,
into the end zone for
another Permian touchdown.!
Chris Comer with another
sensational performance.!
Permian cruises past San Angelo
"and into the quarter"...
Permian was afraid of that.
"Dallas Carter"...
Brian Chavez,
"a great reading player"...
Touchdown.!
Permian defeats Nimitz
48-7.!
Moving into the semi-finals
of the Texas 5-Aplay-offs.
Advancing to the state finals.
Mike Winchell drops back,
throws a 50-yard bomb.!
It's gonna be caught by Parker.!
It's going out ofbounds.
"What a good team"...
And that's it. Permian's
gonna battle Dallas Carter...
for the Texas Class 5-A
State Championship.!
What would it take for you
to come up to Texas Stadium?
How about if y'all come out here?
Where?
Over at Ratliff Stadium?
Yeah.
I still think there'd be
a problem with our fans
sittin' with your fans.
I don't see any problems.
We can bring in
extra police to handle
the crowd-control issues.
Mr. McClary, perhaps
you're not aware, but we
have an all-black community.
And frankly,
between our communities,
there are some issues.
Wait a minute. What issues
are we talkin' about?
You know, I'm not gonna
get into it at this table.
It's just different.
How about if we went
with a neutral site?
Say College Station,
or San Anton;
Somewhere like that?
Or, you know
what we could do,
is the Astrodome.
Astrodome.
I got no problem
with that.
Good.
Let's discuss officials.
I think the simplest thing to do
is get a zebra crew...
outta some neutral place
like San Antonio, or somethin'.
Now are these zebras
gonna be white or black?
Well, as far as I know,
"zebras are white" and "black."
What are we talkin' about here?
How many black stripes
these zebras got?
I believe a zebra's got about
the same amount ofblack ones
as he does white ones.
How many black stripes
you "think a zebra's got?"
It makes sense to hire a crew
as-is. That's how we always do it.
- Don't make sense to me.
- It makes sense to me.
- Not me.
- "Well, not a whole lot"
does make sense to you.
Yeah, there's a lot
that makes sense to me.
So you think having an all-black
officiating crew is gonna
somehow help you win the game?
Watch your mouth.
Hey, Coach.
How you doin'?
Hey.
Ben, how you doin'?
All right, Coach. You?
Oh, pretty good.
Hi, Sharon.
How you doin'?
- We're just out gettin'
flowers for the ladies.
- Secretaries Week.
Oh, is that right? I'll be dogged.
Well, see, I don't have a secretary.
So I don't have to worry.
You win state, Coach,
we'll get you two secretaries.
Everything all right?
Well, yeah.
Everybody's gonna be just fine.
Everything's all right, as long
as we get out there and get
what we need to get done...
and, uh, you know,
win state.
Boy, I sure hope so.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, I want it bad
as y'all do, believe me.
Yes, sir.
'Course, you know, Dallas Carter.
That's a... That's a tough team.
Real tough team.
Yeah? Well.
We're a pretty tough
team too, Coach.
Yeah, that's true.
So, uh, beat 'em.
Or what?
Or...
You know, that'd be a real
bad deal for you, Gary, so...
All right? Let's just
get out there and get it done.
Get that state championship.
Well, I sure appreciate your support.
We believe in you.
I'm glad you do.
We're behind you, Coach.
See you, Sharon.
Well, "that" was subtle.
Yup.
Are we gonna move again?
No, baby.
It's possible.
No.
What do you think about Alaska?
What about Alaska?
Well, you know,
I bet that they are
not nearly as serious about
their football in Alaska.
I think that's a real nice idea.
We should go to Alaska.
"Stay there for a couple years"..."20."
Okay.
Just somethin'
to think about, baby.
Mm-hmm.
I think it'd be really nice.
Build us a nice little igloo.
Baby, these boys are big.
Yeah, they are.
Sure are.
You get any sleep last night?
Oh, yes, sir. I did. I did.
Good. We got a six hour ride,
so you can get you some more.
All right, Coach.
Coach.
You got room for one more?
Absolutely. Hop on.
Mojo has come to Houston.
This is the Astrodome, the eighth
wonder of the world, and today...
it's gonna be Odessa Permian
versus Dallas Carter.
This is a moment these kids have
been looking for their whole life.
They started playing as
eight year olds in the Pop Warner
fields of Odessa, or in Dallas.
They've dreamed of
the state championship
laying in bed late at night,
dreaming of their chance to bring
home the title, for their town,
for their team, for their school.
Folks, you better lock the doors,
turn up the radios, strap yourself in.
We've got east Texas
versus west Texas.
We've got Texas high school football
at its finest.
No doubt. This crowd is jacked.!
This is gonna be an all-out war.!
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen...
Welcome, Dallas Carter fans.
Permian will be
the home team in white.
Carter will be the visiting team in red.
"To the 1988"...
Come on, fellas. Let's shake hands.
Have a good ball game.
- "Texas 5-A"...
- I'm gonna ring your bell
all day long, Mexican.
Football championship.
Let's not fumble.
You too, Goldilocks.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Let's play football!
All right, Dallas
kicking off to Permian.
We're underway
in the state championship.
Harold Jones kickoff
carries eight yards.
Comer should down it there.
Wait.! He's gonna bring it out.!
No.! What are you doing?
Howser makes the tackle
on the three-yard line.
And now Chavez
is very slow to get up as
he was just blasted to the turf.
- Mike I want you to be patient
in there, all right? Keep your cool.
- Yes, sir.
Be a leader. Okay?
Yes, sir.
The run's two-seven-seven dolphin.
Let's go!
Saturday is finally here.
The Texas Bowl is underway.!
Winchell now first and ten
for Permian inside their five-yard line.
Winchell, under center will back up.
Here comes Stuber.!
Dad gum it!
Andjust like that, Stuber
has given Carter a 2-nothing lead.
Which game are we in?
And Whitaker
will find Grande and pass
as Chavez is leveled.
And Grande will take this one
to the half from more than
50 yards away in play.
There's not a Panther
within ten yards ofhim. That's
a Carter Cowboy touchdown.
Carter will go for two.
They will not kick.
No surprise. This team has not kicked
an extra point or a field goal all year.
Whitaker now will make his play. Going
left will get the two-point conversion.
Cowboys, ten.
Permian, nothing.
What's it like out there, Ivory?
They're big.
They're fast.
Fun ride, huh, big boy?
They're dirty.
Ball's gone. Ball's gone!
He's holding me, Ref!
- Plus, they fast.
- Yeah, you said that already.
Hut!
Do not fumble against a team...
Two runs to deep turn!
Keep your heads together!
Help me out!
45-2 split!
It's gonna be Whitaker to Cane
from 26 yards away.
He levels Chavez.!
Oh, and another
Carter Cowboy touchdown.
Go, Cowboys.!
Yeah!
Whoo!
All day long, baby.
All day long.
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
You're gonna have to wake up.
You understand me?
Yes, sir.
Are you gonna let
the offense do everything,
or are you gonna help us out some?
- I'm gonna help us.
- You gonna help us out some? Okay.
You gonna have to keep them out of
the end zone 'cause if they score more
than we do, we lose the game, 'kay?
Right.
All right? So "wake up.!"
It's been all Carter here
in the first quarter.
Carter over 161 yards already,
and Panthers minus 21.
"Winchell is trying"...
Comer stopped at the line again.!
Great grandma's drawers!
I can't believe that!
Winchell's downed again.!
Right now I don't know if we need to
worry so much about the scores,
just whether or not we'll be able
to take all these boys home.
"Permian's offensive line is being"...
What in the world are you doing?
Did you see that?
Back up, Coach.
He almost killed him!
Clay, this game is quickly
spiraling out of control.
At some point you worry
about the safety of the kids.
Tell you what. The Panthers came
into this ball game really fired up.
Right now they've got the wind
just knocked out of'em.
You've got to get your head in the game.
Are you in the game?
- Yes, sir.
- You have to wake up out there!
Yes, sir!
Five minutes left to play in
a half that's been all Carter.
They lead 18-nothing.
Third and one on the Permian 40.
Come on, Preacher!
Whitaker with a pro set in shotgun.
Looking once again to throw the ball.
Gotta come off it.
Let's go!
McCleery's comin'on the zone blitz.
Robert Whitaker will look to throw.
Looking right. Ball is in the air.
"And it's picked offby"...
And I'm pretty sure
the Preacher Man is
headed for the promised land.
He may take this one all the way.!
"He clears"...
Yeah!
Finally a spark oflife
in the form of Ivory Christian.!
Whitaker has taken him down.!
Inside the Mojo's 5.!
We've got plenty of time
to get in this game.
Y'all need to wake up out there
and play football, okay?
You need to find each other.
'Cause you need each other
right now, so find each other.
Go field goal. Let's get on the board.
Elephant-37. Count it on one. Ready.
Break!
Jump on the ball!
Left to Winchell,
drops back, rolls right.
He's gonna run it inside the five.!
Winchell throws this play
towards the end zone.
Anthony has him,
but Mike Winchell...
will stretch himself into the end zone
for the Mojo touchdown.!
- Winchell strives for the goal line.
Holds the ball out over the plane.
- Yes!
He didn't break the plane!
Coach, we've got him...
Hey, Ref! Did you see that?
What? There's no way he got in.
He got in.
How you gonna...
Coach James!
Winchell's without a helmet.!
Kicked in his face.!
There's not a flag
anywhere on the field!
How can you miss that, Ref?
Time has run out in the first half.
Coach Gary Gaines and his Mojo Cats
trail Carter by 26-7.
- What in the hell happened on that...
- That's right, Green. You understand that?
Forty yards? Hell no!
"You guys are" not "doin'"
any pass blockin;
You're just steppin' aside
and lettin' 'em walk in...
Pop, pop, pop!
That's what I want!
All of you around that ball!
To go for two and get it every
single time? That is ridiculous.
Do you realize they have not
even kicked a field goal yet?
Just relax.
We not tryin' to coach y'all now.
Coach done gave y'all
all these adjustments, okay?
If you do everything the coach
told you to do...
Two-point conversions,
I want those gone.
Here is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna use our speed.
"We're gonna run Texas power"...
What's wrong with y'all?
Y'all are playin' like some little girls!
Y'all act like you never
played football before!
These guys are nothin'!
- You hear me?
- They bleed just like we do.
Yes, sir!
- And sweat just like we do.
- Do you hear me?
- They went through two-a-days.
- We went through two-a-days
in 110 degree heat!
- Yes, sir!
I want you to hit everything
that move! If the ref gets
in your way, you hit him!
- Okay, then. Let's play!
- They're cheatin' us too!
They're against us too.
This is our team. This is us!
Let's go right now!
Let's get it off now and let's go!
Permian is gonna have to step up here
and establish some offensive confidence.
Let's go.
Well, it's real simple.
You got two more quarters
and that's it.
Now most of you have been
playing this game for ten years.
You got two more quarters and
after that most of you will never play
this game again as long as you live.
You all have known me
for a while...
and for a long time now, you've been
hearing me talk about being perfect.
Well, I want you
to understand somethin'.
To me, being perfect...
is not about that
scoreboard out there.
It's not about winning.
It's about you and your
relationship to yourself and
your family and your friends.
Bein'perfect...
is about being able to look
your friends in the eye...
and "know" that you
didn't let them down.
Because you told 'em the truth.
And that truth is, is that you did
everything that you could.
There wasn't one more thing
that you could've done.
Can you live in that moment...
as best you can with clear eyes...
and love in your heart?
With joy in your heart?
If you can do that, gentlemen,
then you're perfect.
I want you to take a moment...
and I want you to look
each other in the eyes.
I want you to put each other
in your hearts forever.
Because forever's about to happen
here in just a few minutes.
I want you to close your eyes...
and I want you to think
about Boobie Miles,
who is your brother.
And he would die to be out there
on that field with you tonight.
And I want you to put that
in your hearts.
Boys, my heart is full.
My heart's full.
Ivory.
Our Father...
Who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done...
On earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread...
and forgive us our trespasses.
As we forgive those
who trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation
but deliver us from evil.
- For thine is the kingdom...
- The power and the glory forever.
Amen!
That's it, baby!
Hut.!
- Let go offense!
- Lead and roll.
- Spread right Eagle.
- Are you hungry?
- Thank you.
They're killin' us with their size.
They're playing some
hard-hitting football.!
- Whoo!
- Get off the ball!
Drive hard!
- Sit!
- We will not be able to live,
do you realize that?
Let the boy play.
Get your guys back.
Golly bum!
"Z" up 543. Get to the first landmark
or I'm gonna hit you as soon as
you get there.
- On one, ready.
- Break!
- Get hell into the snap!
- Show me somethin'!
- Whoo!
- Did you see that?
That's the way to play ball.
You know that was a bad call!
Now if he backs up
on the next series, it'll be over.
He can't drop back
fast enough, all right?
Yeah, it's good.
After the blowout of the first half,
we've seen a showcase of defense
here in the third quarter.
The score closing
with Carter on top, 26-14.
10:25 remains
in the fourth quarter.
It's third and ten for Carter as Whitaker
is pinned and hit Drake for six.
Tackled by Thomas.
It's gonna be fourth down.
You know Carter's
going for it on fourth.
Unbelievable.! James is not
even gonna consider a punt.!
So now Whitaker on fourth down
as Carter will go for it.
He's gonna look for Graf.
Graf's the main receiver, and
this one bounces off the turf.
Oh, incomplete.
No way.
Got that touchdown.
Look, did you see it?
I'm gonna talk to him.
Well, I wanna talk to
whoever "did" see it!
I wanna talk to whoever
"did" see it!
This is big, man.
Anybody get a better look? Gary?
- Did you turn? Jason?
- I turned and looked,
but I was lost.
- That ain't no catch.
- I couldn't see it.
- Are you sure he
caught that football?
- His was a catch, Ref.
- Lee, Mack, set 'em up.
We got first down.
What are you talkin' about?
That was a bad call!
This man has it.
This man had the catch.
- There's no way.
The ball came off the turf.
- That is bullshit!
Here's the pass.
Whitaker has found Graf.
Graf makes a one-handed
phenomenal catch
for another Carter T.D.
Chavez in frustration
levels him in the end zone.
Personal foul on the defense.
And that's gonna cost Permian
15 on the kickoff.
Called on the Carter
two-point conversion.
They now lead 34-14.
These Panthers
are gettin'beat physically.
They're gettin'beat mentally.
They're really down.
We've seen games like this before,
but Permian's always
been on the other end.
All right? We're lookin'
for the next play.
Comer got across the five.
Comer, to the 30, to the 35.
Comer could go all the way, folks.
Comer, 25, 20, 15,
10, 5.!
That's a Mojo touchdown.!
Chris Comer has brought
Permian back one more time.!
We're in this ball game now.
We're in this ball game.
- "5:27 to play."
Carter still leads 34-21.
- Come on, Chavo!
They will pitch it to Grande.
Ripped away by Chavez.!
Let's go!
Yeah! Come on!
Now strong right,
81 Trojan horse.
All right. Here we go, fellas.
Let's shock these punks.
Strong right, 81 Trojan horse.
Me and you, baby. We got it.
Throw it deep. On one, ready.
Mike Winchell to
Don Billingsley will go right.
They're on the run, but stop, wait.
Instead he's looking for a receiver.
Winchell's open.!
Winchell's open in the end zone.
"Winchell make a" tremendous "catch.!"
Winchell, with a touchdown reception,
scores the Mojo touchdown.!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
One more, one more.
But is it too little, too late
for Coach Gary Gaines?
Mojo defense is really gonna have to
step it up if they have a prayer
of winning the state championship.
Grande, across midfield.
Dropped at the 40.
- First down!
- Let's go, baby!
The clock now has to be
a concern for Coach Gary Gaines
and the Permian staff.
We need to stop right now.
First and ten now for Carter
from the Permian 30.
Less than two minutes to play.
One more Carter first down,
folks, and that will be it.
- "Grande hit.!"
- Yeah, baby!
They do know how to tackle.
All right!
What's my edge?
Second down and long.
Promptly falls back.
Just keep rollin' it, baby.
Come on!
The clock continues to roll.
This will set up third down.
Permian desperately needs a stop
to get the ball back.
Grande right up the gun
over Chavez.!
Maybejust doing what
he needs for a first down.
First down here,
and the game's over.
It didn't make it.
It's short.
Short.! By inches.!
Okay. Mm-hmm.
James immediately signals
he's goin'for it.
James is gonna gamble.
He can get these four inches
and win the state championship,
right here, right now.
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna do a Texas stunt.
Now, Ivory, you and Steen,
I want you to twist.
Yes, sir.
Steen, you go first.
Yo, Coach.
Ivory, you come offhis butt
into the 'A"gap.
Yes, sir.
Lucas, you crash the "A" gap, too.
Let's shut these cocky
sons-of-guns down!
Now let's go!
Let's shut 'em down.
Go, Donnie, go!
Let's go! Let's shut 'em
down right now.
Let's shut 'em down.
Right here!
Take 'em.
West Texas football, baby.
Whitaker comes to the line.
- Okay, let's go.
- Come on, D.
Looks across.
Calls the cadence.
Hut!
Hands to his running back.
Grande.!
- Let it go. Let it go. Let it go.
- Damn it, boy!
Yeah!
- Mike, I want you to show 'em
who we are.
- Yes, sir.
Okay? Show 'em who we are.
Execute.!
As Winchell gathers his
teammates up into a huddle,
he can see on the big clock down
in the end zone...
one minute
and 40 seconds to play.
Break!
One time out left,
and he has 75 yards
of Astrodome turfto go.
Green, 12, hut, hut, hut!
Winchell wings it off to Comer.
Comer has it, picks up a block.
- That a way, Comer!
- On three!
Off to Billingsley.
Billingsley breaks out a big event.
We're at a first down.
- Way to go, son!
- "Stop the clock"
for goin'out ofbounds.
Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's get wild!
Come on, Michael!
- He wasn't ready!
- Let's go! Let's go!
Winchell adds time as he drops back.
He's looking to the right.
Payne is wide open
down the right sideline.!
The pass is in the air.!
This Tennessee-bound tracer
comes halfway across the field
to knock the ball loose.
Payne had it.
- "I'll tell you. Mike Winchell, folks,"
showin'how tough he is.
- Come on, baby, get up!
Hang in there under
unsurmounting pressure.
Winchell appears to be okay, folks.
He's one tough dude.
He's back on his feet.
Let's go, baby!
We need you, Mike!
- "l" right. 90.
- Mike, you all right?
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm all right, man.
"Under a minute to play"...
"52 seconds"...
Winchell will scan,
pick it to Comer.
It's a bootleg pass.!
He's latched onto it.
It's Wyles, down to the Carter 25.!
Look, I want you to feel it.
Show me some heart!
Permian showing
what a tough out they are.
Come on, Donnie! Go!
That's a first down!
Whose game, baby?
Whose game is it?
Come on. There we go.
Clay, he's hurt.! He's hurt.
He grabs his shoulder.
Trapper helps him off the field.
Feels like he dislocated his shoulder.
See ya, fella!
Bye-bye!
Shake it off.
Get back out there.
- Strong left 90 "Z" five, ready?
- Break!
Permian with 35 seconds
to play go to Comer.!
And Comer over the red zone.
- Ooh, God.
- Ooh!
Did you see that?
I'll back up when
I'm through talkin' to you.
Comer is on Queer Street,
walking towards the Carter sideline.
Winchell on third down, again,
"will drop the pass"...
Hard to the turf.
And Permian will now
have to burn their final time-out.
Third and final time-out.
You have to pass.
You have no choice but to pass.
All their backs are out.
- We gotta go to the air.
- You gotta throw the football.
- They ain't got no runnin' back.
- Trapper! Trapper!
I need a runnin' back!
All right. Just relax.
We'll pop this back in.
On the count of three.
"One, two"...
Aah!
We're good to go.
You're gonna set a Bronco stunt,
then drive into the full pass
three-man coverage.
You got that?
Got it.
So, Clay, if you're Gary Gaines,
what do you do?
Coach Gaines is
done out of running backs.
"We've" got "to go to the air."
A vertical smash
and go to a reverse.
I agree. I agree.
Coach, we gotta get number one
across the goal line.
Squeeze it.
I agree.
Hang on a second,
hang on a second.
Billingsley, can you do it?
- Yes, sir.
- You sure?
- Can you hang onto the ball?
- Yes, sir.
Okay, then.
All right, now here's
what we're gonna do.
We're gonna do "l" right wiggle,
34 switchblade. Now, let's go, Mike.
Hey, Billingsley. They gonna
try to steal the ball from you.
Cover it. Cover the points.
Roll with it. Don't resist it.
You got it, baby.
No more fumbles.
That's right! That's right!
Let's go, baby. It's in your hands.
Don't think about that shoulder.
Just keep driving your feet.
"l"right wiggle,
34 switchblade.
For the state championship.
I love all y'all, baby.
I love all of ya.
Let's go on one, ready?
Break.!
Fifty-five thousand people in
the Houston Astrodome, folks,
and every seat is empty
because everyone is on their feet.
His offensive line digs in.
The Carter defense digs in
to face it.
Down!
Switch.
312.! 312.!
Come on.
Run it right down his throat.
Hut.!
He hands it off to Don Billingsley.!
Billingsley is lookin'
like Larry Csonka.!
- Come on.
- "Billingsley holds it, runs over"
another Dallas Carter Cowboy.
"Down to the" one-"yard line."
What guts to call that play.!
Fooled everybody on the field.
- Holding!
- "Clay, wait a minute. I'm seeing"
a hold call by the official.
Dad gum it!
Ten-yard penalty. Still fourth down.
- That's bullshit!
- What?
Strong right, 20 to Frasier.
Winchell has to hurry.
The clock will start
as soon as the ball is reset.
Let's go! Hurry up!
32! 3! 30!
Set! Hut!
It's Mike Winchell down to the five.!
Is he in?
- You got him short.
- That's the ball game!
I'm gonna miss the heat.
I'm gonna miss the lights.
Yeah, me too.
Stay low, boys.
Keep those feet movin'.
Hey, Chavo.
Be perfect.
You be perfect.
See ya, Mike.
See ya, Don.
See ya, Chavo.
Hey!
*Seagull, you fly across the horizon *
*Into the misty morning sun *
*Nobody asks you where you are goin'*
*Nobody knows where you're from *
* There is a man asking the question *
*Is this really the end of the world *
*Seagull you must have known
for a long time *
* The shape of things to come *
*Now you fly through the sky *
*Never asking why *
*And you fly all around *
* Till somebody *
*Shoots you down *
*Mmm, yeah *
*Seagull, you fly *
*And you fly away today *
*And you fly away tomorrow *
*And you fly away *
*Leave me to my sorrow *
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org