Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(train brakes screeching)
(siren blares)
- man: Where's the fucking...
- Man: I don't know!
Where's the fucking money!
I don't know!
Where is the fucking money!
I don't know, I swear!
I don't know!
(gun cocking)
♪♪
(fire alarm ringing)
(sirens approaching)
(exploding)
Breathe.
Come on, man... Come on.
Just don't go to sleep.
Don't go to sleep.
(heart monitor beeping)
(beeping continues)
(beeping turns into long tone)
man: I never planned
for it to be like this.
Some mistakes you
can never take back.
A near-death experience can make
you realize that life's a gift
that can be taken at
any time and you'll be forced
with a decision to either go out
gracefully or go out swinging.
For me, the choice was obvious,
especially when there's
something worth fighting for.
But let me take you back a day
so you can fully understand why.
♪♪
Man: Okay, I got two plain with
mushroom going to 1420 Dekalb
and three pepperoni going
to 325 Knickerbocker.
Who's taking 'em?
Man'. That's me... Anthem.
But with an "I", not a
I'm a pizza delivery
boy with dreams
of becoming
a real estate mogul.
I mean, come on, man.
I'm not trying to
deliver pizzas all my life.
There's nothing sexy
about that.
- Ronnie's taking 'em.
- What?
That's Ronnie, my best friend
since I was four years old.
An aspiring
architect, but for now,
stuck in the same shit
boat as me.
Nothing sexy about that either.
This is Tony's.
Located in Bushwick, Brooklyn.
This place has been my home
since I was seven years old.
When my dad died, Tony took me
in as one of his own.
Him and my dad
were best friends.
Friendship?
That means everything here.
How you gonna volunteer
me for some shit
you know I don't wanna do, man?
Just so your lazy ass
can sit there
and eat tortellinis all day?
What, 'cause you got
me this job?
Yeah, 'cause
I got you the job here.
Is that how you're gonna
talk to your best friend
for over 15 years, huh?
The one who used to bring you
back in the dodge-ball game
every time I caught the ball?
Who used to beat the little
kids in the sandbox
with the plastic shovel
every time they'd bully you.
Me... The sandbox, man.
That's how far we go back.
I would try to
reverse the role on him,
but he's actually the one
who would beat the kids
in the sandbox for me.
Shit, he's been looking out
for me since day one.
Look at my little ass.
See, I always had to act and get
into some type of trouble,
whether I would find
it or it would find me.
Did I say you could
touch my scooter?
I don't know.
Who told you
you could touch it?
Ronnie went through puberty
real fast so he was a big kid.
He used to roll up to anybody
messing with me and be like...
What's up, motherfucker?
Why you messing with
my brother for?
I'll slap the shit outta y'all.
They would back off real quick.
As we got older, he
kind of stayed the same size
and didn't get much bigger.
So that whole act didn't
really work too much more.
But his mentality
stayed the same.
Ronnie was one stubborn kid.
That was my girl.
Oh, what's up, mamacita?
Hey, what's up, papicito?
You know, you're so fly, I have
to make a song about you, right?
Oh yeah?
Yeah, it goes a little
something like this;
♪Hey yo Anthoni
keep spanking me♪
♪From the back like that
don't pamper me♪
♪And if your man finds
out we gonna have to ride out♪
♪Come to the crib Imma
let you lie down♪
♪After that chill...♪.
Hey, mack.
You made a song about my girl?
Oh, that's your girl?
Yo, Anthoni, I'm gonna beat
the fucking lips off you, man.
You're doing none of the above.
Back up off my brother
'fore I beat the shi...
(crowd groaning)
You see what I mean
by not working anymore?
But that's Ronnie for you.
Who's the wing man Neanderthal
looking bitches for you?
Big ugly bitches just so
you can get your rocks off.
Me.
You gonna talk to me
like that in front of this...
beautiful girl just trying
to order some pizza?
- What's your name?
- Lisa.
Nah, I usually don't
talk to him like this.
I'm actually quite
the gentlemen.
See these waffles?
I baked them.
Hey, enough...
Deliver the pizza.
All right, Tony.
All right, man.
Tony.
Tony: Very cute.
- "Deliver the pizzas!"
- G'head.
(bumping)
♪♪
(cash register dings and opens)
Tony.
Why you always let
those bookey motherfuckers
take the money you
work so hard for?
You ask me if I have
a choice in the matter.
You know those men
they work for?
Who?
- Lomatic.
Now that's one evil, ruthless
piece of shit right there.
A pure psychopath
in every sense.
Over the years, he's managed
to build an empire under him,
extorting mom and pop
shops in the area,
Tony's being one of them.
Anybody he felt
threatened by, offended by,
didn't pay up on time,
he would just kill.
I mean, pure and simple.
You couldn't even fucking fart
in this guy's presence
without sustaining
some type of injury.
I heard hundreds of foul
stories about him.
Shit, I heard onetime,
some pregnant chick
didn't pay him on time
and he ended up using her
stomach as a footstool
for a week.
Now this ain't your
average neighborhood thug.
The word is he did a 15-year
bit up north, got out
and vowed to never be in an
uncomfortable position again.
I guess the prison conditions
really got to him,
'cause now he's
the most comfortable gangster.
YOU'VE EVER SEEN.
I'm talking silk drawers,
Tempur-Pedic mattress,
100% cotton bathrobe,
custom suits...
Shit, I heard one time
he shot one of his own guys
because he bought him
the bed sheets
with the wrong thread count.
That's how fucked up
in the head he is.
But I mean,
his signature, his MO,
is burning people alive.
That's how you knew
Lomatic was there.
♪♪
(knocking)
Why, hello there.
Hi.
Got your pizza right here.
Thank you.
How much I owe you?
Uh, it comes out to $15
and 35 minutes with me.
What?
Here's a 20.
(sighing)
How much longer you gonna
let me go on here, seriously?
You only walked three blocks.
Yeah, well, why didn't you walk
the three blocks then?
And now I'm sitting here
subtracting money off my tip
and you standing there
with your hand out.
You know what... Whatever.
Fine... You keep it.
You sure you don't need
any help with that?
Cut it up for you?
Serve it to you on a plate?
Maybe feed it to you
like the queen of England?
Pizza's finally here, baby?
- Yeah.
- Good.
'Cause I am starving.
Hey.
Oh...
So I take it you two
don't like any sausage
on your pizza, huh?
Ew.
Wait, wait, wait.
I was always infatuated
with you guys.
I always wondered how often
do you, uh, clean the bean?
What?
You know.
Massage the vage.
What are you talking about?
You know.
Tickle the twat.
Goddamn!
(school bell ringing)
Aren't you here at an odd time?
That's Gia, my little sister.
When our dad died,
I kind of took over
the role model position.
My mom was barely home,
working to pay the bills.
That's the life of a flight
attendant for you.
So I pretty much raised her.
Well, me and rated-R
television that is.
She's got quite a mouth on her,
but she means everything to me.
Are you ever not
in detention, huh?
Even on the last day?
I'm still waiting for the day
you come out of school
with the rest of the kids.
It's not my fault.
It's that bitch of
a teacher Miss Barkley.
Watch it.
She's mean and her boobs sag all
the way down to her stomach.
You can't talk like
that about people.
That's why you keep getting
detention in the first place.
Sorry, Anthoni.
Well, at least you finished
the year with good grades.
High five for that.
You know, Tony's Pizzeria
is only three blocks away.
So that's an extra
three blocks I get to spend
with my obnoxious little
kid sister.
Shut up.
You shut up.
- You shut up.
- Big mouth.
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
(horn honking)
Anyway, I gotta tell you
about this last delivery, man.
Straight lesbians, man.
Man: Hold on a second, though.
You talking about those real
good-looking lesbians?
Are you talking about the ones
that wear the fitted hats
and the Champion hoodies?
No, I'm talking about the
good-looking lesbians, man.
I'm talking about the ones
where the two
are walking in the street
and you see them together...
Hey!
Stop fucking around.
I got the last two
deliveries for the day.
Now, which one of you two
procrastinating degenerates
is taking this one?
(with Italian accent) Hey... Ho.
Imma take this one,
okay, my friend?
I'm the best fucking pizza
delivery guy you got over here.
You see that picture... Huh?
I'm not employee of the month
for no fucking reason.
You gimme the pizzas
and I go get your money.
Hey... stop with that
Italian mafia shit.
You know who you sound like?
You sound like Scarface.
(imitating Scarface)
Okay, I reloaded!
Tony: Go home after this.
I'm closing shop and I
don't want to see
your ugly mug here again today.
Okay?
Okay... Relax.
I deliver the pizzas now.
Oh my God.
Now you just
sound Chinese, man.
- Taking Gia home today?
- Yeah, I'm gonna take her home.
I'll see you later.
Yeah, Uncle Ronnie!
Don't you think that's the last
thing you should be eating?
Such a little prick mouth.
(chatter)
boy: Yo, Anthoni...
Let me get a slice.
You ain't getting
no slice, little man.
- Get out of here.
- Come on...
I'll give you my
sister's phone number.
I don't want your sister's
phone number... Get out of here.
- Hook a brother up... come on.
- I'm not hookin' you
up with nothin',
but I will bust your
ass at ball right now.
You ready... You ready?
You can't do nothing.
That's enough ball for you.
I'm outta here.
(music playing)
What's up, mamacita?
Hey, what's up, papicito?
Ain't nothing.
When you gonna let me
come over, huh?
So you can be like
♪Oh Anthoni keep spanking me♪
♪From the back
like that don't pamper me♪
♪And if your man find out...♪.
Yo, Anthoni.
You holler at my girl?
What the fuck... Again, man?
(tires screeching)
(knocking)
Oh man.
Finally.
I been waiting
forever for this.
My God.
Total comes to $14.
Oh, okay.
Hey, man... Let me ask
you a question.
You ever call somebody, like
on the third or fourth ring,
you forgot who you
were calling?
But you gotta figure that
shit out because if you don't,
you look rude, right?
'Cause you called them.
Yeah, that's happened to me.
$14, man.
Hold on, let me get the money.
Hey, man, let me ask
you something.
You ever see a cockroach
on the floor, right?
You go to the next room to get
that bug spray, you come back,
that fucking thing is gone!
Hey, that's happened to me too.
Hold up, this
ain't enough money.
Hey, man... Look.
You ever standing
in the urinal, right?
And you pissing and then the guy
next to you is pissing
at the other urinal.
He asks you the time.
Would you give it to him?
What?
Nah, man.
I don't think
I'd give it to him.
No.
I gave it to him.
You think that's gay?
I don't know, man...
That's on you.
That ain't gay, man.
Some-thing's wrong with you.
Oh yeah.
What the fuck?
Fucking weirdo.
You never know the type
of people you'll run into
in Bushwick.
See, the thing about
this neighborhood
is that any given moment, a
million things are happening.
In the same five minutes on
the same damn block,
you'll have some innocent kids
playing with the fire hydrant
or some girls
playing patty cake.
Right on that comer, there
will be a drug deal
or somebody
about to get killed.
Shit, if there was a street
between good and evil,
it'd be right here between
a bodega and a barbershop.
♪♪
So where's the good shit at?
Money's in the bag.
I'll open the bag
when I see the sugar.
Fuck that.
Where the white bitches?
You couldn't come up with a
better metaphor for cocaine?
You said sugar.
Yo, they think we just
called them white bitches.
No, no, no.
You don't (Spanish word)
to me, papa.
Did this motherfucker just
say Bruce Willis?
That's true.
♪♪
Okay... In what movie?
Both: "The Sixth Sense"!
Yeah... Well, he never
had a gun pointed...
(guns firing)
(music playing)
man: Think about it.
Island.
I-land.
Where's the fucking
"S" in that?
It's silent.
Anthoni: I know you remember
these two motherfuckers.
Pinky and Jamal.
Lomatic's main henchmen.
It's silent says who?
Says who it's silent?
Says the old English people in
the 15th Century, that's who.
Well, them motherfuckers
ain't around, are they?
So I don't see why we have
to keep their legacy
of the silent "S" s.
Making shit complicated.
(humming)
♪♪
I You know you're fucked
you know you're fucked I.
What about pseudonym?
Word starts with a fucking.
Bet you can't spell that shit.
P-S-E-U... Holy shit.
Look at the fucking time.
They're still not back?
Come on... Let's go.
(vehicle starts, music plays)
Holy fuck.
♪♪
What the fuck?
Jamal: Lomatic's
gonna be pissed.
♪♪
(clacking)
(sounds of gunfire playing)
(phone rings)
(gunfire continues)
Anthoni.
I'm in a crazy game
with Tommy right now.
- What's up?
- Is Gia home safe?
Yeah, pause it... Pause it.
Yeah.
Listen, you're
not gonna believe this.
Our lives are about to change.
Tell me why.
I can't go over it
on the phone.
Listen, I need you to
come through to my crib now.
All right, man, but why can't
you tell me over the phone?
Just stop playing fucking
videogames and get over here.
All right, cool.
All right... Peace.
(gunfire and screaming
sounds playing)
Yo, what the fuck, man?
I told you to pause the game.
Anthoni: That's Tommy,
Ronnie's cousin.
He was also a good friend
of mine.
We all grew up
together back in the day,
but he was always off studying
or watching the History
Channel while me and Ronnie
was studying the bitches.
Yo, it was you who made
the irresponsible decision
to answer your phone
during battle.
You don't see 'em
answering the phone
during "Saving Private Ryan"
when they was storming
the beaches at Normandy.
You wanna know why?
'Cause they would have
gotten their asses blown off.
Just like that.
Man, shut the fuck up.
(knocking)
What the fuck?
Yep.
Yo, what'd you get into now, A?
Just listen, all right?
One of the rooms that
I went to go deliver,
the room right next to it had
a fucking dead person's hand
hanging out of it.
I opened the door, I see
dead bodies, a bag of drugs
and a bag of money.
- I took the money.
- All right, that
was not good, A.
And you didn't leave
nothing behind?
You didn't leave no evidence,
no fingerprints,
you didn't
leave anything behind?
Nothing, man... I was like
a fucking surgeon in there.
Man, I didn't leave nothing.
Well, how'd you know
they were dead.
They were fucking
bleeding, hunched over.
Dead, man.
Sometimes, A, a motherfucker
could look dead,
but he's really just bleeding.
And then with the guy's last
little bit of consciousness,
he sees you out
the comer of his eye
and then later on, the guy
gets resuscitated
and you know what he says?
He says it was
the skinny pizza boy.
Nobody was looking at me
half-consciousness
out of the comer of
their eyes, all right?
I saw their eyes.
Their eyes were lifeless, man.
There was nothing in them.
They were dead.
This is some heavy shit, man.
What am I supposed to
do with this?
This is some life-changing
shit you just spring on me, man.
Oh, I'm sorry I sprung so
much money onto your life.
What are we supposed
to do from here?
I'm very apologetic about that.
What do you mean?
What can't we do
from here, man?
I could put myself
through real estate school,
I can put you through
architecture school.
I can put Gia through college.
You know, we can start
up the company
we was always talking about.
- A and R Estates.
Come on, man... This
is a new start for us.
Yeah, A, I mean, look.
I mean, the shit sounds great
hypothetically.
But don't tell
me that somebody's
not looking for this money.
That's why we just gotta go
about our regular routine,
you know, still complaining
about prices that rise,
like, 50 cents or a dollar,
like the Metrocard or gas or,
you know, the Icee dude
around the comer.
You know how he be trying
to charge that extra quarter.
Don't even fucking
get me started.
$1.25.
All right, yeah... Fucking guy.
I mean, eventually, A,
somebody's gonna be asking
where did you and me get money
to start up a goddamn company.
That's why we go to school
and get degrees, man.
People think degrees,
they think money.
Legit money.
Look at that, man.
All right, but we gotta
tell Tommy, though.
Yes, we will tell Tommy.
Together, okay?
Tomorrow, take my shift.
I'm gonna meet
you at your place.
We'll tell Tommy together.
Do not tell Tommy
without me there.
You know Tommy...
Don't even mention it.
I'm not... When have
lever told anything?
I'm not going to say nothing
about anything.
Damn, yo.
- I love you, bro.
- Love you too, bro.
The world, man.
That's it, man.
- Let me hold the money.
- Uh.
- I'll see you tomorrow, man.
- All right... Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
- Imma see you tomorrow.
- Stop here tomorrow, man.
- All right.
♪♪
Ha!
I just hit 330 followers.
I'm a gangster, you're fucking
Tweeting on a stakeout.
You're just mad 'cause
you only got 19 followers.
'Cause I don't use it.
I only got it to read that crazy
shit Charlie Sheen be writing.
Yeah, whatever.
You only got 19
fucking followers.
Shut up... Look.
Who the fuck is that?
Come on, let's do this
before anybody else comes over.
♪♪
(mumbling)
- You ready for this, man?
- Yeah, man.
You're not gonna believe that
shit that's happen to me.
No, no, no.
First I gotta tell you
about the lesbian...
Whoa, lesbians?
Like the sexy ones or the ones
with the fucking hairy armpits...
Fuck the lesbians, man.
- Listen.
- That's what I'm trying to say.
We need to be trying
to fuck the lesbians.
That's a wall men have been
trying to penetrate
for years now
and you just want...
Shut up... Please, shut up.
Okay... What I got to tell
you is way more important...
(knocking)...than some fucking
lesbians... What the fuck?
Who's that?
- Hello.
- Shit.
(gun fires)
♪♪
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Tommy: I know somebody
who can help us
get what we need to
take this motherfucker out.
All right, let's do it.
Come pick me up.
I want it out.
All right.
Anthoni: So who's
this guy again?
The Persian gunman.
And how you know him?
I don't know him know him,
but Freddy told me about him.
Freddy who's locked up
right now Freddy?
I know, I know.
But it's the only
opportunity we got.
It's not very reassuring.
There goes his car right there.
There you 90...
Pull over right there.
I don't like this
shit at all, man.
(music playing)
(car door alarm beeps)
The Persian: So.
You guys want to buy
the good new guns, huh?
Tommy: Yeah, man...
Let me see what you got.
(beeping)
Help yourself.
You mean to tell me
that these are all new guns?
Yes... Brand-new,
untouched and in
perfect condition.
Tommy, come with me
for a second?
I don't trust that
motherfucker not one bit, man.
He's got the most untrustworthy
face I've ever seen.
What are you talking about?
That's his face... He's Persian.
Him being Persian's got
nothing to do with it.
Look at that fucking face.
Come on, man.
We don't got no choice
at this point.
Okay, which one
you want to buy?
We waste too much time here.
You make a choice now, okay?
These guns look like
they've all been used.
For all I know, they have a
hundred bodies on them.
I get pulled over and
take the rap for all of that?
Fuck that.
No used... New.
You speak French?
You buy now, okay?
Yes... Brand-new.
Brand-new, huh?
Then what the fuck is that red
bloodstain right there then?
It's nothing... That's a marker.
Red crayon.
My daughter's crayon
from science project.
Science project, my ass...
Man, fuck this.
I'm out of here with
his untrustworthy face.
- What?
- No.
- Yes.
- No!
- Yes... Buy one, get one free.
Hell no.
Fuck no.
(muttering)
How you gonna wanna buy a gun
with a fucking plaid
button-up on, man?
I'm tired of your button-ups...
This shit is ridiculous.
♪♪
Man: Yeah, I do.
Read the police reports and
said three bodies were found,
but the nurse at Brooklyn
Hospital called,
said that she saw
three of them coming in.
The delivery boy
didn't make it.
The other two are still alive.
Find them and have
them meet me here.
Let them come on their own.
I don't want you guys seen
taking them anywhere.
Might have made statements
about you stupid
motherfuckers already.
They're probably under
surveillance.
I understand, boss.
I'm sick of this couch.
Get it out of here.
Cushions aren't comfortable.
They look cheap.
Suede looks worn.
I don't even like fucking
on this couch no more.
Listen to me very carefully.
I want you to get
me a new couch.
And on a comfort
level of one to 10,
it better be at least an eight.
Is that clear?
Yes, boss.
What level of comfort
does it have to be?
An eight.
Good.
Don't you come back here with
anything less than an eight.
There was only one man that
I could think of
that could hook
me up that I trusted,
so I had to go visit my boy
Kyle at his new spot.
We used to chill all the time
till he moved in with his girl
who's got him pussywhipped
to a level of
jump-how-high kind of shit.
It's real funny because Kyle,
he used to be a real
gangster-type dude.
Always strapped
and robbing people.
He did a three-year bid,
got out,
met this Valley girl that
flipped him like a pancake.
I never seen anything like it.
It's amazing what some
pussy can do to a man.
What's up, Kyle?
Anthoni.
What's going on, brother?
I been better.
- How you been, man?
- Me?
Oh man, I'm good.
I'm really good.
You know, Rose got me
doing a job at tech support.
It pays all right, you know.
But I'm staying out of trouble.
No, baby, I'm the one that
keeps you out of trouble, right?
Yes... Yes you do.
Don't you forget that.
Anthoni: That's Rosemary.
We call her Rose even though
this bitch is far from a flower.
She never really liked me.
I guess it's 'cause I
never really liked her either.
Kept telling Kyle to
man up, you know?
Put the bitch in
place every now and then.
Shit, I wouldn't be surprised
if Kyle told her
every time I did, you know.
"Well, Anthoni said I should
be washing the dishes
"all the time..." but whatever.
Hey, Anthoni.
What's up, Rose?
You want to, uh,
give us a minute?
Sure.
Thanks.
Um, I heard what happened
to Ronnie.
That's some fucked-up shit.
That's actually why I'm here.
I need you to hook me up
with some heavy artillery.
For what?
- I'm gonna kill Lomatic.
- (Laughing)
(whispering) What the fuck?
Are you crazy, man?
You're gonna need a tank and a
fucking SWAT team to kill him.
Man, I heard he killed
some guy for getting him
the wrong shoe insert.
The guy got him the gels
and he wanted the memory foam
or some shit like that, man.
Guess he wasn't
trying to be gellin'.
(chuckles)
Don't get me wrong.
I want him dead just
as much as you do, man,
but there's only so much
people like us can do.
Plus, I ain't touched
a gun in years, man.
I doubt any of my old
connects are still around.
Do you know that they had Ronnie
killed right in front of me?
Hm?
Did you know that they
made me watch helplessly
while gasoline was dripping
down my fucking face?
Do you have any idea
what that feels like, Kyle?
'Cause I don't think you do.
Now, I'm not asking
you, I'm telling you
that I need some fucking guns.
Shit, man.
Shit, man... Let
me see what I can do.
I just don't want to see another
one of my boys die.
There's no choice
in the matter now.
Take this and buy whatever
you can with it.
Where'd you get this?
Don't worry about where
I got it, all right?
Just get me some heavy shit.
Now where's the bathroom?
Uh, it's down the hall
to the left.
♪♪
(sighing)
(zipper unzips, sighing)
Shit.
♪♪
Do you see the space?
It's beautiful.
You can't be the only
person responsible
for bleaching
this apartment, okay?
So we're leaving
it where, again?
Where is that bleach going?
It's going under the sink.
Under the sink... That's right.
Uh-huh.
Anthoni: Uh, excuse me.
Your bathroom
really confuses me.
It would appear as if I, a man,
am being prohibited
to pee while standing
and that I, a man,
am being directed
to pee sitting down.
Is that some kind
of fucking joke?
No.
The sign's correct.
There's no reason why
you should pee standing up.
You can sit down.
Just like us.
No.
Men stand up and pee, okay?
That's why we have
fucking urinals.
Yeah, well, this isn't
a fucking public restroom.
See, you guys, guys are
so inconsiderate
when living with a female
that they leave the seat up
and that's even if they're
considerate enough
to leave it up at all.
Most of the time, they just
piss all over the seat,
leaving it there
for us to sit in.
Do you know what that's like?
To sit in
another person's piss?
Well, not in this household.
Everybody here
pees sitting down.
Okay?
This is fucking blasphemy.
Kyle.
You're just going to sit there?
You don't have anything
to say about this?
Yeah, Kyle, what
do you have to say?
It's comfortable.
I can't believe you, man.
I can't fucking believe...
Yeah, well, believe it.
Now weren't you just leaving?
I was just leaving.
But before I go, you
know, you got some mascara
you might want to wipe
off right there.
- Where?
- Right there.
- Here?
- Yeah, right there.
Your eye.
Mm-hmm... And your cheek.
A little bit down there.
There you go.
Man up and pee, Kyle.
Bye, Anthoni.
Bye, you bitch.
♪♪
Hey, excuse me.
Come here, man.
Sit down.
If you had to give
this couch a comfort rating
from one to 10, what
would you give it?
A 10.
I'll take it.
Tommy: It's gotta be
in here somewhere.
You can't hide 'em too much.
(clacking)
Aha.
Bang bang.
- (phone vibrating)
- Hello?
Pinky: 119 Menahan Street...
First floor.
Be there at 3 p.m. on the dot.
Bring your friend or both of
you end up like your cousin.
Who the fuck is this?
119 Menahan Street.
First floor... 3 p.m.
♪♪
So they didn't give
a name or anything?
No, B.
They just said to meet
'em here at three o'clock
or we fucking dead.
So it's gotta be
Lomatic's people.
Think so?
All right, let me see the guns
you got from your grandfather.
What the fuck are these?
What are we supposed to
do with these, shoot pigeons?
Man, it's all I got.
It's better than nothing.
At last we can hide these in
case we get patted down.
All right, give me mine...
I'm gonna put mine in my shoe.
What are you doing?
You can't put yours
in your shoe too.
- Why not?
- Because then
we'll both be walking with
the same retarded limp.
It's too obvious... Come on.
♪♪
(buzzer buzzing)
Hands up, motherfuckers.
(patting)
Why you guys Walking so funny?
I don't know.
Maybe you forgot about the time
you tried to bum
us alive, you know?
Fuck us up, something
like that?
♪♪
Take a seat, fellas.
Right here on this couch.
Now first off, I'd like
to apologize
for these fucking gorillas
attempting to
bum both of you alive.
Now I'm not sure you're privy
as to why they use
such extreme measures, but see,
I'm missing a substantial
amount of money.
And your friend, who is no
longer here with us...
and again, I'm sorry...
was a lead to my substantial
amount of money.
Now you've seem to, uh,
escape this unfortunate event.
And I just had to make sure
that you wasn't so stupid
as to alert any kind of
authorities about this matter.
Do I make myself clear?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Good.
Now, gentlemen, let
me ask you a question.
How do you like that couch
you're sitting on?
- It's all right.
- It's cool.
Cool.
Cool, huh?
Hmm.
If you had to rate
that couch you're sitting on
on a comfort level from one to
10, how would you rate it?
I don't know, I'd
probably give it a...
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Now before you answer,
sink into it.
Get a feel for the couch.
There you go.
Now tell me what you think.
(whispering)
I'd probably
give it like, a seven.
(whispering) Seven-point-five.
Seven-point-five?
Seven-point-five.
Yeah, whatever...
I Now you're fucked I
both: Seven-point-five.
I Now you're fucked I.
Seven-point-five, huh?
Now I'm getting old,
but my hearing is still keen.
Anthoni, I heard your
primary inclination
was to answer a SEVEN.
And, um...
Tommy.
Good old Tommy
over here convinced you
to a seven-point-five, which
would make it an average
of a seven-point-two-five to
be your final collective answer.
Correct?
Yeah...
I guess you could say that.
♪♪
(gun fires)
Hot damn!
Right between the eyes.
You see that aim?
Huh?
Those trips to
the shooting range pay off.
I told you at least an
eight, motherfucker!
An eight!
I knew that
shit wasn't no eight.
Now get rid of this
piece of shit.
Go throw him in
the river or something.
I don't want to see
his ass anymore.
Why the fuck you got
your hand in your pants.
Um.
My balls... got
stuck to my thigh.
Oh.
I hate when that happens.
You guys can get
the fuck out of here now.
♪♪
All right, here we are.
But I don't wanna
stay with Aunt Jane.
You got to, baby girl.
There's no choice
in the matter.
But I wanna go with you.
You can't.
This is grown man's business.
Anthoni, why don't men like me?
What are you talking about?
First Dad left me, then
Uncle Ronnie and now you.
They all loved you, Gia, and
they left everybody, okay?
And I love you especially.
I promise I'll be back to come
get you when everything's safer.
You mean everything to me.
You promise?
I pinky promise.
Don't be acting like
a little bitch now.
Watch it, all right?
I'm gonna come back
to get you, Gia.
Sorry, Anthoni.
It's all right.
Kill that asshole, Anthoni.
Kill him good.
Now that Gia was safe,
I could finally focus.
If Kyle couldn't come
through for me,
I wouldn't be able to
do shit against Lomatic.
I thought going back to the
untrustworthy faced salesman,
but I couldn't risk
getting arrested
with some dirty-ass guns
before I could even make a move.
Plus... Oh man, that face.
I wouldn't even
buy some beef jerky
from someone with a
face like that.
There are some
things I just can't...
♪♪
(horn honking)
man: Get out of
the fucking street!
All right, we can go now.
Go where... What
are you talking about?
Leave... I mean,
you're here waiting
for somebody worth waiting for.
I'm somebody worth waiting for.
So we can go now.
Get off the sidewalk.
I ain't waiting for you.
I'm waiting for somebody
else and trust me,
you do not want to
see that somebody else.
Uh, you're right.
I don't want to
see somebody else.
I'm looking at you right now.
Why would I want
to see somebody else?
What... You're right.
You don't know me.
So allow me to
introduce myself.
My name's Anthoni with
an "I", not a.
How you doing?
Well, Anthoni, AKA
somebody worth waiting for,
I'm doing fine.
You're doing fine, yes.
This I can see.
And your name is?
And my name is Layla.
Well, it's a pleasure,
but I don't want to waste
too much more of our time
before the somebody else you
clearly don't want me to meet
comes rolling up here,
so, in that case,
why don't you just
give me your number
and then maybe next week,
you actually will be
waiting for me.
You must be crazy.
I'm not giving you my number.
I just met you like,
two seconds ago.
And what makes you think
rm going to give you
my number anyway?
Well, let's not exaggerate.
It was more like
two minutes ago.
But, uh, I don't know.
I walked by, I saw you, you
saw me, we linked eyes.
You know, we had this crazy
instinctive attraction going on.
You know, everything
moved in slow motion.
So instead of leaving it up
to you to come initiate
the conversation, I set it off
so you should kind of
be thanking me right now.
Oh, I should be thanking you?
Yeah, you should be thanking
me because deep inside,
you're kinda happy I
came to come talk to you.
Pssh... Whatever.
Whatever whatever, you're happy
I came to come talk to you.
Yeah, you're just running game.
You're just running game,
but you're happy I
came to come talk to you.
Just give me your phone
so you can shut up
and leave me alone already.
Ringa ding... Who is it?
Anthoni... With an "I", not a.
Yeah, you're crazy.
Here.
You better get out of here
before you get me in trouble.
All right, Imma leave you alone,
but that's just for now, though.
Just for now.
(sighs)
You mind telling me
who the fuck that was
you was just talking to?
Nobody, baby.
Some guy trying to holler.
You know how it is.
Yeah.
I know how it is.
And I know you
value your life too much
to give motherfuckers
the time of day.
(buzzing)
Now don't get me wrong,
I consider myself
to have a fair amount
of game, but I mean, damn,
just two days went by and
a few sext messages...
yeah, that's right, sexting
each other back and forth.
A couple LOLs and some smiley
faces and next thing you know,
she's inviting me over
to her place.
Now this might be a
distraction to my purpose,
but I needed to relieve
some stress.
And this was
the opportunity to do it.
♪♪
Hi.
(Layla laughing)
So I'm gonna see
you again soon, right?
We'll see.
We'll see... Pssh.
What you always say.
What's your, um, let me get
your profile page.
I'll add you.
I'm not giving you my profile.
You have a profile page
and you're not gonna
give it to me?
Yeah.
- We just had sex.
- So?
You'll let me into your
sanctimonious vagina,
but won't let on
your public profile page?
Yeah.
So I can tag your titties,
but I can't tag your picture?
Yeah.
You'll accept my fuck request
but not my friend request?
Enough, Anthoni.
Fine... Whatever.
I don't want it anyway.
I'm not even on
the internet like that.
I could poke your pussy, I can't
poke your profile page?
Bye, Anthoni.
♪♪
How many delivery boys
you got working here, huh?
One.
But you took care
of that, didn't you?
Jamal, Jamal.
Shit.
That's our boy.
Come on.
Come on... Come on.
Motherfucker.
Shit.
If Lomatic finds out,
we're fucking dead.
We might as well have
bought him a Velcro chair.
We got to find this
motherfucking Anthoni.
Just look up his profile page.
That's how we killed
our last three marks.
Yeah.
But I don't know his last name.
Come on... Come on.
Try looking it up
with an "I" and not a.
Boom-Got it.
Searched him with an "I", not
a "Y" and found the right guy.
High five.
Pinky: Shit.
What the fuck?
What do we have here?
♪♪
(shattering)
Layla: What the fuck
are you doing?
Anthoni.
With an not a.
- You heard of him?
- No.
What the fuck are you
busting my door down for?
So you don't know him, huh?
No.
Well, uh, his profile
picture would beg to differ.
Now we haven't
told Lomatic yet,
so let's not make
this difficult.
Looks like you've been tagged.
Don't you like being
tagged, sweetie?
Look at me.
- Layla: Get off of me.
- (Phone vibrating)
- (beeping)
- Hello.
Layla: Anthoni, they're
on their way now.
Get the fuck out of there.
Who's on their way...
What are you talking about?
Lomatic...
He sent Jamal and Pinky.
I had to tell them...
They were going to kill me.
You did what?
(shattering)
You dirty bitch.
I'm sorry!
(gun fires)
(dog barking)
It's over, kid.
Jamal: Motherfucker
making me run and shit.
(mouthing)
♪♪
Woman on P.A.: The next
stop is Central Avenue.
Man on P.A.: Stand clear of
the closing doors, please.
Anthoni: Now that
was too close.
Luckily I had a friend who lived
in the area I could crash at.
You know, reconstruct
my whole battle plan.
His name was Hippy.
♪♪
I barely see him
from time to time,
but we always kept in touch.
I met him at an
Alcoholic Anonymous meeting.
Not that I had a problem.
I just went there
'cause the women were easy.
Beat going to the club any day.
I could never
chill too long with Hippy,
'cause he had the attention span
of a short little baby midget.
I mean, ADD to the max.
Couldn't even have a normal
conversation
without him drifting
off 30 seconds into it,
but I had no choice.
And I needed a place to stay.
(knocking)
Anthoni: Hippy, yo,
what's up, man?
Yo, you know Jamal and Pinky.
Lomatic's goons.
They found me...
They found where I lived.
They busted in my door.
They were shooting at me.
I had to jump out of my
fucking window, man.
That's crazy, man.
(coughing)
Tangerine?
What... Why are you offering
me tangerines right now?
Antioxidants, man.
It helps relieve the stress.
All right, give me one.
Man, you won't believe the shit
I just went through, Hippy.
I jumped from the fire
escape onto the street.
I'm running as fast as I can,
Pinky's fucking fast as hell.
I jumped over a fence.
You know what I ended up doing?
I ended up jumping off of a roof
on top of a fucking train, man.
On top of a train... Am I shot?
Am I bleeding somewhere...
I think I'm bleeding, man.
They must have shot
me somewhere.
Am I bleeding?
No, you look good,
you look good.
I don't feel right.
You look... you look good, man.
It's that bitch Layla.
She set me up, man.
I got caught slipping.
Yo, you don't have no seeds
in your tangerine?
What'd you just ask me?
Seeds.
You don't have no seeds.
I have like, five already.
I'm not even halfway done.
I'm over here telling you
about this life-changing event
and you're asking me about some
fucking tangerine seeds?
I just don't understand
how you had no seeds in yours.
Not even one... And mine...
(Hippy blowing,
seed clattering)
is fucking filled with them.
You're gonna ask me about some
fucking fruit right now?
You didn't swallow
them, did you?
Did you swallow them?
Yeah, HiPPY-
Maybe I swallowed them.
Maybe I juggled them.
I don't know, maybe
I'm thinking about
how I almost
got fucking killed.
Oh no, bro.
You shouldn't have
swallowed them.
It's real bad for your stomach.
Diarrhea for like, 10 days.
Took a shit... Crazy.
You know what, Hippy, fuck you.
And fuck your tangerine seeds.
I'm out of here.
- I'm taking this.
- No, don't go.
No.
I haven't seen you
in, like, 10 years.
Anthoni: To get some closure on
what the fuck was going on,
I had to go see Ralpho.
He was the block wise man.
Anything going
down in the neighborhood,
he would know three days
prior to it happening.
He was like
the anchorman of the hood.
Only thing is that he couldn't
speak a lick of English.
What is it with these tight
jean wearing motherfuckers?
Look at him.
He can't even get his
wallet out of his pocket.
God forbid he fucks around and
puts his keys in there.
He'll end up
stabbing his own leg.
He probably had to lie on his
back just to put them on.
He probably went
to the store and said,
"Hey, what's the tightest
fucking jeans
I could possibly buy here?"
He probably can't even
walk up two steps at a time.
I mean, he probably...
What the fuck?
♪♪
(grumbling)
Situation.
(music playing)
- (speaking Spanish)
- Anthoni! (Speaking Spanish)
(Speaking Spanish)
Fuck.
Yeah, the situation you're
currently in is quite unsavory,
- if I may say so myself.
- What?
Since when do you
start speaking English?
- Eloquently.
- You like that?
Like that shit...
Yeah, man, you know,
I've been incorporating
a new vocabulary
into my everyday speech pattern
so I can sound smarter
and shit, you know.
You keep doing that, Ralpho.
Anyway, I appreciate
the heads up.
(Speaking Spanish)
Situation.
I don't know
what I can do anymore.
He knows where I live, he's
turned out Layla.
He's got a price on my head.
I have no fucking weapons
to defend myself with.
Get those fucking
green beans out of here.
(knocking)
HiPPy. Who's that?
HiPPy. Who is that?
Who's what?
Fucking idiot... Give me this.
(knocking)
(affecting voice) Who is it?
Yo, your Chinese
accent sucks, man.
What's going on, man?
What's up?
(chortles)
You ain't gonna be
needing that no more.
(guns clicking and clacking)
You don't watch
movies or anything?
No, I don't.
He never gave you up.
He did it for a reason.
The question you
need to ask yourself is
are you ready to die?
Yes.
It's like a woman, all right?
You gotta be gentle, all right?
Not gonna blow your
load, right?
How is this like a woman?
You want a little give here.
You want your shoulder pop up...
don't fucking tell me
to calm down.
(gun firing)
♪♪
See that?
You know you're not
in jail no more, right?
I'm just saying.
♪♪
(shattering)
You ready?
One... yo, why are you
talking to me so close?
- Are you ready?
- You were in jail too long.
Are you ready?
You got a strong frame, man.
Are you ready to be killed?
Yes.
I heard you can't
even pee sitting down.
Yo, Ant, why you spreading my
fucking business, man?
That was between me and you.
I don't know why
he telling jokes.
That shit ain't even funny.
Shut the fuck up.
Stop thinking about talking.
I don't want you to
think about talking.
One, two, three.
(clicking)
- (phone ringing)
- Anthoni: Hello.
Layla: Anthoni, it's me.
What the fuck do you want?
I know I messed up, okay?
But I think I can help.
I think you've helped
enough, you snitching bitch.
Listen.
I know Lomatic's place
in and out.
I used to see him
mostly on Thursdays.
Every night at around 9:30, one
of his men would go next door
and take a shit.
Nobody uses Lomatic's bathroom
ever since he shot somebody
for not flushing.
Now when this guy leaves, he's
only gone for about 10 minutes
and within that time,
they leave the front door
open for him.
He usually has three men
posted at the entrance
while he's in his steam room.
If you were gonna do
something incredibly stupid,
that would be the time
to do it.
Why you telling me this?
'Cause regardless of what you
may think, I do care about you.
And I have a feeling you're
going to do something crazy,
so I figured this might help.
I could see
the Empire State Building
clearer than ever tonight.
It casts a shadow over me and
everybody in this city,
lit up the all-powerful green.
Money's what got me into
this whole situation.
Now blood's the only
thing that'll get me out.
Sometimes you gotta reach down
and feel how big
your balls really are.
My focus and mentality is
stronger than ever,
but it's all
for the wrong reasons.
But sometimes a wrong is
necessary for a greater good.
I should be scared, but
for some reason,
I just don't give a fuck.
♪♪
(rain splashing)
That motherfucker jumped from
the roof on to the train car.
Fucking unbelievable.
Dumb motherfuckers.
If I ever catch that
fucking pizza boy.
(guns firing)
♪♪
Oh shit.
What happened?
Anthoni: I got shot.
How'd you get shot already?
My leg.
I got a little carried away.
Nobody told you to run
inside like James fucking Bond.
Yeah, man, what was that about?
Take these motherfuckers out.
I'm going for Lomatic.
♪♪
(guns firing)
Karina's a bitch,
ain't it, motherfucker?
♪♪
(groans)
(gun cocking)
What's up?
You just fucked
up my whole vibe.
Sorry about that.
- (gun fires) Oh, my ass!
(guttural wheezing)
(gun fires, music stops)
You gonna tum off my music too?
That's low, man.
Real low.
How comfortable are
you now, motherfucker?
Huh?
What's the comfort
level on that, huh?
You one dead motherfucker,
you know that?
I'm dead?
Put it down.
Shoot this motherfucker.
You just fucking
killed yourself.
He put a bullet in my asscheek.
Shoot this motherfucker.
Think about this for a minute.
- He's got to die, okay?
- I'm bleeding out my ass!
How long before he kills you?
Shoot this motherfucker!
For buying the wrong sheets,
the wrong couch.
- Hey!
- The wrong fucking slippers.
Shoot this motherfucker.
(gun clicking)
I did just buy this motherfucker
some slippers, didn't I?
Yo, fuck this.
Hey.
Hey!
You dead too, motherfucker!
You fat, greasy, com chip
eating motherfucker!
(laughing)
Look at you.
You ain't got it in you.
You ain't never killed anybody.
I can see it.
You're shaking, boy.
You look a little
sweet around the edges.
Now put that shit down.
I ain't putting shit down.
Ain't nothing sweet over here.
It's just that my leg is fucking
killing me right now.
And I worked so
hard to get here.
And I'm so happy to kill
you right now.
(gun fires)
(wheezing)
So happy.
(clattering)
Shit.
♪♪
Oh shit, you got him.
Yeah, how comfy is your
couch now, motherfucker?
(soft thudding)
That ain't
the only thing I got.
Oh shit.
♪♪
I You know you're fucked
you know you're fucked I.
Oh shit.
Yo, I gotta get back to Rose.
I never been out this late.
From the rooftop on top
of a fucking train, man.
- On top of a train.
- Tangerine?
(laughing)
man: Action.
Hippy, you're not
gonna believe the shit
that just happened to me, man.
You know Pinky and
Jamal, Lomatic's goons?
(laughing)
It's like a fucking
minefield of seeds.
Every time I fucking walk,
there's one on my fucking foot.
Man: They were going
to kill me.
You did what?
Sorry, Anthoni.
What the fuck was that, man?
Round of applause?
Everybody here pees
sitting down, okay?
Anthoni: All right.
I'll pee sitting down then.
(laughing)
(speaking French)
man: Cut.
Man: Vomit in the cup.
What the fuck is this?
What is in here?
M&Ms and some juice,
as you requested.
Oh my God.
Man: Bottle's in, bottle's in.
(clicking)
(laughing)
You guys are fucked
up for real, man.
Man: Guys, mics... come on.
Like, a million mics.
Guess he wasn't trying
to be gellin'.
(stifled laughter)
man: Uncross your legs.
I don't put my legs like that.
Guess he wasn't
trying to be gellin'.
(laughing)
You're killing me, man.
(groaning)
man: Cut it, please.
Hey, motherfucker, hit
me with your fingers,
not with the fucking gun.
(laughing)
♪♪
♪ SLI ♪
♪ Brooklyn void
Brooklyn noise ♪
♪ Fucking with
them Bushwick boys ♪
♪ Right down there on
Myrtle Ave ♪
♪ Watch them
police swerving past ♪
♪ They said Slick ♪
heard you rap ♪
♪ I do not respond to that ♪
♪ I just keep it low-key as I
grind out with the homies yeah ♪
♪ All these rappers is talking
like they was the ones ♪
♪ Who provoking when they
know they wasn't the culprit ♪
♪ Trying to take credit
for something ♪
♪ With zero involvement ♪
♪ Seems to be happening often ♪
♪ Know you insulted 'cause your
girlfriend meets Rollo ♪
♪ She took it
and shit engulfed it ♪
♪ Bull bull bullshit
then the bitch had the nerve ♪
♪ To go on Facebook and
then post it ♪
♪ But I still by
that hot dog stand ♪
♪ Getting my hot dog with
ketchup and mustard ♪
♪ Laying on tracks when I do ♪
♪ The look on they faces
they truly disgusted ♪
♪ Ironically that
is a complement to me ♪
♪ Directed and shot and produce
my own movie ♪
♪ And I also starred
in talk about hard work ♪
♪ Motherfucker don't
get me started ♪
♪ My girlfriend always mad
at me 'cause I'm barely sleep ♪
♪ Till the early morning I was
runnin' on Brooklyn streets ♪
♪ Making music
and video recordings I
♪ Busting my ass it ain't
my time yet ♪
♪ Still working on ways
for my music to surface ♪
♪ Four years I ain't
signed yet ♪
♪ But I believe it's all
working to a larger purpose ♪
♪ I just turned down a
couple contracts ♪
♪ Trying to play me
like I don't know my math ♪
♪ Or my self-worth I
don't fail first ♪
♪ Don't treat
me like no jailbird ♪
♪ Meanwhile in Bushwick the rent
is raising ♪
♪ Directly due
to the gentrification ♪
♪ They're telling you you need
a new place to stay in ♪
♪ And you have to pack up
all your shit and take it ♪
♪ And move to another hood
where the same thing ♪
♪ Gonna happen five
years down the line ♪
♪ These suckers they can't
understand the grind ♪
♪ I'm gonna tum your
ass to a fan of mine ♪
♪ Have you bumpin' slick
that common sense ♪
♪ That's miles away
from that sucker shit ♪
♪ Don't (rapping in French)
they love the French ♪
♪ But they always
trying to ask me this ♪
♪ (rapping in French) ♪
♪ Now will I spit French ♪
♪ Like clippers this shit just
goes over they head ♪
♪ And I still bust my ass ♪
♪ Like the guy that be
selling peeled oranges ♪
♪ Out of the plastic bag
on Morgan Ave ♪
♪ Until then I
am still rapping mad ♪
♪ Brooklyn void Brooklyn noise ♪
♪ Fucking with them
Bushwick boys ♪
♪ Bushwick boys ♪
♪ Myrtle Ave Myrtle Ave ♪
♪ Swerving past swerving past ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org