Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Snowing and blowing up
bushels of fun
Leanne?
Now the jingle hop has--
Jingle bell, Jingle bell, Jingle bell rock
Jingle bells chime in jingle bell time
Dancing and prancing
in Jingle Bell Square
In the frosty air
What a bright time
It's the right time
To rock the night away
Jingle bell time is a swell time
To go glidin' in a one-horse sleigh
Mix and a-mingle in the jinglin' feet
That's the jingle bell rock
Oh, my God!
Listen carefully.
Your wife has been taken.
At 4:30 p.m., you will go
to the Vatashca Street parking garage.
There, on Level 2
you will find a very special car.
You will know which one.
- Steal it.
- Unh!
There are cameras installed
on the inside and the outside of this vehicle.
I'm watching every move you make.
Drive it to the top of the city
and I will contact you there.
It's been a long time
since you've driven...
...but you'll have to overcome your fear
if you want to save her.
Your wife is very beautiful.
If you want her back, then you will
follow my instructions precisely.
If you contact the police,
or if you get caught...
...she will die.
You've done very well so far, Mr. Magna.
During the course of this night,
you will be given several tasks.
If you fail at any...
you will never see your wife again.
How do you like the car?
Do you like it?
It's armored.
It was designed especially for you.
Is she alive?
The police will be looking for you.
If they catch you, ever...
...the game's over.
Is that clear?
Brent? Why is this happening?
Please, help me.
I'm so scared.
Where are you taking me?
Where are you taking me? Wait!
She's fine.
For now.
She will remain that way
as long as you follow my instructions.
I'm watching you, always.
Get rid of your phone.
What do you want?
Where are we?
No! Please, please, don't leave me here!
No!
- Answer.
- Speed up.
Faster.
Turn left.
Go through the intersection
and turn hard left.
No, I can't do that.
I'll dead end into the park.
- Just do it.
- It's Christmas.
- There's gotta be hundreds of people in there.
- I won't ask again.
Shit.
Come on! Get out of my way.
Drive toward the market.
Smash into everything you can.
- I can't do this!
- You have no choice.
Jesus.
Excellent.
Now drive onto the skating rink.
- There's too many people!
- Now.
Get out of the way!
Go straight to the stage
where the man is speaking. Knock it down.
- I'll kill him.
- Do it.
- Are you crazy?
- Now.
Now go down the stairs.
Ah, shit.
Ah...
Mr. Magma, are you there?
Confirm you're still receiving.
I can hear you.
Where's my wife?
Keep going. Now.
Watch out, watch out!
Oh, no, no!
Jesus.
Bravo, Mr. Magna.
Your first task is complete.
Am I done?
We're just getting started, my boy.
We're just getting started.
Turn right, now.
- The water truck.
- Yeah?
Smash into it!
Don't stop.
speed up.
- Faster.
- The light's red down there.
Go through it.
Jesus.
Wonderful, Mr. Brent Magna.
Now turn right. Pull into the
underground construction zone.
Relax...
...and you will await
further instructions.
Get out.
- Get out, now!
- All right.
Do not get out of the car.
You heard me asshole, get out.
Now.
- Look, you got the wrong car. Walk away--
- Now!
- I'm doing you a favor.
- Get out.
- You don't wanna-- Walk away.
- You don't wanna steal--
- Get out of the car!
- Drive away.
- I can't! I got a kid in the car!
- Get out! What?
- Drive away now!
- Drive.
- What do you want me to do with her?
Drive away! Take her with you!
Do it. Drive!
All right, all right, all right!
Get off of me, asshole!
Do not ever point a gun at me, you hear me?
Do not ever point a gun at anyone!
Unh! Don't ever touch me like that again.
Do you know what I could have done to you?
- The hell are you doing?
- Strap yourself in.
- I'm not doing shit!
- Just put on your seatbelt.
- No!
- Strap yourself in.
- Where are you going?
- Just strap yourself in!
Kill her.
She has seen you
and she has seen the vehicle.
- Kill her.
- I'm not gonna do it. I can't do that.
You either shoot her...
...or I'm going to shoot your wife.
One.
Two.
What? What? No.
I can't do that!
I'm not a killer.
It's the right choice.
You'll need her.
You can keep the car.
Can I get out now?
- I'll let you off right up here.
- She is not to be set free.
- I-- Listen.
- Understood?
- It's understood.
Oh, great.
Oh, my God.
What did you do?
Pull over!
Oh! Shit!
Oh, God.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Put on your seatbelt!
Shit. Hey, hey!
Do not touch that gun, all right?
- I need both hands to drive this car!
- Let go of me, asshole! You understand me.
Do not touch that gun!
I don't care. I hope we crash.
Help me! This guy's trying to kill me!
- What are you doing?
- Pull us over!
Get in! Get inside the car!
- This guy's crazy! Help me!
- Get inside this car, all right?
You understand me? Stay in the car!
Pull over.
Please slow down.
- Oh, we're gonna die.
- Shut up.
Oh, my God.
Shit.
No, no, no.
You're the shittiest
driver I've ever seen.
Back off, back off. Jesus!
Oh, shit!
Is he dead?
I hope not.
Listen to me, all right.
I have got to get this car out of the city
right now, or they're gonna murder my wife.
- You understand me?
- Sure.
Let me give you a word to the wise.
Next time you wanna steal a car,
try to make sure that no one is in it.
- It works better.
- I'm not stealing it, you asshole. This is my car.
- What?
- You probably don't understand this...
...because you're a criminal.
Things in this world belong to people
before people like you take them.
This car, which was really great...
...till you added all these cameras
and shit in it to drain the battery...
- ...belongs to me.
- How'd you find the car?
I got a call from a cop saying that he saw my car
parked in the garage where I found you.
What makes you think it was a cop?
Because he said so, genius.
What kind of cop calls
to tell you he's got your car...
...but he still leaves me inside of it?
- It wasn't the police that called.
- Then who was it?
I don't know.
- When was it stolen?
- Whenever you stole it.
When was the last time you saw it?
2 days ago, I guess.
Look, you're obviously very disturbed.
Whatever trouble you're in,
I'm sure you deserve it.
So I'll cut you a deal.
Pull over, get out and I'll let you walk away.
- Or what, you shoot me?
- Give me back my gun and I will.
What's a kid like you doing with a gun, huh?
So if some dipshit like you steps to me,
I can take care of it.
That worked out well for you, didn't it?
Did you recognize the voice,
huh, that voice?
- Your friend who wanted you to kill me?
- He's not my friend, okay?
I'm not the kind of person
you wanna be caught kidnapping.
Yeah? You special, is that it?
Just do me one favor, will you?
Shut the hell up.
You shut up!
What are you doing? Hey.
What the hell?
Jingle bells, jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride
In a one-horse open sleigh
Jingle bells, jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride
In a one-horse open sleigh
Dashing through the snow
O'er the hills we go
Laughing all the way
I can't believe
you threw my phone out the window.
- I have a lot of money, you know.
- Good for you.
As in, if you let me go,
I can give you a lot of money.
- I don't want your money.
- What do you want?
I want you to stop talking.
And I want my wife back.
- And he took her?
- He did.
Whatever you owe him, I can get however
much it is to pay him off, no problem.
We'll take care of it right now.
You have to let me go
and stop almost killing us.
I would love to let you out of this car alright.
Unfortunately, I can't do that.
Why the hell not?
Because he asked me not to
and I am doing whatever he asks.
So, what? What are you supposed to do?
- I don't know.
- Well, who is he?
- What do you know?
Not much.
No, no, no!
Get up!
- Shut up.
- Ow! Aah!
Please. Please. Please, don't shoot me.
Please, don't shoot me.
Quiet.
- Answer.
- It's time for your next task.
- What is it?
- More police are coming.
You'll have 4 minutes to get away.
You'll follow my instructions exactly.
- Someone wants to say hello.
- Please, please.
- Leanne?
- Please. Help.
The clock starts now.
Damn it!
I'm totally screwed.
Oh!
- Ram him.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, my God.
- Keep going.
You're an idiot.
That's assault with a deadly weapon.
They could shoot at us now.
- Speed up.
- Shit.
Turn right now.
Remember, if they catch you...
you'll be a widower.
- Turn left.
- Oh, shit.
- Force him off the road.
- Look out!
- This is not very subtle you know!
- What are you talking about?
You're not making yourself
very hard to find.
God, I promise I'll be good from now on.
Please let me live.
- You're really not helping, okay?
- Turn right.
Great.
Turn right down the alley.
Stop!
Holy shit.
- 2 minutes.
- We're gonna die, please stop!
I don't think you'll make it.
- What are you doing?
- Take a deep breath, okay? And calm down.
Shit.
I wouldn't relax just yet.
- Shit.
- Not again.
- Did you think we were done?
- No, don't!
God!
You're running out of time.
Oh! Oh!
Tick tock, tick tock.
You have less than a minute.
- Turn into the park.
- No, not the park!
Here we go.
Your wife's time is running out.
- Watch out!
- Unh!
- Go through the intersection.
- All right, hold on!
Not much time, Mr. Magna.
Oh, no!
- No, please don't! Don't!
- Yep, yep, yep, hold on!
5...
- ...4...
- Come on, come on, come on!
...3...
- ...2...
- Oh!
...1...
...zero. Bravo, Mr. Magna.
Well done.
Bravo. Your wife lives...
...for now.
Well done.
Answer.
Brent Magna is
both reckless and fearful.
He is, in short...
...a dangerous driver
and should pursue another profession.
Remember that review?
It wasn't very flattering.
They're blind to your real talents...
...which are perfectly
suited to my needs.
Do I know you?
I know you, Mr. Magna...
- ...and I believe in you.
- Listen.
I need to know when this is all
gonna be over, all right? I need--
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
- I hate you.
- Yeah, I love you.
You realize I'll just have to buy another
limited edition Shelby Super Snake...
...take another 6 months to re-time the cams,
open up the intake and customize it.
And then I'm gonna drive
it over your face.
- You sure know a lot about cars for--
- A girl?
Yeah.
Wow.
I like fast cars and computers
and boy things, how butch.
It's the 21st century,
you should join it.
- What are you doing?
- I'm documenting this shit.
I'm not going to jail
after we get arrested.
- Well, nobody's gonna get caught, okay?
- That's right, I forgot.
We're just gonna die because you're a dumb-ass
who attacks the police with a damn car.
Now every cop in this entire country...
...is hoping to run to us, to put a couple bullets
in our heads. That's a good plan.
- We are alive.
- Barely.
Not much of a thinker are you?
Well you know, I didn't actually graduate
from charm school like you so maybe...
...you know someday you can give me
some tutoring or something.
This is what he did
to my beautiful, beautiful paint job.
Just get in the car.
This is all the crap that he drilled
into my carbon fiber interior.
And this is the dumb-ass
who got me into this mess.
- Stop filming me, all right?
- Wave hi to the judge.
- Say hi to all your new friends in jail.
- Hey! Put that thing away! I'm trying-- Just stop it.
What is--? You're like ADD or something.
What are you fiddling with now?
- Stop doing that.
- Why?
Because this guy is watching us, okay?
- And I need you to stop--
- I know what I'm doing.
- Just sit still and listen to me for 2 seconds.
See, I went to school
and I know things...
...which is why I don't have to
steal stuff, like some people.
If you're so smart, you tell me what's
going on with all these cameras, huh?
They're all linked to a single feed.
It's not only encrypted, but it's
piggybacking on a public server.
Huh?
It means that they're hosting
this live feed from these cameras...
...on a government server
without them knowing about it.
So anybody can watch it, even us.
- Wait a second.
- What?
- These aren't coming from the same place.
- Where are they coming from?
Looks like a parking garage.
- Can you tell where it is?
- I don't know. Could be anywhere.
- Do you think it's where he might be?
- Doubt it. But he can see it.
I don't like the fact that he's watching us.
Do you think you can track him
with that thing?
No, and if anyone did,
he would just dump the IP address.
As long as his feed is hosted remotely,
there's no way to find it.
- And that thing isn't really well-hidden.
- What?
Microphone.
- Oh, so he's listening to us too?
- Probably.
Well, I'll give you this,
you are bright.
It's called being educated.
You should look into it
when you're not committing crimes.
Scratch that, you'll be in jail.
All right, answer.
Pull up power plant on the GPS.
We're kind of busy right now.
Learn to multitask.
Or let your new little friend help you.
Look under the visor.
Won't you do that?
I'm uploading a new set of directions.
That's the city power plant.
At exactly 11:30...
...you will be there.
Why are we going to the power plant?
Always so inquisitive.
I like it.
Now listen carefully,
you're to break into the control room.
Access the remote system...
- ...and insert that drive.
- What will that do?
You're a clever girl.
I'm sure you'll figure it out.
He wants to cut the power off.
Why do you want to cut the power?
You have some time until 11:30.
I wouldn't spend it
trying to figure out my motives.
He's a real asshole.
So you don't know who that is?
No.
- No idea?
- I got ideas.
People I used to work with...
...but nobody I know could set up
something like this.
- So why you?
- Because I can drive.
- That's debatable.
- No, I mean, I used to race.
- Really?
- Really.
Professionally, like, real racing.
Don't think I ever saw you on TV.
There was a couple weeks
there where you might have.
And?
And what?
I washed out.
How come?
I don't know, I just did.
Doesn't matter now.
That's a pretty shitty answer.
I washed out because I believed
everybody who told me how great I was.
Turns out the only thing I was great at
was wrecking expensive cars.
So I fell off the pro circuit
and I owed a bunch of money.
This is the only thing
I was ever any good at...
...so I took whatever job
paid the most.
I did some things I'm not proud of.
But then I got out of it. And this...
...is why.
She's beautiful.
- Is she from here?
- Yeah.
She always wanted to come back,
so we thought...
...it'd be a good place
to lay low and start over.
Then I come home from work today,
the door is busted open...
...the place is a wreck,
there's blood on the floor.
My cell phone rings and this voice tells me
if I ever wanna s--
If I ever wanna see her again...
...I gotta do this job.
And if I tell anyone, she'll be dead.
Next thing you know,
I'm driving around in your car.
You souped this thing up yourself?
Yeah, it was a graduation present.
Nice. Something tells me
your dad's not a mechanic.
He's the CEO
of one of the largest banks in town.
We moved here about 2 years ago
for him to take it over.
I barely see him, but this car
is the nicest gift he ever gave me.
Well, I'm sorry about all the damage.
You know, you could also apologize
for taking me hostage.
And you could apologize
for putting a gun in my face.
I will if you let me out.
There's only one thing
I'm concerned about right now...
...and I'm gonna do whatever I have to
to get her back.
So if he says you gotta stay in the car,
you gotta stay in the car.
And where does that get you?
Why is this happening?
What is he after?
You clearly haven't
thought this through.
What happens when this is done
and he gets what he wants?
Why would he even give her back to you?
If I were him, I'd kill her
and I'd probably kill you.
- Shit.
- What?
I'd probably kill me too.
Looks like they've already been here.
If he was already here, why didn't
he just take out the power himself?
I don't know.
Stop here.
Why?
Ever see what happens to a metal car...
...when it touches a transformer
that powers the whole city?
- Just wait here, I'll handle it.
- What, alone?
Yeah, just be ready to go.
You sure?
Turn the car around,
that's what I should do.
No, I should go in after her.
No, she's fine.
She knows what she's doing.
Hello? I don't have much time.
I'm in this car with this man
and his wife was kidnapped.
I speak English. Calm yourself.
Could you just send someone, please?
- What is your, uh, emergency?
- I don't know.
It's this voice telling us what to do.
You have to help us.
- Exactly what is your location?
- I'm at the power plant.
- You make it so much fun.
- Shit.
Wherever that clever mind takes you,
remember, I've already been there.
Look around.
You see? That's right.
The police will think
you blew up the power station.
Can I give you some advice? Run.
Come on, come on.
- Go, go, go!
- What, what, what?
- Drive, drive! Go!
- What happened?
- Hold on.
- Shit.
Aah!
Faster!
Go faster!
Oh!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
I'm not dying for you.
- What happened?
- This is a part of his plan.
I was on camera that whole time.
He could have easily taken out the power
himself, but he lured us in there because...
...he wanted me
to get caught on camera doing it.
You think the cops
would ever believe me now?
Before, it was just you...
...this car.
But now I'm screwed too.
I'm sorry.
I gotta take care of myself.
- Answer.
- Stop her from leaving.
Go to hell.
Where are you taking me?
Where are you taking me? Wait. Wait.
Leanne? Leanne, can you hear me?
Can you--? Please.
Leanne, can you hear me?
Brent. Brent, what's going on?
Are you okay? Have they hurt you?
- Why is this happening?
- Leanne.
- Please help me! Brent?
- Leanne, are you all right, baby?
Please help me!
I'm so scared.
I'm coming after you.
I'm gonna make all this better.
- I'm gonna get--
- Aah!
What--?
Put my wife back on! Put her back on!
Is my wife all right?
I told you not
to let her out of the car.
- I just need to see if she's--
- I warned you.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I know what it's like to disappoint everyone,
but I never thought that I'd let her down.
She's still alive.
You don't have to do this.
I want to.
Where are you? Where are you?
What are you doing?
We gotta figure out his plan.
Oh, shit.
Get down, get down. Come on.
Okay, okay.
He was having you make this.
You're blocking off a path.
Half of these are one-way streets.
With these intersections blocked off,
no one will be able to get through here.
Until they clean this mess up, there'll
only be one way out of the city.
The rest will be a total shit show.
It's an escape route.
I just wish I knew what he was after.
You and me both.
- Answer.
- I have good news for you.
This is your last assignment.
Look up number 5 in the GPS.
Follow the directions precisely.
You have 10 minutes.
- It's the bank.
- What bank?
- He wants us to rob my dad's bank.
- Oh, shit.
We can't do that.
Do as instructed. The clock is ticking.
You can't. There's no way we could do that.
The security's way too tight.
Don't concern yourself with security.
- He wants us to get caught.
- Follow the GPS. Turn around.
This is a suicide mission.
You had to listen to me, we can't do this.
Ignore her.
Listen to me. Turn around now.
- Am I gonna see my wife again?
- Turn around.
- I'm losing my patience with you.
- Listen to me alright.
- No.
- I need to know when I'm going to see my wife.
No, you listen to me, and turn the car around.
This is your last warning.
I need to be told that she is all right
and when this shit is gonna be over!
Do you want to see her again?
Get control of yourself
and turn the car around.
You can't do this.
- Listen to me, this is a setup.
- He will kill her.
That's why they used my car.
it had to be me. Think about it.
My dad, he cut off all of my funds.
Now my car is causing havoc
all over the city...
...and I'm seen robbing his bank?
He wants us to get caught.
- What does he wanna steal?
- Money.
But that's just it,
it's not that kind of bank.
- What do you mean?
- My dad runs an investment bank.
- There's no cash.
- Oh, shit!
- God.
- So, what are you talking about, like safety deposit boxes?
No, there's nothing like that in there,
just computers.
- Bonds. Bearer bonds.
- Bearer bonds? How old are you?
What is he after, then?
What's he trying to steal?
Unless...
Hold on!
- Unless what?
- Unless you don't want to do a record of your money.
- Right, right, like it's dirty money.
- Exactly.
- So how do you move dirty money?
- Look out, look out!
- Come on, help me.
- They could encrypt the information...
...on a numeric transfer key.
A flash drive with account numbers.
If you stole one of these
little transfer keys, right...?
- You could drain the accounts.
- Right.
No one would report that money stolen,
because it's not supposed to exist.
- How much are we talking about?
- It could be billions.
I should have been a banker.
Tell me that you're not serious.
Shit!
- I'm gonna go for it.
- No, don't go for it!
Here we go!
That was awesome.
Aah!
Aah! Get us out of here!
Watch out.
I really, really hate you.
I can understand that.
- What are you doing?
- Just wait.
Okay, just sit still and
be quiet for a minute.
- Okay, it's done. I bought us some time.
- What?
I hacked into the server connected to these
cameras, put on a loop of us driving.
- That's what he can see right now.
- Why?
So that you'll listen to me.
When we get there, we're gonna get
caught and your wife will die.
We're his decoys.
- Great.
- The power's out...
...which means the security
infrastructure has been compromised.
And when that happens,
there's a procedure. Oh, shit.
My dad said something about this.
They're being moved.
They're moving them right now.
They move anything that sensitive to a secure
location until the system is back up...
- ...and then they run like a million tests.
- By the time we get there--
We'll be robbing an empty bank.
Please, let's just find a place
to look at it first.
I guarantee you it's swarming with cops.
How long do we have?
I don't know, 5,
maybe 10 minutes at the most.
Watch where you're going, asshole!
It's the most wonderful time of the year
With the kids jingle-belling
And everyone telling you
"Be of good cheer"
It's the most wonderful time of the year
I'll go check it.
So you were right?
I wish I wasn't.
So, what do we do now?
I'm thinking.
You said there was a procedure.
if the power goes out, they'll move the drives?
- Yeah.
- Where do they move them?
I don't know, it's classified
information for the bank.
Right. Shit.
But they gotta get picked up right.
They have to be picked up from here.
I mean they've got all these cops here
waiting for us.
I mean, what, is there a back door?
ls there another entrance?
Remember that parking spot that we saw?
You asked if I thought
that's where he was?
- Yeah.
- Well, I bet he's there now.
I told you you were bright.
Let's go.
Yeah.
3, 1, 9, 7, 2,
1, 3, 4, 2, 6.
What?
Go, go, go!
- You got it?
- Yeah, go!
Get them!
Answer me.
Answer me, answer me.
Answer!
Answer.
You're dead. Your wife is dead.
It's over! Don't play with me!
We hold the cards now, asshole!
Could you be a little bit more careful?
How do I get this drive out?
Got it!
Knock him! Hit him!
Holy shit!
Oh, my God, go!
- Get down, get down, get down!
- Do something!
Please, get us out of here!
Oh!
- Look out!
- Hold on!
This is Sofia Police Department.
- Shit.
- Pull over the car now!
Lose them.
Driver, pull over car now!
We're trapped.
Sit back. Hold on. You ready?
All right.
Where's the gun? Where's the gun?
- Give me the gun!
- Keep your hands where we can see them.
Now, just go with me on this,
all right? Just go with me.
Back off! Or I will shoot her head!
I will blow her brains out!
Back off! Hey! Hey! See this?
Back off, or I'm killing this girl,
you hear me?
- I will kill this girl right now!
- What the hell are you doing?
I am going to blow her head off!
Now, you. You. Yeah, you!
You okay? Hey!
Back, back, back!
Or I'm killing this girl, you hear me?
Back off! Back off!
That's it, you're doing great.
Get out of my way, copper.
I can't believe that worked.
They're clear.
I've sent you their location.
Intercept them.
What are you doing?
- I'm gonna let you out.
- What?
Come on. You're not a suspect anymore.
They think I kidnapped you.
Just tell them you were a hostage.
- No, I'm--
- I'm serious. I'm serious.
You've done more than enough for me.
Alright I can't risk your life anymore.
- I really can't. You gotta get out, okay?
- No.
- Get out of the car.
- Come on, get out of the car, will you?
- I'm coming with you.
You're an extremely stubborn person,
all right, you know that?
I know.
But I'm still not getting
out of this car.
Besides, without me, you'd probably do
something stupid, like get your face shot off.
All right.
You don't even know my name, do you?
No.
Aah! Go!
Damn it!
- Ow!
- Are you all right?
Hit him!
Damn it!
Get down, get down!
Down!
Look out!
Oh, God.
Get us off the train!
- Where's the gun? Find the gun!
- I don't know!
- Find the gun!
- I'm looking!
Find it!
- You got it? Give it to me!
- I found it! Here!
Just hold the wheel for a second!
I need you to downshift! You ready?
Now!
I have an idea.
Get out.
So we meet up with him.
We do an exchange.
The drive for your wife.
It'll never work. He'll kill us.
I have a way around it.
We use his camera to feed the video
to the cops. They'll see everything.
Answer the phone.
- Answer.
- You think you are so smart?
- I wouldn't be so--
- No, shut up and listen.
We have what you want,
let's make a trade.
- Where?
- You know where I work?
I'll see you there in 2 hours.
Goodnight, asshole.
Where's my wife?
Where's my drive?
- No. No! No!
- Leanne!
Brent?
I need to know they're real.
You. Follow him.
Let her go first.
Oh, thank God you're here.
I love you.
I'm waiting.
Waiting.
Let's go.
- Shoot them.
- Brent, look out!
No! No!
- Throw her in!
- No! Aah!
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
Shit, they got the kid.
- I gotta go after her.
- Go get her.
- You stay with the police.
- Be careful.
Damn it!
Are you hurt, ma'am?
Shit.
He has a gun on me.
Brent, he has a gun.
Please hear me.
I hope you can see this.
Quiet! Don't talk.
Brent, I'm trying
to show you where we are.
Move out of my way!
Brent, yes!
- You're screwed, asshole!
- Shut up!
Come on, come on.
Oh!
Damn it!
What are you doing? Is that a camera?
- Give it to me, give it to me!
- No, give it back!
Ah, shit! Bastard.
Damn it!
Oh, shit.
Shit.
The only way out of the city.
I know where she is.
- Pull over! Give me the gun!
- What are you doing? Stop it!
You want us to die?
Come on, come on!
- Get out!
- What?
Now!
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Stay there.
You're under arrest.
Thanks.
Everybody back!
Ugh!
- I guess I owe you one, huh?
- And you owe me a new car.
Don't worry about the car. It just needs
a new paint job and she'll be fine.
- What's that?
- I don't know.
It's not mine.
- Hello?
- Aren't you going to thank me?
I did for you
what you could never do for yourself.
I showed you what you are made of.
Please excuse me
if I wasn't able to be there in person.
I'm sure you understand,
under the circumstances...
...it would have been
most inconvenient for me.
If you're asking yourself
who I am to you...
...I will answer very simply:
I am your greatest fan.
I always thought you could have been
at the very top of your profession...
...if only you believed you could.
So that's it, you see.
Please send your lovely wife my
best wishes for a happy Christmas.
I'm sincerely glad you worked things out
to be with her for the holidays.
It's the season to be together
with loved ones, so I'm told.
I have very few loved ones.
My consolation is I have
a lot of money.
And now, quite a lot more
of it, thanks to you.
I doubt if our paths will cross again,
but then, life is full of surprises.
So let's just say au revoir.
Be assured,
it's been most entertaining.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org