Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
We'll go in the back.
I don't know, Abbie. Sure you
wanna do this? Getting really nervous.
- I'm sure.
- What if someone finds out?
No one's gonna find out.
Take that stupid hat off.
I don't want him to recognise me.
Know how much trouble we can get in?
Oh, shit, here he comes.
You guys looking for me?
Um...
We heard you had stuff to, uh,
make you faster.
- Who told you that?
- Devon's brother.
Don't say my name.
All right, you've got the money?
Look, I'm gonna go and get the shit.
I need you to wait here.
Not out in the open. Go and hide.
- Where?
- I know. What about over there?
- What, behind it?
- Inside it.
- I'm not getting in a rubbish bin.
- Cameras all over here.
If my boss sees you,
he's gonna get suspicious.
- I don't see any cameras.
- Jesus, just do what he says.
We don't make the rules.
This is his turf.
Come on.
It's not even that bad.
I'm not getting in a rubbish bin.
You know that's how you get diarrhea.
Look, do you want the stuff or not?
- Fine.
- Come on.
Two minutes,
then I'm out of here. Move.
- Give me your jacket.
- What?
Your jacket.
I need to put the stuff into it.
Look, just be careful, all right?
Used to be me dad's.
- Not a sound, all right?
- It's from the '80s.
Yeah, grand. Watch your heads.
I don't think he's ever coming
back. My dad's gonna kill me.
Jesus. Shut up, Devon.
What about my pills?
I knew he was dodgy from the start.
Why'd you get in the bin then?
Jesus. Sorry, isn't it?
I'm here to see Eddie Canellin.
- Are you a family member?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm his son.
Oh, I didn't know Eddie had a son.
Haven't been around lately.
OK, it's Room 23.
Come on, Abbie, get a move on.
- Been doing foot stretches?
- Yeah.
- Every day?
- Yeah, most days.
- I think that guy is following us.
- Who?
The guy behind us.
He was outside the house.
- Sure it's the same guy?
- Unless there's someone else
driving around with a sofa strapped
to the roof, then, yeah, I'm pretty sure.
Wait here. I'll be right back.
Can I help you?
I'm sorry.
I just sort of...
I didn't wanna call to the house.
Do I know you?
Yeah. Mr McGunn, it's me.
- Ray?
- Long time no see.
I'm not sure it's a good idea,
turning up out of the blue like this.
Alice said the door was always open.
- I'm pretty sure she never said that.
- She did.
She, uh, wrote this letter,
saying to stop by whenever I wanted.
This was written 12 years ago.
Yeah, I appreciate it's a long time,
Mr McGunn.
But she does specifically say
to drop by...
whenever I wanted.
- You invited him to the house?
- I didn't invite him, he followed us.
Anyway, I'm not the one
who wrote him the letter.
- That was years ago.
- You don't put stuff like that in writing.
- What am I supposed to say to him?
- Don't say anything.
- You did nothing wrong.
- He tried to kill himself.
- He was just looking for attention.
- Who tried?
- Your father.
- Jesus.
She's got a right to know.
You never told me
he tried to kill himself.
We didn't think it was a good idea
for you to know
how self-destructive he was.
Why would he do that?
Because he's a very confused
and strange man
who needed to stop feeling sorry
for himself.
Mrs McGunn?
There's a lady asking
about the nest of trestle tables.
Yeah. I'll be right over.
I have to get back to work.
Jesus, I can't believe you did this.
I'm not the one
who wrote the letter.
It's OK.
- Ray.
- Alice.
It's great to see you.
Come in.
God, I couldn't believe it
when Frank told me.
- So, what are you doing back in town?
- Uh...
I don't know. I was just in the area.
You know?
Thought I'd stop by, you know,
pay my respects.
Abbie...
um, this is Ray.
Hi.
Um...
- Do you want a drink or something?
- Uh, yeah.
Yeah? Yeah.
Look who's here, Frank.
- So you're into running, is that right?
- Yeah.
She takes it very seriously, Ray.
A lot of competition, but Abbie's
never been afraid to shoot for the gold.
What about yourself, Mr McGunn?
- Still teaching PE down at the school?
- Yes, I am, among other things.
He coaches Abbie's running team too.
All right, that's great.
Ray, sit down.
And you don't need
to call him "Mr McGunn."
Because he's not
your teacher anymore.
So how are you?
Like, what have you been doing
these last, jeez, what is it,
like 12 years?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good. Good.
Yeah. Yeah.
Just getting on with things. Yeah.
Trying to get things back on track.
"Trying to get things back on track."
It's not really a job, though.
No, no, no.
Not technically, I suppose.
Well, when I got out of the hospital,
I got some odd jobs,
but then I got pretty run down,
so I ended up back in hospital.
- Again?
- Yeah.
So wait, is this before or after you...?
You know, you...
- "tried to hurt yourself?"
- Jesus, Frank.
- No, Ray...
- It's all right.
It's all part of the healing process.
I had to go through this self-help stuff
back at the hospital
where they teach you to, you know,
try and use the negative parts
of yourself to build a platform
for your confidence.
- So you've been building a platform?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
For my confidence.
That sounds like time well spent.
I don't want him filling Abbie's head
with all that nonsense.
He's got emotional problems.
I feel sorry for him.
He's a fucking space cadet.
I don't trust him. Why's he showing up
after all this time, huh?
Maybe he wants money.
He's not having a penny.
I'm serious, no handouts.
Look at him, for chrissake.
When did the smelly fuck
last have a bath?
- He can hear us.
- I don't care.
Stop.
This is getting uncomfortable.
- I'm gonna wait in my room.
- No.
Sorry.
I should get going anyway.
Do you want a hug or something?
Never mind.
I'm just gonna go.
He's still out there.
- What?
- Still out there.
- I think he's sleeping in his car.
- No, he's not. Go back to bed.
- What's he doing?
- He's so gross.
Why sleep out there
where we can see him?
Maybe he'll be gone in the morning.
Jesus, Frank, he's not a dog.
I don't care.
He's not luring his way back in here.
No, we can't leave him out there.
These Frank's?
Yeah. Is that all right?
I mean, they're clean and everything.
Yeah, great. Nice and big.
What's this about, Ray?
What are you doing here?
I don't know.
I'm just paying my respects.
Yeah? Well, whatever it is,
I don't want Abbie getting hurt.
It's my dad.
I think he's dying.
Just wanted to see me, you know?
Before anything happened.
I'm sorry.
Good night.
Thanks.
Oh, hey. Bet you thought
I didn't see you there.
I'm high-performance coach
Frank McGunn.
Do you want to be a winner?
Do you dream of being a champion
and one day owning medals
and trophies?
Medals. Trophies.
Then I'm here to help.
The human foot,
a masterpiece of engineering
that top scientists are only now
beginning to unravel the mystery of.
But what if I told you
there was a new way to use your foot?
An amazing technique that could
revolutionize running as we know it
and set you on the path
to becoming a true champion.
So come with me and remember,
the journey of a thousand miles
starts with a single step.
What's it like having a dad
who tried to kill himself?
I already told you,
he's not my dad.
He's a homeless guy
sleeping in the trophy room.
- I hope it's not hereditary.
- Jesus, shut up, Devon.
I mean, what if you have
some sort of gene in your DNA
that turned you
into suicidal depressant?
What are you doing here?
Your mum had to work late
so she asked me to pick you up.
- Why would she do that?
- I don't know. She just did.
Come on, let's go.
I don't know.
Why's he got a sofa on his roof?
I already told you. He's homeless.
- Yeah, well, I don't like him.
- Ugh.
So, what, you do this
running thing every day?
True champions achieve the impossible
by rising above physical pain.
Sounds like something
Frank the Wank would say.
You call my dad "Frank the Wank"?
Yeah, well, most people did
when we were younger.
- That was his name.
- Isn't that our turn?
- This is the wrong way.
- I wanna show you something.
- You're supposed to take us home.
- Yeah, yeah.
Turn around. Right now.
OK, fine. It was supposed
to be a big surprise
and I didn't wanna tell you,
but, well, you forced me, OK?
You've ruined my surprise.
We're gonna go
and see your grandfather.
- Who?
- Your grandfather, we'll go see him.
Are you fucking retarded?
He's been very sick.
It would mean a lot to him.
- This is bullshit.
- Come on, what's the big deal?
I'm not going to see some old, sick guy
I've never heard of.
If Abbie's not going, I'm not going.
Now turn this car around,
I wanna go home.
This place has really changed.
Used to be packed in here all the time.
I swear to God, it was out the door.
I know you. You used to live across
from the Rainbow, right?
Yeah, I used to drink in here.
Raymond? That's it, isn't it?
You used to come down here
with Alice Clancy.
- Yeah.
- Oh, man.
I heard some fucked up things
happened to you.
I don't mean that in a bad way.
- It's all right. It was a longtime ago.
- Sure was.
Still can't believe she ended up
with your old PE teacher.
HEY-
Hey, mister.
- Do I know you from somewhere?
- Don't think so.
Oh. You certainly look familiar.
You don't work at the Seafood Express,
do you?
No. Don't know that place.
I think I might have seen you
down at the nursing home
where my father lives.
Oh, that's right,
your Eddie Canellin's son.
Well, I knew you looked familiar.
So you live near here or something?
Kind of.
I used to live around here,
but been away.
Oh, wow. Where were you?
Off traveling somewhere?
I was in the hospital.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
This is funny. Me thinking
I know you from somewhere
- and then us ending up talking.
- I suppose.
- I'm Rosie, by the way.
- Ray.
I like to come here after work
and just hang out, you know?
See if anybody comes in.
Yeah.
Jesus, who the hell is that?
- Mr McGunn.
- Ray.
Do you know what time it is?
No. Why?
What the hell do you want?
Oh, listen,
I'm sorry for disturbing you.
I just wanted to say thank you.
For what?
For taking me in and everything.
It means a lot to me.
And I don't want you feeling bad
about what happened to me.
I know some people think you drove me
to it, but it's not what I think.
I don't want you thinking
that way either.
Jesus, could this not have waited
until the morning?
Yeah.
It's been hard, you know.
Past few years, no one to talk to.
Oh, fuck it.
You know how it is. Hm?
Go to bed.
OK.
What's the matter?
Everything all right?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Ray said when he was younger,
Mum and him used to call you
Frank the Wank.
What?
He said it was your name.
- That's what people called you.
- And you believed him?
You think I'd let them call me that?
No way, Jose. When I was younger,
I was one of the coolest teachers.
- Ask anyone.
- Is all this really necessary?
I mean, dragging us all out
to the middle of nowhere.
Yes, Abbie needs every bit
of extra training she can get.
Mind if we listened to something else?
Yes, I would mind. I'm listening to it.
Stop it, Frank.
So, what, you're gonna go
running up here?
It's high-altitude endurance training.
Next step in my programme.
Oh, yeah, I saw those workout videos
in my room.
They're not workout videos.
A revolutionary new running technique.
You see, most athletes run upright
and strike the ground heel first.
The Way of The McGunn teaches
shifting your centre of gravity,
leaning forward, using the middle
of your foot to conserve energy.
Conserve energy. Wow.
- Oh, yeah.
- Fuck off.
That's amazing, Mr McGunn.
- This'll help change millions of lives.
- Supposedly.
What you mean "supposedly"?
Once this thing takes off,
it's gonna blow people away.
Ah.
OK, everybody,
I want you to listen up.
It's a whole different world up here.
One wrong move,
they airlift you out in a body bag.
I think we can manage, Frank.
Can I have a word with you, please?
- Can you get that?
- I have it.
- Why were you saying shit about me?
- What do you mean?
You know, all that stuff about my name,
what people used to call me.
Jesus, Frank, I was just saying.
I didn't mean anything by it.
- Come on!
- Frank. Frank, I'm sorry.
It's 11.45,
at an altitude of almost 1,800 feet.
Abbie should be making her way
down along the river. We should...
Thanks, Ray. That's great.
You've ruined the whole shot.
Sorry.
Where the hell is she?
Maybe she got tired and went back.
I mean, it's freezing out.
She's up there in a tiny pair of shorts.
The size of her shorts has nothing
to do with it.
Ooh.
Jesus Christ, Abbie. Come on.
- Frank, it's not that big a deal.
- What?
You're kind of pushing her very hard
to succeed at something that's...
In fairness, it's completely pointless.
"Pointless"? You're fucking pointless.
I mean, what are you even doing here?
Come on, man. Relax, will you?
You know what? I've about had it
with you manipulating everyone.
"Oh, poor Ray, he's so fragile."
- Pack up your shit and get out of here.
- Alice said...
I don't care what Alice said!
Out of my house!
Fuck you, Frank. It's my family
you're living with, remember?
Be grateful. If they stayed with you,
they'd be living on the street.
That's not true.
Sorry, I forgot.
They'd be living in your car.
So, what are you gonna do, huh?
You've got nowhere live. No job.
- No friends.
- Leave it now, Frank.
Abbie is scared she's gonna turn
into a wreck like you.
- Fuck off!
- Whoa!
Frank!
I didn't“ I didn't mean it!
Frank.
Help!
Frank!
Dad?
- Get your ma.
- OK. OK.
Thanks.
Are you OK?
I just can't believe this is happening.
Don't worry, he's gonna wake up.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Oh, hi. Bet you thought
I didn't see you there.
I'm high-performance coach
Frank McGunn.
I'm browsing some of the old medals
and trophies
in my custom-made trophy cabinet.
Now, I know what you're thinking.
"Hey, Frank, how come
all these medals here are gold?
What about all the silver and bronze
you must've picked up?"
Well, the truth is, there aren't any.
You see, with The Way of The McGunn,
we don't believe in second place.
So before we continue,
I have to ask you a question.
Do you have what it takes to take your
place in the pantheon of champions?
Oh, I don't know, Abbie.
I'm not sure about this.
What's the big deal?
It's not like they're illegal or anything.
They're just an energy substitute,
made from natural products.
Natural products?
Well, I'm just not sure you need it,
you know?
If you want me to go up
to the nursing home,
then you have to do this.
- And you'll go see him?
- If you get me the stuff.
All right. But just to get this clear,
- it's just the once, OK?
- Yeah, I know. I know.
I'm looking for some guy, Kenny.
Oh, yeah?
Back there.
- You Kenny?
- That depends.
Who's asking?
I heard you might be able
to fix me up with something,
you know, help me get into shape.
Who told you that?
Just this guy I know.
He said you might be able to give me
something to help me run quicker.
- You're looking for some juice?
- Yeah.
All right.
These are all made
from natural products?
Sure. That's why I hide them
in the toilets cistern.
Let me do the talking. Maybe don't talk
to him unless he talks to you first.
- Should I say hello?
- Yeah.
Don't say it
like you don't wanna be there.
Don't act like you hate me either.
Let me look at you.
- Whoa. What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Don't touch me.
Sorry.
Rosie, have you moved me dad
to another room?
Oh, Ray, I'm so sorry.
I'm afraid Eddie passed away
in the night.
It was really sudden.
The doctor did everything he could.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
You're leaving.
It's probably for the best,
just getting in the way around here.
I've got some paperwork
and the funeral and everything, but...
"after that, I'll be on me way."
Where are you gonna go?
I don't know.
Hadn't thought that far ahead.
Because I was thinking,
you know, if you wanted,
you could stay around here for a while.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, if you wanted to.
Well...
Yeah, I mean, great. If you're sure.
Just have to talk your mum and stuff.
- Whatever, you know.
- Yeah.
It's just a suggestion.
I'm sorry about your dad.
Thanks.
What are we doing here? It's freezing.
Come on. Trust me.
What do you think?
Bet you didn't even know
this place existed.
It may not look like much,
but back in the day,
this is where it all happened.
First time I ever saw your mum,
she was sitting there.
Yeah?
She asked me for a cigarette
and just started talking.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Think when I'm older
I might try to kill myself?
No.
Why would you ask something
like that?
Devon told me it might be genetic.
And because you tried to do it,
I might try to do it.
It's not genetic.
That's not how it works.
So why did you do it?
I don't know. It's hard to explain.
I suppose...
your mum didn't want me around
after you were born, and...
I didn't know how to handle it.
Can't explain it any better than that.
Why didn't she want you around?
I don't know.
She was just worried, you know?
I didn't have a job.
We didn't have anywhere proper to live.
And one day she just said she was
taking you and moving in with Frank.
Then what?
You decided to, you know...
- ..kill yourself.
- I didn't decide that.
It just kind of happened.
Anyway, you shouldn't be worried
about this stuff, you know?
You should be concentrating
on having fun,
getting into trouble.
That's not what Frank says.
No?
He says to be a champion like him,
I've gotta be 100 per cent committed.
I've got to sacrifice everything,
no matter what it takes.
And that's what you want, is it?
To be like that?
I don't know.
Maybe.
On, hi.
I bet you thought
I didn't see you there.
I'm high-performance coach
Gerry Pfeffer.
Me too.
Oh, hey.
I bet you thought
I didn't see you there.
I'm high-performance coach Gerry...
Oh, sorry, I was just...
- Gerry?
- Yes. Yes.
I don't know, Ray.
We got a lot of big races coming up.
Exactly. I can help.
Assistant coaching's
a serious business.
You got no experience,
no references.
According to Frank, you spent time
in some sort of home for the...
- ..mentally ill. Is that right?
- Hm.
Oh, for Christ“ No.
Keep it going. Keep it...
Keep it go... No, don't.
All right, just for a couple minutes
and get your breath back.
Just give us a chance, Gerry.
I can do this.
OK, look, ordinarily,
I'd tell you where to go,
but, uh, Frank's always been
a personal hero of mine,
and what you did up there in that river,
jumping in the water like that,
that took real courage.
God knows we could use
some of that around here.
Come on, girls, come on.
Push on through! Come on.
Yeah.
Do I get a whistle?
Uh, no.
What about a clip chart?
You can hold this one.
- Come on, Abbie!
- Go.
- Come on!
- You can do it.
- Yeah!
- To the finish line.
Ray, did you see that?
- Amazing.
- Well done, Abbie.
What the hell, Abbie?
Where did that come from?
Frank's programme.
I've been watching the DVDs.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, every day.
Hear that? Frank's on his deathbed,
coming up with the goods.
Jesus, Gerry.
Frank's not on his deathbed.
What? No, no, no. He's...
You know what I mean.
He's fine. He's not dying.
He's a million per cent alive.
Easy.
- Hey. Cracking run. Cracking run.
- I won!
Get warmed up. Don't get cold.
- Well, done, girls.
- I won!
- Nice run. Get those tops on.
- You won.
- Great work.
- Thank you.
Do I believe this programme has the
power to change the lives of millions?
Yes, absolutely, I do.
It's about having the courage
to take that next step,
to go that extra mile.
My whole life has led to this point.
This is why I'm here.
To change the world.
You gotta take your time.
Don't shoot too quick.
- Just hit the ball.
- Remember, it's all about geometry.
Whoo-hoo.
Self-taught. Excuse me.
No lessons.
I was one of the best players around.
Remember, I had me own cue
- that screwed back and everything.
- You probably stole it from this place.
Shh.
- Jesus, Alice.
- Two shots.
Hey. Raymo and Alice, huh?
Just like old times.
- Thanks a million.
- Cheers to you.
- It's my go?
- Yeah.
- Move out the way.
- No more of your antics.
- This one's on the house.
- Grand, Tommy.
Yay!
There you go.
- Cheers.
Whoa.
Oh, my, I love this song.
- Do you remember this song?
- Mm-hm.
- Dance with me?
- I will not.
- Please.
- I'm not a dancer.
- You're so boring.
- Alice. Well, you're pissed.
♪ I want to see the bright lights tonight
♪ Meet me
at the station don't be late
♪ I need to spend some money
and it just won't wait
♪ Take me to the dance
and hold me tight
♪ I want to see
the bright lights tonight ♪
Do you ever think
about the stuff Tommy was saying?
Like what?
You know, the past and everything.
Like when we were younger.
I don't know.
Sometimes, I suppose.
I've been thinking about it a lot lately.
About what happened.
Jesus.
I never wanted it to end up
the way it did.
No, I was young and scared and...
Ugh.
I thought all this was what I needed.
Hey, Alice.
You got nothing
to feel bad about, OK?
You got this whole new life going on.
It's great.
I'm happy for you.
Yeah.
I'm glad you came back.
I mean it.
Abbie!
Yeah, well, if it's so good,
how come nobody's ever heard of it?
It happened.
Just a question of time.
I'll show you if you want.
My dad's got tons of DVDs.
Mum?
Mum! 'Oh-my God!
What the hell are you doing?!
Is that guy fucking your mum?
On, God!
Fuck off!
- What are you doing?
- Packing my stuff.
No, no, hang on.
Where are you gonna go?
I don't care,
as long as it's away from here.
We need to talk about this, Abbie.
You can't just leave.
Please, I'm so sorry. Please.
- I know you're upset.
- Don't even talk to me.
- Stay out of it.
- Just trying to help.
Just get the phone. Look, I know
you're confused about what you saw.
- Not confused.
- Hello.
I know exactly what I saw.
- I'm gonna stay at Devon's.
- Just let me explain.
It's the hospital. It's about Frank.
He woke up.
- How is he?
- He's stable.
He's suffering a form
of posttraumatic stress.
It's normal in situations like this.
Has he said anything,
mentioned the accident at all?
He's still experiencing
some disorientation,
his memory may take some time
before it returns.
- So nothing about the accident?
- No.
- Hey. Hello.
- I'm so glad you're OK.
- Be careful, sweetie.
- I was so sad.
Hi. Hi.
- How are you feeling?
- All right.
- You need a blanket?
- Oh, no, darling.
Oh, hi, Ray.
Hello.
- Sweetie?
- Yeah?
Oh, he stopped again.
Hey.
Are you OK?
I've been over that terrain
a hundred times, and nothing.
Not so much as a scratch. How could I
have been so stupid as to fall in?
It was an accident.
Why don't you come outside, huh?
Get some fresh air.
I don't know.
What if they don't respect me?
Nobody's gonna judge you.
Everyone's just glad you're home.
. Hey, Ray.
- Hey.
I tried calling at the front,
but no one answered.
Yeah, we're having
a little get-together. Frank.
On, OK. Yeah.
So we had some of Eddie's things
up at the home.
I thought I'd bring them around
for you.
On.
That's his watch, his wallet,
stuff like that.
Great. Thanks.
Still can't believe he did that.
From what I saw,
Mrs McGunn was really getting into it.
Shut the fuck up, Stuart.
- Pretty cool seeing her vagina, though.
- I said, shut up.
God!
I saw my parents doing it once.
Taped themselves on one
of my brother's wrestling videos.
- Could you see everything?
- Yeah.
Cool.
I suppose I've always been overweight,
but when I got married, I laid it on.
I gained 65 pounds,
can you imagine that?
Terry, that was my husband,
he got really angry.
And pretty soon
we stopped sleeping together.
- I just kept getting bigger and bigger.
- Yeah?
I think that was the worst part,
like, I felt so ashamed.
But instead of trying to give up,
I just kept at it.
I'd sneak out and hit Burger King
or Abrakebabra or Mr Chicken.
Sometimes all three. I didn't
wanna order too much from one.
Yeah? Jeez, that's great.
Would you mind that a second?
Alice.
- Can I speak to you for a second?
- Now's not a great time.
You're not angry with me, are you?
Oh, Jesus, Ray.
I said I can't talk right now.
Let's just talk,
after everything that's happened.
Ray, nothing happened.
I was just upset and confused.
What do you mean?
How can you say nothing happened?
You wanna carry on living a lie?
Jesus, Ray. This isn't a game.
- This is my family.
- It's my family too.
No, it's not.
Don't be an idiot.
What did you think
was going to happen?
Did you think I was going
to go pack my bags
and run away together?
Come on.
Hey! There he is.
We were wondering when
you were gonna show your face, eh?
Death came knocking,
but big Frankie McGunn
did not answer the door.
Good to see you, Frank.
If I could just get your attention.
Frank's asked to say a few words.
You go for it, Frank.
You're amongst friends.
Ahem. First, I'd like
to thank you all for being here
and for your support
at this difficult time.
Our friends, our family.
It's great to see the kids here.
It really means a lot.
But mostly I'd like to thank God
for granting me
this second chance at life...
and for allowing me
to remain among the living
and showing me that my work
on earth is not yet finished.
Amen.
HEY-
I know Alice said that we weren't
supposed to do anything
to get you excited.
But I've got some news.
Really big news.
I got a call from one
of the board members at the club.
They're all really excited
about this new programme of yours.
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
They said if The Way of The McGunn
can generate the kind of results
they've seen with Abbie,
you could be sitting
on a big pot of digital gold.
- He said that?
- "Digital gold," Frank.
Those were his exact words.
- Jesus.
- I know.
He said, as soon as you feel up to it,
he wants you to go down there,
show him what it's all about.
It's so bad if people said it
to your face.
Abbie, can I speak to you
for a second?
Get lost.
Come on, guys, we're going.
I'm sorry about what happened.
The last thing in the world I wanted
was to hurt you.
That's such bullshit.
I can't believe I almost fell for it.
- Abbie...
- You're a fake.
You act like you're this great person,
but you're just a fucking liar!
I'm sorry.
Well, my dad's back now
so we don't need you around anymore.
OK, guys, this is it.
We're gonna show everyone we
are not the worst team in the county.
- We are the worst team in the county.
- We're here because of Abbie.
All right, that might be true,
but that's no reason not to try, OK?
Remember what Coach Frank said.
You put your heart on that track
and you're halfway to winning.
- Even if we come last?
- Yeah.
How can coming last be halfway
to winning?
Because it... I don't know, OK?
Because it just... It just can.
Now, just try your best. Yeah?
- Come on, let's rock.
- Let's go.
Abbie, Abbie.
Good luck out there, yeah?
Come on, Abbie.
- Come on, Abbie!
- Here we go.
Regional record, regional record.
She's broken the regional record.
- She's broken the regional record.
- What?
All the greats have had
their names up there.
Nikki Fitzgibbon.
Tommy Thompson.
Frankie Kennedy back in '96.
Yeah, all the greats, and now you.
I'll have your name up there
by the end of the day. Official.
Now, you just got to provide
a small urine sample.
- A what?
- Yeah, it's just a formality.
You know, make sure
everything's above board.
You never said anything
about a urine sample.
No, I know, but it's, uh...
It's not that big a deal.
You know where it is, it's just...
I can't do it.
Everything OK?
I can't do the test.
Why not?
Why the hell not, Abbie?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Hello?
Oh, he's in physio.
OK.
That was Gerry on the phone.
Oh, yeah? What did he say?
He said he wants you to go down
to the club.
He said it's important.
Jesus, Alice. This is it.
This is really it.
Get this thing off me.
- No, I think we'll finish up here first.
- No.
It's my presentation.
Hill, Gerry, the board,
they'll all be there.
Fred, get me out.
Get Ray on the phone. It's show time.
I'm dead. I'm so fucking dead.
- Think they'll kick me off the team?
- I don't know, maybe.
Taking drugs, that's one
of the worst things you can do.
This is really bad.
I'm too young to go to jail, right?
I don't know, but they can put you
in some teenage detention centre.
- Hi, Frank.
- Hi, Karen.
I have a meeting with Gerry.
OK, you head right in.
They'll be with you shortly.
I know he's a friend of yours, Gerry,
but we need to stick together on this.
Now.
Oh, hi. Bet you thought
I didn't see you there.
I'm high-performance coach
Frank McGunn.
And welcome
to the future of athletics.
What's he doing?
Why has he turned off the lights?
We all have dreams. I know I do.
Ever since I was a child, I remember
dreaming of doing something great.
Achieving something
that no one else could achieve.
- Get that idiot down from there.
- He's in a fucking wheelchair.
All my life I'd asked myself
the same question.
What makes an athlete great?
Was it speed?
Was it power?
Or was it endurance?
And then it came to me
in a moment of innate wisdom.
Moments of innate wisdom.
Now, I could sit here and tell you
about how good the programme is
and how it'll change the lives
of millions of people,
but that's not
the Frank McGunn way.
The journey of a thousand miles
starts with a single step.
- Jesus, Frank.
- I've had enough of this.
Turn on the lights, turn off the music.
Turn it off.
Jesus, Frank, what is all this?
What are you doing?
I'm making me pitch.
- You think that's why you're here?
- Of course, what else?
Will someone please explain to me
what's going on?
Gerry asked me
to make a presentation,
something to get you excited.
This is the club lawyer, Frank,
we thought he should be here for this.
- What's going on?
- Look, there's no...
There's no easy way to do this,
so I'm just...
I'm gonna come out and say it.
Abbie's been using
a contraband substance.
- What?
- You're joking, right?
- Not possible.
- There must be some mistake.
It's possible. How else do you explain
her miraculous improvement?
She's using the programme.
It had nothing to do
with your programme.
No, no, no, it doesn't make sense.
Abbie would never...
I spoke to her this afternoon,
she told me everything.
Where would she even get
something like that?
Look, I can't do this anymore.
It's time you made
some other arrangements.
So, what? That's it?
"So long, Ray, thanks for everything"?
I didn't thank you for anything.
What the fuck would I thank you for?!
I can't believe you bought her drugs!
Jesus Christ,
what were you thinking?
What would possess you
to do something like that?
I asked you a question. Did you hear?
Have you been drinking?
- Maybe.
- Jesus Christ.
Abbie, listen to me, OK?
Are you all right?
I think I wet my pants.
- Oh, my God.
- Abbie.
- Go on. Go on in.
- Yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Hey, can you help us? Please.
We need help!
All right.
So, uh...
Probably just gonna go now. Ahem.
Do you think it'd be OK if I, uh...?
- It's probably not a good idea.
- I'll be really quick, I promise.
Can I come in?
No.
So, I'm probably gonna go now.
Got some stuff I need to take care of.
Abbie.
You know you're the one thing
in me whole life that I'm proud of.
Maybe the only thing
I'll look back on...
and say, "Hey, you know what?
I didn't mess that up."
"She actually turned out
pretty good."
And the reason she turned out so good
is because I wasn't around, you know?
To get in the way or...
That's why me going is...
ls probably the best thing
for everyone.
I'll see you.
You've opened a dialog.
That's a positive move.
The first step on the path
to reconciliation.
But you've still got a long road
ahead of you.
Well, we're all very committed.
That's good.
In order to move forward as a family,
it's important you try to...
To create a platform
to help rebuild your confidence
in one another.
I'm sorry. A platform?
Exactly.
- How old is it?
- You should see.
I think it's sort of abandoned.
You should stay here,
do some repairs.
“Things didn't work out
the way I planned, Ray,
“but I know you tried your best.
"I want to say this now
before ifs too late."
"Don't make the same mistakes! Did."
"Don't end up all alone
in a place like this."
“You lost that little girl once,
and it almost killed you.
"Don't let that happen again."
"She needs you, Ray."
"She might not know it yet,
but she does."
"And you need her too."
So, you sure you wanna do this?
Yeah.
- You want me to come in with you?
- It's fine.
You wait outside. I won't be long.
Hi, Ray.
Abbie.
I was just out with Devon,
and I thought I'd stop by.
So, what, do you want to come in?
Yeah. OK.
Yeah.
So, yeah, still moving in,
but this is basically it.
Your standard layout.
Yeah, it's a pretty cool place.
Uh...
You forgot this.
- I think it's your dad's.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Oh, hey. Abbie, isn't it?
Hi.
Rosie.
Ray showing you around?
- Yeah.
It's really retro, isn't it?
OK, well, I should be getting
on with this, so...
Is she your girlfriend?
Well, I don't...
Kind of.
OK, you got it? That's it.
- OK.
- Don't drop it.
- Fuck.
- I'm going to. It's heavy.
Come on!
Send it in straight.
Will it m?
Mind your step, Devon.
Why don't you put it right here.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5jyjn
Help other users to choose the best subtitles