Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Thank you.
A Professor James Anders
is here to see you, sir.
James Anders?
Who would that be?
James Anders of
West 89th Street, Mark.
40 years, Jim.
42.
Well, if it isn't little Jimmy,
the West Side Terror.
Thank you.
Well Mark, here I am.
A retired old school teacher.
How nice to see you, Jim.
You're one of the few friends of
my childhood, I've never forgotten.
What the hell are you
doing in New York?
Is there something
I can do for you?
Well tell me Mark, is it
true what the papers say?
Is it true that you're involved in
many activities from...
paid murder to high finance?
- Why, Jim?
- I have a deal to propose to you.
Newspapers always exaggerate, Jim.
Besides, they dig up
old stories... you know.
I was a kid. And my father was on his
uppers after the Wall Street crash.
I had to do something. So...
Chicago during Prohibition.
You had to take the first step
in order to arrive at all this.
This is the school in Rio de Janeiro
where I taught history for 30 years.
The Sacred Heart American School.
My classroom...
The end of the class.
That's Sister Clementina
who is photographing me.
And there she is,
Sister Clementina.
A window of my classroom.
And here is what can be see
from that window of my classroom.
The building in front.
Every year, twice a year...
the first Thursday in February
and October at noon.
For 30 years, Mark.
In the building right in front of us.
Diamonds?
- How much?
- 10 million dollars.
And you will have to take charge of
changing the diamonds into dollars.
- And all the rest?
- All the rest I think I've more or less taken care of.
- But how do you...
- I know. I know, theoretically it should be impossible...
After 30 years, Mark...
I think it's all here, right, Mark?
How much money do you need?
Nothing. Between savings and
severance pay, I have enough.
At the moment I need only four men.
My God, Jim. You've been a
schoolteacher for 30 years.
I had to do something
to break up the routine.
Here they are. All specialists.
What branch do you need?
Aristocrats, Atomic Scientists,
Card Cheaters, Charities, Clergy, Coal...
Doctors, Drugs...
Electrotechnicians.
Espionage, Gold,
Homosexuals...
Industries, Judges,
Military...
Movies, Newspapers,
Oilmen...
Playboys.
Plutonium, Police, Politicians,
Poisons...
Safe Crackers.
Steel, Syndicate Killers,
Television...
Tipsters, Union, Uranium,
Vatican...
Vatican?
Why not?
I can't decide between military
and syndicate killers.
This one, naturally.
All four with clean records.
No police force in the world
knows them or their work.
In their fields the very best.
You'll find all information you need on
those cards. I'll tell them you're coming.
Thank you.
Rome... Paris... London.
And that one's living in New York.
Mr Weiss? There's a gentleman
here to see you.
- Mr. Erich Weiss?
- Ja, bitte? Oh, excuse me, what can I do for you?
I'm James Anders.
Mr. Milford asked me to see you.
- Any other questions, Sergeant?
-  You have established the date February 3rd.
But if for some reason February 3rd
would not be possible...
That is a possibility
that must not exist.
The diamonds will arrive in Rio
the first Thursday in February.
The next day they are sorted out and
shipped to every part of the world.
But not this year.
This year, the first Thursday in February
concides with the opening of the carnival in Rio.
The second time
in a half century.
And when it's carnival time in Rio
everything is closed. Everything.
Therefore the diamonds will be
in the safe for four days.
Second time in
a half century.
The safe won't be re-opened
until the following Monday.
But the diamonds...
won't be there of course.
Right, Sergeant?
The money and the passport
with the false name.
A lighter...
The plans for the job.
They must be carried out
meticulously, to the letter.
Everything is accounted for.
Never mind, I'll get out here.
- Good luck.
- Thanks, Professor.
How to get past the corridor
with it's photoelectric cells?
It's difficult, very difficult,
that's certain.
But perhaps...
perhaps it can be done.
These apparatus are like men.
Each has its Achilles Heel.
And we have to find also that
old armored door, Professor.
Well the armored door will be opened
in the simplest way. With its key.
It's impossible to make a duplicate so...
We'll have to figure out some way of
getting hold of it for an hour.
That's not your worry.
Let's get back to you, Signor Rossi.
To me? No.
Don't count on me, Professor.
I love the quite life too much.
My work pays well.
I don't want to be involved in
those affairs any longer.
Besides, all the way to Rio de Janeiro.
I who have never taken an airplane?
No.
- A million dollars.
- Pardon me?
Your share.
A million dollars.
Are the dolls ready yet,
Signor Rossi?
The dolls!
Did I understand you?
A million dollars?
And since there is no
sound alarm system...
all the rest has been
carefully forseen.
So you only have to take
care of the last detail.
The safe.
Are you sure it's
a Royal 1964?
Mind you Professor,
one year before or one year after...
would make the safe
completely different.
It's a Royal 1964.
Well then, there's a certain
Nilson in Switzerland...
He's opened the Royal in
a Stockholm bank.
The Royal I'm interested in
must be opened in 20 minutes.
Nilson is not able
to do that.
Right.
But why 20 minutes?
20 minutes for the safe...
and 10 minutes to get in and get out
of the vault. In all 30 minutes.
The exact time between the watchmen's
rounds inside the building.
It looks as if you've
forseen everything.
Luncheon is ready
for his Lordship
What are you going to do
about your job?
I can take my holidays
whenever I like.
May I?
Keep it.
You'll find it useful.
Thank you.
And who'll take care of
the armored door?
The key to the armored door
is in the hands of a woman.
A woman is as vulnerable as a safe.
That's why for her too
I found a specialist.
Bonjour, Robert!
Bonjour, Monsieur.
Check the horseshoe, will you?
Monsieur Brisach?
There is a gentleman waiting for you.
Robert Breisach?
I'm Professor Anders.
Robert!
- What's it about?
- A woman.
What woman?
- Very rich?
- This woman has a key.
You'll have to get hold of it
for an hour then put it back.
That's all Mr. Breisach.
- The reason?
- By means of this key...
10 million dollars in diamonds
will change hands.
You get the idea, Mr. Breisach?
Perfectly.
- Seems simple.
- I wouldn't bet on that.
But it's rumored that you
are quite a success with women.
Well I have this reputation on almost
three continents, Mr., Anders is it?
Yes, Anders, that's right.
You may keep this.
- It will help you.
- Robert!
- Excuse me. Goodbye
- Goodbye.
Robert, how long will you make me wait?
Have not you heard me calling?
Darling, my love.
Go to hell!
Robert, no more excuses.
Robert, come back!
- Go to hell!
- Come on now!
Monsieur Jean-Paul Audry?
- Are you Mr. Jean-Paul Audry?
- Yes.
The keys and the papers.
Monsieur, your apartment has
been reserved only for four days.
Perfect.
You'll be leaving us on the
first day of the carnival, sir.
As they say: "That's life."
Thank you.
That's mine.
Didn't you forget something, Sergeant?
- Is this the one?
- Identical.
The Professor's window.
That's a diamond company building.
The management offices
are on the 2nd floor.
That's Mary Ann Davis. She
has the key to the vault.
Where do you think you
are, at Indianapolis?
Didn't you see me coming around the corner?
I am on the right and I have the right of way.
Your hairdo is not becoming.
- What?
- That hairdo is not becoming.
You see? I stopped
your talking.
So many words for
such a little thing.
Give me your address and
I'll send you a check.
Meanwhile, my apologies.
My card.
Lucky guy! He has
a way with them.
Shut up. Let's go to work.
Good evening.
Your check, Madam.
But I'd given you
my office address.
Well, your license plate, kind
secretary at the automobile club...
...here I am.
Thank you. You've been
very kind. Good night.
Please...
I've been in Rio for three days
and you're the only person I know.
Could you be my guide in
this huge metropolis,
in which I feel so
lonely and lost?
- I haven't the time Monsieur.
- Jean-Paul.
It should be easy to find the
kind of guide you're looking for.
- The city is full of them.
- Why do you say that?
I haven't asked you to sleep with me.
Therefore I don't see why you...
Senhora.
- This came for you.
- For me?
I have been very discourteous to you.
I hope these flowers will make you forgive me.
Unhappily yours, Jean-Paul Audry
I also have been very unkind to you.
I hope these flowers will
help you forgive me.
Goodbye Monsieur Audry.
And that's enough!
Hey, handsome!
How are you doing?
Breaking in, it's the first day
Remember you only have another two days.
So you'd better pull yourself together.
- Jawoll, mein General!
- Look pretty-boy...
I don't like guys
like you.
I don't like you either.
So what?
Sweet dreams, mein General.
One, two, three, four...
Yes?
We in the office, we wondered if today
might be your birthday, Senhorita Davis.
Senhorita Davis.
- Good evening.
Hello.
For you.
Where are we going?
And after I finished my schooling, I went
to work for the diamond company.
First as a simple typist, then as
assistant to the general manager.
The faithful,
irreplacable secretary.
That's me.
That's all there
is to my life.
Why do you hide your eyes?
I'm near-sighted.
I feel protected with them on.
Protected from what?
It's very beautiful here, isn't it?
No thank you.
Tell me what...
tell me something about you.
What do you do
besides buy flowers?
He finally made it.
But I don't really envy him.
She's not exactly pretty.
It's all the same for him. Pretty or ugly.
Young or old. It's his work.
I want to call you
by your first name.
Alright.
And I want to kiss you.
Why?
What's wrong?
Goodbye, Jean-Paul.
But why?
It's been nice meeting you,
you gave me a lovely day...
now it's finished.
No, wait. Don't be silly.
Let me go, Jean-Paul!
Mary Ann, now come on...
I don't want to see you again
and don't follow me anymore.
- Don't be silly. It's all crazy.
- Just leave me alone!
- Driver.
- Mary Ann!
Mary Ann!
- Lock the door, please.
- It's already done.
I'll perforate from the inside in order
to find the right point of penetration.
There are only two spots which
will unblock the whole mechanism.
Let's begin with this one.
The drill, please.
Thank you.
It enters as if
it were butter.
That's exactly the
basic problem, old man.
You believe you are beginning
to make some headway...
when suddenly you come
upon the unexpected.
Seven minutes
for the drilling.
I think I can still gain
a couple of minutes.
Now let's sum it up. The watchmen come
out of the manager's office you were in.
Four minutes for the corridor
of the photoelectric cell.
Four minutes to return.
- Right?
- Right.
We're in front of
the steel door....
the key.
One minute to open
and close the door.
- And here's the Royal.
- 20 minutes for all the work on the safe.
Nine minutes to get to
the safe and get back.
20 minutes for us
to get the diamonds.
- 29 minutes altogether.
- Well, we have a 1 minute safety margin.
All in all not too bad.
Excuse me, I can't stand this heat
any longer. I'm going to get a bit of air.
Well, I'm going too.
Until tomorrow.
Jean-Paul?
Great day tomorrow, eh?
Good night.
Parlez-vous français? Sprechen Sie deutsch?
Do you speak english?
My name is... Agostino.
I am... Setuaka.
Pleased to meet you, Setuaka.
You don't have any clothes?
You have a man.
I have to go, Agostino.
Everyone, to your places!
Too far away.
She couldn't have seen us.
We are ready for
the alarm test.
What's that?
They've done it.
They've put in the Grand Slam 70.
That, gentlemen, is the
Grand Slam 70.
A system of very sensitive
microphones...
That registers the
slightest noise.
Any noise that is
above 14 decibles...
sets off the alarm.
Not too good, is it?
Well, we might as well
prepare our suitcases.
You're not preparing
anything.
You stay here until I tell you
what to do. And you. And you.
if you are really the supermen everybody
says, crazy your brains! Tread blood!
But find a solution.
Me and the men I lead
never give up, understand?
Kill yourself on those machines! But
tonight the diamonds will be ours.
Is that clear?
I think it's crazy.
Professor says, "go to Rio...
and do this. And this..."
Looks like a promenade.
Instead it's a
highway to prison.
And I'm not going to prison
to make you happy, General.
Put that in the little
bit of brain you have!
The Professor couldn't
have told us.
Grand Slam 70 came
out only two months ago.
Naturally, he couldn't have known.
You know where you
can put your reasoning?
I've never taken a risk in my life.
Not taking any now.
You and Agostino will never
be able to beat that gadget.
So, I'm saying goodbye
to you guys.
And forget that I exist.
You dirty pimp! You're only good
for charming old maids.
You're not even able
to do a man's job.
Now put one thing in that
crusted brain of yours.
You're not moving from here
until I say so.
And take some advice...
Obey. You'd better obey, buster...
Or you want me to smash in
that beautiful face of yours?
Everybody shut up, I mean it!
Shut up.
The Grand Slam 70
foresaw that too.
Blocking the microphones...
interrupts the circuits and
sets the sound box off.
We can cut the lines.
Naturally... Any temperance
sets off the sound box.
Obvious.
Therefore it's difficult.
Very difficult.
But perhaps...
Perhaps it can be done.
But you, Gregg, must shorten
the time of your work.
Leave me alone for a while
and I will show you.
I left the sound meter
here somewhere.
A phonometer.
Where has he gone?
Wait, I'm coming!
So you packed your
suitcase, huh?
Not on the face,
we need it.
Come on, get up.
I won't hurt you anymore.
The key. Tonight.
We'll pull it off, my friend.
10:30 at the corner of the square.
With the key.
Don't count on me.
I've tried everything.
That's not a woman,
that's piece of ice.
I'll never be able to get the key.
Can't you make another one, Gregg?
- Forge one.
- Shut up, you know we can't do that.
- And there's no time.
- We can't make a key like that.
Once it's in the keyhole, it opens and closes
a magnetic field that we don't know anything about.
You'll get me the key.
If you're not able to
convince her, kill her.
- But I never...
- Easiest thing in the world. Pull the trigger.
Maybe you'll be
able to do that.
I'll take his passport.
Without the key, everything
could turn into smoke.
Jean-Paul, you're here...
I'm so glad you came.
But I thought that you were...
Come in.
Is this better?
Do you still want that kiss?
Yes, why?
Because I do, Jean-Paul.
Very much.
- It's time.
- Alright.
- Mary Ann.
- Yes?
I've finished my cigarettes.
Is there a store nearby where I can buy some?
Just a minute.
Jean-Paul.
Aren't these the
cigarettes you smoke?
I remembered and
bought them for you.
Dinner will be ready
in a few minutes.
Caviar, sir...
Pheasant and Cognac...
Tropical salad...
Strawberry pie.
I'll be right back.
I've forgeotten something.
- What?
- Champagne.
Jean-Paul, there's Champagne here.
I'll go fix dinner.
Oh, how silly!
I've broken the only bottle
of Champagne I had.
Do you mind terribly going out to buy another?
There's a store open all night just a block away.
- I'm sorry, darling
- Never mind, I'll be right back.
- Ready?
- Ready.
10 seconds.
Let's go.
Get going.
The nitroglycerin.
- Ready?
- Ready.
Go.
- Voilà!
- Jean-Paul, I was really beginning to worry.
- Jean-Paul!
- Champagne, Madame!
- It will cost you a kiss.
- Is that all?
If you give me another kiss,
I'll tell you a secret.
- The secret.
- I am hungry!
30 minutes from now.
Jean-Paul...
Couldn't you put off leaving
for a few days at least?
No, it's not possible.
But I'll be back in
2 weeks at the latest.
- Who could that be at this hour?
- Stay there, it's for me.
Oh thank you.
You arrived in time!
Have this for your trouble.
Who was it?
Et voilà.
For you Madame.
Jean-Paul, you're really crazy.
I must go now.
It's very late.
Goodbye, Mary Ann.
My jacket.
Mary Ann, when I get back to Rio
could you take a few days off?
I'd like to take a trip.
Maybe up the Amazon or any place you'd like.
You choose the place.
If this business comes off...
and I think it will,
I'll have some money to throw away.
Just think my dear, if we hadn't met
each other, I would have gone back to Europe.
Mais "c'est la vie",
eh, Mary Ann?
Hey, why don't you
say anything?
Well talk about it
when you get back.
Please go away.
Don't say anything more.
Please don't come any closer.
Have a nice trip, Jean-Paul...
and... good luck.
Good luck to you, Mary Ann.
For me?
It's wonderful!
Thank you, Agostino.
Thank you very much.
It's nothing.
- What's the matter?
- I'm going away.
Rome.
Goodbye, Setuaka.
Adios, Agostino.
Chin up, Agostino. We all
must give up something.
In a short while we'll all be back in dear
old Europe. Don't make that face now, come on.
Leave me alone.
Who cares about you?
Come on, we have only
45 minutes to catch a plane.
Here.
We still have 35 minutes.
We're on time all right.
If I could only have a coffee.
I just want to sleep.
Have a tough night, handsome?
You know something, Sergeant.
You bucked me from the
first time I've ever seen you.
Well it's all over now and
I don't have to take it anymore from you.
Now then Miss Davis, tell me, did
this friend of yours know of your work?
Miss Davis, how long have you
known the young man?
You told us his first
name was Jean-Paul.
His surname?
Miss Davis!
Your lack of responsibility
will cost you your job.
Where did you meet him?
Did he say where he was going?
I warn you Miss Davis, you'd better tell us.
Describe him. What did he look like?
- The police!
- Let's turn back.
Morning.
What's going on here?
Documents, please.
Documents.
Get out.
Get out!
- Give me the nitro.
- No.
Not the nitroglycerin.
Do as I said!
No, no.
Take the wheel.
Come on!
No!
Erich!
No, no!
Setuaka!
Hold it!
Welcome to Rome, Mary Ann.
It's a pleasure to see
you again, Professor.
Sit down, please.
Congratulations, Mary Ann
You've done a mgnificent job.
You had forseen everything, Professor.
Even to your dear friend, Milford.
Milford, I coudn't take
any chances on him.
Did you have any trouble
changing bags?
A bit. The manager and the guards only
left me alone in my office for a few seconds.
You had to work fast.
Thieves! Stop him!
Thieves!
- No! Thieves!
- Please, no, please, Mary Ann.
What's happened?
I am going to call the police.
No, no, no. It's not important.
Nothing important, really.
Believe me, please.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/82x5m
Help other users to choose the best subtitles