Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
There either is or is not
a way things are.
The color of the day.
How it felt to be a child.
The feeling of saltwater
on your sunburned legs.
Sometimes the water is yellow.
Sometimes it's red.
The color in memory
depends on the day.
I won't tell the story
the way it happened.
I'll tell it the
way I remember it.
Help! Help!
What's your name?
- Whisper. What's your name? Whisper!
- Finn.
- What's your last name?
- Bell.
- Where do you live?
- By the pier.
Do you have tools?
Do you know what bolt cutters are?
Do you or don't you?
I can find you
and gut you like a fish.
I'll pull out your insides
and make you eat them, hear me?
Be here tomorrow at dawn with bolt
cutters and food, or I'll kill you.
I'll kill you if you tell.
- Anyone! Your folks...
- They're dead.
If you tell anyone, the last sound
you hear will be your own scream. Go!
Finn!
- Oh, it's you, Joe.
- Did I scare you?
- So you went out today?
- Yeah! I got a nice tan.
No fish.
Setting traps, like everybody.
- Where's the fire?
- Nowhere. Just got homework.
Maggie's on a kind of rant today,
so you be careful, okay?
- Are you coming home soon?
- In an hour.
If you finish your work,
we'll go to Carvel's.
You rest up. We've got
a gardening job tomorrow.
- Joe?
- Yeah?
Nothing.
Hey, Finn!
How do you smoke a swordfish?
Put the bill in your mouth
and light the tail.
I'll see you later.
I was raised with some
freedom from my sister, Maggie.
Joe was her man.
They banned big fishing rigs
that year, and we were poor.
We got by on what Joe earned
on charters and lawn work.
Hey.
Come on, come here.
Come on!
Are you alone?
- You deaf? Are you alone?
- No.
You're not alone
or you're not deaf?
Here, I brought you
something to drink.
Attaboy!
Here, I took this for you.
What's this?
Birth control pills?
Here, this too.
Percodan.
Attaboy, now you're talking.
What else?
Come on, come on, come on!
Do you bite your nails?
That's a bad habit.
People say the eyes
are the windows to the soul. Bullshit.
Hands. That's the sign of a gentleman.
Come on, let's go. Come on.
- What?
- Come on.
- In the boat.
- If I don't get home...
Fuck your uncle, get in the boat.
Pick up the anchor. Let's go.
Shut up and get in the boat.
- Where are we going?
- Mexico.
- What?
- Police boat.
Stop!
Ahoy there!
Son, are you all right?
- Where are you headed?
- Nowhere.
Some lady thought she saw a raft
here yesterday.
A man on it wearing a prison suit.
Did you see anything like that?
- No.
- Tie up a line. We'll tow you in.
That was the end of it.
Perhaps you had an experience
like that as a child and told no one.
Perhaps you had a brush with
a world so large you seldom...
... or never saw it again.
Jesus! It's the land time forgot.
Nora Driggers Dinsmoor.
Wait here. I'll find out
what they want us to do.
- Is it all right if I look around?
- No! You stay put till I come back.
God knows what's in these weeds.
Nora Driggers Dinsmoor,
richest lady in the gulf.
She lost her mind 30 years ago
when her fiancé left her...
... at the altar.
What's your name?
Finn.
Hey, Finn!
We're out of here. She slipped me
$500 under the door.
Gas money, she called it.
Weirdest thing.
- What?
- Nothing. Can I ride with you?
You smell like fertilizer.
Really? I do?
Mag!
- You've got the wrong number.
- You won't believe...
Yes, well, he just...
Did he do something bad?
I'll be glad to.
That sounds really...
You got it. Okay.
Three on Saturday. This Saturday?
And thank you so much, ma'am.
You won't believe
where we were today.
That was Nora Driggers Dinsmoor.
It was too good to be true.
She wants her money back?
She wants him. Finn!
The richest lady
in the state calls me...
...and wants my little brother
to play with her niece.
"Why"? The old bat liked you.
He's a likable kid, he's adorable.
Who cares? Joe, this is
a really good thing.
How'd she even know...?
Dinsmoor never met Finn.
She slipped this under the door.
What is it, Joe? God!
Do you like living with all
the dead people down here?
What's wrong with people here?
I'm tired of working so much.
They took away the nets.
Convict Arthur Lustig
was recaptured this evening.
This concludes
a four-day manhunt for Lustig...
... the convicted murderer
of Gene Valiente.
Valiente, reputed mob boss
of the Catalano family...
... was gunned down in his home
last Christmas.
Lustig will be returned
to death row...
... and is scheduled to die
by lethal injection March 16th.
Holy shit!
Hey, you look sharp.
- How do I smell?
- You smell clean. Tea time.
- Be polite. "Yes, ma'am", "No, ma'am".
- I will.
- Are you okay with this?
- He's great. Go ahead.
Say, "May I", "Please",
all that stuff.
Oh, the gardener.
The design of this floor is
from the Alhambra in Spain.
The ceiling's gold leaf, real gold.
It's just like the Thousand
Wing ceiling at Venice's Accademia.
Old Ms. Dinsmoor
hadn't been seen in years.
I'd heard she was crazy.
Go ahead.
Aren't you coming?
But nobody knew how crazy.
Her room smelled of dead
flowers and cat piss.
Boom boom.
Chicka-boom!
Besame, besame mucho
Each time I cling to your kiss
I hear music divine
Hold me my darling and say
that you'll always be mine
This joy's something new, my arms
they're holding you
I never knew this thrill before
Whoever thought I'd be holding you
close, whispering...
- Who are you?
- Finn, ma'am.
- What are you doing in my bedroom?
- I don't know.
Give me your hand.
- What is this?
- Your... Your boob.
My heart. It's my heart. It's broken.
- Can you tell?
- I'm sorry.
"Sorry." Come.
Shoo, shoo. Tabby, scram.
Wow! That's the biggest cat
I've ever seen.
- What do you feed it?
- Other cats.
Well, go ahead.
You can proceed.
- Dance.
- Huh?
I'd like you to dance. That's why
you're here. To entertain me.
Pony, foxtrot, frug,
Philly Dog, fandango. Anything.
I can't. I'm sorry, ma'am.
You "can't"? "I'm sorry, ma'am."
Or you won't? You dance.
Dance, dance, dance!
- Get out of here.
- Wait!
I can draw.
You can use my lipstick and eyebrow
pencil on the dressing table.
Estella!
Estella?
- Is tea ready?
- I'd like you to sit for a portrait.
- A portrait? By whom?
- That boy.
The gardener?
I'll be in my room.
Come back and sit.
Please.
And you. Come sit by me.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
What do you think of her?
Come on, whisper in my ear.
Come on.
I think she's a snob.
Anything else?
I think she's real pretty.
I think she doesn't like me.
But you love her.
She'll break your heart, it's a fact.
It's tragic, you're already in love.
And though I guarantee you...
...that the girl will hurt you
terribly, you'll still pursue her.
Ain't love grand?
- I'd like to go now.
- Have you finished?
Before I'm a teenager, please.
Can I go now?
Would you like to come again?
Would you like to see Estella again?
Yes.
Poor boy, poor boy, poor boy.
This is yours, dear.
The ways of the rich and all my
longing, which began that day.
To paint for the rich, to have
their freedom, to love Estella.
The things we cannot have.
Give this to your guardian.
Would you see Finn out, please?
Chicka-boom!
Want some?
It's not poisoned.
You remember it.
You remember how it felt.
And then I went home to draw it.
I'm going to work.
What are you going to do before bed?
Brush my teeth.
That's really beautiful, Finn.
Keep it up, okay?
Maggie left that night.
She never came back.
I'll see you when you wake up.
Joe raised me.
We never said a word.
I visited Paradiso Perduto
Saturdays.
Feel it, feel it, feel it, feel it.
The money Dinsmoor paid
kept me in paints and brushes.
And there was Estella.
Smile. Smile.
Smi... All right, don't smile.
Yes, feel it!
Wonderful, wonderful!
Feel it in your bones.
- Where are you going?
- Cocktails at Rewald's.
Lane? Another cocktail,
and we'll be able to eat him.
Carl Rewald. Lane is his father.
Carl doesn't drink.
Cue balls. The whole family's pickled.
Who's your escort?
- Please, this is the '80s...
- I'll bring you.
Finn will make a fine date.
Oh, God!
Then it's done.
Fine, but you meet me there. 1115
North Ocean. Wear your dinner jacket.
- How much time have you got?
- None, I'm late! I'm dead. Wow!
That'll pass as a dinner jacket.
- This is a girl's.
- Keep it buttoned, no one will notice.
- Where did you get this?
- It's Maggie's.
- It's one of the only things she left.
- What a bitch!
What?
- "What?" Come here.
- Jesus!
- Are you all right for money?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- A little nervous?
- Yeah, a little.
There you go.
You just be yourself, huh?
Come on, have fun.
- You're not on the list.
- Check the name Dinsmoor?
I did, sir. You're not on this list.
Please leave now.
Hi, Mrs. Lee!
Use your usual spot.
Hi.
- Do you want to get me out of here?
- Yes.
Come on in.
- Where do you want to go?
- Your house?
All right. Let's go.
The moths are
from the Thousand Wing ceiling.
Joe's not here. He's...
He's playing dominoes.
- Is that your room?
- Yeah.
I wasn't really
expecting company...
...you know.
- You still draw.
- Yeah.
They're hanging a couple
at Washington Federal.
The bank?
- Go to New York.
- New York?
Center of the art world.
Here, you'll end up painting
coconuts for tourists.
- When did you do this?
- A while ago.
I don't wear my hair like that
anymore.
But you should.
- I mean...
- Do you like it that way?
What else do you like?
How come we see each other
every week, but we never did anything?
- "Did anything"?
- Saw a movie, whatever.
You never asked.
And if I had?
I'm here, aren't I?
- Are you with anyone?
- Right this second?
- No, I mean like...
- Like a steady boyfriend?
No.
- You could have anyone.
- No, I...
What about you?
- Why not?
- 'Cause I...
I just...
I know.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- It's late. What time is it?
- It's 10:30. Where are you going?
I've got to get home.
I have a million things to do tonight.
Stay!
Don't speak French.
Estella?
Excuse me. Have you seen Estella?
Dinsmoor was weirder than
usual, but I had to see Estella.
I never come here. Never.
Do you know why?
Twenty-six years ago, I trusted.
I saved myself. I was a virgin.
It's funny, huh?
Those were the times,
that's how I was raised.
What kind of creature takes
such a thing, such a gift, a trust?
Who does this? Takes advantage
of a 42-year-old woman?
What kind of creature leaves
this woman waiting like a fool?
A man does this, so men must pay.
Am I right?
- Estella will make men weep.
- Do you know where she is?
She'll break them.
I taught her well.
When she returns, she'll cut through
them like a hot knife through butter.
- Returns?
- Oh, my dear boy!
Didn't you know?
She's left for school.
Switzerland for two years, then Paris.
Didn't she say goodbye?
I'm sure she meant to.
See you next week, dear.
Seven years passed.
I stopped going to Paradiso Perduto.
I stopped painting.
I put aside fantasy and the wealthy...
... and the heavenly girl
who did not want me.
None of it would happen to me again.
I'd seen through it.
I elected to grow up.
Finn! This is Jerry Ragno.
Jerry, Mr. Ragno
is a lawyer in Miami.
And New York. We have
offices in Manhattan. So, Finn...
...I'm empowered by my client
to make your dreams come true.
Really? Any particular dream
or just all of them?
Have you ever shown your work?
No.
They had Finn's painting
at Washington Federal Bank.
Eight years ago. I gave all that up.
I don't understand what this is about.
How would you like a one-man show
at the Thrall Gallery?
My client, Erica Thrall, wants you
in New York for a one-man show.
Have you ever sent slides
to the Thrall Gallery?
I sent slides everywhere
in high school.
They made an impression.
A ticket to New York...
...plus $1000 for incidentals.
Sorry, they're all in hundreds.
The hundreds aren't the problem.
I just... I don't paint anymore.
Whose business was it
what I did with my life?
Who'd gotten my life in order? Me.
I was in control.
And everything I wanted, I had.
Ms. Dinsmoor?
Are cocktails ready, Thomas?
No, it's me. It's Finn.
- I came...
Looking for Estella.
- That hook is in deep, isn't it, dear?
- I came to ask you a question.
After nearly 10 years
without a word, without a visit...
...you've come to interrogate me.
How interesting.
- I'm sorry. Things happened.
- The love of your life left you.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Come closer.
I've gone red.
- I noticed. It's nice.
- And look at you.
All grown up. A man.
Ms. Dinsmoor, a lawyer named Ragno
came to see me.
- The spider.
- Do you know him?
"Ragno" means "spider" in Italian.
You must learn other languages.
He represents an art gallery owner in
New York who wants to show my work.
You can draw. Can't dance
worth a shit, but you can draw.
Did you know anything about this?
- Estella is in New York.
- I doubt our paths will cross.
- So you're going?
- Should I?
I remember watching you
from that very window.
Scared little mouse scurrying across
my garden and through my front door.
Now another door opens.
What will our mouse do?
- I expect an invitation.
- I'm sorry?
To your opening, your show.
- What equipment are you flying?
- What?
Is it a wide body or a 767?
I've no idea,
I just hope it stays up there.
- You'd better get on.
- Yeah.
What happens if I get up there
and I can't deliver?
Finn. There's nothing harder
than being given your chance.
- At least that's what I hear.
- Yeah?
Taxi!
- Have you got change for a dollar?
- What?
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you, man! Fuck you!
Well, then, there I was.
Ms. Dinsmoor, as my secret benefactor,
sent me to New York to draw.
To have the girl, to have it all.
And I looked out on the great city,
as so many before, which held it all.
And it was that close,
and it was mine.
"Liebchen, guten Morgen." Are you still
holding the red and green Picasso?
I think I have somebody interested.
No, I can't say right now.
Just the Picasso.
Fabelhaft. Danke.
Here's where you
show me your work, darling.
- I told you, I don't have any.
- Then you'd better get busy.
Why am I here?
You saw some slides?
I gave Keith Haring a show
after he drew a sketch in my hand.
But which paintings did you like?
I saw the beginning of something,
and here you are.
Annette, Sotheby's.
What you do is up to you. Stay and
paint or enjoy the sights and go home.
Either way, I always enjoy
meeting a young painter.
Look, I mean, I'll do it.
I said that I'll do the paintings.
Wonderful. Call Marcy
when you have something for us.
And I could still draw.
Nothing had lessened it as much
as I had abused it, abandoned it.
It was a gift, and it was still mine.
And everything else was less real.
What can it mean?
That picture of the world.
But when it's true, we recognize it
in ourselves, in others.
We recognize it, like love,
completely undeserved.
You're drooling.
So, Finn Bell.
In New York.
That's right.
I thought I saw you last Christmas.
I was driving down 5th.
I just got here.
Actually, now that I see you,
this guy was bigger.
- He's bigger.
- Fatter.
- He had long hair.
- You thought it was me?
- I hadn't seen you in years.
- It has been a while.
And here we are.
- I have to run.
- Wait, maybe we could...
Tomorrow at the Borough Club
around 6. I'm meeting some friends.
If you're free, that is.
I'm free.
I'm glad you're here.
A long time ago there lived
two brilliant artists. True geniuses.
One day one of them
was painting out in the forest...
... and he came upon this dog
who was crying, obviously lost.
A puppy.
Yes, sure. A puppy, fine.
He couldn't concentrate anyway,
so he scooped the puppy up...
... and took him into town
to find its owner...
... who turned out to be
the prince of the kingdom...
... who was eternally grateful
and very wealthy.
That artist's name was Michelangelo.
True story.
The other artist's name was... Nobody
knows, he was never heard from again.
Right, that's so true, Walter.
Can I smoke?
- It's your last one.
- That's all right.
So you... Cigarette, please.
You're from Florida too?
- Yes.
- Everybody is from Florida.
I'm not, I hate Florida.
Too much sun.
Really?
Actually, Finn was my childhood...
What were you exactly?
He was my first love.
If that's what you say.
He painted a beautiful portrait of me
when I was 10.
I sat for a portrait once. Electric.
You sucked off de Kooning!
- I'd like to paint you again.
- Would you?
I want to paint your portrait.
- What do you think, sweetheart?
Me?
Well, gee.
Do you charge by the inch
or by the hour?
- What?
- How do you price your art?
By its size, square footage,
or the time it takes to make...
...the art?
I've actually never sold a painting.
Excuse me, sir!
Please, sir. Excuse me, sir.
That's a club jacket you have on,
this is your jacket.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
- What are you doing here?
- Don't you want to paint me?
You've slept all day.
It's time to work.
- Do you want to do it right now?
- Mm-hm.
Okay.
How did you get in here?
They just let you in, huh?
It's not top-of-the-line security.
- Do you want me sitting or standing?
- Both. I mean, whatever.
Sitting.
I have to go. I have dinner
in one hour and I look a mess.
- What are you doing?
- You forgot your shoes.
What is it like not to feel anything?
Get the fuck out of here!
Say there was a little girl.
And from the time she could
understand, she was taught to fear.
Say she was taught to fear daylight.
She was taught it was her enemy,
that it would hurt her.
And then one sunny day...
...you ask her to go outside and play,
and she won't.
Can you be angry at her?
I knew that girl, saw the light
in her eyes. That's still what I see.
We are who we are.
People don't change.
Yeah, hold on.
- What is it? Yeah?
- Hi, Finn.
- Walter.
- I know.
Is this a bad time for you?
- I can...
- It's all right, come on in.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, come on in.
Thank you.
- What are you doing here?
- Estella said she posed for you.
And I...
...was curious. Wow!
- You're really good.
- I had a good subject.
Yeah, I'll say. She is incredible.
I've got to be insane, right?
- Why?
- To risk losing her.
God, look at that one!
Look at this.
And I still can't commit.
That's certifiable, right?
You don't look crazy to me.
I feel like a cliff diver
in Acapulco.
I'm right at the edge, I'm supposed
to leap, the tide is high...
...and I think your friend Estella
is trying to give me a little shove.
- What do you mean?
- You know, these, you...
It's her charming little version
of a wake-up call.
But, you know, I understand.
I'm dragging my feet.
I'm sorry you got pulled into this mess.
She doesn't want to hurt you.
In fact, I know that she
really cares about you. Really.
It's just who she is, you know?
But I love her.
I don't know. You know her longer
than I. Any advice for me?
What do you think I should do
about me and Estella?
I think you two are perfect together.
Well, thank you.
I should get out of your hair.
I appreciate your time.
You're really good. I look forward
to seeing your show.
Next week, I received a
postcard from Ms. Dinsmoor.
A beach with palm trees, it
said, "How's my little mouse doing?"
What were her plans for me?
Why was she promoting me?
What could her reason be, if not
to make me equal with Estella?
That same day,
I got a call from Ragno.
- Hello?
In here.
What do you think of the digs?
- It's cozy.
It's yours.
- What do you mean?
- You open in 10 weeks.
We can reschedule, if...
- No, I'll be ready.
You're moving here.
We've got food, paint, canvas.
Anything else, just ask Erica.
Do you know what I'd like? I'd like
some money. Some living expenses.
- I don't believe...
- Done.
- Anything else?
- Some publicity for my show.
No one's actually heard of you.
"Fisherman from the Gulf Coast
Lands on Manhattan's Art Scene"?
- My, aren't we media savvy.
- We learn.
Call Marion, she'll know.
- Toast in my absence, I'm late.
She's a barrel of laughs.
An artist dropped out,
she had to redo her schedules.
It's like someone wants
to turn this frog into a prince.
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
It appears as if I have
a fairy godmother.
Aren't you too old to believe
in fairy godmothers?
Whatever you say, Spider man.
"Ragno" means "spider" in Italian.
See you at your opening. "Ciao."
I was born again. Why not?
I had never asked for anything.
If Dinsmoor, the art world and
the world chose to adopt me...
... I could take it.
New York held it out, and I'd take it
and say thanks.
You would too.
I was an orphan, raised by my
sister Maggie and her boyfriend Joe.
Maggie took off
when I was still a kid.
Joe was a big drug smuggler.
Spent the '70s
in the Raiford Penitentiary.
I came home one day,
I found him dead on the couch.
He had OD'd.
They took the apartment away,
so I spent the next years in a car.
It wasn't that bad.
It was a big car, a '68 Riviera.
It's a miracle you survived.
- Do you like my paintings?
- Yeah.
Why don't you tell me
about this beauty right here.
That's some girl I knew
back in Florida.
I used to have a huge crush on her.
Now I can't even remember her name.
- This one looks a lot like the girl.
- It's the same girl. She grew up.
- And you don't remember her name?
- No.
Delicious. It's all coming
together, as I promised.
Finn frenzy! Imagine what will happen
when they see your wonderful work.
Your beloved per diem...
...and an invitation
to the Hamilton Museum benefit.
Toss that.
I killed a publicist for this.
It is the event.
Old money, new money, big money.
Everyone will be there,
including you.
Erica!
- These are Finn's new paintings.
- It's for you.
- If you don't like the portraits...
Don't jump.
Would you save me?
Not in this suit.
How are you?
Good. And you?
Pretty well.
Good-looking suit!
Good-looking day!
It is.
Seen "New York Magazine"?
Are you in it?
It's just a little piece. It's
nice. You didn't see it?
Thrall thinks that the show
will get good reviews.
I don't want to jinx it,
but what does she know?
The curator from the Whitney
came by. That was exciting.
Wow! I'll say I knew you when.
Listen.
What?
Walter asked me to marry him.
He wants to marry me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Why are you telling me this?
Because...
I just... I wanted to know
if you had anything to say.
Congratulations.
Sounds wonderful.
I wish you both the best of luck.
- I've got to go. I've got to...
- Finn.
- I've got some business.
- Finn, wait.
Why had she told me?
She told me to wound me,
or out of habit or to drive me mad.
I didn't care if it was a clue or it
was a plea or it was a tease.
No. She told me so I would stop her,
and of course I would.
Fashionably late. I have hordes
of people to meet you.
This is the senator.
Finn! Sorry, senator.
As the evening mists
Were rising
Finn! So good to see you.
A friend of mine is decorating...
- Have you seen Estella?
- No.
Very interested in getting
some art. Interested?
I wanted to call you.
Congratulations on your success.
You're all over the place.
The boy with the hands.
I saw your spread. Anton Le Farge.
Be nice to Anton,
he has a lot of empty wall space.
I'm taking my time.
You should get to Finn
while his rates are reasonable.
How did we say you should price
your art? Was it by canvas size or...?
By its beauty.
- There you are.
- I have to talk to you.
- We've got to go, we're late.
- We just got here.
We're to meet the Barrows
at Kelly and Ping's 10 minutes ago.
Good night, kids. Have fun.
Congratulations again, Finn.
This is the artist I was telling you
about. Senator Elwood, Finn Bell.
Thrall has told me
so much about you.
- What about my friend?
- Not now.
Thrall is a loser in this town,
I can introduce you to...
- Sorry.
- It's all relationships, isn't it?
Don't touch me.
Can I get you a taxi, sir?
Excuse me, sir. Sir! Sir!
Hey, Finn! This is Finn.
How do you do?
- Can I offer you a chair or a towel?
- Would you like to dance?
Do you know him?
Yes.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes.
I want you inside me.
I have to go home,
I owe my aunt a visit.
But you'll be back?
For your show? Of course.
I do love the way you dance.
Hi!
Congratulations!
- Have you seen Estella?
- I'll send her over when she arrives.
- Congratulations! Great job.
- It's wonderful, Finn.
- So...
- Look who's here.
- All your dreams come true?
- We'll see.
I want you to meet some people.
- Have you seen Estella?
- No.
There's a very important guy here,
Carter Macleish, he's a critic.
- Congratulations!
- Thanks.
Nice to see you!
We'll be right back. Thanks.
- Is Clemente here?
- Carter. Nice to see you.
- Finn Bell, Carter Macleish.
- Congratulations.
Ruth you know. It's a most impressive
show, wouldn't you say?
It is that!
Richard! Richard! Will you do
a photo of us? Carter, come on.
Finn! Finn!
What is that?
Do another one.
- I think you have a fan here.
- I'm sorry, will you excuse me?
Hey, Finn! How are you doing?
Surprise, surprise!
- What are you doing here?
- Where did you think I'd be?
I had to change in my car.
It's a rental tux, but what the hell.
It looks good.
Do you want to get a juice?
It's Jerry, huh? Hey, Jerry!
Jerry! You son of a bitch,
you weren't bullshitting, were you?
Erica Thrall,
my Uncle Joe.
Miss Thrall, hi. This is
your place, right? It's very nice.
- Carter Macleish.
- Are you also from Florida?
- Yes. I operate a fishing boat.
- This is Ruth.
- Hi.
- Hey, Ruth.
Hey!
Look at me!
Uncle Joe, the drug smuggler?
I thought you were dead.
- Drugs?
- No, she's thinking about...
No, I've been sober
for a good, long time now.
Carter can't believe
it's your first show.
- No, it's not.
- What do you mean?
Finn had a show at the Washington
Federal a couple of years ago.
- You know the Washington Federal?
- No.
- It's not a gallery.
- It's a bank. Savings and loan.
- A bank?
- This is my first gallery show.
And you're self-taught?
That was a gift.
Finn always had it.
Seven months old, his sister and I took
him to the beach. He drew in the sand.
One night he took Maggie's best
perfume and drew with it in the street.
He poured it all out,
and then he lit it...
Just up in flames. The most beautiful
designs you ever saw. Just...
- Are you all right?
That's my fault.
Your trousers, are they all right?
Just leave it, Joe.
Erica, it's fine.
Joe, just leave it!
I'm sor...
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, it's just...
Oh, man. Excuse me, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Joe. Joe!
Jeez, I'm...
Listen, I'm going to head out,
because I'm starving.
I'm going to find a McDonald's
or something and...
So you go back in, and I'm going
to talk to you later.
Joe! Come on, I mean...
Joe, listen. This is work.
Sure. Come on, I get it.
Finn.
You dazzle them.
Go ahead.
Jeez, I'm proud of you, Finn.
And I always have been.
So, just...
Finn!
Go see if they know
how to smoke a swordfish.
The night
all my dreams came true.
Like all happy endings it was
a tragedy, of my own device.
For I'd succeeded.
I'd cut myself loose...
... from Joe, from the past,
from the gulf, from poverty.
I had invented myself.
I had done it cruelly,
but I had done it. I was free.
I did it! I did it!
I am a wild success!
I showed them all! All my paintings.
You don't have to be embarrassed
by me anymore. I'm rich!
Isn't that what you wanted?
Isn't it great? Are we happy now?
Don't you understand that
everything I do, I do it for you?
Anything that might be
special in me is you.
Estella!
Finn! What a lovely surprise!
- What are you doing here?
- I own this house. I was born here.
- I haven't been here for ages.
- Where's Estella?
Since I had to come up for the event,
I figured, "Why not stay there?"
- What event? My opening?
- No. Estella's wedding.
- What?
- You were the catalyst.
The fool wouldn't commit to Estella,
but then you came on the scene.
- I don't believe it.
- Storybook, isn't it?
Why?
At first you were practice for her,
a teaching device.
Throw a mouse in with the snake,
teach it to hunt, swallow food whole.
I must say, you didn't provide
much of a challenge.
Now, now.
You enjoyed it.
And I warned you, years ago.
I didn't have to do that.
I told you the girl
would hurt you terribly. Didn't I?
You chose not to listen.
Well...
I suggest you look on the bright side.
We are together, joined.
You, Estella and I.
A pyramid of pain.
It's not love, but it is a bond.
We are together.
Give me your hand.
Do you know what this is?
It's my heart.
And it's broken.
Can you feel that?
I'm sorry.
What have I done?!
The girl, the money, fame, revenge.
They had been Dinsmoor's
sick obsessions.
And now they were mine.
He's not under the car, Jojo.
How are you?
- Who's this kid?
- Don't worry about him. Keep looking.
Hey!
Listen, listen.
Can I just talk one second?
Can I call the police on your
phone? Some armed guys are chasing me.
All right, come on.
Here you go.
Hello? There are some
armed gentlemen chasing me.
Could you send some police to...?
What's the address?
111 Greenwich.
111 Greenwich Street.
Arthur Lustig. Could you send them
as soon as you can, please?
Thanks. Arthur Lustig.
So the police are coming?
And these guys, they're after you?
This is a great place.
Are you an artist?
Yes, I am.
Tonight was my opening.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
What's your name?
Finnegan Bell.
- Like Finn?
- Exactly.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
I don't think so.
- You don't remember me, do you?
- No.
Look, I don't know...
Whisper! Whisper! Whisper!
That's right, my boy. It's me.
Look at you. Look at you!
You're all grown up.
Don't you want to know
what happened to me?
After I left you,
they caught me.
I escaped again, and I relocated...
...many years abroad.
Until now. Until now.
I'm glad things
worked out for you.
Fucking glad.
It's great.
Who's that handsome young man over
there? You did think about me!
You scared the shit out of me.
I like that. Yeah, I like that.
That's really good.
How much is it?
- Is it for sale?
- Actually, the whole show sold out.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks, I'm lucky.
No, you're not lucky.
You deserve your success.
You're a talented young man.
You're a fine artist.
Your whole...
This place is...
Might I ask a personal question?
- What does a place like this cost?
- The rent?
I don't know.
It's taken care of.
Oh, yeah? Could I ask who by?
- A lawyer. Why?
- No reason. I'm happy for you.
- Do you mind if I have a drink?
- The cops will be here any minute.
- They're always late.
- It is late.
- I'm sure you understand.
- Understand?
You're sure I would understand what?
The police
will be here any minute.
- No, they won't.
- They won't. Why not?
- I didn't call them.
- You didn't?
I pressed my finger on the button.
- Why?
- They're looking for me too.
They are?
And those guys down there?
Old associates. They have a beef about
something they should've figured out.
- You should leave.
- Let me finish my drink.
Just give me a minute.
It's so good to see you.
You don't know how happy it makes me
to see how you've turned out.
You grew up. Little Finn.
You're a grownup.
You're a man now.
A famous artist.
You live this life.
Mix with all kinds of
interesting people.
I'm very impressed, and nobody
deserves it better than you.
I remember when you were a little
kid. A good-hearted little kid.
Little Finn.
The one person who did a really
pure and good thing for me.
Congratulations on your success,
on your show, on everything.
To you.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
I do.
It's just that... the truth is,
it's making me really uncomfortable.
Would you mind?
I don't want you feeling badly.
I just came to see you, say hello.
Now I'm happy.
If it was another night, we...
This is great.
This is the way it should be.
Ragno did a good job.
Hey. Hey.
Don't go down there. Those guys
are there. There's a better way.
You know where you're headed?
JFK.
So where are you going?
Paris, city of lights.
Come with me to Paris.
I'll get a ticket on the Concorde.
I can't go to France.
You will love Paris.
I love Paris in the springtime
I love Paris in the fall
Paris is a beautiful city, a
city of culture, a magnificent city.
It's got elegance, beauty.
You gotta go to Paris.
You won't regret it.
Every artist must go to Paris
at least once.
The streets, the romance,
the women. The women...
- You should come.
- I can't go to France.
Do you hear that shrieking?
The subway's wheels...
- Is that you? Arthur!
- You look like Howard Hughes.
- Have you been on a desert island?
- I've been on vacation.
You're heavier.
I got fat. I got kids too.
Age catches up with you.
Arthur, Tommy wants to invite
you to the club for old time's sake.
- Give me Tommy's number...
- We'll come over.
- All right, two minutes.
We're coming there, Arthur.
We'll wait right here.
Come on!
What are you doing there?
You told me to come over here.
I thought you wanted me
to come over here.
Tommy's not going to like this.
Come here!
Sorry, guys.
You have this much fun
with your artist friends?
- Is this fun? You're having fun?
- Are you going to miss me?
- Why don't you come?
- I can't go to Paris.
I love Paris in the springtime
I love Paris in the...
No, no, I'm not hurt.
- You're hurt bad.
- Stay, stay. Attaboy.
Oh, jeez.
I did a lot of bad things in my life.
A lot of bad things.
But the one good thing...
...is that any money I had,
anything I had...
...and I made bullshit money,
I gave to you.
All for you.
The one good thing I did...
I set you up, I sent you to New York.
I did it all.
- I bought that show.
- All my paintings?
You're a great artist.
Open up my suitcase.
Open my suitcase.
What do you want?
Pull out the paper bag.
Pull it back. That's it.
Remember this?
See this?
Very special.
Look at this.
It's beautiful.
- What time is it?
- It's almost 6:00.
We've still got time.
Perhaps he should have died
those years ago back in the gulf.
Perhaps.
But he'd lived to be my benefactor.
For good and ill.
I went to Paris, worked there...
... and received everything
I thought I wanted.
I heard about Estella from
time to time. She was divorced.
The years went by.
And then one day, I went home.
Hi. I'm Finn.
Joe!
You dog! You dog. Why didn't you
tell us you were coming?
- Who is he?
- This is Jesse and Clemma.
And you came in time to do the
dishes. Are you hungry?
Joe told me Ms. Dinsmoor
had died alone some years back.
Her body lay there
undiscovered for a month.
The mansion was due to be
torn down for a housing tract.
I sat there and thought back
over the things I'd done.
Over my life.
And where, in that brief,
violent time, it had gone.
And then, she came back again.
Estella?
Finn?
Is that you?
Is that your little girl?
Oh, God.
She's beautiful.
What are you doing here?
I brought her
to show her this place.
What's left of it.
- Have you been here often?
- No.
No, me neither.
So, you're doing great.
I hear all about you.
I'm doing all right.
Yeah.
Things have been different for me.
For a long time I'd get...
What?
I think about you.
A lot lately.
I'm glad.
Can you ever forgive me?
Don't you know me at all?
She did know me.
And I knew her.
I always had, from the first instant.
And the rest of it, it didn't matter.
It was past.
It was as if it had never been.
There was just my memory of it.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org