[eerie music]
♪
[answering machine beeps]
- HI, SWEETIE.
UM, WHERE ARE YOU GUYS?
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THIS.
♪
[answering machine beeps]
HI, IT'S ME AGAIN.
YOUR CELL'S GOING STRAIGHT
TO VOICEMAIL.
HOPE EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
PLEASE CALL.
[heart pounding]
♪
[answering machine beeps]
SARA.
A-ARE YOU THERE?
PLEASE, PICK UP, SWEETIE.
SARA.
[heart pounding]
[soft piano music]
♪
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
[ominous music]
♪
[clock ticking]
[water dripping]
[cat meows]
[telephone rings]
[answering machine beeps]
both:
HELLO!
- SARA...
- FRANK...
both: AND ADAM
AREN'T HERE AT THE MOMENT.
- BUT PLEASE LEAVE YOUR NAME
AND NUMBER AFTER THE BEEP.
[answering machine beeps]
- HI, SWEETIE.
HOPE YOUR DATE NIGHT WENT WELL.
WE HAD A FUN NIGHT HERE.
ADAM LOVES WATCHING
ALL THE CARS
PASSING BY THE CONDO.
LISTEN, I CALLED
MY DOCTOR FRIEND,
AND SHE'S NOT SURE IF ADAM'S
GETTING ENOUGH PROTEIN.
HE LOOKS VERY PALE.
AND HARDLY ANY BABY FAT.
OH, BY THE WAY,
I TRIED CALLING YOUR CELL,
BUT I KEPT GETTING
A BUSY SIGNAL.
IT'S PROBABLY BAD RECEPTION.
OH, SWEETIE, WE REALLY MISS YOU.
I HOPE YOU CAN STAY FOR LUNCH
WHEN YOU COME TO PICK UP ADAM
TOMORROW MORNING.
I KNOW YOUR FATHER WILL WANT
TO SPEND TIME WITH HIS DAUGHTER.
ANYWAY, GIVE ME A CALL
WHEN YOU GET HOME
IF IT'S NOT TOO LATE, OKAY?
LOVE YOU.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU, HONEY.
[answering machine beeps]
[clock ticking]
[keys jingling]
[locks clicking]
[alarm beeping]
[buttons beep]
[cat meows]
[ominous music]
[cat purring]
♪
[clock ticking]
[crowd roaring on TV]
[sportscaster speaking
indistinctly]
[TV shuts off]
♪
- HERE'S MY TWO FAVORITE PEOPLE
IN THE WHOLE, WIDE WORLD.
- LOOK, ADAM, IT'S DADDY.
SAY HI TO DADDY!
- ADAM, BABY,
CAN YOU SAY "DA-DA"?
DA-DA?
[laughs]
AND HERE'S MY GORGEOUS WIFE.
- AW.
- THOSE BEAUTIFUL EYES
I WAKE UP TO EVERY SING--
♪
[glass bottles clatter]
- [sighs]
[door creaks]
[bouncy music plays]
♪
[mobile clacking]
[lullaby music plays]
♪
[ominous music]
[lullaby music plays]
[liquid splashing]
[telephone rings]
[answering machine beeps]
both:
HELLO!
- SARA...
- FRANK...
both: AND ADAM
AREN'T HERE AT THE MOMENT.
- BUT PLEASE LEAVE YOUR NAME
AND NUMBER AFTER THE BEEP.
[answering machine beeps]
- SARA MCANDREWS,
THIS IS DEPUTY SANDERS CALLING
FROM THE COUNTY SHERRIFF'S
OFFICE.
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
MY APOLOGIES FOR CALLING
SO LATE.
IT'S BEEN ONE OF THOSE DAYS,
AND WE'RE SEVERELY UNDERSTAFFED.
SO REGARDING THIS TRESPASSER
YOU SAW ON YOUR PROPERTY
THIS MORNING,
REST ASSURED,
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST A DRIFTER
PASSING THROUGH.
IN ANY CASE,
I'LL DROP BY TOMORROW,
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S
ALL RIGHT, AND...
WELL, I'LL HAVE ONE
OF THOSE DELICIOUS BROWNIES
THAT EVERYONE'S
BEEN TALKING ABOUT.
WE'RE HERE FOR YOUR SAFETY,
OKAY?
HOPE YOU FOLKS HAVE
A GREAT NIGHT.
[stairs creaking]
[ominous music]
♪
[clock ticking]
[drill buzzing]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[drill buzzing]
[buttons beep]
[ominous music]
♪
[suspenseful music]
[ominous music]
♪
[cat meows]
[vehicle approaching]
- HEY, HONEY.
- WHAT?
- YOU KNOW, NEXT TIME WE GO OUT,
WOULD YOU MIND JUST LEAVING
ONE LIGHT ON?
- NO, IT'S SUPPOSED TO LOOK
LIKE WE'RE HOME.
- YEAH, BUT, LIKE, WE DIDN'T
MOVE IN TO A LIGHTHOUSE.
- YEAH, YOU'RE FUNNY.
SUCH A JOKESTER.
- AM I?
- YEAH.
- I'M NOT AS FUNNY
AS WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL
THAT DANCE THING THING
YOU MADE ME SIT THROUGH.
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT WAS AWFUL.
- OH, COME ON.
IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
- IT WAS HORRIBLE.
- WHAT?
ARE YOU ALWAYS THIS DIFFICULT?
NO, I THOUGHT IT WAS
REALLY BEAUTIFUL, AND...
- [sighs]
- YOU ARE A PHILISTINE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
IT INVOLVES A LOT MORE SKILL
THAN ONE OF YOUR FOOTBALL GAMES.
- AS IN, A GAGGLE
OF HAIRLESS MEN
RUNNING AROUND,
ROLLING ON TOP OF ONE ANOTHER,
ON A LARGE STEEL TABLE--
- YEAH, EXACTLY.
- NAKED, HAIRLESS MEN?
- NO, MEN TAKEN OVER
BY THE SPIRIT OF DANCE.
AND THEY WEREN'T ALL HAIRLESS.
- UGH, PLEASE.
NOW I CAN'T EAT
IN THE CAFETERIA ANYMORE.
- WHY?
- BECAUSE THEY JUST INSTALLED
THE EXACT SAME KIND OF TABLE.
- OH, NO.
- I'M GONNA BE OBSESSING
OVER EVERY LITTLE STAIN
ON THE THING.
- WELL, MAYBE
IN BETWEEN MEETINGS,
YOU AND TONY CAN TRY IT OUT.
- [laughs]
- YOU TWO WOULD MAKE
A TERRIFIC DUO.
- OH, GOD.
- [laughs]
I'D DEFINITELY PAY
TO SEE THAT.
YOU GUYS WOULD PROBABLY DRAW
QUITE THE CROWD
IF WE DIDN'T LIVE
IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
- SWEETHEART, YOU KNOW...
OUR SON'S GONNA THANK YOU
FOR IT LATER.
HE'LL TELL YOU
IN HIS DEEP, MANLY VOICE--
HE'LL SAY, "THANKS, MA.
"THANKS FOR FOLLOWING PA
TO THE COUNTRYSIDE.
"I'M A LUCKY BOY, YOU KNOW?
"I CAN SEE THAT NOW.
I LEARNED
WHAT IT WAS LIKE TO"--
- LIVE LIKE A PEASANT.
- [laughs]
"TO BREATH THE FRESH AIR,
"YOU KNOW, TO RIDE MY BIKE
IN THE FOREST,
"TO BE ABLE TO PRACTICE
MY FOOTBALL SKILLS
"IN MY HUGE BACKYARD
WITHOUT BEING BOTHERED
BY THE RIFFRAFF FROM YOUR OLD
DISGUSTING NEIGHBORHOOD."
- MM.
- HEY.
NOTHING BEATS A REAL HOME.
NOW, WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THAT,
CITY GIRL?
- MM.
- HMM?
- I SAY THAT I NEED
A GLASS OF MILK.
- ALL RIGHT.
- [gasps]
- WHOOPS.
- HONEY, COULD YOU PLEASE CHECK
THE MESSAGES?
[answering machine beeps]
- TWO NEW MESSAGES.
- HI, SWEETIE.
HOPE YOUR DATE NIGHT WENT WELL.
WE HAD A FUN NIGHT.
OH, ADAM LOVES WATCHING
ALL THE CARS
PASSING BY THE CONDO.
LISTEN, I CALLED
MY DOCTOR FRIEND--
- SURE YOU DID.
- AND SHE'S NOT SURE IF ADAM'S
GETTING ENOUGH PROTEIN.
HE LOOKS VERY PALE.
AND HARDLY ANY BABY FAT.
OH, BY THE WAY,
I TRIED CALLING YOUR CELL,
BUT I KEPT GETTING
A BUSY SIGNAL.
IT'S PROBABLY BAD RECEPTION.
OH, SWEETIE, WE REALLY MISS YOU.
I HOPE YOU CAN STAY FOR LUNCH
WHEN YOU COME TO PICK UP ADAM
TOMORROW MORNING.
I KNOW YOUR FATHER WILL WANT
TO SPEND TIME WITH HIS DAUGHTER.
ANYWAY, GIVE ME A CALL
WHEN YOU GET HOME
IF IT'S NOT TOO LATE, OKAY?
- CRITTERS.
- LOVE YOU.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU, HONEY.
- [groans]
WHAT AM I, CHOPPED LIVER?
- SARA MCANDREWS,
THIS IS DEPUTY SANDERS CALLING
FROM THE COUNTY SHERRIFF'S
OFFICE.
I GOT YOUR MESSAGE.
MY APOLOGIES FOR CALLING
SO LATE--
[answering machine beeps]
- YOU KNOW--
S-SHE CAN'T HELP HERSELF,
CAN SHE, RIGHT?
SHE HAS TO FIND SOMETHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
NO, SHE IS THE ONE
THAT NEEDS TO SEE A DOCTOR,
'CAUSE SHE ALWAYS WANTS US
TO FEEL GUILTY
OR WORRIED ABOUT SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, BUT I--
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT SHE'S TRYING TO DO.
SHE CAN'T STAND
THAT HER LITTLE ANGEL
IS NOW INDEPENDENT
AND SO FAR AWAY FROM HER.
YOU KNOW, T-TOMORROW--
[gasps]
- MM.
TOMORROW, TOMORROW, TOMORROW.
TONIGHT IS JUST YOU AND ME...
- MM-HMM.
- ALONE.
SO WHY DON'T YOU STOP TALKING?
- MMM.
[laughs]
HONEY.
- WHAT?
- I HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
- WHAT'S HER NAME?
- SERIOUSLY?
WHAT'S HER NAME?
WHY DON'T YOU GO SERVE ME
SOMETHING TO DRINK
INSTEAD OF BEING SUCH A PERV.
[telephone beeps]
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
HE'S OKAY.
- SHE SAID HE WAS FINE, BABY.
DON'T WORRY SO MUCH.
I'M YOUR BABY TONIGHT.
- [laughs]
BABY, I REALLY HAVE
TO HAVE A SHOWER.
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST STAY HERE
AND MAINTAIN YOUR CONCENTRATION?
- CAN I SPY ON YOU
IN THE SHOWER?
- DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
[line beeping]
[sighs]
[ominous music]
♪
[acoustic bluesy guitar plays]
- ♪ I KNOW SHE WILL
♪ I'M SURE SHE WILL ♪
♪
♪ I KNOW SHE WILL
♪ OH, YES SHE WILL
♪ I'M SURE SHE WILL ♪
♪
- CRITTERS?
- ♪ WHEN I PUT MY ARMS
- KITTY.
[smooches]
[cat meows]
- ♪ ARMS AROUND HER
♪ YOU HEAR HER HOLLER
♪ YOU HEAR HER MOAN
[cat meows]
♪ I KNOW SHE WILL
♪ WHOA, YES SHE WILL
- CRITTERS.
CRITTERS, COME HERE.
OOH.
GOOD LITTLE BABY.
♪
ARE YOU POUTING?
- ♪ I'M SURE SHE WILL ♪
♪ LET ME COME BACK HOME
♪
♪ I KNOW SHE WILL
♪ I'M SURE SHE WILL ♪
- FRANK.
♪
- [over phone]
HELLO?
- HI, MOM.
DID I WAKE YOU?
- OH, NO, HONEY, HI.
I'M UP.
- SO HOW'S ADAM?
- SLEEPING LIKE A BABY.
- ♪ HOME LATE
♪ OH, I JUST MAY
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY WE'RE ALWAYS HAVING
THIS CONVERSATION.
- DID YOU CALL THE POLICE?
- [sighs]
YES.
I LEFT A MESSAGE
FOR THE SHERRIFF.
- LEFT A MESSAGE?
WHAT KIND OF GODFORSAKEN PLACE
DID YOU MOVE TO?
LISTEN, MAKE SURE
THE DOORS ARE LOCKED.
- YEP, THEY ARE LOCKED,
AND ALL OF THE LIGHTS ARE ON.
- AND HOW ABOUT THAT HUSBAND
OF YOURS?
IS HE DOING ANYTHING
ABOUT IT?
- WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- WELL, HE'S YOUR HUSBAND,
ISN'T HE?
- LOOK, MOM, HE IS DOING
THE BEST THAT HE CAN.
♪
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING.
I'M NOT EVEN SURE
THAT I SAW WHAT I SAW.
- HONEY, IF YOU DON'T FEEL SAFE
OVER THERE,
YOU'LL ALWAYS HAVE A PLACE HERE.
YOU CAN STAY WITH US AS LONG
AS YOU LIKE, OKAY?
- OKAY.
I'VE BEEN REALLY TIRED LATELY,
SO I'M GONNA GO AND SLEEP
FOR 100 YEARS.
- OH, YOU DO THAT,
SLEEPING BEAUTY.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING.
- MM-HMM.
GIVE ADAM A KISS FOR ME.
- DON'T WORRY.
I WILL.
SWEET DREAMS, DARLING.
LOVE YOU.
- NIGHT.
- ♪ I KNOW SHE WILL
♪ OH, YES SHE WILL
♪ LET ME COME BACK HOME
- GLAD TO KNOW
I CAN STILL SURPRISE YOU.
- WELL, I DIDN'T HEAR YOU.
- A VOTRE SERVICE, MADAME.
- OH.
WOW, I DIDN'T REALIZE
THE WAITERS AROUND HERE
HAD SUCH CASUAL UNIFORMS.
- WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT HELPS ME MAINTAIN
MY CONCENTRATION.
- MM.
- OH, AND BY THE WAY,
IS IT POSSIBLE
THAT MY SURPRISE IS WAITING
IN THE BEDROOM?
- YOU LITTLE SHIT.
YOU'RE GONNA TOTALLY RUIN
YOUR SURPRISE.
- COME ON.
COME HERE.
- NO.
- OH, JUST GIVE ME ONE KISS.
- I DESERVE IT.
- MM-MM.
GET LOST.
- LET ME COME IN.
- GO.
- OH, I GET IT.
I GET IT.
YOU NEED TO PRACTICE, UH,
YOUR CHOREOGRAPHY, RIGHT?
OKAY, JUST REMEMBER THAT IT'S
F-R-A-N-K.
- THAT'S REALLY FUNNY, BABE.
- I'M GONNA GO OUT
IN THE LIVING ROOM
AND REARRANGE THE FURNITURE,
OKAY?
YOU KNOW, I'M GONNA MOVE THINGS
AROUND.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON, KITTEN.
- ♪ EVERYWHERE I GO
[water spraying]
♪ YEAH, EVERYWHERE I GO
♪
♪ I SEE THAT SAME OLD 158
♪ I KNOW I'M BILLED OUT, BABY ♪
♪ WHOO, LORD
♪ UNCLE SAM SAY,
"BILL, DON'T BE LATE" ♪
♪
♪ YES, I'VE GOT
MY QUESTIONNAIRE, BABE ♪
♪ AND I FOUND THAT
OLD NUMBER OF MINE ♪
♪
♪ NOW
♪ I GUESS I WELL
TO START MOVING ♪
♪ OOH, BABY
♪ THERE AIN'T NO NEED
OF CRYING ♪
♪
♪ ALL YOU YOUNG MEN
♪ I MEAN, COME ON
AND FOLLOW ME ♪
♪
[ominous music]
[bluesy music playing]
♪ YES, ALL YOU YOUNG MEN
[ominous music]
[knocks at door]
- GO AWAY.
♪
[knocks at door]
GO AWAY.
♪ LORD, WHOO
♪ LORD, NOW, BOYS,
WHY CAN'T WE? ♪
♪
[upbeat bluesy music]
♪ I HAD A WOMAN
♪ I HAD A BROKEN HEART
♪ EVEN THOUGH I WISH
SHE'D TELL ME ♪
♪ WHAT THAT WOMAN LEFT ME FOR
♪ THAT'S WHAT I BEEN WONDERIN' ♪
♪ I BEEN WONDERIN'
ALL DAY LONG ♪
♪
♪ MAYBE I WILL HAVE
TO WONDER ON ♪
♪ AND I'LL TRY ♪
♪ TO MAKE ME FEEL GOOD
♪ SAY MY GAL WOULD BE GOOD
♪ IF SHE JUST ONLY
UNDERSTOOD-- ♪
♪ UNDERSTOOD--
[ominous music]
♪
- WHAT THE FUCK?
[coughing]
[gasping]
♪
[coughing]
S-SARA.
[gurgles]
- CAN YOU TURN THE MUSIC
BACK ON, HONEY?
FRANK.
UGH...
BETTER NOT BE ASLEEP.
[lighter clicking]
AAH.
OH, SHIT.
[cat meows]
CRITTERS.
[cat meowing]
♪
FRANK?
HONEY?
♪
FRANK?
[lullaby music playing]
♪
[screaming]
[groaning]
[taser crackles]
♪
[drill buzzing in distance]
[drill buzzing]
[soft room tone]
[crowd roaring on TV]
[ominous music]
♪
[whimpering]
[straining]
[straining over monitor]
[buzzer sounds on TV]
[groans]
FRANK!
[screams]
[sobbing over monitor]
FRANK!
[screaming]
[gasping]
[muffled screams]
[gagging over monitor]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[coughing]
[whimpering]
[gasping]
[sobbing]
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS TO US?
WHAT DID YOU DO TO MY HUSBAND?
I'M SORRY.
I'LL CALM DOWN.
I PROMISE.
[sobbing]
WHERE'S MY HUSBAND?
I WANT TO SEE HIM.
PLEASE.
LET ME SEE MY HUSBAND.
[ominous music]
♪
[metal jangling]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[strains]
- [screams]
[screams]
- [sobbing]
FRANK!
[groans]
[sobbing]
FRANK!
[metal jangling]
[groans]
WHAT THE FUCK DO YOU WANT
WITH US?
YOU FUCKING PSYCHO!
I'M GONNA FUCKING KILL YOU.
[sobbing]
WHAT DID YOU DO TO MY HUSBAND?
[screams]
[ominous music]
♪
[gasps]
[gasping]
[camera beeping]
[doorbell rings]
- SHH.
- MR. MCANDREWS?
M.T.S. SECURITY.
ARE YOU THERE?
[knocks at door]
HELLO?
MR. MCANDREWS?
[knocks at door]
THE SILENT ALARM WAS ACTIVATED.
MR.--
MR. MCANDREWS, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
I JUST STOPPED BY TO CHECK
AND MAKE SURE EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
HELLO?
ANYBODY HOME?
[knocks at door]
MR. MCANDREWS!
I CAN SEE YOUR LIGHTS ARE ON.
ARE YOU HOME?
YEAH, I AM MISSING
THE END OF THE GAME FOR THIS.
MR. MCANDREWS!
[flashlight tapping]
[dialing phone]
[phone vibrating]
- [groans]
- GOOD EVENING, MR. MCANDREWS.
M.T.S. SECURITY HERE.
YEAH, YOUR SILENT ALARM
WAS ACTIVATED,
AND I AM CURRENTLY
ON THE PREMISES...
AT YOUR DOOR, ACTUALLY.
[metal jangling]
YEAH, WELL, I'VE CHECKED
AROUND THE HOUSE,
AND EVERYTHING SEEMS FINE.
I WILL HAVE TO NOTIFY
THE LOCAL POLICE, HOWEVER.
THAT'S A STANDARD PROCEDURE
WHENEVER WE'RE CALLED OUT
FOR NO GOOD REASON, SO...
IF YOU COULD PLEASE GET IN TOUCH
WITH US.
- [gasping]
- YOU GO AHEAD AND HAVE YOURSELF
A GOOD EVENING...
WHEREVER YOU ARE, ASSHOLE.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[car turns over]
- [sobbing]
WAIT.
- [breathing heavily]
[phone beeping]
[breathing heavily]
[door slams]
♪
[electronic beeping]
[inhales deeply]
[phone beeping]
[line ringing]
- YOU HAVE REACHED THE KING
COUNTY SHERIFF'S DEPARTMENT.
ALL DEPUTIES
ARE CURRENTLY ON PATROL.
- PLEASE,
SOMEBODY'S IN MY HOUSE.
HE'S TRYING TO KILL ME.
- PLEASE HOLD AS WE ATTEMPT
TO TRANSFER YOUR CALL
TO THE OFFICER ON DUTY.
- ARE YOU FUCKING SERIOUS?
- 555-8699.
[footsteps creaking]
[line ringing]
[shuffling footsteps]
[footsteps receding]
[line ringing]
- DEPUTY SANDERS HERE.
- HELLO?
- HELLO.
- HELLO, THIS IS SARA,
SARA MCANDREWS.
- OH, HEY, MRS. MCANDREWS.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU GOT MY MESSAGE EARLIER--
- HE'S IN THE HOUSE.
- 'SCUSE ME?
- HE'S IN MY HOUSE.
- SAY AGAIN.
- SOMEONE HERE IS
TRYING TO KILL ME.
- I'M SORRY.
MA'AM, TRY TO REMAIN CALM.
WHO IS TRYING TO KILL YOU?
- I DON'T KNOW.
A FUCKING PSYCHO.
- MCANDREWS, ARE YOU ABLE
TO GET SOMEWHERE SAFE?
- HE'S BLOCKED OUT
ALL THE EXITS.
I DON'T KNOW IF WE CAN GET OUT.
HE'S GONNA FIND ME.
MISS MCANDREWS,
I NEED YOU TO TELL ME
EXACTLY WHERE YOU ARE.
WHERE IS YOUR FAMILY?
- FRANK IS DEAD.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M ON MY WAY, MA'AM.
[phone crackling and spitting]
- GONNA DIE.
[sighs]
- ARE YOU IN A SAFE PLACE,
MRS. MCANDREWS?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU--
SPEAK UP.
- HELLO?
[crackling]
[phone beeps]
FUCK!
♪
[door slams]
[rapid footsteps]
[rustling]
[step creaking]
[plastic rustling]
[tape rasping]
- [gasps]
♪
[plastic squealing]
[key tinkles]
[dragging and thumping]
[clicking]
[clattering and banging]
[ball bouncing]
[clattering]
[abrupt silence]
- HERE'S MY TWO FAVORITE PEOPLE
IN THE WHOLE, WIDE WORLD.
- LOOK AT HIM!
IT'S DADDY!
SAY HI TO DADDY!
- ADAM, BABY,
CAN YOU SAY, "DA-DA"?
DA-DA?
HERE'S MY GORGEOUS WIFE.
- AW.
[ball bouncing]
- THOSE BEAUTIFUL EYES
I WAKE UP TO
EVERY SINGLE MORNING.
I AM THE LUCKIEST MAN.
- [gasps]
- I LOVE YOU, BABY GIRL.
- I LOVE YOU MORE.
- I WANT YOU.
- [laughs]
- LET ME KNOW IF--
- IT IS.
TURN IT OFF.
TURN OFF THE CAMERA.
- HERE'S MY TWO FAVORITE PEOPLE
IN THE WHOLE, WIDE WORLD.
- LOOK AT HIM!
IT'S DADDY!
SAY HI TO DADDY!
[panting]
[yelps]
[wheezes]
[gun clattering]
AAH!
[yelps]
[banging]
[yelling]
LEAVE ME ALONE!
[clattering]
GO AWAY!
STOP IT!
[banging]
[shrieks]
[sobs]
PLEASE.
I CALLED THE POLICE!
[silence]
I CALLED THE POLICE.
[drill buzzing]
[rattling and banging]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[door creaking]
[soft piano music]
♪
[wind chimes tinkling]
[softly sobbing]
[moaning]
[gasping]
[coughing]
[moans]
[wheezes]
[wheezing]
[sobbing]
- [breathing heavily]
- [sobbing]
- I HAD A LOVELY TIME.
[gunshot]
[gurgling]
[wheezing]
- [panting]
[phone beeping]
[line ringing]
- YOU HAVE REACHED THE KING
COUNTY SHERIFF'S DEPARTMENT.
ALL DEPUTIES
ARE CURRENTLY ON PATROL.
PLEASE HOLD AS WE ATTEMPT
TO TRANSFER YOUR CALL
TO THE OFFICER ON DUTY.
FOR ALL MEDICAL EMERGENCIES,
DIAL 555-8699.
[line ringing]
[phone vibrating]
- [gasping]
- [shrieks]
[classical choral music]
♪
- [gurgles]
[wheezing]
[grunts]
[panting]
[wheezing]
[gunshots]
[grunting and wheezing]
[gurgles]
[grunts]
[chimes tinkling]
SANDERS.
IT'S SANDERS.
MICHAEL--
I BEEN--
I BEEN SHOT.
I WENT TO MCANDREWS HOUSE.
YOU GOT TO GET OUT HERE.
WE GOT TWO VICTIMS DOWN.
IT'S A HUSBAND AND WIFE.
GET AN AMBULANCE OUT HERE
RIGHT AWAY.
THE PERPETRATOR'S MALE.
6'1".
[bluesy music]
♪
- ♪ I'M THE NIGHT WATCHMAN ♪
♪ AND I DON'T BE SEEN
IN THE DAY ♪
♪ I'M THE NIGHT WATCHMAN ♪
♪ AND I DON'T BE SEEN
IN THE DAY ♪
♪ I DECLARE
I DO MY WORK AT NIGHT ♪
♪ WHOO, LORD, AND I DECLARE
I'M HAPPY AND GAY ♪
♪ 'ROUND FACTORIES
AND SAW MILLS ♪
♪ BABE, YOU'LL ALWAYS SEE
ME THERE ♪
♪ YEAH, BABY
♪ I DECLARE
YOU'LL ALWAYS SEE ME THERE ♪
♪ NOW, DON'T BE SCARED
TO CALL ME ♪
♪ WHOO, LORD, GAL, I GOT PLENTY
OF TIME TO SPARE ♪
♪ I'M KNOWN IN THIS COUNTRY ♪
♪ TO BE THE BEST
NIGHT WATCHMAN IN TOWN ♪
♪ MMM
♪ I DECLARE I'M THE BEST
NIGHT WATCHMAN IN TOWN ♪
♪ NOW, IF YOU'LL CLOCK ME
PUNCH IN ♪
♪ WHOO, LORD I'LL PUNCH IN
ON MY NEXT GO ROUND ♪
♪ I'VE GOT
A LOT OF COMPETITION ♪
♪ BABY, BUT I CAN'T LOSE ♪
♪ YEAH, LOT OF COMPETITION
♪ NO, BUT I DECLARE
I CAN'T LOSE ♪
♪ I KNOW I'VE GOT TO WIN ♪
♪ WHOO, LORD, I DECLARE
WITH THIS KEY I USE ♪
♪ I MAKES IT AROUND
♪ TO MY CLOCKS, BABY,
EVERY NIGHT ♪
♪ I MAKES IT AROUND
♪ I'M MEAN TO MY CLOCKS
EVERY NIGHT ♪
♪ I DECLARE I LOVE
TO PUNCH CLOCKS, BABY ♪
♪ WHOO, LORD, WHEN THE MOON
IS SHINING BRIGHT ♪
♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org