Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Shit.
Hey.
Are late, is the
second time this week.
- Not so bad.
- Yes, you better come quickly.
The game is tonight
and we are already late.
Realized.
Hello
Forgive me for being so late.
He was my teacher
psychology.
- Yes?
- Yes, said the research work ...
... It was the best he had seen.
It's about baby mice or chimpanzees.
Chimpanzee babies.
Hey, seriously, I would be surprised
than they are capable.
Not so pretty
like people.
Tell me.
Okay?
You know I'm still
worried about it?
Actually, I wanted to go. This is part
very important in the ritual of the sport.
How can I change this?
Elizabeth.
Hello, I thought it was you.
- Hello, Mike.
- Eddy.
Where are you two?
Let the town's Mike
spend the weekend
is a return weekend
at home, so we ...
The team does not need you, Mike?
Just for the weekend ... asshole.
Right.
Oh, did I say that.
There is a feast
of charities,
wondered if he could come.
Oh, that bad.
In fact, we'll be out
the whole weekend, so ...
Great, it's an honor, man.
Yes, we're already late, so ...
So ... I see you Monday,
okay?
Right.
Welcome to MT. Bliss. City
the State Champion Tigers
Shelby.
- Can I talk to you a second?
- I'm a little busy.
It only takes a minute.
Honey, do it all the more enjoyable
possible, but you have to collaborate.
You just have to trust that I will pay.
I think, really, but the bank
need to see some progress.
I said I'll give the bank
... and I will.
It is now ...
Look, I'ma tell you one thing.
I'll talk about it with the bank tomorrow?
Okay, Shelby.
Really need to go there this time.
Sorry is that ...
I can not stand aqule type.
What the hell have you seen him?
Obviously not enough.
55th
What about you and your ex-girlfriend?
What was his name?
Shelby?
An ancient history.
No need to worry about it.
Okay.
I was just checking.
Hello, Billy.
Hello, Shel.
So, suppose that Mickey will
the game tonight.
He is spending the weekend.
Really? I do not know.
Do not be jealous.
You know? I know not seen since
he came home last year,
but will have to wait,
because it's my turn.
I thought you had finished.
Yes, we have not seen since
school, but ...
... I still think we can continue,
when it comes to the team and all that.
I wish I had
a girl like that.
Whatever is to have a girl like that.
That is true.
Do I get early, we
press conference.
Okay.
Tigers in front.
Yes, in front Tigers.
We have a celebrity in the stadium.
Oh, my God.
- Relax.
- It's great to see you.
- Hey, Billy.
- Hello
And you should be ...
No, no, no.
Do not tell me.
Sara Elizabeth Mitchum. Born in 1988,
in Illinois. A brother, a sister.
- It's amazing.
- But scary.
No, I have to read the files.
See who's going out with my cousin.
Satisfy me that there is a mad
or whatever.
Elizabeth, this is my cousin Billy.
- Nice to know.
- Also.
There is food, I will get
Another thing, okay?
- OK
- Right.
It's beautiful.
Just wanted to see you before the Shelby.
I think she thinks
are still together.
What? C'mon
she was joking.
No, no.
No kidding.
She talks about you all the time.
Very healthy.
- Why do not you sit down?
- Yes
Actually, the whole pizza?
- OK, open your wallet ...
- It's so cool.
He is the greatest.
Always wanted to be like him.
- Yes?
- Yes
If it had been in
championship game ...
... had lost.
Hey, Mike. How's life?
My brother goes into
basketball team.
- Oh yeah?
- Yes, of course.
- Now still real serious?
- Of course it should be, Mike?
Now that is not angry.
I do not want to embarrass him
in front of his girlfriend.
Suffice it to say.
Are you sure you want to come?
Maybe go home.
What? At the restaurant?
Yes, come on.
I want to know their friends.
Why can not we go?
See you there.
Come on.
What?
Sta You okay?
Yes.
What's happening?
Nothing, no problem. Just ...
Contact Mickey.
Well, why do not you know
want to go to Alley, is because,
is the restaurant of my ex-girlfriend.
She is the owner.
Well, his family had,
and now it's her.
Are the owners of the Alley?
Yes.
Well I think ...
Billy told me that she still
think we're together.
Why does she think that?
Me've no idea,
do not talk to her for months.
This is bizarre.
It's not a bad person,
it just ...
It's a little bit ... Just ... It's intense.
And you?
Look, I understand that.
Do not worry about it.
I've had problems before.
I'll behave.
Hello Mike.
Shelby has not seen it?
She'll be so excited,
're always talking about you.
Hello
She's back there,
You should go talk to her.
It's probably a good idea.
I'll see Billy.
- Give me that.
- Thanks.
Hello
Shel.
Mickey.
Shel, wait, wait.
- Slow.
- How slow?
Since when is like slowly?
Shelby, who knows?
Wait.
I felt you so much.
Shelby, no.
I can not.
What do you mean?
Know what I mean, Shelby.
We finish.
Remember?
I felt bad after school
and would not live here anymore.
Do not remember that?
But I'm building
an annex in the house.
It's enough to get a
family, as you said.
Look, I know this is
difficult for you and know
left her without an explanation,
but do not know what else to do.
Okay, I forgive you.
I mean, I had to
go to another school e. ..
... I was always
problems with my mother e. ..
We can fix that.
Shelby, not listening.
I have a girlfriend.
It is here, outside.
Gotta go,
this was a bad idea.
Sorry, Shelby.
I should not have come here.
Hey, Eddie,
what happens?
What?
No, no. Let's discuss
when you return to school.
Eddie?
I'm losing you.
Is there anywhere in this city where there
with signal coverage decent?
I think not.
Elizabeth.
We gotta go.
Really?
Yes, this was a bad idea.
- Hey, must be ...
- Elizabeth.
Shelby?
Yes, nice to meet you.
Well done, Mickey.
She is very beautiful.
I saw your restaurant
I think it's great.
I wish there was something
so in our school.
Thank you.
Maybe one day,
buy something there.
Hey, let me get a drink.
You know?
We have to go home ...
C'mon, just one drink.
Yes, a drink sounds great.
Okay, what drink?
All we have, I think.
It is a brave girl.
- What is Tequila.
- Tequila.
Listen, do not want to seem
strange, therefore,
why not say Mickey
has good taste and leave it?
Fair enough.
Great.
Good taste.
You are comparing notes?
And this big.
What is penis size.
Stay out of trouble.
Agreed.
Are you kidding?
I can not do that.
I have to know the
Mike's parents later.
Really?
No problem.
What?
No, no, they are wonderful,
trust me.
Do not do that, what?
Not that I am the best
to judge, it's just that ...
They have a strange thing as
that first impression.
So do not let them see what is
completely drunk and be fine.
It's a promise.
So do not be paranoid
not mean that.
It's just ...
... I was Mike's girlfriend
for three years and look at me.
I'm not an angel.
Yes, but he was 12.
Sorry.
I have offended you?
If you had seen your face.
Hello, okay?
Yes.
I like that garora.
I like you, too.
Now get outta here, we are
trying to talk to you.
Okay,
okay.
Agreed.
Here we go.
Bye, guys.
Good night.
Goodbye, Shel.
Thank you for being ...
Sympathetic?
See? I'm not so bad.
It is the reason why you
like me, right?
Goodnight, Shelby.
... No matter how magnificent it is.
You're going to walk, right?
Let's do it.
Are you okay?
What? Forgot something?
I can not go see his mother,
I'm totally drunk.
All I want is to create
a good impression, you know?
It's late and I was drinking e. ..
... I do not think well.
You're brilliant.
Billy, tell him how she's okay.
I've never seen so well.
I never saw, Billy.
There is a hotel or some
something like that to stay?
Can not we go tomorrow?
- This is stupid ...
- No, no, no. Not for me.
I thought that I would support it, ok?
I'll feel better tomorrow,
if you're sober.
- Okay, I'm with you.
- No, can not.
She is waiting, should
be excited to see him.
Personally, I have training
to handle situations like this.
Can I take her to the motel and you to
home safely. OK? No problem.
This is perfect.
Yes, I agree.
I'll get the bags.
Okay?
Hello
We have rooms.
Tonight we are full.
- No, but the sign says ...
- The signal is broken.
Anyway it gets crowded
once a year.
Come back home at night?
Then go.
Okay.
Where is the nearest motel?
It's all over the neighborhood.
How?
How far is it?
4 miles to the west.
4 miles?
You must be kidding.
NO SERVICE
What?
VACANCIES
NO VACANCIES.
My son?
304th
Hello, Mom.
Had to stay awake?
Could not sleep.
Moreover, his father is
snoring again.
- Hey, I thought it would ...
- I would ... I want it ...
... next morning she had to
stay the night in a motel.
Because she is drunk?
Called and said that they had
seen in the Alley with a drunk girl.
She exceeded slightly.
She did not want to cause
bad impression, Mom
Oh, that's nonsense.
That's what I said.
You know how women are.
Oh, never mind.
I'm very satisfied
to have you at home.
Hey.
Shit.
Hey, Hey.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
Elizabeth.
Missed call Mike
Hey, I am.
Call me when you wake up,
Bucar you go.
Goodbye.
- Hello
- Hello, Mom.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Let's go fishing, remember?
Are you serious?
There's something
better to do?
This is my number one son.
Hello, Dad.
- How do you dormu?
- Well
So, Mike, it seems that cats
Wild are not going so well this year.
- Come on, please.
- What? I'm just saying.
Maybe if Mike were in
team would be something else.
I doubt it, father.
He is so modest.
When will seek to Elizabeth?
I do not know
not answer the phone.
Because she is still sleeping.
Come on, come to fish,
when we get it back.
Okay.
Be careful where you step.
Awake.
What happened?
Remember?
Well, I hoped
could tell me.
What I can say is that you were
victim of being hit with stray?
What was on the road alone?
Where was Mike?
I do not know.
My God, sometimes, is an idiot.
He left me at once
road, as well.
But at least had the decency
back 10 minutes later.
I still have stuff from when
my mother was sick,
well, I care for you.
God knows what would have happened
if I had not appeared.
- I want to leave now.
- I bet you want, dear.
Unfortunately for both,
can not let you go.
I mean, do not want to be
responsible if it let you go ...
... Others may collect ..
... Others have internal bleeding ..
... A blood clot
or something like that.
I have to sedate you
not to scream.
I have to call Mike.
Do not worry, I called and
I left a message.
I'm sure it arrives
before I finish watching this.
That is, if he finds,
their voice messages.
I mean, you know what is
horrible with the phone.
It is one of the reasons they
come first.
Do not get me wrong,
I love Mike.
Has to mature
sooner or later.
What are you doing?
It is one thing that will
help her sleep.
Not sure if I want to sleep.
Hey, trust me.
You can relax with this thing?
It may continue to feel bad,
let her catch her breath.
What should I do,
I let the weekend
all in a fucking motel?
Not the full weekend,
is a couple of hours.
Afraid of losing it?
They are so, so seriously?
Yes, I think so.
As I was with Shelby or what?
I mean, I have no complaint.
But it's not a sexual thing,
is like ...
... It is an intimate adult relationship.
Whatever.
Maybe.
No, the Shelby was different.
It was like a job.
Do what he did,
for it was never enough.
Elizabeth is like ...
... I am enough, you know?
No, yes ...
I know.
What?
No, thought I found a rope.
Fuck you.
Mike.
Hey, where is beautiful?
Shelby.
Could you tell me what room
Mitchum is Elizabeth?
- When you registered?
- Last night.
No, sorry.
Are you sure that this is
her name?
Yes, I am sure.
I have no one by that name.
Maybe why not there?
Maybe she has done,
but not at this motel.
Because here was not recorded.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Was stationed here.
This does not smell right, man.
What?
This whole situation.
I mean, what do you think?
Perhaps he was cold, though.
422nd
What?
No way.
No, I know Elizabeth.
She would not.
Even if it did,
at least have called.
Something happened.
He called his friends?
I called everyone I know.
Nothing.
Is there anything
we can do?
Follow the car satellite
or something?
I can not communicate missing
at least 48 hours.
Until then may be dead.
So Mike, shit like this
does not happen in this city.
Oh, my God.
Elizabeth?
You awake?
You know? If you are going to mess us
affairs of other people ...
... You should ask permission first.
He knows that should not
Pressing the ankle.
Let's see what you did.
Sorry Shelby,
not go to your room.
Does it hurts?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- And this?
Shelby, please stop.
Stop, stop.
And this?
I spent much time caring
you last night, you know?
The least we could do,
is to collaborate a little.
Instead, it was giving a
walk and fuck it all.
It seems that I have
put it right again.
No, no, no,
please.
Why are you asking me this?
I'm trying to help her.
Look at this guy, William,
entered and started quickly.
Hello
Hello Mike.
How has this number?
Elizabeth gave me last night.
She's great.
Does your mother like her?
Yes, get along well.
Great.
I said I would.
Well, whatever.
I wonder if
we could see.
Spend some time together
or whatever.
Listen, I do not interpret bad.
Just go through the Alley.
I'm sure Elizabeth
understand.
- And dinner?
- No, I can not, my parents planned ...
And lunch?
Lunch?
Okay,
lunch.
Great.
See you there.
Bye, Shelby.
Finally woke up, right?
There was a Shelby.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Problems with the girls?
Almost always.
Where to go?
Problems with the girls.
It is still your favorite, right?
Here you go.
Thank you.
You know? You have not changed much.
When your team plays on television,
I always try to find him.
It's silly, is not it?
I swear I saw him once.
Probably
not to you.
What was Mickey?
It seems she saw the devil.
Look, why can not play ...
This is not Rugby.
Oh, then?
Elizabeth?
Why say that?
I dunno, it's just that ...
has this guy.
She said something
the other night, Shelby?
You know Mike, I feel strange.
She drank a lot.
So do not give much attention.
- What?
- It just ...
Not ... I know, she said she had
something going on in her mind.
But she loves you, Mike.
Anyone can see.
The probe to mind?
Yes, she said something
about an ex-boyfriend.
Who, Eddie?
You know? I do not remember the name.
Oh, my God.
Listen.
Everyone has an ex in her past.
I mean, sometimes,
think of me, huh?
I do not know, it's just that ...
Yesterday I took her to the motel because she
did not want to meet my mom drunk
and now nothing makes sense.
She did not even
answer the phone.
I thought you said that
they got along very well.
I did not know what to say.
I am sorry.
It may be necessary
some time for her.
I'm sure she'll call
when it is ready to talk.
I must go.
Hey, after going to Pitt?
Maybe.
Well, maybe we see ourselves there.
You know?
I had lunch with Mike today.
It seems going very well.
Good to see you can get
upon his feet.
Sorry to be so cold here.
Is that the heater is broken.
Dorma well.
The telephone does not work.
Just needed a little water.
Really?
Why do not seem ...
... That, Elizabeth.
Looks like a phone.
It is a phone, right?
Please do not.
Please, what?
"Please, you have saved
on the road, where it was abandoned?
I thought I had done it.
"Please give a
a bed and a roof?
I thought I had done that.
"Please be a
nurse for yourself?
Well, I tried to do this,
but you're so selfish ...
... All we get in return are
suspect, lies and shit.
Shelby, that is a kidnapping.
Kidnapping?
Can not you see I try to help her?
Great.
Look what you made me do.
What you want from me?
I want to begin enjoying
my hospitality.
I appreciate it.
Oh, Shelby,
You know?
Mike was right about you.
It is a selfish bitch.
I suggest you go up the stairs
and going to bed
before that, really,
I lose patience.
We called the morgue,
to the hospital and guess what,
no body matches
the description of it.
In fact, there is dead.
- Thanks, man.
- I tried.
It's Elizabeth.
Look at this.
Seems to have become easier.
Sorry, things
walked too fast.
I went back to school. I need time
to think. Talk soon, Elizabeth.
- She was scared.
- No way.
Look, I know it sucks, but look
bright side, at least know what is right.
I have to call her.
Michael, calm down.
Michael, what are you doing?
Michael, you have to make time for
she loves you, it's a girl. Stop.
Does this ex-boyfriend?
Eddie?
- As you know ...?
- Elizabeth had a call from Eddie.
When we were in the Alley
and talking with Shel ...
- Why did not you say something?
- No thought was strange, until now.
Oh, my God.
Know what I think what's the problem?
I guess you have never before been rejected.
Never.
Dude, no offense, but
I can not hear it ...
No, no. Have to listen because
need some perspective.
Mike, you came to receive
his jersey retired.
you're the only good thing
shit happened in this city.
You know how I feel when I see him playing
out any experiments that went ...
... For one who did not even garora
the decency to end up in your face?
She pretended that she went to the motel
to be able to escape you,
Stay with a
girlfriend like this ...
... I pity you.
You know what? That's right.
Fuck it, let's have fun.
So it is spoken.
Come on Rita.
Let's see some fours.
I'm not going to any
strip club.
Just kidding.
Rita retired.
Unfortunately.
- What do you think of Pitt?
- Do not go to Pitt, Shelby will be there.
Okay, so we go to pitt.
So ...
How am I?
Do you think Michael will like it?
You know? I'll see you later.
There appears to be very bad
since it is not on your side.
It is not surprising.
are you?
You know?
I think Michael will like.
Wish me luck.
- Health
- Exactly.
Yes, that's it.
Hello, everyone.
- How are you?
- You are very sexy.
Thank you.
Shel, Shel.
Wait.
What?
This is not a good idea.
Yes, go for a more peaceful place.
No, not that.
What is it?
I can not do this.
I'm drunk and I'm not
thinking logically.
No.
This is a good thing.
Finally, not listening
all that shit they say.
Gotta go.
Hey.
She does not love you, Mike.
Come on.
Whether breakfast, Mike?
No new posts.
Good morning.
My God, my mother recalls.
All fragile and weak.
Setia me sick, only to see it.
Have you ever lost someone like that?
No.
Because it's not like disappear,
know?
Then when they go,
all the time that we take care of them,
realize that it was like.
It only hurts losing a child.
That's baloney.
Should eat.
The more you eat, the more
will be well soon.
The faster you eat,
the faster you can go ...
... Without Mike.
Think they'll like?
I do not know
but I like it.
I went to many places to
find the right size, but ...
... He does not care.
Last night I almost
I hurt her boyfriend.
And I think this may be the night.
Think?
- Lloyd.
- Hello There, Shelby.
Tried to call, but I think what happened
something with your phone.
Are you okay?
Ah, yes, I was just,
arranging the heater.
I come in?
Oh, sure.
Of course.
Warnings account canceled ...
Account in debt ...
I regret that the house is
a mess.
I had no time for anything lately.
I thought I had spoken to
going to the bank.
Yes, said next week.
You said yesterday.
And really, should have passed
there two months ago.
But I have tried
change a thing.
One thing that really
Mike and I had thought,
the need for extra space.
It's that damn heater
make noise all day.
Are you sure that there is no way
you can get more money from the bank?
Shelby.
Guess you do not understand.
There is profit taking in the Alley.
Not pay their debts.
And is using this
home as collateral.
What are you saying?
I'm saying is losing
this house and the Alley.
Can not be with this house.
It was the home of my mother.
- Shelby, sorry.
- What will become of me and Mike?
It is the decision of the bank.
You can stay until the end of January.
- After that.
- I want you to go away now.
Hey.
Help.
Help me.
This is all your fault.
Just because Lloyd saw her on the bench with Mike
is that he knew he was lying.
I understand what you are trying to do.
Want to come back with him.
You can not control everything?
The truth is we can not
control everything, Shelby.
What s happening to you
is the result of what he does.
Nobody understands what I went through.
All I have to do is wait
to come see this place
to know how much you're fucked.
I can not.
Do not make me psychoanalysis.
They are liars.
Understand.
These are lies.
Shelby, do not do this, no.
you are pathetic.
Mike, Shelby,
tries to kill me, Elizabeth.
Nice try, thanks
again by the coat.
Mike will like.
What are you doing?
Please
please.
How did it?
This is not even possible.
Someone is making cheating.
See you then.
Thank you.
Mike, darling.
You have a visitor.
Hello, everyone.
- Hello, Shelby.
- Hello There, Shelby.
- Hello, Mr. Donaldson.
- Hello, Shelby.
I can speak a second?
Yes, after this game.
Great.
Ok
What do you have?
Oh, my God.
POISONOUS PLANTS
Death certificate
There will be an autopsy at the request
his daughter, Shelby Mercer.
So, Shelby, wanted to talk?
Wait a minute.
Okay?
It's a surprise.
It is for you.
Open.
Thanks, Shelby.
Where ...?
Thought you might like.
Yes, this is ... is great.
Truth.
Thank you.
Wear it,
do not be shy.
Come on, try it.
Look ...
Impressive.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Shelby, please.
What?
What is it?
- Why is it so?
- Listen, we're finished.
Finished.
I thought we could be friends,
but obviously you can not.
- But last night ...
- He was drunk, Shelby.
- Do not say that.
- It's true.
I was drunk, confused and upset
with Elizabeth, but that is what we like.
Do not care that feels
the same for me or not.
If that selfish bitch had died
a month ago I would have stayed with you.
I could have you in the
school and everything would have been fine.
But that's not what happened.
She was his mother, Shelby American.
I can not believe what he said,
what is wrong with you?
Please, Mickey.
You're all I have.
Please
I do not put in this position.
Shelby.
Come on, everything will be fine.
Give me just a little time.
It's your fault, genius.
Which part is my fault?
You addressed the situation worse.
How?
I do not know, maybe if you like
was a bitch last night?
What has to do this?
What do you mean?
What do I mean? I'm tired of
listen to you complain all the time.
Garora has a wonderful, beautiful
smart and all they do is reject it.
Yes, if you think that is so good
why not her?
Yes it's a good question.
Yes, it loves you, idiot.
Shelby does anything for you.
You left the city and
she still loves you.
Was rejected 10 times and
still loves you.
As all of this city.
Do not start with that shit.
Sorry, that is,
was too much for you.
See you tomorrow.
Shit.
No, please.
You stupid bitch.
My parents have money.
What did you say?
EPoSS pay what you want.
Think you want your money?
I know what you think.
You read those papers.
- I do not understand.
- I understand.
You had to deal with a lot.
It was not his job to care for his mother.
Do not kill.
Listen, Shelby.
There is nothing you have done
that can not be undone.
If you let me go, go away
and do not count anything. Interest.
People do not always
do what they say.
There was never anything enough,
Good for her.
Never.
Shelby.
All you're thinking
in doing, please do not.
I like to solve everything.
Everything depended on me.
There was nobody to help us.
I had to make a decision.
She was a monster.
Do not be like her,
stop what you started.
What are you doing?
No.
Hello, everyone.
Mom, go away.
Are you ready?
Here you go.
No, better not think the jacket.
Why? He was so good on you.
I do not know, Shelby gave me.
Well, you should use it.
Will not want to hurt him
feelings, right?
- Hello
What happened to you?
Is that fell down the stairs.
Okay?
I'm fine.
What's happening?
Was in the neighborhood and thought ...
... I thought going on here wanted to see if
that left her at the ceremony Mike.
Billy.
Yes, I thought I would
react this way.
But just thought ...
... In check.
852nd
You know, Billy?
Now, is not a good time.
All is well with you, Shelby?
Yes, I'm fine.
It was only a weekend
somewhat difficult.
Sorry how
Mickey has been treating it,
It's an idiot I told him.
Okay.
I'm used to it.
Maybe that will happen some
bring it back.
Yes, maybe it is time ...
... you go ahead
You know what I mean?
Know the number of boys ...
... They wanted a girl like you?
Are the fuses.
I'll check the basement, okay?
No, Billy.
Never mind,
we can fix later.
Not after repair,
repair now, so good.
Not a big problem.
We going to the ceremony.
Relax, be right back.
Sorry, Billy.
Now, I'll put it
a new jail.
Coach.
Hello, how are you?
Hello Mike.
See you there.
I brought the camera.
Come, come here.
Just so you know, I am
completely against it.
I think it is a mistake
withdraw a player like that.
Sends cheating
current players.
Telling them that the best years
their lives are about to end.
Give them permission to lose.
I do not like losing, Donaldson.
Coach,'m sorry.
I had no idea.
Oh, so where is your mood?
Of course I like.
What do you think they teach
of you at school?
Look, I gotta go.
Do not be nervous when they speak
your name, okay?
Really?
I have seen many great
Players go through those doors.
But few show commitment
the skill and elegance
the young man that I will present today.
Let's give a warm welcome by
back to the actual number 7
Kevin Michael Donaldson.
Billy, I am.
Call me when it arrives,
I know where is Elizabeth.
Eli
Shelby.
Opens.
Where is she, Shelby?
Elizabeth.
Where the hell is she, Shelby?
Shit.
Excuse me, excuse me.
I would not want it that way.
Shelby.
you're sick.
Need help.
Do not say that.
Do not do anything foolish.
What?
This is what we want?
Do not do anything stupid ...
Come on.
Here we go.
Go sit ...
... In order to free her.
Okay.
Look for a knife.
Right.
Mike!
You said it was forever.
Elizabeth, no.
Do not.
Come on.
Shelby.
Mother,
go away.
Translate by: jinbatsu
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3s77u
Help other users to choose the best subtitles