Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Excuse me.
Pa?
You all right, Pa?
- You're up early.
- I got a big day ahead.
I wish you didn't have to go.
I promised to help this friend.
Goddamn outhouse.
One of these days soon,
I'm changing all that.
Damn soon.
You drive careful now.
Young man? Young man.
I'm terribly sorry.
Ma'am, can I have a root beer?
- Anything else to go with that?
- Some aspirins, please.
"Friend P. Came out in August...
"...and after you left, I met someone.
"He put me onto something
we could bring off beautiful.
"A cinch, the perfect score.
"It"s a sure thing. Am depending on you.
"Love, Dick.
"P.S. Will meet your bus, November 14.
"M-day."M"for money, honey."
Fill her up, buddy.
You sure got a perfect day for it.
- What's that?
- Hunting pheasants.
Yes, indeedy.
Deadeye Dick Hickock?
Them birds don't know it,
but this is their last day on Earth.
Good morning, Daddy.
- Well, you're up early.
- I've got a furious day ahead.
'Morning, Dad.
- Thought maybe I smelled smoke.
- Yeah.
Me, too. Could be a leaky valve.
Could be.
Peppermints before breakfast
might stunt your growth.
Daddy, phone.
It's the insurance man.
This afternoon, anytime before dark.
Hello?
I want to call
the Kansas State Penitentiary.
Person-to-person. Rev. James Post.
Rev. James Post.
My name is...
Perry Smith.
He'll be checking in sometime tomorrow.
- Can I see the room, please?
- Ain't you working today?
Now, ain't you?
Hello.
Perry.
Of course, I remember you.
Kansas City?
Missouri.
I'm at the bus terminal.
I'm waiting for Willie Jay.
Did something hold up his parole?
- I was supposed to meet him right here.
- Perry, think.
You've already broken parole
by quitting your job.
You'll break it again
if you step into Kansas.
Whatever you do,
don't cross that river into Kansas.
Can you tell me where he went?
Please, Jim.
It's very important.
Maybe the most important thing in my life.
Go back. Why not see your father?
'Morning, Ma.
Daddy, you know Jolene?
I promised to teach her
how to bake a cherry pie.
- Sounds serious.
- She insists on today.
That makes it practically a catastrophe.
Because I also promised
to help Roxy with her trumpet solo.
And errands for Mother in Garden City,
lunch with Susan...
Suppose I take care
of your mother's errands?
Thank you, Daddy.
Also provided for your convenience,
at the baggage counter...
... are identification tags.
This is your last call...
... for Buckner, Bluffington, Lexington,
Waverly, Marshall...
... and intermediate flights.
Now boarding at door number six.
Stick 'em up!
- Hey, buddy.
- How long have you been standing there?
Long enough to catch your late late show.
- Just between you and I.
- You and me.
How come you always go into a trance
every time you look in the mirror?
Just like you was looking
at some gorgeous piece of butt.
What in the hell is in here?
Concrete?
That's all my stuff. Books, letters, songs.
Souvenirs from Korea.
And our ticket to fame and fortune.
I got a secret map that's going to lead us...
...straight to the sunken treasure
of Captain Cortés.
$60 million in Spanish gold,
off the coast of Mexico.
So, that's why that map's
so frigging heavy.
Welcome back to Kansas, buddy.
The heart of America.
The land of wheat, corn, bibles, and...
...natural gas.
That map's not as heavy as yours,
but it's the real thing.
And it's gonna get us $10,000 by tonight.
Four hundred miles west of here,
Big Daddy Clutter's place.
That's the layout. The works.
Somewhere in that office,
in one little old safe.
And inside that safe, $10,000, maybe more.
You've seen it?
The safe!
Right after you left the zoo,
a new guy moved into the cell.
Floyd Wells,
serving three to five for robbery.
He once worked for Clutter. He saw it.
And that's your perfect score?
Baby, it's a cinch.
I promise you, honey,
we'll blast hair all over them walls.
- Hello, Roxy.
- 'Morning, Mr. Clutter.
I think Nancy's expecting you.
You want to watch it, boy.
You'll end up an aspirin junkie.
Been one for seven years.
Got the habit in the hospital.
Doctors.
They made a dwarf out of me.
Doctors and lawyers. What do they care?
Ever see a millionaire
fry in the electric chair?
Hell, no.
There's two kinds of laws, honey:
One for the rich and one for the poor.
Look at me.
I crack up my car,
wake up in a charity ward...
...and don't even recognize myself.
I hate to count how much classy pussy
that's cost me.
They left you a wonderful smile, though.
Yeah, the all-American boy.
That was stupid.
Stealing a lousy pack of razor blades,
to prove what?
Everybody steals something sometime.
It's the national pastime, baby.
Stealing and cheating.
If they caught every cheating wife
and tax chiseler...
...the whole country
would be behind prison walls.
- Where are the black stockings?
- They didn't have black.
- Stop someplace else.
- Where?
- A Catholic hospital.
- Sure.
We'll just barge in like it was
a goddamn five-and-dime.
Sister, sweetie, we gotta have
some black stockings to hide our face.
Okay, forget it.
Anyway, nuns are bad luck.
Kind of sexy, though.
You wouldn't think so if you'd lived
in one of those orphan homes...
...with those black widows always at you.
Always sneaking up in the dark,
spying while you sleep.
Hitting you with a flashlight
for wetting the bed.
That's the first time
I was saved by the yellow bird.
The what?
Sort of a parrot.
Taller than Jesus.
Brilliant yellow, like a sunflower.
It attacked those nuns
like an avenging angel.
The nuns begged for mercy.
But the yellow bird
slaughtered them anyway.
Then the bird folded me in its wings...
...and lifted me up to paradise.
That's one hell of a bird
to have on your side.
Anyway, that's why I have
an aversion to nuns...
...and God and religion.
Forget it.
Black stockings are a waste of time.
No one's gonna remember us
because we're leaving no witnesses.
How about staying at our place tonight?
Frozen stiff TV dinners on trays...
...spaghetti, macaroni or pizza.
- Sounds irresistible.
- I'll tell Mom.
- Golly, Sue. C"est impossible.
- Pourquoi, chérie?
- Bobby's coming over.
- I'll pick you up for church tomorrow.
9:00 sharp.
A full day's work
deserves a full-course dinner.
The condemned ate a hearty meal.
I don't know what they ate,
but tonight, cheeseburgers.
Tomorrow?
Mexico.
- Fabulous Mexico.
- Land of the hot tamales.
Gold country.
Remember Bogart
in Treasure of the Sierra Madre?
We could get us a couple of burros.
Some tools.
Slow down, honey.
I don't know gold dust from diarrhea.
Well, I do.
My old man prospected for gold in Alaska.
He taught me all the ins and outs.
Yeah. And we end up nuts.
No gold, nothing. Just like in the movie.
You never meant it...
...about going to Mexico, did you?
Did you?
Sure, baby.
Sure we're going.
But first we gotta dig up some capital.
Like tonight.
$5,000 a piece, for one hour's work.
- May I take your orders?
- Two cheeseburgers, please.
Getting insured is like...
...well, when you wash your car,
it always rains.
Know what we call this
in the insurance game?
The solemn moment.
I guess when a man makes out a policy
or takes out his last will...
...it's only natural to think about mortality.
Herb, as of this minute,
your life is worth $40,000.
In case of accidental death,
double indemnity.
New York Life wishes you
a very long and very healthy life.
- And so do I.
That waitress.
Nice piece of blonde chicken.
Why'd you pick me for this job?
A perfect score needs perfect partners.
Together we're a perfect fit.
It's your score. Where do I fit in?
I got you figured for a natural-born killer.
Or did you lie about that punk in Vegas?
No.
Why did you kill him?
No special reason. Just for the hell of it.
That's the best reason of all.
Back there, you wanted to kill me.
Just for a second, right?
It passed.
Hair-trigger temper.
Somebody crosses you, voom!
Yes, sir. You've got the gift, boy.
Remember the chaplain's clerk, Willie Jay?
- The guy you painted to look like Jesus?
- He said the same thing:
"Unstable, explosive."
He is a flaming faggot.
He has a brilliant mind.
Then how come
he got caught stealing five times?
- He was the best friend I ever had.
- I'm the only friend you got now.
Friend to the end, for better or worse.
Till death do us part?
All we need is a ring, sugar.
Is that Bobby?
Look at that land, will you?
Oil money, gas money, wheat money.
Share the wealth, baby.
- How does it feel?
- What?
Being a father.
Great.
- Your kids, you love them?
- I'm their father, ain't I?
I didn't ask if you were their father.
I asked if you love them.
I'm crazy about 'em.
- But you left them.
- Left their mother.
Okay. She left me.
There was this piece of tail,
nothing serious.
Just a quickie in the back seat.
She blew the whistle on me.
Said I knocked her up.
That's how I got to be a two-time loser.
You ditched the kids for her.
Jesus, baby.
I had to do the right thing by her, didn't I?
Well? Didn't I?
Yeah.
- 'Night!
- See you tomorrow, Bobby.
- How much longer?
- Seven miles.
Fill her up with regular.
Want some candy?
No.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Coming?
Let's go.
News from the Associated Press,
NBC, and the Garden City Telegram.
- Goodnight, Dad.
- Goodnight, Son.
Winds from the south
at about 15 miles per hour.
The Garden City Sale Company reported
3,273 cattle at the auction yesterday.
'Night.
... calves went from $26.50 to $30.
However, very few reached the $30 mark.
The medium and good kinds
sold as high as $26.50...
Look at that spread.
Don't tell me this guy ain't loaded.
Let's pull out of here.
Now, before it's too late.
- Pa?
- Maybe they're still asleep.
Nancy?
Don't touch it.
Don't touch anything.
Been up there?
My God.
There's two more in the basement.
I just saw two ambulances
going up to Clutter's.
I just wondering what's happening.
The Sheriff placed an urgent call
to the Kansas Bureau of Investigation.
In Topeka, Logan Sanford, KBI chief,
assigned four men to the Clutter case.
They are agents Dewey, Nye,
Duntz, and Church.
- What happened to the basketball game?
- It got interrupted. Terrible thing, that.
I've never been so hungry in my whole life.
Agent Alvin Dewey arrived
at the Clutter house...
... in advance of the other KBI men.
Mr. Dewey, resident of Garden City,
was placed in charge of the case.
Were all four tied with the same cord?
All tied with the same square knot.
Used by anybody
who works with livestock.
- Find any shell casings?
- Nope.
Which means that...
...you can bet
they didn't leave any fingerprints either.
Al.
- This is the housekeeper.
- Thank you for coming.
- Are they still...
- No, no, ma'am.
They've been taken to the funeral home.
Now, if you'll just look around
with Mr. Church here...
...to see if anything is missing...
They never hurt anybody. Why them?
Al, you knew Clutter.
Did he have a safe?
Keep a lot of cash on hand?
The old Kansas myth.
Every farmer with a good spread
is supposed to have...
...a hidden black box somewhere
filled with money.
No. Herb paid everything by check.
Even a $2 haircut.
Well, then why...
...if they're going
to shoot them all anyway, why...
...did they first cut Clutter's throat?
Why did they first put him
on a soft mattress box?
To make him comfy?
And why the pillow under the boy's head?
We keep saying "they."
It could have been one man.
A madman.
This picture was taken
with a time exposure.
It shows only what the eye saw.
This picture was taken with a flashbulb.
That's a different pair of shoes.
Yeah.
We know there were at least two of them.
You won't see it there.
The flash made them stand out in the dust.
- You develop those pictures yourself?
- Yes.
- Newspaper boys seen this?
- Not yet.
Keep it that way.
Al, when can we see the Clutter home?
Why were the men killed in the basement?
I'll talk facts, not theories.
It happened around 2:00 a.m.
All four were apparently killed
by the same weapon.
Shotgun, 12-gauge.
Mr. Clutter's throat was cut.
Before he was shot?
Probably.
All four were tied
with the same nylon sash-cord...
...sold in most hardware stores.
And their mouths were taped.
How were they tied? What kind of knots?
Can we see police pictures?
- Find the murder weapon?
- Not yet.
- Any clues or fingerprints?
- Lots. All belong to the family.
They say that Nancy's boyfriend
is a prime suspect.
- Is that what they say?
- He was the last one to see them alive.
- Except the killers.
- Then there were more than one?
- Were the women sexually molested?
- The coroner says not.
- Why didn't the dog bark?
- He didn't bark?
- Nobody heard him.
- Nobody heard the gunshots either.
Mr. Dewey, in your opinion...
...do you think it could have been
an inside job, sir?
- Why didn't Mr. Clutter resist?
- Mr. Dewey, just a moment, Mr. Dewey.
What about the hired man?
His check was made out for $1,707.
Mr. Clutter's first premium
on a straight life policy...
...worth $40,000.
Double indemnity makes it $80,000.
And that makes it a strange coincidence.
And that's all it is, a coincidence.
I didn't catch your name.
Bill Jensen, Weekly magazine.
If you're not here to write news,
what is your interest?
Fairly basic.
What's basic about a stupid...
...senseless crime?
A violent, unknown force
destroys a decent, ordinary family.
No clues. No logic.
Makes us all feel frightened. Vulnerable.
Murder's no mystery. Only the motive.
Got one?
I smoke too much.
How'd they enter the house?
A key? Force a window?
Probably just walked in.
- Don't people around here lock doors?
- They will tonight.
I know something's wrong here.
I feel it.
I don't know what it is, but...
Mr. Clutter never allowed smoking
in the house.
Sorry.
Something.
But of course.
The radio!
Kenyon always listened
to the news and weather...
...before he went to bed.
But where's his radio?
Since the night of horror, two days ago...
... few people are seen on the streets
of Garden City after dark.
To date, no clues have been uncovered.
No clues whatever.
It was generally known that Clutter
never had large sums of cash on hand.
No expensive jewels.
Nor even a steel safe in which to...
Perry, baby,
if you don't want that burger...
You and your hotshot
prison buddy Floyd Wells.
Big, fat safe in the wall.
$10,000. "A cinch."
Okay, Floyd's a jerk.
But we scored, didn't we?
Perfecto.
You call an 800-mile drive...
...and the rest of it, for 43...
...lousy dollars, you call that perfect?
And that!
You don't believe that con
about no clues do you?
You worry too much.
How are them cowboys
gonna connect us? Remember?
No witnesses.
I know one.
You. You're a witness.
Jesus, kid. For a minute,
I thought you blew your cork.
You're so right.
We're the only ones who saw it...
...and that, honey, is our big ace.
Because if they can't split us apart,
they can't get a confession.
And if they can't get a confession,
they got nothing.
Next move...
...Mexico.
- Once we beat it out of the country.
- On what?
$43 and a smile and bullshit?
You guessed it, Chief.
It's the smile that does it.
Like it says in the commercials:
"The family that sticks together
lives forever."
Officers investigating the slaying
have appealed to the public...
... for help in solving the crime.
A Kansas paper, The Hutchison News,
has offered a reward for any information...
... leading to the capture
and conviction of the person...
... or persons, guilty of the Clutter murders.
A reward of $1,000.
What about the reward?
That's right, $1,000.
Yes, sir. Where are you calling from?
Yeah. Go ahead.
Who?
How do you know he was a foreigner?
- I see. Thank you very much, sir.
- Another tip?
He says he saw a foreigner running.
How does a foreigner run, anyway?
Just how many people
have tried to claim this reward?
Just about everybody.
A mysterious stranger did it.
Hired killers did it.
A jealous neighbor did it.
Seems like the only one
who didn't do it is the butler.
Any luck?
None of the Clutters had shoes
with a cat's paw.
No diamond pattern, either.
Insurance money goes to the family.
And this, Nancy Clutter's.
Found it hidden in the toe of her slipper.
Something must've scared her.
All of which brings us back
to the motive of robbery.
I can believe one man might work up
enough rage to do it.
But two?
Who would kill four people in cold blood
for a radio...
...a pair of binoculars and $40 in cash?
These days? Take your pick
on any crowded street.
You ever hang any paper?
I couldn't cash a check even if it was good.
Easy, baby. Casual.
Excuse me. My name's Hickock.
Richie. And you're?
Sharp. Luke Sharp.
I'll bet in school
they called you Look Sharp.
See that gentleman over there?
Would you believe a runt like that
is getting married?
Well, maybe he ain't any Fred Astaire
but he's my best friend...
...and I'm his best man.
My wedding present to him
is going to be what you might call...
...his trousseau.
Ideal shade for an informal ceremony,
don't you think?
Perfectly ideal.
Of course,
we are a tiny bit oddly proportioned.
I mean, the upper torso is so large
compared to the legs.
I'm terribly sorry.
He's not ashamed of them scars.
They gave him the Bronze Star in Korea.
Luke, have you ever been to Eden Roc?
In Miami Beach.
That's where the happy couple
is shacking up for their honeymoon.
Two weeks all paid up.
Surprise gift from the folks.
He's a very lucky man.
He deserves it.
And with these, $192.70.
Would you like them wrapped
and taken to your car?
No hurry.
Deliver them when the suit is ready.
Oh, no!
Four silly dollars.
We're awfully sorry.
We'll have to come back some other time.
I'd gladly give you a check.
But then you hardly know me.
We're really grateful for your courtesy.
- Lf it's a personal check, perhaps.
- You're sure?
- I wouldn't want to inconvenience you.
- Perfectly all right.
Which bank would you like?
It's immaterial, I'm sure.
My driver's license, identity card,
insurance card, country club...
She's a private number.
- Was that $192?
- And $0.70.
Would you care if I...
- Never mind.
- No, please.
Well, I could use a little loose change.
I see.
Suppose I just make this out for $280...
...and $0.70, of course.
Well, I suppose.
Mr. Sharp, you're a brick.
You're good. You're really good.
Smooth. No sweat. No strain.
- You're an artist, boy.
- Right.
If you're getting married,
you need a wedding ring.
- Why not two of them?
- Why not?
Cameras, diamond rings, TV sets
are the easiest things to hock or sell.
You know, there's got to be
something wrong with us...
...to do what we did.
Nobody, but nobody,
ever gets away with a thing like that.
Will you shut up about it?
I can't shake this feeling
that we forgot something that night.
I don't know what,
something that belongs to us.
You want to go back to that house
and look for whatever the hell it is?
Because that would make us
not only crazy, but insane.
Any luck?
If they didn't leave any fingerprints,
you can be sure...
...they didn't leave any murder weapons.
People who used to work for Clutter,
going back 15 years.
Hired men,
people he used to do business with...
- Just keep talking.
- Upstairs?
Don't look up.
- See something?
- I'm not sure.
Now you take the office side
and I'll go around the kitchen side.
It's true, really true.
We're on our way
and never coming back, never.
And no regrets.
For you. You are leaving nothing.
What about my old man? And my mother.
They'll still be there
when my checks start bouncing.
It's nice the way
you think about your folks.
I'm a real thoughtful bastard.
'Morning, Bess. Coffee?
Hey, Alvin,
that prowler at the Clutter house...
...get a confession out of him yet?
- Yep.
His confession proved he didn't do it:
Escaped mental patient.
If he's the wrong one,
why in hell don't you find the right one?
I've got a house full of women
who are afraid to go to the toilet alone.
Bunch of gabby old women gassing away,
scaring each other.
Somebody with a grudge done it.
Somebody who hated the Clutters.
Nobody asked you.
Nobody hated the Clutters.
Leastways, nobody that knew them.
Phone.
If this can happen to a decent,
God-fearing family...
...who's safe anymore?
Hello?
- From here?
- No, from Topeka. It's urgent!
Okay, Mr. Sandrew.
Tell Alvin it's a prisoner. In Lancing.
Get me a rap sheet on this man, please.
He mentioned the Clutter case.
He wouldn't say any more
unless he was called out of the cellblock.
I have the warden on the other phone now.
Might be a break.
If it is, I'll be out to Garden City tonight
with the tape.
No, phone's too risky.
Hello? Yes.
"KSP 1-4-3-2-3. Floyd Wells."
- I first met him in the penitentiary.
- Hickock?
Yes, sir. We shared the same cell.
Go ahead, Floyd.
We swapped life stories and I told him...
... how I once worked
for a farmer named Clutter.
Did you work for him?
Yes, sir. Ten, eleven years ago.
Dick wanted to know if Mr. Clutter
was rich and I said, "Well...
"...sometimes it cost him $10,000
a week to run his operation."
After that, Dick never let up.
Just kept asking questions.
How many was in the family?
Did Clutter keep a safe?
Dick said how he was going
to rob the Clutter place...
... him and his buddy.
And how he was gonna kill
all the witnesses.
I just never believed him.
I thought it was just...
What took him so long to speak up?
Afraid of other prisoners.
Issue a pickup warrant.
All points bulletin.
We better make it for parole violation,
passing bad checks.
If they know they're wanted for murder...
- Yeah.
- The question is why they did it.
Why did Cain kill Abel? And who cares?
They did it, and they'll swing for it.
If they did it and if we can prove it.
When we cross this bridge,
we're in Mexico.
Free, clear and safe.
Fabulous Mexico.
Mr. Smith?
Mr. Tex Smith?
- Cops?
- Kansas Bureau of Investigation.
Is this your son, Perry?
Yep, that's him all right.
Gets his looks from his mother.
Part Cherokee.
- Will you have some coffee?
- When did you see him last?
- Couple of years ago.
- In prison?
I was just fixing to make some grub.
You want some eats?
He was in for three and a half years.
He's been out on parole for six months.
Well, then I guess I haven't seen him
for five or six years.
That's not surprising though.
He's a lone wolf just like me.
You can rest easy on one thing sure...
...you won't be having
any more trouble with Perry.
He's learned his lesson for sure.
When he wrote me from prison,
I wrote him back pronto.
"Boy, you take your punishment
with a smile.
"I didn't raise you to steal,
so don't expect me to cry...
"...because you got it tough
behind the bars."
Perry's no fool. He knows when he's beat.
You fellows have got him whipped forever.
The law's the boss.
He knows the difference
between right and wrong.
I taught my kids a golden rule:
Always tell the truth...
...wash in the morning,
be sober and independent.
I showed him how.
How to prospect, how to trap fur,
how to carpenter, how to bake bread...
...how to be his own boss.
Yes, he's a chip off the old block, all right.
I never had no trouble with my kids,
not as long as Flo and me was together.
But she wanted the wild life.
So she took the kids and ran off.
Turned them against me.
All but Perry.
I don't know what got into her.
She started drinking.
Turned into a hopeless drunk.
Started stepping out with young men.
I caught her once and I...
Anyway, she died drunk.
Choked to death on her own vomit.
So I took Perry and we started roaming
to forget it all.
I took him with me everywhere.
How that boy loved me.
At night, when it was cold...
...we'd sleep cuddled up.
He'd hang onto me with his little arms,
so tight.
I'd tell him stories about
the great adventures we was gonna have.
How we was gonna strike it rich.
Buried treasures.
Gold.
In Alaska.
That's where this picture was took.
Him and me in Alaska.
You just ask Perry if I wasn't
a good father to him.
I always shared, always.
When I eat, he eats.
You just tell Perry,
when I die all my insurance goes to him.
Yes, sir.
His life is all set.
Great news!
I met this kid. He's a shoeshine boy.
He's got a cousin in Yucatan, a fisherman.
- And he's got a powerboat.
- So?
So, we drive to Yucatan, we sell the car...
...buy us a load of deepsea diving gear...
...and "pow," we hit the Cortés jackpot.
$60 million in Spanish gold.
Of course, we'll have to cut the kid in,
and his cousin, too.
But even so, Yucatan!
Hot, dry, clean...
...no crowd, no noise.
Doing what we came to do.
- How much can we get for the car?
- $120.
Is that all?
Enough to pay the bills.
Hotel, bar, groceries.
And with what's left over,
I bought us two bus tickets...
...as far as Barstow, California.
After that, we walk.
So get rid of that ton and a half of garbage.
Ship it! Dump it! Burn it! I don't care.
Only get rid of it, by tonight.
'Cause come tomorrow, we're gone.
- Back to the States.
- Now listen.
You listen! I've had it!
You, your maps, fishing boats,
buried treasure, all of it!
Everything! Stop jacking off.
There isn't any caskets of gold.
No buried treasure.
And even if there was, hell, boy,
you can't even swim.
You want to stick with me, okay.
You wanna split, that's okay, too.
Only make up your mind.
- I'll ship our stuff back to Vegas.
- Good.
I got a little señorita coming over tonight.
I'll try to be finished packing
before you get back.
What for? Hell, I'm not bashful, baby.
And that, if we find the motive,
we find the killer.
Lf.
This report was written six months...
...before the Clutters were killed.
It's called,
Murder Without Apparent Motive.
At the Menninger Clinic,
right here in Kansas...
...a study was made of four killers.
They all had certain things in common.
They all committed senseless murders.
They all felt physically inferior
and sexually inadequate.
Their childhood was violent,
or one parent was missing.
Or someone else had raised them.
They couldn't distinguish
between fantasy and reality.
They didn't hate their victims,
they didn't even know them.
They felt no guilt about their crime,
and got nothing out of it.
And most important,
they told the police or a psychiatrist...
...that they felt the urge to kill,
before they committed murder.
Their warnings were disregarded.
So, who killed the Clutters?
Someday, somebody will explain
to me the motive of a newspaper.
First you scream, "Find the bastards."
Till we find them you want to get us fired.
When we find them,
you accuse us of brutality.
Before we can go into court,
you give them a trial by newspaper.
When we finally get a conviction
you want to save them...
...by proving they were crazy
in the first place.
All of which adds up to one thing:
You've got the killers.
Off the record, have you got them?
Suspects.
Even if we catch them, that's all we've got.
Because without a confession, the evidence
we got so far, we couldn't go to trial.
Unless we can place the suspects
in this spot...
...unless we can tie the killers
to that piece of rope...
...they'll never hang.
Perry!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4q5yy
Help other users to choose the best subtitles