Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Naveen2505 Presents resync subs njoy
(Ambulance siren)
MAN:
We got vultures circling here.
Lacs to the neck, chest, hands,
shoulder-- take your pick.
How many times
was she stabbed?
She's lost
too much blood.
Jed! Need a large bore IV, stat!
Neighbours watched it happen,
and no one even called the cops.
We did what we could, but--
Does she have a name?
Allison Parks.
Okay, Allison, stay with us.
Gonna have to jump her.
Gimme 360.
Charge 360.
Oh, my god.
He loved me.
Wait a minute.
She's trying to say something.
Clear!
Kaitlyn! Kaitlyn!
You all right?
He loved me.
Where is she?!
Oh, thank God.
What
happened?
Shit, Kate, your heart just
stopped... that's all.
Hey, hey, hey!
Take it easy.
You've taken
some punishment today.
What the hell happened in there?
What do you mean?
Well, grabbing a patient in the
middle of an ICD?
You have a death wish?
No, she was lucid.
She was awake.
Who?
The girl. That girl.
Did she make it?
Let's just worry
about you, okay?
She was responsive.
She was scared to death,
but she was responsive.
What are you talking about,
sweetie?
She looked right at me.
She spoke to me. She was trying
to talk to me.
She was trying to...
tell me something.
That girl had been stabbed over
a dozen times.
You have any idea
how much blood she lost?
She couldn't have said a word.
No... No, she--
she spoke to me.
She was trying to tell me--
I think she was trying to tell
me who stabbed her.
Honey, that girl was dead
before she ever came
through those doors.
So, let me guess...
no witnesses, right?
14 witnesses
watched her go down.
Watched it? What do you mean,
"Watched it?"
Did you get statements?
Heard a scuffle, they looked out
the window,
and they watched a little girl
get stabbed
like they was watching
television.
Here's the best part:
no one bothered to call 911.
Well, that is just wonderful.
Do me a favour, will you?
Grab some shots
from the windows,
looking down on this area.
Sure thing.
So why would no one call the
cops, huh? Tell me that.
Listen, man, I find that fact a
bit depressing,
but... not us.
14 people means 14 witnesses.
Somebody saw something.
Best I could get was
a vague description.
Male. Race unknown.
Black jacket.
Maybe a blue baseball cap.
And not one person caught a
glimpse of the perp's face?
It's too dark out here.
How long's this lamp been out?
I don't know.
It's a good question.
Well, do me a favour,
will you?
Go ask somebody.
Thanks.
Started off to be
such a great day.
Kate! Whoa. Kaitlyn.
What?
Where do you think you're going?
You're still in shock from the
defib. You need to rest.
No, I gotta go home.
Hey! You can go home
when you've been released.
How many times have you had the
same conversation
with your own patients?
I-- No, I have to go home and
take care of my mom.
She can't be without me
for this long.
I'll check in on her.
Just tell me where I need to--
Val, I'm going. I'm sorry,
but my mother needs me.
How's she holding up?
Well, uh, they gave her
six weeks,
and six months later, she's
still here, so... there's that.
Look, take the next
couple days off, okay?
I'll cover for you.
Go be with your mom
and rest.
I mean really rest.
And call me if you need
anything. Anything.
Thank you.
Oh, and say hi
to your mom for me..
Okay.
Ma'am? Ma'am! Are you okay?
We got vultures circling here.
Lacs to the chest, hands, neck,
shoulder-- take your pick.
How many times
was she stabbed?
She's lost
too much blood.
Jed! Need a large bore IV, stat!
Bunch of neighbours
watched it happen.
No one even called the cops.
We did what we could, but--
Gonna have to jump her.
Gimme 360.
Charge 360.
He loved me.
Clear!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You look tired.
You're one to talk.
Don't be stubborn.
Tell me.
It was a nightmare.
That's all.
Everything's fine.
You know, you don't have to
sleep in that chair every night.
It's fine.
It's not!
The chair is no good.
That is why you're tired.
Now, you have your own bed.
You should use it.
Swallow.
You know, I just
worry about you.
Don't.
Something is troubling you.
Now, I may be sick,
but I'm not stupid.
It's a patient.
Died yesterday.
She was stabbed to death.
It was bad.
I'm sure she suffered.
I'm sure you did
everything you could.
No, I didn't.
I couldn't do anything.
I looked right at this girl,
Mom. I looked right at her.
And she-- she was
looking back at me,
like, into me.
Like she wanted something. Like
she wanted me to do something.
Like she was trying to reach
out, and--
(Glass shattering)
Heavens.
Honey, just let it go.
It's all right.
(Kettle whistling)
TV:
We're at the scene of a grisly
murder of a local woman
where police have made
no arrests at this point,
and they have few leads.
The attack appears to be a
mugging gone wrong.
The tragic tale of
a desperate criminal
who falls upon
an unsuspecting victim
in a dark and somewhat
isolated location.
No, that's not right.
Allison Parks was simply in the
wrong place at the wrong time,
and unfortunately,
random crimes such as this
are fairly difficult to solve.
I can't stop thinking
about that girl.
Yeah, I know. It was horrible.
But the cops'll find the guy;
I'm sure.
No, they're giving up.
What are you talking about?
They're not even looking in the
right place.
And you know the right place?
Well, whoever killed Allison
knew her.
Whoa. Allison?
She said, "He loved me."
Okay, do you hear yourself?
You're not making any sense.
She told me.
That girl didn't tell you
anything. She was dead.
Okay, so, what?
You think I'm hallucinating?
You think I'm just
making all this up?
No, I don't.
Look, honey, I know you, okay?
And you always want to believe
that you can help,
but sometimes we do everything,
and it's just not enough.
Yeah...
We do what we do, okay?
Let the cops do what they do.
Allison?
Allison, is that you?
Oh, Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
You look just like her.
I thought I was seeing a ghost.
So, what'd you find?
Whole lot of nothing.
Well, nice work then.
Gave witnesses a bunch of
baseball hats to look at.
It's pointless.
What about the knife wound?
Nothing conclusive, but the lab
said the wounds, and I quote,
"Were consistent with a large
kitchen knife,
possessing precise serration,
approximately six inches long.
Yeah? Yeah, that'd do it.
I like the part about precise
serration. Precise serration.
It's like the lab guy is going
shopping for a wedding gift.
So, what? Some tweaker?
He tries to sneak a couple of
bucks out of this girl?
Is that what happens?
Then she starts screaming
and he just flips out?
He's got a big ol' knife
and he uses it to shut her up.
I don't get a lot of visitors.
Thank you.
Still can't believe she's gone.
Tragedy.
How did you two meet?
School.
Oh. Classmates.
I heard there were witnesses.
Did you see anything?
I, uh-- No.
Are you-- are you hungry?
I could heat up
some frozen dinners.
But your window is-- it looks
right out onto the courtyard.
You didn't see anything?
Uh, uh...
I was out, like I told you.
But I heard all about it from
the couple in 3E.
Horrible.
I just-- Poor Alli.
Just screamed and screamed
and screamed.
Nobody should have to hear that.
I don't understand.
Why didn't anyone
call the police?
It was so awful.
So loud.
Everybody figured someone else,
surely, would call the cops,
you know, after
all that screaming.
That's what happened--
must've been what happened.
Everybody just thought
the same thing:
that somebody else was
gonna take care of it.
It's not that hard to
understand, really.
I thought you said
you weren't here.
I wasn't.
So what if more than one person
called the police.
Every single one of you should
have been calling the police.
What do you want from me?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
It's just--
The police, they think
it was random,
that it was a mugging.
Yeah.
Yeah, some crackhead.
Do you believe that?
If that's what they say.
What do I know?
I'm just trying
to make sense of all this.
I don't understand who would
want to hurt Allison.
She said something
to me about, um...
about a man in her life.
Someone she cared about.
Does that ring any bells?
Listen, I've explained
all this to the detective.
I barely knew her,
all right?
She was my neighbour.
Seemed like a sweet girl.
I wave at her, in the hallway.
She gave me the keys
to her apartment
so I could go in
and water her plants
when she would go away
with her boyfriend.
That's it.
Her boyfriend.
Yeah, scruffy kid.
Artsy type.
But he may have
been around for months.
What's his name?
You and Allison were close,
and you never talked
about her boyfriend?
I've bothered you enough. Thank
you so much for the coffee.
I'm gonna-- I should go.
Oh, oh, wait, wait, wait.
We're just getting
to know each other.
I can't send you
back out in the cold.
No, really, I should take off.
Let me make us some dinner.
I have some frozen dinners
I can warm up.
You like brandy?
No, but you know, I wouldn't
say no to a glass of water.
Oh, that's no trouble at all.
Like ice?
You want ice, sweetheart?
Ow.
Hey, you all right?
Where is he?
Who? Where is who?
The guy with the knife!
Where is he?
Who?
The guy, where'd he go?
There's nobody here.
Okay, how about
we try this again?
I am Detective Peter Rafferty,
and you are not
a friend or relative of
Allison Parks, correct?
Correct.
Did you know Miss Parks?
No.
But you have a perfectly
good reason
for snooping around
her apartment.
I was one of the nurses on duty
when she came in.
I was there when she died.
I'm gonna call that a "no."
I didn't take anything.
I was just looking around.
Looking for what?
Anything.
Somebody has to
find out who did this.
You're right.
Someone needs to find out.
I happen to be the
lead investigator.
I saw you on the news. Didn't
exactly inspire any confidence.
Ma'am, crimes like this are
fairly complicated,
but the system works.
Given enough time,
the bad guy always gets caught.
You believe any of that?
I'll call that a "no."
Whoever did this,
Allison knew her. She told me.
Miss Parks told you?
She looked at me.
She looked right
at me and she said,
"He loved me."
It was the last thing she said.
Yeah, I know,
I'm just some nurse,
but I don't think that's
something I would say
if my attacker was
some random crack addict.
Ma'am, the hospital said that
she died in the ambulance.
That's not-- no, that's wrong.
Well, actually, right here.
"Despite all efforts, I was
unable to kick-start her heart."
That's what it says.
Well, sometimes there are
discrepancies.
Between alive and dead?
She was alive.
That's fine, ma'am.
Go on, please.
This wasn't a mugging.
Whoever killed Allison knew her,
loved her.
If you have any evidence
suggesting that there's some
sort of conspiracy--
Even if the hospital was wrong,
which is highly possible,
considering how badly they
screwed up on my tonsils--
even if-- I mean, "He loved me"
could mean anything.
It could mean a puppy she had
when she was nine years old.
No, look, that's not it.
I know what she meant.
So you went to her apartment?
Yeah, I felt like I had to
help her. Somebody has to.
Why were you running?
I-- I thought I saw someone.
You thought you saw
someone in the apartment?
No...
Well, I--
Look, it was dark, you know...
and... I probably
just got spooked.
And... this is gonna sound
really crazy, but...
It was like I was imagining
the murder through her eyes.
I was there.
And then, you showed up,
and it was gone.
Just out of curiosity,
are you currently using
any psychiatric drugs?
Go to hell.
"Just out of curiosity."
That's real subtle.
It's not like you weren't
thinking it too.
Miss Monahan. Kate.
Hold up, please.
Are you arresting me? Because
if not, I'm gonna go home.
Look, I am sorry about
Detective Canto back there.
He's a good cop, just not always
known for his tact.
Well, whatever. Forget it.
Take this, please.
If you remember anything,
anything at all,
or if you just wanna talk,
feel free to call me anytime.
You know, I'm not
the bad guy here.
I don't know;
it's hard to explain.
It felt like I was really there.
But it was just like your
imagination, right?
I don't know.
I mean, it felt so real.
Do you hear yourself?
Yeah, I do.
Your brain was hit
with enough voltage...
I'm just glad you're not talking
to trees at this point.
Thank you. Thanks.
Hey, I don't understand
what you were doing
in the girl's apartment
in the first place.
This... is Allison's boyfriend,
and I think I know
where I can find him.
You took this from a crime
scene?
The cops aren't doing anything.
Nobody's doing anything but me.
Maybe I could help you schedule
some time up on the 4th floor.
Oh, my god.
I didn't mean it like that.
Listen, Valerie, I don't need
a stupid shrink.
I need somebody I can trust.
I need somebody who believes me.
You're my best friend.
Kaitlyn, you need to drop this
before you get yourself killed.
Katie?
Sorry, I'm running late, Mom.
It'll be ready in about ten.
(Glass shattering)
Mom, are you okay?
Mom!
Mom? Oh, God. Mom!
Listen to me. Listen to me, Mom.
You're having--
Listen to me! You're having an
allergic reaction.
Just stay focused. Please stay
focused on me, right now.
I need you to calm down.
Breathe. This is epinephrine.
Watch.
It's adrenaline for the
swelling.
You're gonna feel a little
pinch, and you're gonna be fine.
All right, try and slow down
your breath.
Slow down your breath.
Mom? Look at me. Look at me.
Breathe. Breathe.
(Breathing)
There you go.
Good.
It's okay.
You gotta stop scaring me
like that.
What would I do without you?
Allison was taken from us
suddenly,
and without warning.
Her death was random
and heartbreaking.
It should remind us all
to cherish the short time we
have upon this earth.
Today may be filled
with sadness,
yet we take comfort
in our knowledge
that while Allison's body
has passed on,
her soul remains with us,
now and forever.
Her memory...
provides us with
strength and guidance.
Now, please, may we bow our
heads in silent prayer.
Let us pray.
(Tires screeching)
(Cars honking)
Who are you?
I'm-- It's--
Are you a cop?
No.
I was there when Allison died.
This is where we used to come
and hang out all the time...
listen to tracks
I was working on.
I'm a DJ, so...
You know, Allison said something
right before she died,
and I'm just trying to figure
out what it means.
What did she say?
"He loved me."
She said it like...
she couldn't believe
this was happening to her.
Like somebody she loved
really betrayed her.
I don't know who Alli
was in love with,
but it sure as hell wasn't me.
How long had it been since you
talked to Alli?
Months ago.
Really? That long?
Yeah, Alli and I, we dated,
but that was like, 6 months ago.
And we didn't talk since then.
Alli was a mess,
and she started going through
depression a year ago, and--
She was depressed.
Yeah, well, who isn't, right?
I don't know. She started seeing
some quack doctor.
I don't know what
they talked about, but--
I don't know, we started
fighting all the time.
You know, she started
blaming me for shit.
For crazy shit. I just couldn't
take it anymore. I ended it.
You ended it?
Yeah.
I mean, Alli, she was cool,
but she was out of her mind.
I just bounced out of there
and I never looked back.
Do you know if there was anyone
else in her life?
No clue.
That's between her...
and God.
And that shrink.
Do you know his name?
Doctor, uh...
Bennett or... Barrett.
I don't know.
She just always
called him "Graham."
Thanks.
Why do you care
who killed Alli anyway?
Somebody has to.
He loved me.
(Screaming)
Go on.
Oh, um...
Sorry-- I lost
my train of thought.
It happens.
I don't remember
what I was saying.
It's okay.
Sometimes we lose track
of what we're talking about.
Our memories--
we get caught up in them.
It was really vivid.
You were talking about your
mother's illness?
I was?
Mm-hmm.
My mother?
Yeah.
No, I don't think so.
You wanna hide from this.
I know. It's okay. It's painful.
But trust me, it'll hurt less
to keep talking.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Did you give up your apartment
when she became ill?
Mm-hmm.
Why? Because it was easier?
To live with her while she was
undergoing her treatments.
Look, I don't need
a pity party here, okay?
I made choices.
But like you said yourself,
you're all she had.
No.
What do you mean?
You gave up your own life
to take care of her.
How does that make you feel?
That's not why I'm here.
I love my mother.
This isn't about her.
Happy birthday.
What is this?
Another day,
another body.
No, no, no, no.
Give this to Gehrke. Come on.
I can't. Reed put this on us.
Didn't even say "pretty please."
What?
Something's not right here.
How about we take a case
we can actually solve?
There's something this nurse
said that just stuck with me.
Maybe it was her
pretty blue eyes.
Oh, and this looks like just a
random mugging.
Maybe too much.
It's like the attacker did
everything humanly possible
to make this look like a
case-closed mugging gone wrong.
I don't know.
Maybe she was onto something.
The nurse that sees dead people?
Yeah, we should definitely
substitute
her judgement for ours.
Maybe it was somebody
that she knew.
Maybe it was somebody she knew
that disguised himself
and made a conscious decision to
do it in a public place.
Maybe he wanted to do it
right in the centre of the
goddamn courtyard
so there would be a witness,
a witness that would testify
that it wasn't him.
I'm gonna tell you the same
thing that you told me,
the first day on the job.
It's never that complicated.
DR. BARRETT:
Why are you here?
Well, I'd like to
talk about Allison.
Ms. Parks' death
was an awful, awful thing.
And, um...
when something like that
happens, we feel...
out of control, angry, helpless.
These are normal things.
It's perfectly normal
to feel these things.
There's nothing you could do.
There's nothing any of us
could've done.
Who loved her?
Hm?
I think whoever did this
loved her.
Do you have any idea
who it could be?
I'm not about to talk to you
about my former patients.
Besides, Allison
hasn't seen me in months.
Why not? What happened?
Was it depression?
Was there a boyfriend? Was it...
I see our time is up.
All right, wait a minute--
But I do think it would be good
for you to come back
and for us to keep talking.
Mom? I'm home!
Mom?
Mom!
Katie?
What? What is it, honey?
I was just here and I--
What?
You were gone.
I just-- I just walked in here,
and I didn't see you,
and I thought--
I thought maybe you had wandered
off or something.
Wandered off? I wish.
Honey, you should relax.
Did you hang that
picture back up?
You did.
I did?
Don't you remember?
KAITLYN:
You told me to call you if I had
any new information.
PETER:
That's right.
Should I come down there?
No. No, here's no good.
Why?
Can we do this someplace else?
Uh, you know the diner
by the hospital?
I'm on my way.
Great.
CANTO:
What do you got?
I've got a lead, pal.
Wouldn't happen to be a blonde,
about 5'8", would it?
It was unique.
Kind of like this.
Whoever killed her, took it.
So, how do you know this?
Did you see a broken necklace at
the crime scene?
No, I didn't.
Well, she wasn't wearing it when
she came into the ER,
so find the necklace,
find the killer.
Okay, well, it's not
that simple.
Well, it's a clue,
so do something.
Okay, I bust you snooping around
the crime scene.
Suddenly you have inside
information.
You have new evidence.
Let's consider for the moment
that I'm not a complete idiot.
You want me to believe you?
Why don't you start
by not lying to me?
I'm not lying to you.
You're not telling me something.
Try me.
I'm having memories.
What does that mean,
"memories?"
I'm remembering the murder.
I know things
I can't possibly know.
It's like I'm reliving it
through her eyes,
over and over again.
I died that night too.
Listen, in the ER, we hit
Allison with the paddles,
and the electricity went through
her body and into mine,
and my heart stopped.
And once they revived me,
I started seeing things
that weren't there,
and having memories
that weren't mine.
If you interfere
with this case again,
I'm gonna be forced
to arrest you
for obstruction of justice.
Do you understand that?
Look, I know how crazy I sound.
Do you?
I do. Yes! I do.
But I'm not lying about this.
And she was wearing
a necklace.
No, I saw her wearing
that necklace.
I saw the killer take it, and
run with it, and now it's gone.
Okay, the perp
also stole her wallet.
It would make sense
that he took any jewellery.
It still fits the scenario
of a mugging.
It wasn't a mugging.
This was personal.
I saw him go for the necklace
like it was his,
like he wanted it back
while he was stabbing me.
Stabbing... her, you mean.
Oh, yeah. Yes, of course.
Of course.
I think I can prove it.
I knew it!
I knew your were a cop!
Just have a couple of questions
for you, all right?
So, what, you're gonna
arrest me now?
Let's just keep the focus
on me for right now.
Look, I already told you cops
everything. So what do you want?
We want to know
about the necklace.
I don't know anything
about a necklace.
You've never seen this before?
Yeah... That necklace.
Yeah, I know that necklace.
What?
You give it to her?
No.
You know who did?
Look, that was Alli's fave, man.
She wore it every day.
I don't know. I thought
maybe she bought it.
All I know is she never took it
off, once she got it.
You mind if I go
through your gear.
I don't have anything to hide.
You're not gonna find anything.
You're not gonna find--
It's not like I have it.
So, what? You're not a cop,
or what?
No. I'm not.
Well, so why do you know
about the necklace?
What are you,
a psychic or something?
Well, we need to
find this necklace.
I thought you said
it wasn't that simple.
Honestly, at the time, I didn't
think the necklace existed.
So, what do we do now?
Well, tell me about
these flashes,
these visions, the clues.
How do you have them?
What sets them off?
I don't know, really.
I thought I was going crazy.
And sometimes I don't even know
that they've happened
until after they're over.
PETER:
Well, we're about to
trigger one right now.
If anything's going to set one
off, it's being here.
This is exactly where
we found the body.
So you, uh, you seeing anything?
Feeling anything?
I don't think
it works like that.
Okay, just relax, Kate.
Try and remember. You've been
here before in your memory.
So, right here, this is where
you ended up, right?
Yeah, but I don't-- I don't
really want to see it again.
We need this, Kate.
There's nobody else here.
You're safe, okay?
Nothing bad is going to happen.
Shit.
Just walk me through it from
your perspective.
She, what? She ran out?
She tripped? She fell?
Yeah.
Okay, and the guy is crouched
over, he's attacking?
Yes.
Stabbing.
Yeah.
Okay. That's good.
That's good.
Can you see his face?
No, it's too dark.
Okay, just-- just--
close your eyes
and try and see it, Kate.
You want me to close my eyes?
Can you tell me
what he's wearing?
Um...
He's in black,
and he's got a knife.
Okay, good. That's good.
Can you describe it?
It's a big knife.
It's a kitchen knife.
And... the necklace?
You have the necklace on?
Yeah. Yeah, it's around my neck,
and, um...
And he yanks it, and takes off,
and then I wake up,
and it's the same place,
every time.
It's the same place
I wake up, every time.
Okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's all right.
He's been watching us
the whole time.
Who?
Please tell me you saw that.
Okay, come on. Come on.
We're never going to
find it here.
Well, I'm gonna look anyway.
He pulled it off
her neck, Peter.
I got 14 eyewitnesses, Kaitlyn.
The only one that saw something
is the one that wasn't there.
So, humour me, please.
I'm gonna check in the bedroom.
(Phone ringing)
Don't touch anything.
Hey, Val. I'm sorry, I just got
wrapped up in something.
Can you-- No, I'm fine.
Yeah, my mom's fine too. There's
just something I need to--
I gotta go.
Any luck?
No.
You might be right.
I don't think it's here.
So how do we find it?
Well, I can add it to the
evidence report.
With any luck, it'll turn up at
a pawn shop,
and it's not particularly
valuable.
There's a pawn shop
over by my apartment.
I-- I-- I've got this covered.
It's not your responsibility,
Kaitlyn.
Do not let this
take over your life.
I'm fine.
I know. I know.
But I'm on this,
with a new lead, thanks to you.
So, what am I
supposed to do now?
You're supposed to
take care of yourself.
That's it. Come on.
Come on.
DR. BARRETT:
If I could, I'd like to bring us
back to your mother's illness.
Big surprise.
If you could, I'd like you
to start talking about
how it felt
when you first started
taking care of your mother.
You know, the police
don't think Allison's murder
was random anymore.
They found some new evidence.
I just thought you might
find that interesting.
Do you find it interesting?
Yes, I do.
And your mother's illness--
Isn't.
But I did what
I had to do, you know?
She just got so sick so fast.
There wasn't really time to
think about anything else.
You know, like in the ER.
You don't think, you just react.
She needed daily care,
and I wanted it done right,
so... I don't know;
moving in with her seemed
like the only solution.
To be honest with you,
I didn't think. I just reacted.
I wanna be there for her,
at the end.
So, uh, yeah...
I mean, yeah, it's--
it's frustrating,
but she needs me, so...
Do you feel like she's
a burden at all?
No. Never.
No resentment or anger
in your difficult situation?
You're only human. I mean, it
doesn't mean you don't love her.
She gave me everything.
She never asked me for anything.
And you want me to sit here
and whine about it?
God...
I can see why Allison
stopped seeing you.
Just trying to help you.
When I moved in with my mother,
she said she would never
be a burden to me,
and she never was.
That's good.
I'm sure she just
wants you to be happy.
Sometimes, accepting
your feelings--
I found a gun, though.
Gun?
Yeah, I don't know
what kind it was.
It was a handgun.
I was looking
through her closets,
going through some stuff,
and I found it in a shoebox.
Didn't really make any sense,
because my mother hates guns.
Eventually I found the receipt.
She bought it the day
she was diagnosed.
And what did you do?
I got rid of it.
Did you confront her about it?
Kaitlyn, I think your
frustration with your mother
and your inability to
communicate your feelings
is what's fuelling
your unhealthy obsession
with Allison.
Fucking great.
Where do I send the cheque?
You feel powerless
to help your mother,
so you're struggling
to find a situation
that you can take control of.
She didn't deserve to die!
She was innocent,
and nobody is fighting for her!
They're just-- they're brushing
this thing off
like it's something random,
and I am the only one doing a
goddamn thing about it!
Okay. Okay.
I'm so tired. I can't think.
Yeah, it's okay.
Just take a deep breath.
Nice deep breath.
Breathe.
You can say anything in here.
You can think, feel,
anything in here.
You're safe. It's okay.
All right?
We shouldn't do this.
Oh...
It's okay, Allison.
It's only me.
What about your wife?
She can never find out.
Help me.
Get off me!
You okay?
We were lovers.
Excuse me?
Kaitlyn, are you okay?
Don't touch me!
Don't you ever touch me!
Man, please tell me you didn't
do what I think you did.
Peter, I know who did it.
Come here. Come here.
I told you we shouldn't
do this here.
I found a murderer. Where do you
want me to go? A fire station?
Okay, so you saw something.
Yeah, Dr. Graham Barrett.
Allison's therapist.
He's the killer. I've been going
there, pretending I'm a patient.
Dammit, Kate,
do you hear yourself?
Hey, don't throw this
in my face.
I put myself in her surroundings
like your told me to,
and it triggered something.
This is not a game.
I told you to lay off,
that I would handle this.
Allison and Dr. Barrett were
having an affair.
I saw it. I saw it as clear
as I'm seeing you.
He kissed me-- I mean her.
He kissed her.
He kissed you?
Yeah, in the memory.
I don't really know
how else to explain it,
but he didn't want
his wife to find out,
and I guess they started
this thing on the side,
and then it got too serious.
And then she threatened
to go to the wife--
Yeah, and then he kills her to
keep her quiet.
You have to arrest him,
right now.
I can't arrest someone, Kate,
without evidence. I just--
He killed her!
Keep your voice down.
Right now, all we have is your
word and your vision,
which is all we have right now.
That's it.
I thought you said
you believed me.
I do believe you, Kate. I do.
But there's protocol.
There's procedure.
And unfortunately, your way
won't hold up in court,
and it'll most likely
cost me my job.
Please tell me
you understand that.
I understand.
You gotta let me
run with this, Kate.
I'm not sure what I told him.
In session, I blacked out for a
few seconds, maybe minutes,
and I don't know what I said.
I don't know what he knows.
What if he knows that
I know he's the killer.
I mean, if he was willing to do
that to Allison,
what could happen to me?
Nothing.
Nothing's gonna
happen to you, Kate.
I won't let anything happen
to you, I promise. Okay?
Is he still out there?
Yeah, it's his job.
Makes me nervous.
Peter said he wanted to have
somebody watching us all night.
He wants us to be safe.
You better take him some coffee.
Think so?
Well, he's gonna be sitting
outside in the cold all night.
We want him wide awake.
It's the least we could do.
All right.
I know all about
your psychic nurse.
Canto was right.
You are too close to this.
Hey, Rafferty, this--
We're not wasting any more of
the taxpayer's money.
There's no reason to keep a car
outside the nurse's place
all damn night.
Man, I did it for your own good.
Somebody order a coffee?
What are you doing here?
You are gonna give Allison a
message from me.
Please get in the car.
Please-- please don't get out
of the car. Please--
I just want to talk.
Are you drunk?
I've been thinking
a lot about Allison, and...
Do you, still talk--
do you talk to her?
No, of course not.
Yeah, but you're like one of
those psychics or something.
No, could you please
get back in the car?
Yeah, but I just
want to talk to her.
Let go of me.
Let go of me!
Aahh!
You have the right to remain
silent. I suggest you use it.
I just want to talk to Alli!
You all right?
You gotta cut him loose, man.
I just need a little more time.
CANTO:
You can't charge him. You can't
hold him. You know how it works.
We didn't find shit in his
apartment, his car either.
What about his alibi?
Checked out.
He was DJ-ing the night
that Parks was murdered.
Yeah?
30 witnesses can
place him at the scene.
Might be a douchebag,
but he's not our killer.
So...
You are a pathetic little
piece of shit.
You're gonna stay away from her.
You hear me?
I catch you within
half a mile of her
and I swear to God I will break
every bone in your body.
You hear me?
Cut him loose.
(Knocking)
Hey.
Hi.
You been okay?
Yeah, you know... You?
Been following the shrink.
Care you see what I found?
My mom's asleep. This might
not be the best time.
Any suggestion on what
I should do with all of this?
So this is Barrett's place?
Yep. Lives with his wife
on the top floor.
The night that Allison Parks
was killed,
he had the whole place
to himself. No alibi.
Really?
Yeah, wife was out of town.
Some convention.
Turns out she goes out of town
about once a month.
Well, then, that must've been
when he had Allison over.
That would be my theory
at the moment.
We need to search his place.
We need to find the necklace,
the knife... something.
We do, but that requires a
search warrant.
But you can get that.
The press is already
watching me like a hawk.
They think I'm working on
another case as it is.
But...
I can get one.
If that's what we need...
I'll get one.
I don't know how,
but I'll make it happen.
Oh, and to think,
when you first met me,
you were ready to toss me
in the loony bin
and throw away the key.
I was a little skeptical.
Oh, a little bit? Okay.
Well, thank you,
for believing in me.
No, thank you.
For what?
It's been a long time
since...
since I believed in anything.
Sorry...
Sorry! I--
I haven't snuck a boy up here
since high school.
My mom is in the other room.
Then we will
have to be very quiet.
I haven't slept that well
in months.
What's wrong?
She's not there.
What do you mean?
Your mother.
There's no one living
in that room.
There hasn't been for a long
time, as far as I can tell.
What are you talking about?
Mom?
Hey, Ma!
What's wrong, honey?
Nothing. Nothing.
That's not fun--
You're not funny!
Do you have someone over?
It's Peter.
Mom, uh, this is
Detective Peter Rafferty.
Peter, this is my mom.
Okay, now let's have some eggs.
Patricia Monahan, aged 62,
died two months ago
from complications
from pancreatic cancer.
That doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, well, I'm looking right
at her death certificate, man.
Trust me, she ain't breathing.
Thanks for covering for me,
the past few days.
You feeling okay? You seem--
What? Happy?
I was gonna say "distracted."
Oh, well, okay...
Peter, you know, the cop?
He came over last night,
and he brought some food,
and we had some wine--
Sweetie, I am so sorry.
Why? I thought you'd
be happy for me.
Hello, Kaitlyn.
Wait. Wait, wait...
what is this?
It's good to see you again.
It's been a long time.
No! Get away from me!
She's just here
to help you get better.
No, I don't need help!
I don't need this!
Let go of me!
You! What did you do?
What did you tell them?
What is going on?
What's going on?
What did you do?
I told them the truth.
Get a hold of yourself,
for God's sake.
I did everything. I did
everything you told me to do.
Calm down, now. Calm down.
We talked about this.
You can't just show up here.
You said you would
stay with me.
We were going to be
together forever!
Allison, you stop it.
You shouldn't be here right now.
You said you loved me.
Allison, I said stop it!
What is happening to me?
Hey!
What have they got me on?
It's okay, honey.
Dr. Rosen's--
No, I saw Dr. Rosen
and Dr. Barrett.
He's-- he's trying
to keep my quiet.
We're trying
to help you now.
Okay? It's okay.
Valerie, he's gonna
try and kill me.
It's okay, honey.
Just relax.
No, I--
No!
It's okay.
There you go, sweetie.
Go away.
I'm sorry, Kaitlyn.
You were the only one who
believed me.
They're just gonna monitor you
for a few days.
Just to make sure
everything is okay.
Did you tell Dr. Rosen
you fucked me,
or did you leave
that part out?
What about my mother?
What if she needs her shots,
and I'm not there to help her?
You don't need to worry about
that right now.
What does that mean?
All that's important
is that you get healthy.
That's it: that you
get back on your feet.
I am healthy. I'm healthy!
I don't need this!
I am so confused. This doesn't
make any sense to me.
Come on, we have
to help Allison.
We've gotta find that necklace,
and you have to
arrest Dr. Barrett.
I'm not crazy, Peter.
You know that. You know!
Come on, I'm not crazy.
I had a memory.
A real one. It was like the one
with the necklace.
I want to show you something.
I found this in
your mother's house.
So?
I know you took this from
Allison's apartment,
the day I found you in the
courtyard. I know that.
Yeah, I had a vision.
The other picture fell,
and that led me to--
Look at what she's wearing.
You saw this in the photo.
Not in some vision or memory.
You saw it in the photo,
and then you subconsciously
tied it to Allison's murder.
No, I'm-- I never saw that
necklace. Not that way.
I care about you, Kaitlyn.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'm here for you.
But you have to want
to get help.
Hello, Kaitlyn. You came to see
me a couple of times
when your mother first got sick.
Do you remember?
How about we take these off?
Hm? And talk a little bit.
Are you starting
to feel a little better?
Okay.
Detective Rafferty?
She's suffering from severe
disorientation.
I think the day her mother died
was so traumatic
she's blocked it out.
Now her mind is working to try
and explain everything all away.
Over time, and in
the right environment,
she'll find a way
to sort out what's real.
Here's my card.
It has my direct number.
As more questions arise...
Thank you.
Kaitlyn...
Kaitlyn?
Kate!
Cop says to the hooker,
"It's not polite to talk
with your mouth full."
(Phone ringing)
Yeah, it's Rafferty.
Then where the hell is she?
Kaitlyn!
Kaitlyn, open up! It's me!
(Shattering)
KAITLYN (recording):
Hi, Mom?
It's not important.
Are you okay?
I know. Can you just hold on
a little bit longer?
There's something I have to do.
(Screaming)
How did you get in here?
I know what you did.
I know you killed Allison Parks.
I saw it. I found this.
I saw it.
I saw everything!
How about we talk this through
like reasonable people?
Think we can do that?
Kaitlyn, I didn't kill anyone.
I didn't kill Allison.
I found her necklace.
I don't know what
you think that means.
Proof!
Proof of what?
That I gave her a necklace
as an innocent gift?
It's a clarity symbol.
I thought it would help her.
She gave it back to me.
No! No, stop lying!
I saw everything.
What have you seen?
I saw the way you treated her.
I saw the way you looked at her,
the way you threw her away when
you were done with her, and now,
now you're trying to do
the same thing with me, again.
But that's not gonna work.
I saw you! I saw you
murder Allison Parks!
Let me help you.
I know you think you're doing
the right thing here.
I realize that,
but I want you to listen to the
sound of my voice, Kaitlyn.
You're suffering from something
we call post-event information.
It's a-- after a trauma,
your memories are vulnerable
to facts and suggestions,
ideas that you learn
after the tragedy has occurred.
I saw you at the hospital
with Dr. Rosen.
You don't know me.
I didn't kill anyone.
The mind is a complicated organ.
Our memories are like
a jigsaw puzzle.
But your mind is tricking you.
It's creating puzzle pieces that
don't even exist right now.
Shut up!
Let me help you.
You need help.
I know what I saw.
I don't know what
you want from me.
I want the truth.
I want the truth about Allison.
I want to know what's real.
Real.
You want the truth.
Truth is that we had an affair.
And I don't know how you--
This was our secret.
I didn't kill her.
My wife and I, we were
having problems, and...
One day, after a really
emotional session,
Allison and I, we kissed...
I know that was wrong.
I know it now.
I never meant for it
to become serious,
but it did.
Hell, we ended up seeing each
other after every session.
Why didn't you come forward?
Why didn't you come forward when
she was murdered
and tell people what you knew?
Why would I want to put my wife
through all that, after?
What would be the point?
If the affair ever got out,
my career would be ruined.
I would be finished.
Allison appreciated that.
She said she understood that.
When I went to break it off...
She asked me to leave my wife,
and I told her I couldn't.
She threw the necklace
back in my face,
and she walked out the door,
and I never saw her again.
That's the truth.
You gotta believe me.
I would never kill Alli--
I would never hurt her.
Not in a million years.
I loved her.
I love her still.
(Gunshot)
Kaitlyn, wait, wait!
No, no, no, no...
I got him.
Okay, okay, okay. I need you to
put the gun down.
Help me.
I'm gonna put my gun down.
He did it!
I need you to put it down now.
He killed her. You believe me,
right? That he killed her?
I'm innocent!
Shut up!
Kaitlyn! Kaitlyn!
Listen to me, you're confused
right now.
Stop saying that to me.
Kate, this is not
about Allison, okay?
This is about your mother.
Listen to me, you did everything
you could, Kate. You did.
But sometimes,
it's just not enough.
You know that.
She loved me.
This, Kate, this is not,
gonna bring her back, okay?
Kate, I know what happened.
I read the medical files, Kate.
I know what happened,
the day that she died.
(Glass shattering)
Did that stupid picture
fall again?
I'll be right there.
Your mother was sick, Kate.
She had cancer.
There's not rhyme or reason
for it.
Mom?
Mom!
Mom, hang on.
Hang on! Hang on, Mom!
Mom, stay with me, please!
You're okay. You're okay.
Mom, just a minute,
just a minute.
Please, please, please hang on!
Hang on!
Mom! Hang on, please!
Mom! Please don't!
Mom! Mom!
No! Please don't!
Mom! Please!
No! No!
Mom! Mom!
(Crying)
I just-- I just-- I let her die.
She loved me.
She loved you.
It's almost exactly what you
thought you heard Allison say.
You see what's happening here?
This man did not kill Allison.
I know you'd like there to be
more to this, Kate,
but there's just not.
Your mother's gone, Kate.
(Screaming)
But there's absolutely
nothing...
nothing that you
can do about this.
Help me.
I thought I told you nobody
could find out.
(Gunshot)
Goddammit, Kate!
Detective Rafferty. I need an
ambulance to my location.
Shots fired. I have a man down.
Please respond.
Priority three.
MINISTER:
Life is precious,
but life is also
beyond our control.
While difficult to accept,
we often have little power
over such things.
When our time comes,
and our time must come,
it does so without warning
or explanation.
Thus we should embrace
every second
we are allowed to remain
on this vibrant planet.
take care
thank u
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org