Captioning made possible by
warner bros.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
There's just
nothin' down there.
Nothin'. I haven't
seen a building
In, like, 20 minutes.
Look at that.
We're not on vacation,
hap, remember.
Cheer up, will ya?
Tell that
To her, partner.
Better hang on, guys.
It's gonna get rough again.
Whoa.
There goes my lunch.
Detective eckhart, I'm
detective ellie burr.
Oh, hi.
Nice to meet you.
Here, let me help.
Eckhart: How ya doin'?
Good.
Halibut fishing capital
of the world. Ok.
Detective dormer, such
an honor to meet you.
I'm detective
ellie burr.
Welcome to nightmute.
Got the car right here.
It's so incredible
to be working with you,
Detective dormer.
I've followed
all of your cases--
Theodore dineli,
frank prud'homme,
Uh, the ocean park
shootings,
And especially
The leland street
murders.
Is that where, uh,
Ronald langley cut you
In the basement
of 325 leland street?
You certainly
did your homework, detective.
The leland street
murders
Was my case study
at the academy.
So, I'm gonna just
take you guys
Over to the lodge
and drop your--
Just take us to the station.
Right.
We need to get started.
Most homicides
are solved
By work done
in the first 72 hours.
Well, it's 48 hours.
We're a day behind.
But who's countin'?
Uh, yeah, come in.
They got you
behind a desk, huh?
Charlie bubbles.
How ya doin', man?
I haven't seen you
boys since, well--
Hey, charlie.
I don't know.
7 years?
8 years.
I am old.
Charlie: Ellie,
get everyone in the bullpen.
I gotta show you off
a little.
Nice kid.
Yeah, loves the job.
Yeah.
You know, when I called
buck for advice on this,
I never
actually expected
That he'd send
you guys up here.
Something about that
bullshit you've got
Going on down there
with internal affairs?
They're moving in,
charlie.
Aw, come on, man.
It's nothing.
It's the usual crap.
Buck just figured
You could use some help
up here.
They got finn and kentor
on narcotics theft,
Corelli on a bad shooting.
Now the fuckers
are wading through files
Looking for headlines,
but, uh--
Yeah, it's gonna
blow over.
Got a message here
from a guy named warfield.
I.A.'s pit bull.
He wants to be posted
on your movements.
I think you'll find
It's a bit more
straightforward up here.
Good guys, bad guys,
But a lot less
public relations.
It's simple...
Except for this.
[charlie clears throat]
ok, listen up.
Detectives dormer
and eckhart
On loan from buck lundgard,
Los angeles
robbery and homicide.
They'll be helping us
with the connell case.
Helping?
We're damn lucky
to have 'em.
Anything they want to see,
you show them.
Anyplace they want to go,
you take 'em.
This is detective
fred duggar.
He's been heading up
the investigation.
Well, hello, fred.
Pleasure.
Nice to meet you.
Want to get
right on it?
All right.
You seen what we got?
Yeah. I want to
start with the body.
You got the report,
right?
Well, I want to see
the body for myself.
Ok.
Coroner:
Clear cause of death
Was herniation
of the brain stem
Due to intercerebral
hemorrhage.
Beaten to death.
These contusions?
Coroner:
Superficial.
Most of the trauma
was to her face
And the top
of her neck.
Eckhart:
Any signs of rig?
No.
This one covers
an older bruise.
Coroner: There's
an older one here, too.
They're both in the report.
He washed her hair.
Scrubbed her nails.
Duggar: It's all
in the report, detective.
Doesn't say in the report
that he clipped 'em, too.
She could've
clipped 'em herself.
Nope.
No polish
on the ends of the nails.
She painted 'em herself.
Someone else
cut 'em shorter.
Toes, too.
Eckhart: Naked
when you found her?
Duggar: Yeah. Last seen
wearing a red paisley dress.
No fibers,
flakes, hairs?
We know about
forensics work up here.
I told you.
Body gave us nothing.
Oh, she gave us
plenty.
All this trouble,
all this care.
Why?
Ellie: He knew her.
He knows we can
connect him to it.
This isn't some random psycho,
crime of passion?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe.
But whatever happened,
His reaction to it
wasn't passion.
He didn't panic.
Didn't chop her up or burn
her beyond recognition.
He just thought about what
we would be looking for
And then calmly removed
all those traces.
No haste, no rush.
Why would he
clip the nails
After
scrubbing them?
Well, manipulating the body.
Prolonging the moment.
Eckhart:
No mutilation.
Not this time.
You think
there's been others?
No.
But there's gonna be.
This guy,
He crossed the line,
And he didn't even blink.
You don't
come back from that.
Ok, let's go find out
who kay was.
Fred said
not to touch anything,
So I haven't tidied up yet.
She hates it when
I go into her room anyway.
Thank you,
mrs. Connelly.
Mmm.
So, she went to a party
Friday night?
Ellie: Um,
not exactly a party.
It's, um, a local dive
where the kids hang out.
No diary, huh?
We didn't find one,
But her mom did say
that she keeps a journal.
Duggar: Friends said she argued
with her boyfriend Friday,
And she stormed off
just after midnight.
She did, huh?
This is interesting.
Who is this?
Tanya francke,
Kay's best friend.
I want to talk to her.
Who...Is kay connell?
Who is she?
Is she popular,
Or is she a loner?
Did she like this town?
Did she want to bolt
The first chance
she got?
Did she have,
uh, dreams?
She knew this guy.
We know her,
maybe we can know him.
This is designer.
This is expensive.
The boyfriend,
uh, randy--
Randy stetz.
He could afford this?
He's still
in high school.
Well, her mother
didn't buy it.
What are we
thinkin'?
Oh, I don't know.
Uh, stepfather?
Any rich uncles?
No.
An admirer.
Yeah.
All right, I want to talk
to the boyfriend.
I can get him
to the station.
No, no. No. I want
to go to the school,
Where he is
in his class.
Pull him out
in front of his friends,
Catch him off-guard.
I want to, you know,
get people talkin'.
So, how far away
is the school?
[clears throat]
It's 10:00,
detective dormer.
You bet.
At night.
Oh.
So when does it get
dark around here?
Uh, it doesn't.
Not this time of year.
Yeah,
I heard about that.
How come you didn't
know that, hap?
Lower 48.
Lower 48?
You're
not from here.
I can tell
by your walk.
How's that?
Unsure.
Huh.
Dormer and eckhart.
We have
a reservation.
Don't be fooled
By my friend's
frivolous demeanor.
Inside, he's all business.
Your restaurant
still serving?
Yeah. Kitchen's
about to close, though.
Oh. Well, we'll be quick.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Eckhart: Well, we got
the halibut calabrese,
Got the halibut olympian.
Keep going.
Halibut cajun-style.
Oh, I can't wait to see
what they got for dessert.
Natives are
getting restless.
We gotta talk.
No, we don't.
You just want
to sit tight, huh?
Nothing's changed.
Nothing's changed?
What the fuck
do you think we're doing
In the halibut fishing capital
of the world, will?
Buck figured charlie
could use the help--
Buck figured I.A.
Would be coming to me next,
And he was right.
Warfield had me
locked in his office
For 3 hours yesterday,
will.
3 fuckin' hours.
Hap,
He's rattlin'
your cage, pal.
That's all.
Me and trish
talked it through,
And, uh, I'm sorry,
But I gotta cut a deal.
Don't even say this
shit to me, hap.
You're not
gonna be involved.
I'm not?
No.
Of course I'm
gonna be involved.
You're a goddamn hero.
With your reputation,
he can't touch you.
My reputation's
the whole problem.
I mean,
you think warfield
Gives a flying fuck
about you
Shaking down a couple
of drug dealers?
You think that's gonna
get him his headlines?
He needs the big fish.
He's putting
the squeeze on you
To get to me.
It's very simple, hap.
But you're clean, will.
I'm a good cop, yeah.
But there's always
something they can use,
You know, to get
at your credibility.
You know that.
Have you any idea
What this is
gonna do?
I mean, just think
about all my cases.
All the cases
depended on my word,
My judgment.
All those fuckers
back on the street.
Now, you think
about that.
That's
what you'd do.
That's bullshit.
They got nothin' on you
Because there's
nothing to get.
Dobbs.
What about dobbs?
That's different.
It's different?
Because even warfield
doesn't want shit like dobbs
Back on the street.
It's a house
of cards, man.
Once it starts,
it's just gonna tumble.
All of it.
That's a chance
I gotta take, pal.
I got family, will.
Don't give me
that family shit.
Warfield made it clear:
I get probation.
We're cops, man.
This is not about us.
This is about all the
people who depend on us,
People with families.
I spent my life
doing this. My life.
You're gonna destroy it
like that.
Why? Why?
So some I.A. Prick
gets one step closer
To being
chief of police
Or playing golf
with the mayor
Or whatever the fuck
else he's after?
You finished?
Sorry. I gotta cut a deal.
So, make any decisions?
Um, boy, you do
everything around here?
After 11:00, pretty much.
Ah. Heh.
Over to you, will.
What are you having?
Lost my appetite.
Dormer: Excuse me.
Morning.
Hi.
What kind of calls
do you get around here?
Mostly drinking-related
problems,
Um, domestic abuse,
bar fights.
That sort of stuff.
People here,
they come from all over.
They come to live life
the way they want to,
So most people
keep themselves
To themselves.
Chief nyback won't
let me handle anything
Over a misdemeanor
anyway, so...
You shouldn't knock
misdemeanors.
No, but it's
such small stuff.
It gets so boring.
Well, it's
all about small stuff.
You know, small lies,
small mistakes.
People give themselves away
same in misdemeanors
As they do in murder cases.
It's just human nature.
Well, aren't you
gonna write that down?
Dormer: Friends
making you nervous, randy?
They think you did it?
You killed her?
No smoking
on school premises.
Did you love her?
Randy, did you love her?
Sure. She was nice.
"she was nice." wow.
Well, that makes me
all soft inside.
Ever occur to you
she didn't love you back?
She loved me.
Wanted me every night.
Oh, probably
to pass the time, I think.
A girl like kay connell,
She was looking for more
than some loser, right?
What can I say, officer?
Love is blind.
You live on your own?
On top of his grandpa's
building.
You don't have an alibi
for Friday night.
Didn't know
I was gonna need one.
At the party, what'd
you fight about?
Stuff. I don't know.
It's no big deal.
Oh, I heard
it was a loud fight.
I guess.
Yeah, I heard
it was pretty rough.
Wasn't rough.
Well, not like
the other times.
You know, those times
she wouldn't listen to you,
Couldn't keep
her mouth shut.
You keep fishing, man.
Eckhart: We saw
the bruises, randy.
They said
she was beaten up.
Not those bruises.
Randy, come on.
The old bruises.
Your bruises.
All right,
you know what?
I'm sick
of this bullshit.
I haven't
done anything wrong.
You haven't?
Hey, fuck you!
You're just
a little prick
In a leather jacket.
What the fuck
do you know?
Randy.
This whole thing
you're doing,
You know,
this fuck-the-world act,
Now, that might work
with your mama.
It might even work with
a couple of these local cops
Who've known you
long enough
To figure you're too dumb
ever to kill anyone
Without leaving
a couple of witnesses
And a signed confession.
It ain't gonna work with me...
Because I know things,
you understand?
I know...
You beat your girlfriend.
I know she was
seeing somebody else,
Somebody she might've
even gone to see
After she walked out on you
Friday night.
Now, are you
gonna tell us
Who that somebody
might be,
Or are you so fuckin' stupid
You're gonna leave yourself
As the last person
to see kay connell alive?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I couldn't get her
to tell me.
How hard did you try?
Pretty hard.
You think he, um--
no.
How'd it go?
We gotta find out
where this came from.
I tried. Um,
mrs. Connell doesn't know,
Her friends didn't know.
You try
the jewelry stores?
Small things.
Remember?
The second you're
About to dismiss
something,
Think about it.
Look at it again.
Want me
to write that down?
No, I'll
remember it.
[cell phone rings]
Ellie burr.
Where was it?
Duggar: In a fishing cabin
on the beach.
This is
definitely kay's?
Nyback:
Her books are in it.
Duggar:
Couple of kids found it.
Cabin been secured?
Francis is
headed there right now.
Well, you stop him.
Tell him to stay clear.
Nyback: Rich.
Biology and algebra.
Let's find out
who she studied with.
where she bought this.
"otherwise engaged,
Another j. Brody mystery."
Who reads this kind of crap?
I read
that kind of crap.
Read it after it's dusted.
Find anything
that strikes you plotwise,
Underlined passages.
Just let me know. Anything.
There it is. Diary.
Every word.
That's it.
Put it into evidence?
No, no.
Why?
Ellie, I want you
to call every radio
And tv station
from here to anchorage.
You tell 'em
we're looking for the bag
Kay connell
left the party with.
Get it on the air
in the next hour.
You got it.
You fill that bag
up with books,
Put it back
where it was found.
Gonna eat
this son of a bitch alive
Knowing he missed
something this big.
You know something,
charlie,
Maybe this, uh,
This isn't such a hot idea.
Guy picks up a bag,
that don't make him guilty.
Will, it's solid.
I don't know.
This kind of thing,
Maybe we do this
by the numbers.
Come on, will.
Hey, I.A.'s
gonna be on my ass.
I know I don't
want this turning up
In some courtroom
6 months from now
When my rep's in the shit
And they're pulling apart
all my cases.
Come on, will.
That's bullshit.
Fuck you care?
Someone out there
Just beat a 17-year-old
girl to death.
Your job is to find him.
You're a cop,
not a lawyer.
Don't let I.A.
Cut your balls off.
Charlie's right, will.
[caw]
O.P. One,
this is o.P. 2.
We still
got nothing.
Eckhart: Yeah,
it's nice. Light.
Farrell:
All plastic
Except for
the barrel
And firing pin.
Never rusts.
What do ya carry
down in l.A.?
Smith & wesson .45.
Excellent.
Anything?
Farrell: No.
Maybe this guy doesn't
listen to the radio.
Prefers the voices
in his head.
Hey, will?
O.P. One,
this is o.P. 2.
Be advised:
We got somebody
Moving
towards the cabin.
Ok, fan out.
Nice and easy.
[megaphone feedback]
Come on, let's go.
Let's go!
Police!
Come out!
Fuck.
Down there, huh?
All right,
down to the water.
Go! Spread out.
Go!
Fuck it.
Farrell: Dormer.
Hold it!
Who's there?!
You ok?
Ok.
I'm ok.
[running footsteps]
Will.
Don't talk, don't talk.
Don't talk.
Don't talk. Don't talk.
Here. Here.
You--you sh--
You--you shot...
No, I couldn't see, hap.
I couldn't see
in the fog.
Here. Here.
Are you trying to--
Are you trying
to kill me?
You fuckin'...
No. Listen, hap.
Listen to me.
[sobbing]
no, no, no.
Why? Why?
I couldn't see you
in the fog.
I couldn't.
Couldn't see you, hap.
[gagging]
No. Come on. Come on.
Man down!
Duggar: Who's down?!
Man down here!
Duggar: Spread out!
Dormer, where'd he go?
Which way?
Dormer, which way?!
That way.
Nyback: Farrell went down,
You gave chase.
After you left farrell,
You heard
the killer's second shot.
You ran down
to the water,
You found hap.
Will?
Is that what happened?
Did hap say anything?
Goddamn!
Why didn't I know about
the goddamn tunnel?!
You don't move in
on an armed suspect
Without knowing
his exits.
Look, will, there's a bunch
of those tunnels out there.
I mean, closed 60 years ago
when they were mines.
I don't even know
most of them myself,
And I grew up here.
I had him, charlie.
Close as you are now.
I could smell
the son of a bitch.
And I blew it.
There's no point in
blaming yourself, will.
I fucked up everything.
Don't you come apart on
me now, you understand?
I need you to find
this bastard.
[knocking]
Yeah?
You wanted
to see me.
You're on detective
eckhart's shooting.
But we know
what happened, and...
I'm on
the connell case.
Anchorage called. They
want to send someone up.
I told them we can
handle it ourselves.
We can, can't we?
Sure.
Write it up. Doesn't
have to be shakespeare.
Just enough to fry
this son of a bitch for
A few seconds longer.
Am I right, will?
[ringing]
Girl: Hello?
Uh...Jenny.
It's will.
Can I, uh--
Can you put
your mother on?
Trish: Hello?
Trish, uh, it's will.
[sighs]
what's happened?
They won't tell me
anything.
Uh, it--
it's hap, uh...
Is he ok?
No, he's gone, trish.
He's dead.
[weakly] what?
[sobbing]
Trish, I can't tell you
how sorry I am.
What was he doing, will?
This guy killed a girl.
And so we--we, uh...
We had him, uh...
We found him,
and we had him cornered.
And then he ran
and then, uh...
Hap, well...
I'm so sorry.
I'm just so sorry.
Did he suffer?
Oh, no, I don't--
Did he say anything?
Well, when I found him,
He...
He was peaceful.
Did you get him?
No, no. Not yet.
You find him.
And when you do,
you don't arrest him.
You understand me,
will dormer?
Don't you dare
fucking arrest him.
Ok, trish.
[sobbing]
understand?
Ok.
Trish, listen, I-I'm--
[click]
[vomiting]
[spits]
Radio reporter:
...Homicide division
Was shot and killed
earlier this evening
In an abortive attempt
to apprehend the suspect
In the murder of 17-year-old
local girl kay connell--
I'm sorry.
It's been on the radio
for hours. We don't--
We're not used to this
kind of stuff up here.
He was standing
right there last night.
I hope
I was nice to him.
He liked you.
[floorboards creak]
[grunts]
[sighs]
Detective, I'm sorry
to bother you,
But could you just
point out here
Where you were when you
heard that second shot?
I'm really sorry
that I have to make you
Do this right now.
That's all right, ellie.
You're doing your job.
Where was I? There.
Thank you.
No sign of farrell's
bullet yet, huh?
No, but, uh, we'll
have the other one
For ballistics
after the autopsy.
I'm really sorry.
How you doing?
Ok.
Clean through, huh?
Yep. No souvenir.
Bullet got lost in
the rocks, I guess.
Well, better luck
next time.
You ever been shot,
detective dormer?
Yeah, I have. It kind
of itches, don't it?
We gotta catch him.
Did you get
a look at him?
When?
When, uh, I left you.
Did you see anything?
I was in whole lot
of pain.
And when I heard
that second shot,
I kept my goddamn
head down.
Hey, I'm--
I'm sorry about
detective eckhart.
Sorry about
that megaphone.
Maybe if I hadn't--
Farrell, listen.
What were
we doing out there
Running around
in the fog anyway?
Were we doing it
for our health?
We were chasing someone.
So anything that happened
on that beach
Is not your fault.
That's the fault
of one man
And one man only.
And that's the man
Who beat kay connell
to death.
At this point,
Detective dormer
encountered officer brooks.
The suspect,
obscured by the fog,
Shot officer brooks
in the vastus externus
Of the upper left thigh.
Francis, you're farrell.
You were shot in the leg.
Francis:
Oh, come on, ellie.
Rich, when you
get this shot,
Make sure we get
the cone.
Is this his blood?
Ketchup maybe.
Was he eating
a hot dog?
Dormer: And anything
he might have dropped
Or stepped on
you put in a bag.
Cigarette butts,
gum wrappers,
Coins, anything.
A suspect will often
leave something behind.
Ellie:
Detective dormer gave chase,
Losing the suspect
in the fog,
Then heard a shot
Coming from
a northeasterly direction.
He wasn't lying that way.
How do you know?
'cause I saw him.
You need to turn this way.
Are we almost done here?
My nads are freezing off.
Ellie, I think
I found something!
Duggar: Do you think they
should start further over?
No, no. It's
a waste of time.
He stayed down
by the water
As far as he could.
I saw him
over the rocks.
He knew he'd
lose us down there.
[cell phone rings]
Duggar.
Where'd he find it?
Ok.
Yeah, just, uh,
let me know.
Ok. I will.
Dormer?
They found
farrell's bullet.
Looks like a .38.
After the autopsy,
we'll get both bullets
To the lab
in anchorage,
See if we can get a fix
on the murder weapon.
That is,
if it's ok with you.
A guy came by
to see you today.
Said he was
your new partner.
Did he leave a name?
Nope.
[telephone rings]
Can I borrow
this tape here?
Pioneer lodge.
Man:
Warfield for dormer.
Detective?
John warfield.
He's called
a couple times.
Want me to lie?
No, it's all right.
I'll take it.
Thank you.
Dormer here.
Warfield: I was shocked
to hear about
Your partner there,
detective.
It's terrible.
I was actually just getting
to know him a little bit.
What do you want?
I think we both know
what I want, detective,
And I think you know eckhart
was gonna give it to me.
You know, you got
something to say,
Why don't you
just say it?
He told you about our little
conversation, didn't he?
Say it.
Well, let's just say
I'm very, very interested
To see your report on what
happened there yesterday.
Don't presume to know
what happened.
You weren't here.
But then again,
you never are, are you?
I mean, you're always
sitting safe behind
Some fuckin' desk
reading your bullshit reports.
And that is why
I have nothing
But contempt for you.
You and all
the assholes like you
Risk nothing,
Spend all day sucking
the marrow out of real cops
When you never had the balls
to be one yourself.
[gunshot]
Coroner: Detective,
you came yourself.
Yeah.
Sign here.
Coroner: He didn't
suffer too much.
What's the caliber?
I don't know.
The gunshot victims
I see here
Are from hunting
rifles and shotguns.
It wasn't
one of those.
Had any sleep,
detective?
Yeah.
[gasps]
What the hell's
wrong with you?
Sorry.
No. No problem.
The bullet.
I want results
by tomorrow morning.
Aye, aye, captain.
I'm thinking
we should check
On randy stetz's
whereabouts 2 nights ago.
You think it was
randy out there?
Well, he still doesn't
have an alibi
For the night
kay was killed.
You're the one saying
he beat her up.
Well, you
check it out then.
I will.
[clicking pen]
[pumping coffee]
[whirring]
[slam]
[thud]
Ellie:
Detective dormer?
My report.
I finished it.
So I just need you
to, um, look it over,
And, uh, sign it.
It's pretty
self-explanatory.
Yeah?
I'm looking forward
To getting back
to working with you.
I know we have more
important things to do
Than paperwork.
Uh, a man died, ellie.
This is important.
Oh, of course.
I didn't mean to imply that
that wasn't--
Be sure of all your facts
before you file this thing.
It's your name
on the report.
[glass breaks]
He couldn't have
come from there.
[telephone rings]
[ring]
Dormer here.
Hello?
Man: Can't sleep, will?
Me neither.
Who's this?
I got a nap
this afternoon,
But I guess
you had to work.
Who am I speaking to?
You get rid of
your clock yet?
Won't really help.
When I first moved up here,
I once went 5 nights.
Can you believe that?
This crazy light.
A name,
or I'm gonna hang up.
No, you're not.
You need the company.
Nothing as lonely
as not sleeping.
Feels like the whole
fucking planet's deserted.
Just you and me.
So, uh...
Why don't you tell me
who I'm talking to,
And we can chat a while.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Not until you understand
a couple of things.
Like what?
I saw.
Saw what?
Saw you shoot
your partner.
Saw him die
in your arms
On that beach.
I thought you might try
to blame me.
That's why
I dropped my gun.
My uncle's old .38.
Yeah.
Did you pick it up?
I mean, what about
the ballistics--
Listen to me now.
I don't know what
you think you saw,
But, uh,
we should discuss
This thing,
don't you think,
Face to face?
The situation isn't yours
to control, will.
I saw you do it.
Get it?
I'll control
this situation, pal,
Because you don't
hide from me
In a town this small.
Get it?
Yeah.
No, not for long.
That's why
I need your help.
So don't worry about not
telling anyone anything.
We're partners on this.
[click, dial tone]
[alarm beeps]
...But to be remembered as
the kay we knew and loved.
Swimming, hiking
through the kebaughs,
Meeting at darrow's
after school,
And always,
Always with a smile
on her face.
Detective dormer?
I want to check
something with you.
Uh, I was going over
my report last night,
And I have a question
about where you think
That second shot
came from.
See, you said you heard it
from the water line,
But from the way detective
eckhart's body fell,
I don't think it could
have come from the rocks
Further up
from the water.
So do you think
it's possible
That maybe
you heard the shot
Before you hit
the water line?
Detective dormer?
Yeah, it's possible.
Yeah.
[motorcycle engine cranks]
Why don't
I give her a ride?
Randy: I thought
I smelled something.
How you doing, randy?
You still coping?
You're that cop.
Yeah.
Are you coming
or not?
Not.
Ooh. Hey.
You want
a stick of gum?
Mm-mmm.
I love cwing gum.
Keeps me awake.
I never met anyone
from l.A. Before.
You're not missing much.
So how do you like
our shithole town?
Oh, it's not bad.
Were you good friends
with kay?
Yeah, best friends.
Since grade school.
Boy, that's a long time.
Yeah, we were
like sisters.
Like sisters?
Must be pretty tough
for you
What happened then, hmm?
Everyone keeps telling me
I'm doing great considering.
But they're all
real worried about me.
They don't even care if
I show up for school or not.
They're worried
I haven't cried yet.
But...Ain't no law says
you gotta cry, right?
No, there ain't.
[laughs]
What about
her other friends?
Do we have to talk
about kay right now?
God.
I just don't want
to think about all that.
Let's just drive.
I understand.
You want me to
take you somewhere?
Sure, as long
as it's fun.
Young, impressionable girl
Left alone with older
los angeles cop.
Who know where
we might go, right?
Well, I know a place.
Hmm, let's just
drift a while.
Oh, look at this.
Who does he think he is?
What's he think
he's doing?
[honking horn]
Hey, move over.
Let him move over.
Hey, come on.
Move over!
What the fuck
are you doing?!
Move over,
you crazy fuck!
Holy shit.
I moved over.
Just a little visit
to the dump.
I mean, you should feel
right at home here, honey.
You just about fucking
killed us both!
Get off of me.
What the fuck is this?
So you and kay
were like sisters.
Yes. I told you
already.
Well, how come there's
torn pictures of you
In her bedroom?
Why was her boyfriend's
hands clamped
All over your ass
at her funeral?
Randy stetz doesn't have
an alibi for Friday night
Because he was out
with you.
You were out fucking your
best friend's boyfriend.
That what best friends do?
Look, she never really
loved randy, ok?
She didn't
really love him?
No.
That's interesting.
How do you figure that?
She had someone else?
I don't know.
Someone bought
her dresses,
Jewelry,
all that shit.
Hey, look around.
Come here. I want
to show you something.
See? Maybe you'll understand
why I brought you here.
This is the spot
Where your best friend's
naked body was dumped,
Wrapped up
in garbage bags!
Tanya...
I know you don't
want anyone knowing
That you betrayed
your best friend
With randy.
That's why you will not
give him an alibi
For Friday night.
I know that.
Now you tell me
who kay was seeing,
And we can forget
the whole thing.
It'll be
our little secret.
Our little secret.
But I need a name.
I need a name.
I don't know.
She wouldn't tell me, ok?
She wouldn't tell you?
What do you mean
She wouldn't tell you,
her best friend?
It was her big
fucking secret.
Secret?
Why a secret?
I don't--
'cause she thought
she was special and...
She kept saying she was
gonna get out of here
And he was gonna help her.
Who? Who? Who is he?
I don't know.
She talked
about him, though.
Yeah.
She talked to you
about him then?
Yeah.
And--and--and--
When she talked about him,
what did she call him?
She called him something,
right? She was--
Yes!
What?
What'd she call him?
Brody.
Ok, she called him
fucking brody.
But that's not
his real name,
So what's the fucking
difference?
Jesus, you happy now,
you fucking asshole?!
Ok, you did good, honey.
Come on.
I'll let you drive.
You want to drive?
It's just poetry.
I read it line by line.
It's, uh,
nothing specific.
Verses on nature, love,
that sort of stuff.
Uh-huh.
Detective dormer?
Line one.
Dormer here.
Man:
How you holding up?
Can't be easy
to keep working
After 3 days
of no sleep.
Hard to keep focus.
I mean, are you
seeing things yet?
You know, those
little flashes,
Tricks of light?
Hmm.
See yourartner?
I see kay sometimes.
What can I do
for you, sir?
Why couldn't you tell
anyone you shot him?
I mean, it was
an accident, right?
Well, I should hope so,
for your sake.
You know what
I'm saying?
No need for threats.
I'm just trying
to make you understand
My own situation.
See, you thought
no one would believe you
Because of the trouble
in los angeles, right?
I know what that's like,
will.
Uh-huh.
I got
the same problem.
You do, huh?
Mm-hmm.
I'm not who
you think I am.
You're not?
No. I'm not a murderer
any more than you are.
Well, then why don't we
get together, you know?
Just--just talk,
have a few beers, whatever.
Yeah, throw a little gas
on the fire, huh?
Yeah.
[click, dial tone]
I gotta go check
some things out.
Why don't you, uh,
put this stuff
Back into evidence
and tell, uh--
What's that guy?
Fred.
You tell him, uh,
I'll see him
in the morning.
Oh, and can
we return this?
Her mother might
like it back.
Oh, sure.
[baby crying]
[dog barks]
Look at this.
That's right.
Come on. That's right.
[dog barks]
[keys rattle in lock]
[dogs whining]
[dog barking]
Uhh!
Here you go.
[telephone rings]
Answering machine:
Hi, this is walter.
If you want to leave
a message, wait for the beep.
[beep]
Walter:
Will, are you there?
Where else could you go
in that state?
Ah, and you must
have been freezing.
If you want
to take a shower.
Should be some clean
towels in the bathroom.
[click]
[telephone rings]
Hi, this is walter.
If you want to leave a message,
wait for the beep.
[beep]
Walter: Will, pick up.
I'm not dumb enough
to call back.
Walter finch.
Will...Will dormer.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to help you,
and you're running around
Like a fuckin' maniac.
Were you gonna kill me?
How would you explain
that one?
Well, no one
gets too upset
When child murderers
are brought in feet first.
There's no evidence
that I killed kay.
You only know it
'cause I told you
What I saw
on that beach.
Come on.
What's wrong with you?
Guess I'm a little cranky.
Lack of sleep, you know.
Get some rest, will you?
I've got some pills
in the bathroom cabinet,
And my bed's
nice and comfy.
Another night
up like this,
And you're really
gonna lose it.
Hallucinating, babbling.
God knows what.
Tomorrow, when you're
feeling better, we'll meet--
In public--
and sort things out. Ok?
There's a ferry
about 5 miles north
Of nightmute.
I'll be on the 11:00.
And, will...
Before you leave,
could you feed the dogs?
They're on a diet.
Duggar: Dormer...
Fax from the lab.
Murder weapon was
a .38 smith & wesson.
Ah.
And we also found
something else
Might be worth
checking out. Ellie--
I found this...
At the connells.
And?
And it's the same author
of the book
We found in kay's
backpack.
It's signed
by the author.
Turns out
he's a local writer.
Kay had all his books.
I think we should
check it out.
Small stuff, right?
Well, yeah.
Sure, sure.
Nice work, ellie.
She's got sharp eyes, huh?
Oh, you bet your ass
she does.
Good stuff.
Will:
Oh, what a view.
I'm not
who you think I am.
No?
Walter finch.
Lousy writer.
Lonely freak.
Murderer.
No?
When I was 7 years old,
My grandmother
took me to portland.
We were walking along,
these 2 guys ran by.
They snatched her purse.
That night, a police officer
came to our hotel
To ask questions.
He stood the whole time.
Uniform looked brand-new.
Shoes, badge were polished.
He was like a soldier,
only better.
I have great respect
for your profession.
That's why
I write about it.
I even wanted
to become a cop
After I finished
high school.
I just couldn't pass
all the tests.
Well, you should have
tried out
For internal affairs.
They'd have taken you.
What do you want
from me, finch?
After kay died,
I knew that everyone
Would think
that I meant to do it.
So I cleaned the body up,
removed all trace of evidence
Connected to me.
Except
for your fuckin' novel.
Huh?
Under pressure,
you don't always
See the wood
for the trees.
You, for one, should have
figured that one out by now.
You know, when I heard
that they had brought
Somebody from l.A.,
I panicked.
I wasn't worried
about the locals.
I knew they'd connect me
to kay eventually.
I could handle them.
They never look
in the eyes of a killer.
Killing changes you.
You know that.
It's not guilt.
I never meant to do it.
It's like awareness.
Life is so important.
How could it be
so fuckin' fragile?
You'd see it right away,
wouldn't you?
You trying
to impress me, finch?
Because you got
the wrong guy.
Killing that girl
made you feel special.
But you're not.
You're the same distorted,
pathetic freak
I've been dealing with
for 30 years.
You know how many of you
I caught
with your pants down?
I never touched her
like that.
You wanted to.
Now you wish you had.
Hmm?
Best you could do is...
Clip her nails.
Now you're so different.
You don't get it,
do you, finch?
You're my job.
You're what
I'm paid to do.
You're about
as mysterious to me
As a blocked toilet
is to a fuckin' plumber.
Reasons for doing
what you did?
Who gives a fuck?
Motivations
are everything, will.
What did you see
through the fog?
I saw pretty clearly,
didn't I?
I saw you take aim--
Come on.
Forget it, finch.
Shoot your partner
in the chest.
Oh, well.
I heard him say,
"get away from me."
Why?
Have anything to do
With that internal affairs
investigation?
All that tension
in your department?
You think I'm
that easy, huh?
I'm just saying
that's how it looks. You know?
I mean, maybe even
how it feels.
How did it feel
when you found out it was hap?
Guilt? Relief?
Suddenly,
you're free and clear.
Did you ever think about it
before that moment?
I mean,
what would it be like
If he wasn't there anymore?
It doesn't mean you did it
on purpose, you know?
You figure if you got
something on me
Then I'm just gonna
roll over
And protect
my reputation.
Well, protect
your life's work.
Every one of those
scumbags you put away
Will be
back on the street
Before you even
go on trial.
Hap gone, you're
free and clear.
Why mess with that?
Kay connell.
Remember her?
It's your choice.
Think of all the other
kay connells.
Do the math.
You're a pragmatist.
You have to be
because of your job.
I know this
isn't easy for you,
But I'm trying
to get you to understand
We're in the same
situation here.
You didn't mean
to kill hap
Any more than I meant
to kill kay.
That's kind of hard
for them to believe,
So that's why
we need each other.
We gotta find a patsy
for the connell case,
Make it stick.
Do that, and you go back
to los angeles,
And I can go back
to living my life.
So, what do you need
from me?
What do they know
about me?
Uh, they found a signed copy
of one of your books
At kay's house.
So you're going to be
brought in for questioning.
At the station.
Yeah, that's what
they usually do.
They bring you
to the station.
Brought in
for questioning.
I could write that
easily.
Calm down.
It's no big thing.
Preliminary inquiries.
You know?
You just tell the truth.
Well, tell them about
randy, how he, uh--
What are you talking
about randy for?
Well--
Talk about
your relationship with kay.
You can't hide it,
so you just say it.
Randy is none
of your business.
It's not your affair.
Well,
shouldn't I tell them
That she was unhappy?
You can tell 'em
she was unhappy,
But just let them
find randy themselves.
You know?
That way,
they'll make it stick.
You understand?
We need a wild card.
A wild card?
Yeah.
Something that's theirs.
Something we can use.
You know, it's in every
good detective novel.
You still have the .38?
No.
Really?
That's a shame.
We could use that.
That'd be very
convincing for them.
[ferry horn blows]
This is my stop.
Dormer!
Wild card!
[ferry horn blows]
Good night, everyone.
Good night, francis.
Working
some overtime, huh?
Nice.
Cracking
some big cases?
Good night.
Good night, guys.
[telephone rings]
[ring]
Yeah?
Walter: This is always
the worst time of night for me.
Too late for yesterday,
too early for tomorrow.
What do you want?
I'm sorry about
the tape recorder.
I had to make sure
you'd follow through.
I know
this is hard for you.
I'll follow through.
I've been
thinking it over.
I should tell them
about randy.
I think that's
a bad idea, walter.
But he's the patsy, will.
And besides, he deserves it.
You should have heard the shit
kay told me about him.
How he abused her.
Yeah, but these are cops,
you know, walter.
They're not children.
You don't just...
Throw something like that
in their lap.
Leave randy to me.
I'll push 'em toward randy
When the time is right.
You understand?
Yeah, but we don't
have the gun, will.
How we gonna convince them
he's guilty
If we don't have that, hmm?
I mean, unless I tell them--
Did you keep
the dress?
Dress?
Kay's dress, yeah.
Her nail clippings.
What'd you do
with those things?
That's great.
Her dress.
We could use that.
That's even better
than the gun.
We just have to
think of a place
Where he could have
taken the body.
Where'd you take her?
I mean, she died
in the cabin, right?
Yeah.
So, where'd you take her
to clean her up?
You don't wanna
think about that, will.
This is tough enough
for you already.
But it was an accident,
right?
Yeah. I didn't mean
to kill her, will.
You know that, don't you?
I know.
Now what happened?
She called and said
that she and randy
Had had a fight.
And, uh, she wanted
to come over and talk.
And I said,
"meet me at our place."
It's the cabin at the beach.
And...
Yeah?
She comes over.
She's distraught
And a little drunk.
And, um, you know,
she starts telling me
About how randy and tanya
are carrying on, and...
I only wanted
to comfort her.
Hold her.
Mmm...You know?
I kissed her and...
Got a little excited, and...
[nervous laugh]
she started laughing at me.
She wouldn't stop laughing.
You ever had somebody
laugh at you
When--when you're
like that, will?
I mean, when you're
really vulnerable.
Laughing their ass
off at you.
Someone you thought
respected you.
You ever have that
happen, will?
I just wanted to stop
her laughing, that's all.
And then, you know, I...
I hit her.
Couple of times, just to,
you know, just to stop her.
Let her know.
Get a little respect.
And, you know,
randy did it all the time.
I think she even liked it
when he did it.
You know,
she never blamed him.
She never wanted
to leave him.
But, no, I do it,
and she starts screaming.
She wouldn't stop.
You know? I--I--
Unh! Uhh!
She's terrified.
She's screaming her head off.
I put my hand
over her mouth.
Then--and then,
I'm really scared.
I'm like, yeah.
I'm scared shitless.
More scared than I've
ever been before.
And, you know, I--
I am more scared than her.
And then...
Everything was clear.
There was no turning back.
[water trickling]
And, after that,
I was calm.
Real calm.
You and I
share a secret.
We know how easy
it is to kill somebody.
That ultimate taboo--
It doesn't exist
outside our minds.
I didn't murder her.
I killed her, but it--
it just ended up that way.
So, where'd you take
the body?
Thanks for listening to me.
Feels good to talk
about that stuff.
I'll be able
to sleep now.
You wanna talk about hap?
Morning, ellie.
Your phone
isn't working.
Yeah, I know.
I turned it off.
I needed to sleep.
You know? I'm sorry.
Fred called that author.
He said he was
more than happy to cooperate.
He'll be in first thing,
so, uh,
We need to get
to the office.
Good.
I forgot to tell you.
They sell these
In a chain of stores
in anchorage.
No way of finding out
who bought it.
Ok.
I bet you're
looking forward
To getting back
to los angeles
When this
is all over.
Back to robbery
homicide, or...
Maybe not.
What are you saying
to me, ellie?
Nothin'.
Are--
are you doing ok?
I mean, you haven't
been sleeping much,
Detective dormer.
No, I haven't. No.
A good cop can't sleep
Because a piece
of the puzzle's missing,
And a bad cop
can't sleep
'cause his conscience
won't let him.
You said that once.
I did?
Well, sounds like
something I'd say, doesn't it?
I'll see you
back there!
Duggar: So you were acquainted
with the deceased--kay connell?
Yes, I was.
In what regard
were you her familiar?
You're welcome.
How did you know her,
finch?
She was an avid reader
of my detective novels.
Duggar: When did you
meet her for the first time?
About a year ago.
She came
to one of my signings
Here in nightmute.
She hung around
afterwards,
And we chatted
about my writing
And how she wanted
to write, and...
And then,
we started talking,
And she asked
if she could visit me
And talk about books
and things like that.
And she did?
We became very close.
She got
comfortable enough
To show me
some of her own writing.
What did she write?
Poetry, actually.
Any good?
No, not really.
You tell her that?
Why would I?
So, uh, exactly
what was the nature
Of your relationship
to this girl, finch?
I guess I was someone
she could talk to.
Someone outside
of her everyday life.
I think that's why
she needed me.
Why she probably
approached me.
Why'd she need you
for that?
Well...
Her boyfriend randy...
Randy stetz.
Abusive little prick.
He hit her.
We know all this
already, finch.
No, but it
was getting worse.
So?
No, but it was
a lot worse, really.
Why
all this eagerness
To talk about
randy stetz, finch?
Well...Oh, you're right.
I'm sorry, detective.
It's probably
all hearsay anyway,
And I--I don't want
to say anything
That could be taken
the wrong way.
Excuse me. Mr. Finch,
anything you say to us
At this stage
is in strict confidence.
Secondly, we're not
a bunch of hotheads
Who are just gonna...
Draw a bunch of crazy
conclusions. Ok?
Ok.
Please, uh, continue.
There was
one more thing.
It probably doesn't
mean very much,
But I think that kay
was getting scared.
I probably have myself
to blame for that.
Why is that?
Well,
randy knew who I was.
Not--not who I was,
but...
He knew that she
had a friend.
Someone she could
confide in,
And that made him
furious.
She was always writing
about how scared she was,
And her letters were getting
more and more desperate.
You still have
any of these letters,
By any chance?
You know, I probably do.
Do you think it might help?
They might.
Ok...
Anything else?
The thing that
worried her the most...
Was the gun.
He had this old handgun.
He showed it to her.
I don't know
where he got it.
I mean, it probably
wasn't even his, but...
He said
he was gonna use it
If he found out
who she was seeing.
He kept it hidden
in a heating vent.
You know,
in the skirting boards.
Might be the .38.
[mumbling]
yeah.
Get me judge biggs--
What are you doing?
I'm gonna get a search warrant
over to randy's place.
You got that?
Get judge biggs on the phone,
right away.
I want everyone moving
in 5 minutes.
I should
get over there.
Hey, you know what? No.
No?
What do you mean no?
You're the guy
he's talking to,
For christ sakes.
Yeah, so?
Yeah, so, we're
waiting for the warrant.
Is that ok with you?
Francis: Ok, I'll try
that number.
Mr. Finch, do you know
when randy showed her the gun?
Walter: February?
Francis: I'm looking
for judge biggs.
Walter: No. No.
Probably January.
Why didn't you come forward
with this information
When she died?
She swore me to secrecy.
She didn't want anybody
to know about that.
Even when
she was dead,
She didn't
want anyone to know?
Beaten to death.
I was honoring
her wishes.
A body dumped
on a pile of garbage.
I was her friend.
You weren't her friend.
All right.
Acquaintance, all right?
We were close, and--
You were close?
Mm-hmm.
She was attractive.
Did you have sex
with her?
She was 17.
17, she was attractive.
I suppose.
Suppose? She was.
Right.
Well, so did you
have sex with her?
No. I was her mentor.
You bought her things.
Yeah.
Gifts?
Yes.
What kind of gifts?
Books, mostly.
That's what she loved.
Books?
Mm-hmm.
What about this?
You give her this?
Yes.
Why?
You wanted to see
How she looked
with it on?
No.
No?
Why would you
give her jewelry?
It was just a present.
Present? You bought
a lot of presents.
You bought her
dresses.
Yes.
What's wrong with that?
Well, nothing wrong.
I'm just trying
To figure out what kind
of mentor you were.
I gave her things
she couldn't have.
[scoffs]
You just wanted
to fuck her, didn't you?
Son of a bitch!
Duggar: Dormer!
Dormer! Dormer!
Better cool off.
Sick bastard.
Hey, you cool down.
Yeah. Yeah.
Cool...Down.
All right.
I need a break.
[tires screeching]
I have to apologize
on behalf of my colleague.
He's, uh...
[clears throat]
He's been under
a lot of pressure lately.
But, uh, he's a good cop.
Well, I'd hate to see
the bad cop.
[dog barking]
Francis:
Search and seizure warrant.
Yes, sir.
Randy stetz, and we'll
fill in the rest later.
Got our warrant!
Mr. Finch, thank you.
We appreciate it.
Francis, you're coming
with me. Let's go.
You're not
going with him?
No.
[siren]
You're not
on the connell case?
Yeah. I'm, uh, covering
the, uh, shooting
Of detective dormer's
partner.
Heard about that.
It's tragic.
So, should I still call you
about kay's letters?
Yeah. Call me.
I'll come pick them up.
Ok.
Duggar, pounding on door:
Stetz! We got a warrant.
We're coming in.
All right,
turn the place over.
Give me a hand,
will you?
Under there.
Try over there.
Rich, look here.
Rich: I got it!
Hey, fred!
All right.
[oil dripping]
Just in time, dormer.
Had it
in the motor oil.
What the fuck is this?
[police radio chatter]
Duggar: So now he's saying
he was with tanya francke
The night kay was killed.
Well, that's
what she told me.
When?
When I questioned her.
Oh, that's nice.
Were you planning
on telling anyone or...
Well, that's what
I'm doing now, isn't it?
Randy and tanya were
screwing around on kay.
Clearly she's just
trying to protect him.
Nyback: What's he say
about the gun?
He says it isn't his.
I think once we get
the ballistics match,
He's gonna be a little
more forthcoming.
So, uh, you leaving us?
First thing tomorrow.
If spencer can remember
Where he parked
the plane, right? Heh!
I really thought
you wanted to kill me
In that interview room.
I did.
Randy stetz is in jail.
Told you I'd write
an ending they'd like.
You were too wrapped up
in the details.
The details?
He's innocent.
No, he isn't.
He beat kay.
One day he'd do
something worse,
Maybe a lot worse.
How'd you know
I planted the gun?
You wanted to help me
even before I showed you
That tape recorder.
You had to have
a wild card.
You're a good man.
I know that even if
you've forgotten it.
When were you gonna
point them at me, will?
When you found out where
kay's dress was, hmm?
Where I took
the body, right?
If you have a gun
and the forensics,
Wouldn't matter what
kind of crazy bullshit
I told them about you
killing your parer,
Would it?
May I have the tape?
Did you make
other copies?
What?
Did you make
other copies?
Why would I?
To stop me
from turning you in.
Or killing you.
I don't have
a hold over you, will.
I never did. You made
your own choices.
It's like
I wasn't even here.
Why kill me? It's not
gonna help randy.
After your little scene
at the police department,
It's not gonna do you
any good if I show up dead.
A lot of ways
a man can die.
Like an accident, huh?
Like hap. Like kay.
It took you 10 minutes
To beat kay connell
to death.
10 fucking minutes.
You calling that
an accident?
It took you only
a fraction of a second
To kill your partner.
Does that make it
Any more
of an accident, will?
Is this an accident?
If you want it to be.
It's over, walter.
It's over.
I'm gonna tell them
everything.
Tell them about hap,
about you, about everything.
What good
would that do, will?
It'll end
this fucking thing.
It's not gonna end it.
You haven't
had any sleep.
You're not thinking
straight, will.
What are you gonna do--
tell them the truth?
You shot your partner,
And you lied
about it, will.
To them, you're a liar,
and you're a killer.
You're tainted forever.
You don't get to pick
when you tell the truth.
The truth is
beyond that.
That tape was
the only physical proof
That you and I ever had
a conversation
Outside of that
interview room.
To them
I'm just a writer
That kay connell
admired,
And randy stetz
is a killer,
And you're a hero cop.
Your life's work
is intact.
Another abusive scumbag
is in jail.
Everything is
as it should be.
Go back
to los angeles, will.
The case against randy
is pretty solid.
And I can take care
of everything up here.
I got it all worked out.
Go home.
Walter: Midnight
of your sixth night.
You broke
my record, will.
[car door closes,
engine starts]
Farrell:
Randy stetz.
He was an asshole.
Duggar: You knew him
when he was a little kid?
Our dads were
on the same boat.
Used to wait
for them together.
Bad seed, man.
Francis: How do you
like our beer?
[all laughing]
Duggar: I think what dormer
needs is a little shut-eye.
White nights
getting to you?
Hasn't been easy.
Farrell:
Better than winter.
Rich: You got that right.
In winter,
the sun barely comes up
For 5 months straight.
Duggar: Like you're being
sucked into a black hole.
Ellie: Hi, guys.
Hey, nancy drew,
you hear? We got him.
Farrell:
Rich found the gun.
I heard.
Oh, nancy's got
something on her mind.
I found this
out on the beach.
What is it?
Shell casing, 9mm.
The murder weapon
was a .38,
And none of us carries
a 9mm duty weapon...
Or backup weapon, right?
Duggar:
Come on!
Get a hobby,
would you?
What? It's
a legitimate point,
Isn't it,
detective dormer?
Oh, this case
is closed, ellie.
Hold the fort, boys.
I'm just gonna go
Find the men's room.
Relieve myself
of some of your
Fine alaskan beer.
Hey, do you want
a beer or something?
No, thanks.
Rich: He's good people,
right?
Duggar: Don't get
carried away.
Hey, farrell,
what has 2 thumbs
And loves blow jobs?
I don't know.
This guy.
[men laugh]
Sorry.
Well, it's been
something, dormer.
It's been really great
working with you.
You gonna run will
to the airport?
No, I gotta go pick up
those letters from finch...
He lives
in umkumiut.
At his lake house,
and detective dormer
Will just have to leave
my car at the dock.
If that's ok with you.
Yeah, it's fine.
Farrell: You don't think
I tried to tell her that?
It's been a pleasure.
Yeah.
Get some sleep.
Rachel, knocking:
Detective dormer?
What is it?
Someone's complaining
about the noise.
He says he can't sleep.
Something wrong?
Well, uh,
It's so fucking
bright in here.
Look.
No, it's dark in here.
Please...
There's this guy.
Wayne dobbs, 24,
Works part-time
in a copy store.
Every day, he watches
this 8-year-old boy
Waiting for his carpool
across the street.
This is one of
your cases?
Yeah. Hap and me.
A year and a half ago.
For 6 months,
he watches this kid.
Finally gets up the nerve,
he goes down there,
Grabs that boy
before the carpool comes,
Takes him back
to his apartment,
And keeps him there
for 3 days.
He tortures m, and...
Makes him do things,
And finally he's had
enough.
He gets a rope,
And he hangs the boy
in a storage space
In the basement
of the building.
But he didn't do it
right.
The little boy's neck
didn't break, so...
He just dangled there
for a while
And then died finally
from the shock.
Landlord found the body
5 days later.
The second I met
this guy dobbs,
I knewe was guilty.
That's what I do.
That's my job.
I assign guilt.
You find the evidence,
Figure out who did it,
And then you go get them
and put them away.
This time, there wasn't
enough evidence,
And it's reasonable doubt
to a jury,
Because a jury never...
Met a child murderer
before...
But I have.
Anyway...
I, uh...
I went and took
some blood samples
From the boy's
dead body.
And I planted them...
In dobbs' apartment.
I could feel it
right there.
This is gonna
catch up with me.
I don't do things
like that.
So how did it
catch up with you?
Internal affairs
was coming down
On our department,
And hap, he was
gonna cut a deal...
And bring me
straight in with it.
They would've
reopened dobbs' case,
And he'd have walked.
Now that's
not gonna happen.
And I don't know how...
How I feel about that.
But dobbs was guilty.
Dobbs needed to be
convicted,
So the end
justifies the means.
Right?
I'm in no position
to judge.
Why not?
There are 2 kinds of people
who live in alaska.
The ones
who are born here,
And the ones who come here
to escape something else.
I wasn't born here.
Well, why don't you
tell me what you think?
Here, now, in this room,
You and me.
Please.
I guess it's about
what you thought
Was right at the time.
And what you're willing
to live with.
[engine starts]
Officer:
Nightmute police department.
Detective burr.
Uh, she's not here
right now.
She left town about
20 minutes ago to go--
[barking]
Mr. Finch?
Detective burr.
Are they friendly?
Oh, yeah. Didn't expect
to see you this soon.
Sorry about the mess,
Just doing
a little work here.
Oh, no problem.
Do you think
kay's letters
Could really strengthen
the case against randy?
Possibly.
[windshield wipers squeak]
[horn blares]
[tires screech]
Watch
your head here.
I've done it
a thousand times.
Sorry about
all the clutter.
I am a pack rat.
I keep everything.
I know I got 'em.
I just don't know where.
They gotta be here
somewhere.
Working on a new
book, mr. Finch?
Have you read
any of my books?
I haven't--
[barking]
She knows, will.
Where is she?
She knows
you killed hap.
You would've
realized it yourself
If you weren't
so fucking strung out.
I saw it
at the questioning.
The way she was
looking at you.
Where is she, finch?
Calm down, now I got
everything under control.
If anything
happened to her--
She's ok. But if we
don't do something
And she talks,
you're fucked.
Everything you've worked
for is destroyed,
Do you get it?
Now give me--
[cocks gun]
show me where she is.
Show her to me now.
She's ok. Listen,
I mean, I--I--
it's all fine.
Let's search
this place.
What are
we looking for?
For the dress.
What dress?
Ellie's.
Ellie's?
Kay's dress.
You're rambling.
Thank god you got taking care o.
Us?
She saw the dress.
What us?
We're in the same boat.
Where'd you get us?
Don't talk to me
About us,
you sick mother...
She's alive, will.
Ellie?
[gunshot]
Hold it!
Don't move.
You shot
detective eckhart.
And finch saw you
do it.
Yeah.
Did you mean
to shoot hap?
I...I don't know
anymore.
I, uh, I don't know.
I couldn't see him
through the fog,
But when
I got up close,
He was, uh...
He was afraid of me.
And he thought
I meant to do it,
So...Maybe I did.
I just don't know
anymore.
[shotgun blast]
Where's your gun?
He took it.
Keep your head down.
All right, now listen.
I got 7 rounds
in this clip.
Ok.
Make it last.
Head down.
Ok, go, go!
[gunshot]
You forgot
the wild card, will.
Ellie:
Detective dormer!
I called for backup.
They'll be here soon.
Dormer...Just hold on.
Hold on.
Nobody needs to know.
You didn't
mean to do it,
And I know that
even if you don't.
No, don't, don't.
What?
Why?
Don't lose your way.
Hang on.
Dormer.
Let me sleep.
No.
Just let me sleep.
Captioning made possible by
warner bros.
Captioned by the national
captioning institute
--www.Ncicap.Org--
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3nnjn
Help other users to choose the best subtitles