Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
That man's crazy.
This is terrible.
Take Dr Bruckner to intensive care
immediately.
7 years later
As long as she finds me attractive.
And now, doctor...
Yuck, what a face.
That's Professor Bruckner. He's been
in a coma for 7 years.
He used to be a surgeon.
I feel sorry for him.
-Sorry? He's a creep.
Good evening.
-Good evening.
Did you look at the records?
-Yes, I'm almost finished.
This is Bert, the new assistant.
And this is Kim.
A glass of wine. You?
It's a bit scary to do my rounds
for the first time.
Do you really have to go?
-I have a date.
Have you done Coma yet?
No, do I have to?
I thought we might do it together.
Sorry, I have to make a phone call.
Peter speaking. Is Amy there?
I'll wait.
Finally, were you having a bath?
-Hi, Peter.
I haven't heard from you for
a while.
How are you?
I wanted to discuss that with you
tonight.
That's impossible.
I already have a date.
-Cancel it.
Duh.
-Are you going to a party?
No, he's coming to me.
Not that asshole with the leather
jacket?
Or are you into SM these days?
-That's enough.
Anything else?
-Let me know if you want a trio.
What about that?
Wasn't I doing your shift?
-What time is it?
Almost 8:30 pm.
-Damn.
Where's Kim?
-Isn't she back yet?
No.
Darling, I'll call you back later.
Bye.
She'll be pissed off.
What took you so long?
We already called the hospital.
Have you been drinking?
-Come on, mum.
I smell alcohol.
-Why are you so late?
The girl who was doing my shift
was gone.
Call Hank and Shirley.
Nice little car.
How do I look?
Good, you should wear a tuxedo
more often.
Not bad.
-Behave, you're a guest here.
Bobby will keep an eye on you.
Why aren't you going anywhere?
You know I have an early start
tomorrow.
Amy's home alone too.
-She already has a boyfriend.
The one with the motor bike?
-Yes.
You can't take him seriously.
-Do you take Peter seriously?
Go now.
Have fun.
Hello.
-Hello.
Sorry, we had to wait for Peter.
He had a late shift.
If our car hadn't been in the garage,
we could have given you a lift.
Have your parents left, Ted?
-No, they'll be a bit later.
Ask your mother to bring my Tupperware
containers. I need them.
Call Peter.
-Why?
Just do it.
-What's wrong?
I haven't had this car for half
a year yet.
It looks like it's been cut with
a knife.
What's wrong now?
Come here.
What's wrong?
-Come here, Peter.
Do you have to do that now?
-Stay out of it.
You said you'd be careful with
my car.
Did you do that?
It was like that already.
You're not saying I did this with
a knife, are you?
Don't ask me.
Can you continue this conversation
tomorrow?
It's already 9 pm.
-Let's go.
Bye.
-Bye.
Aren't you going to the party?
-No, mum, I'm staying with Amy.
Ok, careful with the fireworks.
-Of course.
Oh and Mrs Bogaerd needs her
Tupperware containers.
I'll have to try and find them and we're
late as it is.
John, did you...
Hey, Dennis.
Get lost, Dennis!
Amy, will you bring the firewood?
I thought you'd do that.
-But I'm fixing your walkman.
Ok.
Ted?
Stop it!
How did you get in?
-Your backdoor was open.
That doesn't mean you can come in.
You're so hard.
What do you want?
-Isn't it clear?
Mum!
I'll explain one more time.
Ted called me two weeks ago.
He wanted us to have a drink together.
I said yes and it was very nice.
So it's been going on for a while.
Amy, that's not what we agreed.
-Agreed?
You've been doing the same thing.
I don't care.
You're seeing that nurse... Kim or
something.
You're jealous.
Jealousy doesn't have anything
to do with it.
No, it's got nothing to do with it.
You'd better leave.
Why?
-It's not working between us.
We've known each other since we were 12.
-It has always worked.
Until that asshole moved here.
-That's when I noticed the difference.
What?
If you like mummy's boys in leather,
that's your problem.
See you.
She's all yours again. I'm done.
Good.
What's that? Is that the best
you could find?
You can't buy her with this.
Bastard, why do you treat me like this?
I can't help that she likes me, not you.
She doesn't want you. You just
keep calling her.
She called me, I swear.
Stop lying.
Let me go. I want to see her.
-No.
I changed my mind. I'm going back
to her.
Bye, Teddy.
Have a seat.
These things have become so small.
It's very finicky.
They want you to buy a new one,
instead of fixing it.
You're very good at that.
I bet you want to talk about Amy.
-Why?
They all want that.
-They who?
I'm popular with those guys.
-Which guys?
From school and the football club.
She had a lot of dates lately.
The guys like her.
So Ted and her aren't going steady yet?
-In his dreams.
My father hates him.
Shall we play a bit? Where's
your sax?
Downstairs.
I think she likes you.
Really?
At least, I hope so.
Amy!
I heard you've been seeing the
entire football team.
Yes and we had a great time.
Why are you here?
Why do you think?
We went to school together, grew up
together. You're like a brother to me.
No more and no less.
So I'm your brother?
Asshole!
Hey.
-I have one more problem.
What's that?
Ted. I'm sure he'll be here soon.
That's no longer a problem.
-Why?
I saw him outside just now.
He won't bother you again.
What do you mean? I decide who
I see.
Stop worrying about that loser.
Stop it.
It's up to you. Damnit.
I'm fed up.
Bob!
-Yes.
Will you play the piano?
-Has Peter left yet?
He just left.
I'm coming.
Tonight wasn't a party for everybody.
Three victims were reported at
St Anna Hospital.
It was described as a terrible massacre.
We're going there live.
Well-known American Professor Bruckner,
who went into a coma 7 years ago...
after a car accident, with bad burns,
has disappeared from the hospital.
The murders were committed around
the same time.
The police haven't found a trace of the
killer yet, but what can you tell us?
We're checking all the staff who've
been working tonight.
We don't have any solid leads yet.
Thank you. Back to the stu...
Dennis.
American Professor Bruckner has
a reputation in the medical world.
Eight years ago, he made the news with
a controversial experiment.
Have a look at some archive
footage.
The Minister refused permission, deeming
the experiments a public health risk.
I'm now talking to Dr Horvath.
He's one of Professor Bruckner's
colleagues.
Could the experiment have been done
with Professor Bruckner himself?
That's absolutely impossible.
Then how do you explain he came out of
his coma and can walk apparently?
That has never happened before,
as far as we know.
I don't have an explanation either.
We simply don't know enough about
the human brain yet.
Can many years of coma corrupt
one's mind?
That's a fact. The longer the coma,
the worse the brain damage.
Professor Bruckner is proof of this.
It's a case of life imitating art.
Professor Bruckner was a kind of
Frankenstein.
But he became the monster of his own
experiments.
So you admit experiments have been done
with Professor Bruckner.
Was it a brain operation or
an experiment with medication?
Number 8. Looking all quiet.
This has to be it. Number 6.
He must be the last one to have seen
the killer.
Such nonsense. I've never had such
a boring New Year's Eve.
We're talking about a murder
case here.
Come back quickly and ask if the
champagne's cold.
Do you know if Peter has gone home?
-Yes, why?
Are you sure he went home?
-Yes, I think so.
Why?
I keep calling him but he doesn't
answer.
He must be asleep.
Amy!
-Yes!
Come here.
-Ok.
Listen to this.
After the gruesome murders in
St Anna Hospital earlier tonight...
the police are telling people in
the area to be careful...
and to stay home.
Put a tape in it. Sit down.
It's great!
Well done.
Keep it for a while. It also belongs
to you now.
Thanks. Are you going to see Peter?
-Yes, but I won't be long.
See you soon.
Oh good.
Peter, where are you? It's me, Amy.
Peter.
Are you in there?
Dennis, you scared me.
Come on!
Jesus, Bobby!
Bobby, hurry, please.
Damnit, Bobby, answer the phone.
Amy, watch out!
-Bobby!
Get up!
Come.
I don't know where your room key is.
Now what?
No, much bigger.
Hurry up, Bob.
Come on.
Quick!
Come on, Bobby.
Go, Amy
There's no plug on it.
Peter... it's Peter.
Amy, watch out!
Peter, I thought you were dead.
Peter.
-Where did he go?
Shall I get you a band-aid?
Gee...
Is this better?
-Yes.
Bob, get some band-aids.
He's got Bobby. We have to go
after him.
I'll go after him and you stay here
in case Bobby comes back.
Bruckner!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4zkyx
Help other users to choose the best subtitles