Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I feel like you're driving me to
court martial. This is crazy.
What did I do? I feel like you're
gonna pull over and snuff me.
What, you're not allowed to talk?
Hey, Forest...
- We can talk, sir.
- Oh, I see. So it's personal?
No, you intimidate them.
Dear God, you're a woman!
I honestly, I couldn't have called that.
I mean, I would apologize, but isn't
that what we're going for here?
I thought of you as a soldier first.
- I'm an airman.
Well you have actually excellent
bone structure there. I'm kinda...
having a hard time not looking
at you now. Is that weird?
C'mon, it's OK, laugh. Hey!
- Sir, I have a question to ask.
- Yes, please.
It is true you went 12-for-12 with
last year's Maxim cover models?
That is an excellent question.
Yes and no. March and I
had a scheduling conflict,
but fortunately the Christmas
cover was twins. Anything else?
You're kidding me
with a hand up, right?
Is it cool if I take
a picture with you?
Yes, it's very cool.
I don't wanna see this
on your MySpace page.
Please, no gang signs.
No, throw it up, I'm kidding.
Yeah, peace! I love peace.
I'd be outta job with peace.
C'mon! Just click it, don't change
the settings, just click it.
What's going on?
Jimmy, stay with Stark!
Lie down!
Son of a bitch!
- Wait, wait, give me a gun!
- Stay here!
Tony Stark.
Visionary. Genius.
American patriot.
Even from an early age,
the son of legendary weapons
developer Howard Stark
quickly stole the spotlight
with his brilliant and unique mind.
At age four, he built
his first circuit board.
At age six, his first engine.
And at seventeen, he graduated
Summa Cum Laude from MIT.
Then, the passing of a titan.
Howard Stark's life long friend
and ally Obadiah Stane,
steps in to help fill the gap
left by the legendary founder.
Until at age 21,
the prodigal son returns,
and is anointed the new CEO
of Stark Industries.
With the keys to the kingdom,
Tony ushers in a new era
for his father's legacy,
creating smarter weapons,
advanced robotics,
satellite targeting.
Today, Tony Stark has changed
the face of the weapons industry,
by ensuring freedom
and protecting America and
her interests around the globe.
As liaison to Stark Industries,
I've had the unique privilege
of serving with a real patriot.
He is my friend and
he is my great mentor.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my honor
to present this year's Apogee
Award to Mr. Tony Stark!
Tony?
Thank you, Colonel.
This is beautiful. Thank you.
Thank you all very much.
This is wonderful.
Well, I'm not Tony Stark.
But if I were Tony...
...I would tell you
how honored I feel,
and what a joy it is to receive
this very prestigious award.
Tony, you know,
the best thing about Tony...
...is also the worst thing -
he's always working.
C'mon!
We should just stay
till the morning.
- You are unbelievable!
- Oh, no. They roped you into this?
Nobody roped me into anything.
But they told me...
that if I presented you with an award,
you'd be deeply honored.
Of course I'd be deeply honored.
And it's you!
That's great. So when do we do it?
One more round. - There you go.
There it is. That was easy.
I'm so sorry. - Yeah, it's OK.
Wow, would you look at that?
That's... that's something else.
I don't have any of those
swooping around. All right, ride!
Give me a hand, will you?
OK, you too.
I don't blow on man's hands.
There it is! It's the Lieutenant
Colonel Rhodes' roll, and...
That's what happens.
Worse things have happened,
I think we're gonna be fine.
Color me up, will you?
- This is where I exit.
- Tomorrow don't be late.
- Yeah, you can count on it.
- I'm serious.
- I know, I know.
Render unto Caesar that which
is Caesar's. There you go.
Mr. Stark! Excuse me!
Mr. Stark!
Christine Everheart,
Vanity Fair magazine.
Can I ask you a couple of
questions? - She's cute.
- She's alright? Hi.
- Hi.
Yeah. Okay, go.
You've been called the Da Vinci of
our time. What do you say to that?
Absolutely ridiculous.
I don't paint.
And what do you say to your other
nickname, the Merchant of Death?
That's not bad.
Let me guess... Berkeley?
Brown, actually.
Well, Ms. Brown.
It's an imperfect world,
but it's the only one we've got.
I guarantee you the day weapons are
no longer needed to keep the peace,
we'll start making bricks and
beams for baby hospitals.
Rehearse that much?
Every night in front of
the mirror before bedtime.
- I can see that.
- I'd like to show you firsthand.
All I want is the serious answer.
Okay, here is serious.
My old man had a philosophy:
"Peace means having a bigger
stick than the other guy."
That's a great line, coming
from a guy selling the sticks.
My father helped defeat Nazis.
He worked on the Manhattan Project.
A lot of people, including
your professors at Brown,
would call that being a hero.
And a lot of people would
also call that war-profiteering.
Tell me, do you plan to report
on the millions we've saved by
advancing medical technology?
Or kept from starvation
with our intelli-crops?
All those breakthroughs:
military funding, honey.
Wow, did you ever lose an hour
of sleep your whole life?
I'd be prepared to
lose a few with you.
Good morning. It's 7 a.m.
The weather in Malibu is 72
degrees with scattered clouds.
The surf conditions are fair
with waist to shoulder highlines,
high tide will be at 10:52 a.m.
Tony? Hey, Tony!
You are not authorized to
access this area. - Jesus!
That's Jarvis, he runs the house.
I've got your clothes here, they've
been dry cleaned and pressed.
And there's a car
waiting for you outside
that will take you
anywhere you'd like to go.
You must be the famous
Pepper Potts. - Indeed I am.
After all these years, Tony still
has you picking up the dry cleaning?
I do anything and everything
that Mr. Stark requires.
Including occasionally taking out
the trash. Would that be all?
Give me the exploded view.
The compression in cylinder 3
appears to be low.
Note that.
- I'll try again later...
- Please don't turn down my music.
I'll keep you posted.
You are supposed to be half way
around the world right now.
- How did she take it?
- Like a champ.
Might've tried to
hustle me out of here.
Your flight was scheduled to
leave an hour and a half ago.
That's funny... I thought with
it being my plane and all,
that it would just wait
for me to get there.
I need to speak to you about couple of
things before I get you outta the door.
I mean, doesn't it kind of defeat the
purpose of having your own plane
if it departs before you arrive?
Larry called, he's got another
buyer for the Jackson Pollock
in the wings, do you
want it, yes or no?
Is it a good representation
of his Spring Period?
No the "Springs" is actually the
neighborhood in East Hampton,
where he lived and worked,
not "spring" like the season.
I think it's a fair example...
I think it's incredibly overpriced.
I need it. Buy it, store it.
Okay... the MIT
commencement speech.
Is in June... please, don't
harangue me about that stuff.
Well, they are haranguing me,
so I'm gonna say yes...
I need you to sign this
before you get on the plane.
What are you trying to get rid
of me for? What, you got plans?
- As a matter of fact, I do.
- I don't like it when you have plans.
I'm allowed to have
plans on my birthday.
It's your birthday. - Yes.
- I knew that. Already?
Yeah, isn't that strange,
it's the same day as last year.
Well, get yourself something
nice from me. - I already did.
- And?
- Oh, it was very nice.
Very tasteful.
Thank you, Mr. Stark.
You're welcome, Ms. Potts.
You're good! I thought
I've lost you back there.
You did, sir.
I took it across Mojave.
- Ah, I gotcha, I gotcha.
What's wrong with you?
- What?
Three hours! - I got caught
doing a piece for Vanity Fair.
Three hours. For three hours,
you got me standing here.
I'm waiting on you now.
Lets go. C'mon.
Wheels up! Rock and roll!
What're you reading?
- Nothing.
C'mon, sourpatch,
don't be mad.
I told you I'm not mad,
I'm indifferent, okay?
- I said I was sorry.
- Good morning, Mr. Stark.
- No need to apologize.
- I told him I was sorry but he...
I'm just indifferent right now.
You don't respect yourself,
so I know you don't respect me.
- I respect you.
- I'm just your babysitter,
and so, when you need your
diaper changed, thank you...
let me know and I'll
get you a bottle, okay?
Hey, heat up the sake, will you?
Thanks for reminding me.
I'm not talking... we're not drinking,
we're working right now.
And you are constitutionally
incapable of being responsible.
It would be irresponsible
not to drink.
I'm just talking about
the night cup. - Hot sake?
- Yes, two please.
- No, just...
I'm not drinking,
I don't want any.
That's what I'm talking about.
When I get up in the morning,
and I'm putting on my uniform,
you know what I recognize?
I see in that mirror that every
person that's got this uniform
will get my back! - Here we
go again. I'm not like you.
No, you don't have to be like me.
But you're more than... yes you are.
Will you excuse me,
I'm a little bit distracted here.
No, you can't be distracted
right now. Listen to me!
BAGRAM AIR BASE,
AFGHANISTAN
General.
Welcome, Mr. Stark.
We look forward to your
weapons presentation.
Is it better to be feared
or respected?
And I say, is it too much
to ask for both?
With that in mind, I humbly
present the crown jewel
of Stark Industries freedom line.
It's the first missile system
to incorporate our proprietary
repulsor technology.
They say the best weapon is
one you never have to fire.
I respectfully disagree.
I prefer the weapon you
only have to fire once.
That's how dad did it,
that's how America does it...
and it's worked out
pretty well so far.
Find an excuse to let
one of these off the chain,
and I personally guarantee you
the bad guys won't even want
to come out of their caves.
For your consideration,
the Jericho.
We throw one of these in with every
purchase of 500 million or more.
To peace!
- Tony.
- Obie, what are you doing up?
I couldn't sleep till I found out
how it went. How did it go?
Went great, looks like it's
gonna be an early Christmas.
Hey, way to go, my boy.
I'll see you tomorrow, yeah?
Why aren't you wearing
those pyjamas I got you?
Good night, Tony.
Hey Tony!
I'm sorry, this is the fun-vee.
The hum-drum-vee is back there.
- Nice job.
- See you back at base.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
What the hell did you do to me?
What I did?
What I did is to save your life.
I removed all the shrapnel I could,
but there's a lot left,
and it's headed into
your atrial septum.
Here, wanna see?
I have a souvenir.
Take a look.
I've seen many wounds
like that in my village.
We call them the walking dead.
Because in takes about a week for
the balls to reach the vital organs.
- What is this?
- That is an electromagnet.
Hooked up to a car battery.
And it's keeping the shrapnel
from entering your heart.
That's right. Smile!
We met once, you know.
At the technical
conference in Bern.
- Don't remember.
- No, you wouldn't.
If I had been that drunk,
I wouldn't have been able to stand,
much less give a lecture
on integrated circuits.
Where are we?
Come on, stand up.
Stand up.
Do as I do.
C'mon, put your hands up.
Those are my guns.
How did they get my guns?
Do you understand me?
Do as I do.
He says: "Welcome Tony Stark,
the most famous mass murderer
in the history of America."
He is honored.
He wants you to build a missile.
The Jericho missile
that you demonstrated.
This one.
I refuse.
Tony!
He wants to know
what you think.
I think he got a lot
of my weapons.
He says they have everything you
need to build a Jericho missile.
He wants you to make
the list of materials.
He says for you to start
working immediately,
and when you're done,
he will set you free.
No, I won't.
No, he won't.
I'm sure they're
looking for you, Stark.
But they will never find
you in these mountains.
Look...
What you just saw...
that is your legacy, Stark.
Your life's work in the
hands of those murderers.
Is that how you want to go out?
Is this the last act of defiance
of the great Tony Stark?
Or are you going to do
something about it?
Why should I do anything?
They're gonna kill me, you...
Either way, if they don't,
I'll probably be dead in a week.
Well then... this is a very
important week for you, isn't it?
If this is gonna be my workstation,
I want it well lit,
I want all of these tools.
Welding gear, I don't care if it's
acetylene or propane.
I need a soldering station,
I need helmets,
I need goggles,
I would like a smelting cup.
I need two sets
of precision tools.
How many languages do you speak?
A lot. But apparently
not enough for this place.
They speak Arabic,
Urdu, Dari, Pashto,
Mongolian, Farsi, Russian.
Who are these people?
They are your loyal
customers, sir.
They call themselves
The Ten Rings.
You know, we might
be more productive
if you include me in the
planning process? - Aha.
Okay. We don't need this.
What is that?
That's palladium, 0.15 grams.
We need at least 1.6,
so why don't you go break
down the other eleven.
What are they doing?
Working.
Careful. Careful, we only
get one shot at this.
Relax, I've steady hands.
Why do you think
you're still alive, huh?
What do I call you?
- My name is Yinsen.
- Yinsen... nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Wow, that doesn't look
like a Jericho missile.
That's because it is a
miniaturized Arc reactor.
We got a big one powering
my factory at home.
It should keep the shrapnel
out of my heart.
But what could it generate?
If my math is right,
and it always is...
three gigajoules per second.
That could run your heart
for the 50 lifetimes. - Yeah.
Or something big for 50 minutes.
This is our ticket outta here.
- What is it?
'Flying the mountain' look.
Impressive.
Shesh Besh.
Good roll.
You still didn't tell me
where you're from.
I'm from a small
town called Gulmira.
It's actually a nice place.
- You got a family?
- Yes.
And I will see them
when I leave here.
And you, Stark?
Nothing.
No.
So you're a man who has
everything... and nothing.
Doesn't look anything
like the photo.
Maybe he modified it.
- The tail doesn't seem right.
- Well, too bad.
Relax.
The bow and arrow once was the
pinnacle of weapons technology.
It allowed the great Genghis Khan
to rule from the Pacific
to the Ukraine.
An empire twice the size
of Alexander the Great.
And four times the size
of the Roman empire.
But today,
whoever holds the latest
Stark weapons,
rules these lands.
And soon...
...it will be my turn.
Why did you fail me?
We're working on it.
Diligently.
I spared your life.
Is this how you repay me?
It's very complex.
We're trying hard.
On your knees.
You think I'm an idiot?
Tell me the truth.
We are working hard.
Open your mouth.
- What does he want?
- You think I'm a fool?
What is going on?
Tell me the truth.
We are working on Jericho.
What do you want,
a delivery date?
I need him.
He's a good assistant.
You have till tomorrow...
...to assemble my missile.
- Okay?
- Yes.
Can you move?
Say it again.
41 steps straight ahead,
then 16 steps, left from
the door, four to the right.
33 steps, turn right.
Where is Stark?
He was here a moment ago.
Go find him!
Yinsen!
Stark!
Say something.
He is speaking Hungarian,
I don't...
- Speak Hungarian.
- Okay...
What do you know?
- How did that work?
- Oh my goodness.
- It worked all right.
- What do I do?
- Let me finish this.
- Finish last powering sequence.
Okay.
Now! Tell me, tell me!
F 11. Tell me when you
see a progress bar.
It should be up right now.
Talk to me, tell me when
you see it. - I have it.
- Press Ctrl + I.
- Got it.
'Enter'. I, 'Enter'. Come over
here and button me up.
They are coming!
Doesn't need to look pretty,
just get it done.
They are coming.
Make sure that checkpoints are
clear before you follow me out, OK?
We need more time.
Okay.
I'm gonna go
buy you some time.
Stick to the plan!
Yinsen!
- Yinsen!
- Watch out!
Stark.
Come on. We gotta go.
Move with me. C'mon, we got
a plan, we need to stick to it.
This was always the plan, Stark.
Come on, you're going to
go see your family again.
My family is dead.
I'm going to see them now, Stark.
It's okay.
I want this.
Thank you for saving me.
Don't waste it.
Don't waste your life.
My turn.
Not bad.
How was the fun-vee?
Next time you ride with me, okay?
Watch it coming up here.
Are you kidding me with this?
Get rid of them.
Your eyes are red.
Few tears for your
long lost boss?
Tears of joy.
I hate job hunting.
Yeah, vacation's over.
Where to, sir?
Take us to the hospital, please.
- No. - No? Tony...
- You have to go to the hospital.
- I don't have to do anything.
I was in captivity for three months.
There are two things I want to do.
I want an American cheeseburger...
...and the other one...
- That's not going to happen.
It's not what you think. I want you
to call for a press conference now.
Call for a press conference?
What on earth for?
Yeah, Hogan, drive.
Cheeseburger first.
Look at this!
Tony!
I thought you'll be
in a hospital.
Look at you!
Oh, burger, you had
to have a burger.
Did you get me one of those?
There was only one left,
I needed it.
Hey, look who's here!
- Ms. Potts?
- Yes.
May I speak with you
for a moment?
I'm not part of the press conference,
but it's about to begin right now.
I am not a reporter.
I'm agent Phil Coulson,
with the Strategic
Homeland Intervention,
Enforcement and
Logistics Division.
- That's quite a mouthful.
- I know. We're working on it.
We've been approached
already by the DOD, FBI, CIA...
We are a separate division.
With a more specific focus.
We need to debrief Mr. Stark about
the circumstances of his escape.
- I'll put something in a book,
shell I? - Thank you.
Hey, would it be alright
if everyone sat down?
Will you sit down? That way
you can see me, and I can...
A little less formal...
What's up with the lovin'?
Don't look at me,
I don't know what he's up to.
- Good to see you.
I never got to say
goodbye to dad.
goodbye to my father.
There's questions that
I would've asked him.
I would've asked him how he felt
about what his company did...
...if he was conflicted,
if he ever had doubts.
Or maybe he was every inch of a man
we all remember from the newsreels.
I saw young Americans killed...
...by the very weapons I created
to defend them and protect them.
And I saw that I had
become part of a system
that is comfortable with
zero-accountability.
What happened over there?
I had my eyes opened.
I came to realize that
I have more to offer
this world than just making
things that blow up.
And that is why, effective
immediately, I'm shutting down
the weapons manufacturing
division of Stark International...
...untill such a time,
as I can decide
what the future of
this company will be,
what direction it should take,
the one I'm comfortable with,
and is consistent with the highest
good of this country and the world.
What we should
take away from this...
...is that Tony's back!
And he's healthier than ever.
We are gonna have a little
internal discussion
and we'll get back to
you with a follow-up.
- Where is he?
- He's inside.
That... that went well.
Did I just paint a target
on the back of my head?
Your head?
What about my head?
What do you think the over-under
on a stock drop is gonna be?
- Optimistically? 40 Points?
- At minimum.
Tony, we're a
weapons manufacturer.
Obie, I just... I don't want
the body count to be up...
That's what we do. We're iron
mongers, we make weapons.
My name is on facade
of the building.
What we do keeps the world
from falling into chaos.
Not based on what I saw.
We're not doing a
good enough job.
We can do better, we're
gonna do something else.
Oh, like what? You want us
to make baby bottles?
I think we should take another
look into Arc Reactor technology.
Oh, come on. The Arc Reactor,
that's a publicity stunt!
Tony, c'mon! We built that thing
to shut the hippies up!
- It works.
- Yeah, as a science project.
The Arc was never cost-effective.
We knew that before we built it.
Arc Reactor technology,
that's a dead end, right?
- Maybe.
- Am I right?
We haven't had a breakthrough
in that, in what... 30 years.
That's what they say.
Could you have a
lousier poker face?
Just tell me, who told you?
- Never mind who told me.
- Show me.
- Rhodey or Pepper.
- I wanna see it.
- Okay, Rhodey.
It works.
Listen to me, Tony.
We are a team,
do you understand?
There's nothing we can't do
if we stick together,
like your father and I.
I'm sorry I didn't give you a
heads up, okay? But if I had...
Tony, no more of this
'ready - fire - aim' business.
- Do you understand me?
- That was dad's line.
You gotta let me handle this.
We're gonna have to play whole
different kind of ball now.
We're gonna have to
take a lot of heat.
I want you to promise me
that you're gonna lay low.
Stark Industries. I've got one
recommendation. Ready, ready?
Sell, sell, sell!
Abandon ship!
Does the 'Hindenburg'
ring any bells?
Let me show you the new
Stark Industries business plan!
Look, that's a weapons company
that doesn't make weapons!
Pepper!
How big are your hands?
- What?
- How big are your hands?
- I don't understand why...
- Get down here. I need you.
Hey!
Let's see them.
Show me your hands.
Oh, wow, they are small.
Very petite, indeed.
I just need your
help for a sec.
Oh my God, is that the thing
that's keeping you alive?
It was, it is now an antique.
This is what will be keeping me
alive for the foreseeable future.
I was swapping it up
for an upgraded unit
and I just ran into a
little... speed bump.
Speed bump?
What's happening?
It's nothing,
it's just a little snag.
There's an exposed wire
under this device
and is contacting a socket wall
and is causing a little
bit of a short circuit.
What do you want me to do?
Put that on the table over
there. That is irrelevant.
I just want you to reach in...
and you're just gonna
gently lift the wire out.
Is it safe?
Yeah, it should be fine.
It's just like an operation,
you just don't let it
touch the socket wall.
- What's Operation?
- It's just a game, never mind.
- Just gently lift the wire.
- Okay. - Okay? Great.
You know, I don't think
that I am qualified to do this.
No, no, you're fine.
You're the most capable,
qualified and trustworthy
person I've ever met.
You're gonna do great.
Is it too much of a problem to ask?
Cause I really need your help here.
- Oh, there's pus!
- It's not pus.
It's a plasmic discharge, it's from
the device, not from my body.
- It smells!
- Yeah, it does.
The copper wire.
The copper wire, you got it?
- I got it.
Now don't let it touch...
...the sides, that's what I was
trying to tell you before.
Okay, now make sure that
when you pull it out,
you don't pull out the magnet
and the end of it. That was it...
...that you just pulled out.
- Oh God. OK, what do I do?
- Don't put it back in!
- What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm just going into cardiac
arrest cause you yanked out...
- What? I thought you said this
was safe! - We gotta hurry.
Take this, you gotta switch,
real quick. - Okay, okay.
Tony, it's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna make this okay.
You gotta touch
that to base plate.
And make sure you...
Was that so hard?
That was fun, right?
I got it, I got it.
Nice.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I feel great.
Are you okay?
Don't ever, ever...
...ever ask me to do anything
like that ever again.
I don't have anyone but you.
Are we ready?
What do you want me
to do with this?
That? Destroy it.
Incinerate it.
You don't wanna keep it?
Pepper, I've been
called many things.
Nostalgic is not one of them.
- Would that be all, Mr. Stark?
- That would be all, Ms. Potts.
Hey butterfingers, come here.
What's all this stuff doing
on top of my desk?
That's my phone, that's
a picture of me and my dad...
Right there. In garbage.
All that stuff.
The future of air combat.
Is it manned or unmanned?
I tell you, in my experience,
no unmanned aerial vehicle
will ever trump
a pilot's instinct,
his insight - that ability
to look into a situation
beyond the obvious
and discern its outcome.
Or pilot's judgement.
Colonel, it's... why not
a pilot without a plane?
Look who fell outta the sky!
Mr. Tony Stark.
Speaking about manned
or unmanned,
you gotta get him to tell you
about the time he guessed wrong.
It's spring break,
just remember that.
Spring break 1987, that lovely
lady, what was his name?
Was it Ivan?
Don't do that, they'll believe it.
Don't do that.
Give us a couple
of minutes, you guys.
- I'm surprised.
- Why?
I swear I didn't expect to see
you walking around so soon.
I'm doing a little
better than walking.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Rhodey, I'm working
on something big.
I came to talk to you.
I want you to be part of it.
You're about to make a whole lotta
people around here real happy,
cause that little stunt at the
press conference, that was juicy.
This is not for the military.
I'm not... it's different.
What, are you humanitarian
now or something?
I need you to listen to me.
No, what you need is time
to get your mind right.
I'm serious.
It was nice seeing you, Tony.
Thanks.
- Jarvis, are you up?
- For you sir, always.
I'd like to open a new
project file, index as: Mark 2.
Shell I store this on the Stark
Industries' central database?
I don't know who to trust
right now. Till further notice,
why don't we just keep everything
on my private server.
Working on a secret
project, are we, sir?
I don't want this winding
up in the wrong hands.
Maybe in mine it could
actually do some good.
Next.
Up.
Not the boot, Dummy, right here.
You got me?
Stay put. Nice.
And you, you're no better
at it at all. Lift... I got it.
Okay, I'm sorry,
am I in your way?
Up.
That's great, don't even move.
You... are a tragedy.
Okay, lets do this right.
Start mark, half meter
back of the center.
Dummy, look for light.
Stand back for fire safety.
You, roll it.
Activate hand controls.
We are gonna start up
nice and easy,
raising 10% thrust capacity
to achieve lift.
And 3, 2, 1.
Up two? Alright, step back.
I've been buzzing you.
Did you hear the intercom?
Yeah, everything's... what?
- Obadiah's upstairs.
- Great, I'll be right up.
I thought you said you were
done making weapons?
It isn't. This is
a flight stabilizer.
It's completely harmless.
I didn't expect that.
How'd it go?
Oh, went that bad huh?
Just because I brought
pizza back from New York
doesn't mean it went bad.
- Sure doesn't. Oh, boy.
It would've gone better
if you were there.
You told me to lay low and
that's what I've been doing.
I lay low and you
take care of all the...
Hey, c'mon.
In public, the press...
This was a Board of
Directors meeting.
Directors meeting?
The Board is claiming
a Post Traumatic Stress.
They are filing an injunction.
- A what?
They wanna lock you out.
Why, cause the stocks dip 40 points?
We knew this was gonna happen.
- 56 and a half.
- It doesn't matter.
We own a controlling
interest in the company.
Tony, the Board has rights too.
They are making the case that
you and your new direction
isn't in a company's
best interest.
I'm being responsible.
That's a new direction.
For me... for the company.
I mean, me on the company's behalf
being responsible for the way that...
- Oh, this is great!
- Oh c'mon, wait! Tony, Tony!
- I'll be in the shop.
- Hey, hey, Tony, listen.
I'm trying to turn
this thing around,
but you gotta give me something.
Something to pitch them.
Let me have the engineers
analyze that, you know,
draw some specs.
- No.
No. Absolutely not.
This one stays with me.
That's it Obie.
Forget it.
Alright, well this
stays with me then.
Go on, here, you can have
a piece. Take two. - Thank you.
Do you mind if I come down there
to see what you're doing?
Good night, Obie.
Day 11, Test 37,
Configuration 2.0.
For lack of a better option,
Dummy is still on fire safety.
If you douse me again,
and I'm not on fire,
I'm donating you to a city college.
Alright, nice and easy.
Seriously, just gonna start off
with 1% thrust capacity.
And 3, 2, 1.
Please don't follow me around
with it either cause I feel
like I'm going to catch on fire
spontaneously. Just stand down.
If something happens,
then come in.
Again, lets bring it up to 2.5%.
3, 2, 1...
Okay, this is where
I don't want to be.
Not the car,
not the car.
It could be worse.
We are fine.
Okay, we are getting there.
Yeah. I can fly.
- Jarvis, are you there?
- At your service, sir.
Engage head up display.
Check.
Import all preferences
from home interface.
Will do, sir.
Alright, what do you say?
I have indeed been uploaded,
sir. We're online and ready.
Start the virtual walkaround.
Importing preferences and
calibrating virtual environment.
- Do a check on control surfaces.
- As you wish.
Test complete. Preparing to
power down and begin diagnostics.
Ah, yes... tell you what.
Do a weather and ATC check.
Start listening
the ground control.
Sir, there are still terabytes
of calculations needed
before an actual flight.
- Jarvis...
Sometimes you gotta run
before you can walk.
Ready? And 3, 2, 1.
It feels like a dream.
Recast.AI, the collaborative platform
for building bots! https://recast.ai