Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Shall I tell you something?
Time ruins everything.
I just made that up.
What happened to you?
I will tell you.
I spent some time in prison
because...
because I had sex with my daughter.
The western syndrome.
I think about it all the time.
It was everything I had left,
I had nothing else.
I never had anything.
It was cute.
Easy now.
We`re all... mefisto`s.
I want to bring you some fun.
Guys who fool around a bit and
then hear it`s something bad.
That it`s dramatic.
But you can`t forget the joy
and the happiness.
There are no...
There are no crimes,
only actions.
I have to start over.
I have to quit, I have to live.
Keep on fighting, staying alive.
I understand you completely.
Do you have something to drink?
No, I don¢¥t have anything to drink.
I have no penny.
Oh what...
What¢¥s that noise outside?
Nothing.
The assholes from downstairs.
They give their usual show
in the Rectum.
Right.
- Rectum!
What kind of crime?
- With blood.
Blood? Does someone have
her period or something?
May I wait here for a while?
They still owe me money.
WHat happened?
I told you those bastards
wouldn`t pay.
Step aside please.
Morad, check out that guys
fucked up face.
Is your leg fucked up, pal?
Your ass too, I hope.
Like Alex. I hope you bleed a lot.
And that you`re in a lot of pain.
His asshole must have
bled a lot.
Fucker. Fag.
Because of those two guys
the fuckers got us.
They will be happy in the street.
But I want my money.
Why are we still standing here?
We`ll get our money or go.
Fucking fags.
There are gays all over here.
It`s god damn impossible,
they are everywhere.
Clear the path.
Get rid of that asshole.
And cuff him.
They will fuck him in the
ass in prison.
I`m waiting for my money.
- Move it.
I hope you`ll be miserable in jail
and that they fuck you in the ass.
Fucking history and philosophy
teacher.
Fuscking moron.
- All philosophers are fags.
I hope they get you hard.
To the station.
- In prison there are no condoms.
You`ll get aids straigh away, fag.
What are you doing?
- I`m looking for The Tapeworm.
You have to pay.
- I`m already paying.
Go ahead.
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm?
We`ll find him,
we`ll find him.
You`re not human anymore. Even animals
don`t revenge themselves, Marcus.
It`s going totally wrong.
Leave me alone.
- You won`t survive.
It`s none of your business.
- It smells like shit here.
Quit it, Marcus.
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm?
- No.
Marcus, come back!
I won`t save you.
Marcus, stop it now.
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm?
- No.
Pierre!
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm?
Do you know The Tapeworm?
The Tapeworm?
Pierre!
It goes on downstairs.
We`re going once.
We`re going down once.
Come on, one time. Help me, Pierre.
Do you know The Tapeworm?
Why are you smiling?
The Tapeworm...
Do you know The Tapeworm? No?
let me go! Don`t you know him?
Do you know The Tapeworm?
- Do you want to suck my cock?
No.
Do you know where The Tapeworm is?
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm?
Do you want to suck my dick?
Come back. You want to fuck?
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm?
He`s here often.
Maybe upstairs.
The Tapeworm...
Are you The Tapeworm?
Let me go.
Do you know The Tapeworm?
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm? He`s here often.
- Doesn`t ring a bell.
Do you work here often?
- Yes, but it doesn`t ring a bell.
Don`t you know him either?
- Search. You won`t find him far from here.
Do you know a guy named The Tapeworm?
The Tapeworm? No.
Do you know The Tapeworm?
- I have him in my stomach.
You there. Do you know The Tapeworm?
Yes, he`s my pal.
- You know him?
He`s my friend, I said.
- Where is he?
Take me to him.
- He`s fucking a fag.
Forget The Tapeworm. Fist me.
- Don`t touch me.
Come on fist me.
- Keep your hands off me.
Shut up. Take me to him.
- Fist me.
Fist me then!
- Take me to him.
Fist me! What kind of guy are you?
Keep quiet! I`m not a fag.
Where is he? Come on.
- I`ll take you to The Tapeworm.
Take me to him!
- Two hands up your ass!
Stop it.
Are you sure you want
to see The Tapeworm?
Fist me, that`s much better.
Are you sure you want to see
him? Fisting me is much better.
I like you.
You make me think about someone else.
Take me to him, I said.
Take it easy.
Take me to him. Where is he?
Give me a drink.
- Give him a drink.
Drink! Where is he?
One Pepsi.
- Where is he?
The Tapeworm? In your ass.
The Tapeworm is in your ass. You know?
You want my fist against your yaw,
fucking fag?
Where is he? I know him.
I know him. Bring me to him.
Damned parachutist.
- Take me to him.
You should fuck their brains out.
Show them you`re a hero.
Dammit, is that what you want?
Take me to him.
Take me to him!
- I confess!
- I confess, dammit!
Go on! Go on!
Where is he?
Hurry up dammit!
- The Tapeworm is dangerous.
Are you sure you want to see
The Tapeworm?
Hit me one more time.
Where is he?
- There he is.
Fuck off.
What`s happening?
- Who`s The Tapeworm here?
Are you The Tapeworm?
I asked you something.
Who`s The Tapeworm?
I asked you something. Gone with that.
You know him?
Who`s The Tapeworm?
Who?
- What do you want from The Tapeworm?
I¢¥m looking for him.
Are you The Tapeworm perhaps?
Are you him?
Come on, fuck him! Fuck him!
Stop it!
Fucking fag!
Nice work. Good.
Fucking slit-eye.
Quit your insanity.
- We`re getting near.
Stop it.
- Wait, I`m asking.
Well, I`m waiting.
Where`s the Rectum?
- Which Rectum?
A fag bar.
- Do you need one?
Is it a whore bar?
Do you want my cock up your rectum?
Don¢¥t you know The Rectum?
- I only know this here.
Aren`t you a fag?
Where`s The Rectum?
What are you doing?
- Who are you going to hit now?
Come on.
- Yes, I have nothing else to do.
Do you know a place that...
The Rectum, do you know it?
The Rectum, a gay bar.
You know it?
That way, I think.
- There?
It`s over there! Come on!
What are you doing? Come on!
We`re close!
Are you coming?
Come on!
- Stop it!
Are you being pussy too now?
You`re crazy!
- We¢¥re going to The rectum! Come on!
Hurry up.
Drive!
Who`s followinf you?
- Drive, I said!
Are the whore`s after you?
You`re not even telling where to,
We`re going to The Rectum!
- The Rectum! That`s clear.
Everyone knows where The rectum is.
Could you show the way, please?
It`s a gay bar.
If you took care of Alex with that much
energy, nothing would have happened.
Picture that with your little
brain, moron.
With your damned inhibitions!
Are you done preaching?
The Rectum is a gay bar.
Could you point it
out on a map?
It`s a fag bar.
Do you know what that is?
Are you gay?
- No! I`m looking for a gay bar.
Don`t you know some bars?
A lot.
- Well, take us to a gay bar.
You are gay.
- No! And now shut up.
Be quiet now and
leave me alone.
Sorry, sir.
- Take us to The Rectum.
Take it easy, marcus.
I`m going crazy here.
I don`t know a Rectum.
Don`t you have a phone?
Cal then!
Don`t you have
slit-eye friends?
Don`t insult me
or I will beat you up.
Bring me to The Rectum.
I will beat him up too, sir.
Don`t take it ill of him.
He`s crazy. It`s a moron.
- Doesn`t matter.
Okay, take it easy. Easy.
One bar with guys.
- Guys?
Try to get your brain working,
fucking asshole.
Take me to The Rectum.
- Get out now.
Shut up and get out.
Just try to get me
out, fucker.
Get out, please.
I am fed up with it.
Alex would be ashamed.
- Get out now. Hurry.
Take it easy, we`re getting out.
get out, I said! Get out!
What do you want
with that pepperspray?
Filthy asshole!
- Get out!
Stop it! Get out, please.
I am fed up with it.
How much do I owe you?
Stop it, Marcus!
Fucking stop it!
Fuck off!
Fuck off! Go on!
- My taxi!
You`re crazy! Stupid fucker!
Drop dead, filthy Chinese.
You`re insane!
- We`re going to The Rectum.
Stop it now with
your stupid revenge.
We`ll pay, we¢¥ll pay.
- Only whore¢¥s are here.
It`s the whore street.
They don¢¥t know anything else.
That¢¥s not your business.
- Stop it! Why, not my business?
Stop it! What, did you want to hit me?
Don¢¥t stay here.
We will give you money.
We¢¥re going to Alex
in the hospital.
Which girl do you know?
What do you want to do?
Being more stupid than...
You don¢¥t know who it was.
Don¢¥t you wnat to know?
Nobody knows who it is.
And you¢¥re not helping Alex with that.
I will give you money.
- Well, who do you know?
It¢¥s a bit further.
- What will you get with anger?
What kind of crazy
revenge is this?
Come to Alex
in the hospital.
You want to hit me? Is that it?
What¢¥s wrong with you dammit?
Then go to the hospital.
You know those two?
- Ask those whores.
What¢¥s his name?
- Guillermo Nunez.
Do you know Guillermo Nunez?
What?
What does she say?
- Ask the other one.
Donna, I know her.
I meant her.
We deliver better work
than the cops.
Drunkards with a gun.
Zuipschuiten met 'n pistool.
The police, they are morons.
De politie, dat zijn eikels.
What do you know, teacher?
The human stupidity,
that¢¥s what I know. In a mass.
Which one is it?
- There.
She?
- Donna!
Stop it!
- I didn¢¥t do anything!
Do you know Guillermo Nunez?
- No.
you don¢¥t know Guillermo Nunez?
He¢¥s my friend.
- You don¢¥t know him?
Nobody knows Guillermo Nunez.
Who is it? Tell me.
What does she say? Concha?
The blonde?
Thank you, Donna.
Concha, are you Concha?
Do you know Guillermo Nunez?
Keep your hands off her.
Leave her alone.
We won¢¥t do her anything.
Marcus, she didn¢¥t do anything.
Who do you think we are?
- Fuck off.
Are you crazy, Marcus?
Answer me!
It¢¥s about a rape.
Please!
- Rape, you hear?
Marcus, please!
- Rape!
Are you totally?
- Easy now.
Leave her alone
or I won¢¥t pay.
Take it easy. Stop it, stop it.
Let go!
- I will push!
Come on, dammit. Alex...
- Tell him to stop,
Stop it now, Marcus. Please.
Are you crazy?
You¢¥re fucking insane!
Do you know Guillermo Nunez?
Tell me.
Who is Guillermo Nunez?
Who is Jo? I don¢¥t know a Jo.
- I am Guillemo.
lk ben Guillermo.
You have become a transvestite,
great.
I will pay you now.
- That will tell she was there.
No.
- Did you see it?
Pick up! Go on.
Stop it, Marcus.
- What did you see?
Cut out her eye.
- Come on, stab!
Fuck off, you.
- Tell me.
It¢¥s The Tapeworm. I know him.
The Tapeworm is a pimp.
Where can we find him?
Where? I will rebuild
your transvestite face.
Where is he?
- Where can I find him?
What¢¥s the name of that club?
- Rectum.
A Tapeworm in The Rectum?
Are you playing me?
It¢¥s a nightclub
for gays.
There¢¥s a taxi!
Taxi!
Did you use alcohol?
No. No drugs either?
No drugs?
But according to your
so-called colleague...
you used drugs regulary.
He can say whatever he wants.
- Is it true or not?
I didn¢¥t use anything.
And the victim?
I don¢¥t know.
- No? Didn¢¥t you live together?
Did you live together?
Don¢¥t you want to answer?
You don¢¥t make it easy for us.
Did you leave before
or after the victim?
Pull yourself together.
- After, after.
After? how much after?
- 15 minutes.
Now that¢¥s an answer.
15 minutes.
And when did Mr. Marcus
go outside?
He came in the alley with me.
He came in the alley with you.
Did he leave sometime
earlier in the evening?
I don¢¥t know.
- You don¢¥t know?
Did you notice
something special?
Were there people
around the victim?
Did she talk to certain people?
Did she have a fight with someone?
No? With you maybe?
With Mr. Marcus?
And didn¢¥t you have
a fight with Marcus?
You didn¢¥t have a
fight with Mr. Marcus?
I will need a phone number
where I can reach you.
I¢¥m listening
01... 44... 76... 12... 26.
Good. Is that your private number?
Is it your private number?
Give him back his papers.
Take your papers back.
Take your papers.
I will contact you when
I need you. You may go.
Go ahead, it¢¥s allright.
You may go.
Good evening.
Are you allright?
The woman who was attacked...
is she someone you know?
You don¢¥t feel very good, huh?
It¢¥s tough.
You always think it only happens
to other people, but if it happens to you,
you are helplessly lost.
Are you counting on the cops?
What do you think the police
will do? Nothing, and you know that.
Will they find the perpetrator?
Will they put him in jail?
Will they give him food and clothes?
Will they wash him?
Will they give him a doctor?
Your girlfriend didn¢¥t
get a doctor.
Who are you?
Who I am?
As a matter of fact...
I could become your best friend.
I cna help you find the perpetrator.
You look honest.
Nicely dressed.
Obviously you have money.
If you have some money, we could
help you get revenge.
The perpetrator spilled blood.
Blood shouts for revenge.
Revenge is a human right.
Laid, come over.
You understand it right away.
Explain who we are.
This here is our neighbourhood.
We find everyone, faster than
the morons over there.
Exactly.
- Listen to him.
Not very long ago someone
was raped here.
We have found the perpetrator.
We made him clear not to
do it again.
Do you want revenge or not?
Or do you want him to go to prison?
You hesitate?
- Do you know him?
Ofcourse. We found a hand bag
with identity.
The name was Guillermo Nunez.
Are you in?
Pay and we deliver him.
You shouldn¢¥t hesitate.
You¢¥re hurting yourself.
What¢¥s wrong? You¢¥re shivering.
This is only for men.
Don¢¥t be a pussy. Okay?
Are you in or not?
Man yourself.
Take me with you.
- Are you in?
We¢¥ll leave the cops for what they are.
- Come.
Go home then.
- You don¢¥t realize your luck.
Shall I...
- You¢¥re ruining it with Alex.
I¢¥ll give you money for a taxi.
You¢¥re ruining the party
the whole evening.
What¢¥s happening?
- A whore got raped.
You won¢¥t get through
- We want a taxi.
No, gentlemen.
- We only want a taxi.
- Don¢¥t act so stupid.
Something happened,
the street is blocked.
Alex!
Wait!
Alex! What happened?
Sir, take it easy.
- What happened?
She has been raped and is in a coma now.
Sir, please.
Let us do our work, sir.
Sir, take it easy.
Just let us do our work.
Take him away.
- Sir, please.
We can¢¥t work like that.
- Take him away.
Who are you, sir?
Is she your wife?
- Do you know that man?
I will have to ask you some questions.
Who are you?
She¢¥s my wife.
- Do you know that man?
Sir, please.
- She is my wife.
Keep him on a distance.
It¢¥s dangerous.
Please go around the tunnel.
Thank you.
Here! Filthy bitch.
Filthy bitch, you¢¥re dead.
Hold on, you.
Wait!
- Leave me alone.
Wait, I said.
Would you just shut up?
I won¢¥t do you anything.
Shut your fucking mouth.
You want to taste this?
Will you shut up now?
Fucking bitch.
Shall I give you a pretty smile?
Fucking whore.
Does that excite you?
Tell me.
Does it make you horney?
Well, well.
You are pretty hot.
Please...
- Shut up.
Leave me alone
- Shut up, I said.
Lift up your skirt.
Leave me alone.
- Lift up your skirt.
Shut up.
Dammit.
- Leave me alone, please.
Please.
Go sit on your knees.
On your knees!
On your knees! I¢¥m going
to fuck you. On your knees!
And now lie down.
Lie down.
Shut up.
Well, well.
You have a nice ass.
I¢¥m going to fuck you, whore.
Who pays for your clothes?
Your guy?
What an asshole that he lets
you walk around like this outside.
You little whore.
Shut up!
Shut up or I¢¥ll kill you.
Understand?
Dammit!
Open your legs! Open your legs!
Open your legs, dammit!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Lay still... Don¢¥t move.
I¢¥m going to fuck you in your ass.
I will fuck your ass untill it bleeds!
I will fuck your ass like
you have never fucked.
You little whore.
Don¢¥t move.
You¢¥ve been fucked
in your ass before, huh?
Does your guy do it in your ass?
Do you like it?
Dammit.
Don¢¥t move, dammit!
Lay still, don¢¥t move.
Don¢¥t move, don¢¥t move.
Don¢¥t move, dammit!
Dammit!
You have a nice tight ass.
I will fuck your ass untill it bleeds!
If you dare to shit,
you die. Understand?
Fucking bitch.
You have such a tight ass.
A nice fag ass.
Usually I don¢¥t like that.
Bitch. But this time...
Will you shut up already?
Whore! in your ass!
You¢¥ve never been fucked in
your ass like this, huh?
Dammit, is that blood or cum?
Your ass is getting bigger, huh?
Are you bleeding?
Dammit.
Oh yeah, nice.
Damn, that¢¥s nice.
Tell your daddy it¢¥s nice.
Tell daddy it¢¥s nice.
Say daddy to me.
Say daddy.
Say daddy, bitch!
Shut up!
Dammit.
Dammit... God damnit
Good.
That was nice.
Where are you going, bitch?
WHere are you going?
Where are you going like that?
Did you think I was
done with you?
Little whore.
Look at me.
Look at me when
I¢¥m talking to you.
Look at me, dammit.
Filthy bitch, look at me.
Little whore. Fucking bitch.
Come here!
Ugly bitch!
Bitch!
You think you can do anything, huh?
You think you can do anything
because you're beautiful, huh?
Dirty cunt! Dirty...
Come here!
I'm gonna hit your face real hard!
I'm not finished with you!
Come here! Here! Here!
Fucking bitch! Here!
Are you happy now? Or do you want
some more?
Want some? Fucking whore!
Please!
Little cunt, that you are!
Over here!
This is for your rotten face!
Now I'm all finished with you.
Fucking cunt.
What do you want to say to me?
You do not care about my
sexuality.
But you engage me in it.
-You never talk about yours.
Because there is nothing to tell.
What is it then?
-There is always something.
What are you doing with your dick?
Don't bitch about it.
-Are you gonna keep it to wanking?
Don't be like that. I think about
Alex and you, and that's painful.
You are alone for 3 years now.
-So what?
What do you do?
You are sent by God,
because my pal Pierre...
has a problem.
-What about it?
We must find a way to losen
Pierre a bit up.
I want to take care of that.
-You see...but how?
You are with two
and I'm not alone either.
In the toilets.
-Now shut up.
That's where it happens all the time.
-Alex is alone.
Come on.
-Go, Pierre.
You are saying that I bitch about
your sexuality, and what about you?
Are you afraid?
-Pierre is very nice.
Forget it. I know how it goes.
We make fun,
we get completly stoned...
but I did that 15 years, 30 years ago.
Hello.
-Don't do that.
Stop it, Marcus.
Leave me alone.
You can't do that to Alex.
Leave Fatima alone.
Fatima, come on.
Don't do it. You are going to regret
if you sober up.
Forget about it. Come on.
Go with me.
He's very nice.
First a present.
Don't do that shit.
Leave it.
Stop it, Pierre.
Stop it. Don't do it.
You are a pain in the ass.
And, girls?
Delicious.
I got to go see Pierre
who only loves rats and
may not be left alone.
Are you coming back?
Soon?
-Yeah. Thanks, girls.
Are you going to leave us alone?
This is Pierre
and he needs your love.
Alex is dancing all alone.
Don't be an moron.
Give him some pleasure, ladies.
-Piss off.
You are saying that I bitch about
your sexuality and what do you do?
I know. Come on, Marcus.
I really hate it when you act like that.
If you are not doing it for me,
then do it for her.
No, Marcus stays here.
Come on. Don't be such an idiot.
Alex has to dance all by himself.
Come on.
Leave him.
Here I am!
-Come on.
Marcus, you are fantastic.
-It's rotten, Marcus.
That's life, mate.
Then it didn't have any sense
to bring her along.
Why did you bring her if you
are doing it that way?
Why are you doing it that way?
Come on, have a drink.
You are in need of a glass of water
You don't have to act like that.
You take her with you and...
-Look at the ladies.
You can be a dickhead
without being with her too.
Stay with her.
You need to have some fun.
-Do you call this fun?
Yes, this is fun.
You are just like a priest.
I feel like a nanny.
-Our little priest.
I go with a teenager loaded
with drugs.
Have some water. Come on.
Have a drink.
Here, drink the water. From the sink.
Give me a shot of water from the sink.
There was a queue at the john.
I couldn't piss.
Stop it, Marcus.
-I opened the tap.
Leave it.
-Come on, quit it.
Quit it, Pierre.
Before you fuck up everything.
Come on.
-You are not funny.
It's not funny like that.
They'll see you.
You are even more fierce then an animal.
You are not funny.
Did you come for that, dickhead?
-What, dickhead?
I came to watch them dance,
therefore I'm a dickhead.
Don't be like that, Marcus. Really.
Look how beautiful she is.
Look how she dances.
Look how gorgeous. Brunette,
blonde, brunette, blonde.
Behave like an adult.
-We'll fuck'em all.
Found your girlfriends?
-So?
Hello.
- What's your name?
Joanna. Is that you?
- Vincent.
Hello, Vincent.
- No, my name is Marcus.
And you?
- Aurele.
Aurele? This is Alex.
No, that's Alex.
- I know.
I'm Marcus.
Marcus.
Come on.
-I've had it with that cunt.
Don't be so annoying.
-He brings misfortune.
I give him some pussy.
He doesn't want them.
I give him coke, he doesn't like it.
I present him a glass, he says no.
Such a bore.
You picked a weird one as lean
as a lath, Alex.
No, I rather watch you.
I bear heavy secrets.
-Dance with me.
Let me have a look at you.
You didn't use to dance.
There is the hairy monkey.
Stop it, Marcus.
Do something.
What has he swallowed?
Stop it.
In the past you never danced.
-I dance with you.
You dance to forget, huh?
Your Marcus is out of his mind.
What are you doing?
You didn't use to dance like that.
In the past you didn't dance that way.
Let yourself go.
-I'm completly relaxed.
Dance with me.
-You scare me. You're never like this.
I never saw you like this.
There you have got him again.
Do I scare you?
-Funny, huh?
Do you think that's funny?
I can do it too.
Please. Dance with me.
I'm with you. I look at you.
You are in great shape.
Remember? Be careful.
You are playing a dangerous game,
Alex.
Marcus has a lot of fun.
-Come with me.
Very nice to see you.
-The pleasure is all mine. How are you?
I'm going to say hi to a few mates.
Everything okay?
Sorry.
How about you?
And?
-And, does it grow?
He never knows when to quit.
I'm happy. You look hot.
Quit it.
I really enjoy it to see you
I'm completly wasted from the dancing.
I've also danced alot.
-Everything okay?
I'm happy.
I'm in a very special period.
I'll tell you about it.
I'm here with a guy.
Pierre?
- No.
I'm with Marcus.
I think he's completely insane.
-Yeah, it looks like it.
I want to have dinner with you
one evening.
Thank you.
-Then I'll tell you all.
She must tell me everything.
What does she have to tell?
-I don't know.
Are you alright?
-Yeah, of course.
Okay. Will you call me?
-Promised.
Well...
See you later.
Stop it.
- What?
What did you take?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
I'm sober as water.
My name is Jean-Francois.
Did you see your eyes?
-What's wrong with them?
You don't control your mouth.
You don't control your breasts.
Quit it, I want to rest.
-I've been looking for you for a while.
I was dancing.
Why do you have to swallow pills
to make fun?
I don't know. It's fun.
-You are no longer 15.
Sometimes you can be very sweet...
and soft, and at other moments
you can be a real moron.
Quit it, Alex.
-I want to go home.
I want to go home, I want some rest.
I'll bring you home.
-You look like a ghost.
Stop it, you are annoying me.
-Wait, I'll bring you home.
Don't touch me.
Come on!
I'll bring you home, I told you!
Alex, goddammit!
I'm leaving.
- Where are you going?
I'm tired.
- But you're only here for an hour.
I want to go home.
-A minute ago, you were still dancing.
What's wrong?
-He's completely stoned.
I know.
-Take care of him.
He doesn't need me, you do.
-No I don't.
Don't worry.
I'll call you tomorrow.
No. I came for you.
To see you.
It has been months. I have to make
up something to see you.
To see you dance.
-Don't torture yourself like that.
I don't.
I can take it.
It's from esthetical pleasure.
From nostalgia to see you again.
Don't go away.
I'll call you tomorrow. Promised.
Why?
-You are a darling.
No, I'm not a darling. It's
uncareful to leave you alone.
I'm reading a very good book.
-How long?
Months.
-How many pages? 43?
It's really good.
After the index it's with each page...
What's it about?
-Well, it says...
The book?
-The book says...
It seems to be that the future is
completely decided already. Everything is fixed.
And the proof is the prophetic dreams.
Beautiful. That gets us asleep
at least.
Who knows what we are going to dream.
-You should write...
Sometimes I dream that I'm asleep.
My only dream.
Come on.
-Then you get relaxed.
Very suspenseful.
-Direction Louis Blanc.
Isn't that our stop?
-No, the next one.
You have to sleep.
Do you sleep 2 hours?
How many times did collapse,
after hours of work.
Was it good? Tell me.
You can't do it either, huh?
Terrible, huh?
What will make you come?
Stop it.
Why do you say something like that?
It's your own fault, if you go out
with your ex boy-friends
You can't make her come, huh?
We'll explain it to you one time.
-No, seriously.
What?
-Does he really make you come?
I don't say...
-You don't have to say anything.
Quit it. He with his monkey face.
Tell me.
Come on.
Don't be like that.
"Yes, we come."
You see how you are now, Pierre?
You want to explain everything.
Do you come or not?
I haven't been able to for years.
Don't excite yourself.
Everything is fine.
That's why you're in the back
and I'm up front.
No, seriously. There is nobody.
-Stop it.
Did he do something nice
or not?
You don't talk about that stuff.
Shall we do them then?
In turns.
That way we'll see if it works on them.
-It's complicated.
Did it work or not?
You held against me that...
I've been thinking for a long time...
I had results.
Excellent results, since...
Can he do it?
-We're not talking about sex.
Why not?
-You can talk about everything...
We can talk about sex,
just not with you.
He wants to explain everything.
Like sex. Sex is an act, you
don't talk about it.
But you can say how it is?
Did you enjoy a bit,
yes or no?
It's a vulgar question.
For me it was finished.
Why do you say that?
- I had to, from my cardiologist.
He said I would die from it.
"Her orgasm or your heart," she said.
Seriously.
- Stop it now.
there, a metro.
And it's blue with colors.
Did you achieve something or not?
Pierre!
- No, seriously.
We will explain everything.
Liar.
Liars have a big nose,
you have big ears.
Do I have a big nose?
- No, big ears. Your nose is nothing.
By the way, with the wind... look.
What an airflow.
Ladies and gentlemen,
a couple that cums.
One time...
One time she screamed.
- In four years, very good.
Because she bumped into
the pedestal.
Why are you acting like that?
The only tangible proof
of an orgasm.
And I believed in it.
I thought: Finally.
She cried. And it was bleeding.
You know what people say?
There are no women
who can't come,
only men who can't fuck.
And that's it.
-Why are you hurting yourself?
I am not. Tell me the truth and
I swill accept it.
I was too cerebral to
make her cum.
Then she follows a diet of banana's
and testosteron, and it's done.
You are trite.
- Seriously.
Do you do it for a banana diet?
Bravo.
Look at that couple going to a party
who don't share their bed secrets.
You have to be able to be tender.
- And you were so progressive.
I'll write it down, you never know
if I find the one.
It has been long that..
A knot, thank you.
No, I kept it for you.
How are those things called again?
Go on, tell me.
A tender gesture.
- No, for you it's hopeless.
You won't succeed anymore.
- Tell me.
You take care of your rats.
You can still do that.
I can't make them cum.
That's illegal.
I'm going crazy
or I'll rape children.
How do you do it?
- Don't make jokes about that.
Alex, what was the problem?
- What do you think?
His onomatopoeia?
His skin? His smell?
Or was it the tarzan yell?
Unimaginable.
You're saying I'm too intellectual.
Now I'm asking for something simple.
She gives a stroke,
she goes like...
Maybe you can sing at the same time.
What's that to me?
Am I annoying?
- No.
I am annoying. Sorry.
Sir, madam.
Excuse me.
Madam is coming.
Madam is coming,
but keeps it to herself.
How far are you with Sylvie?
- Like with the others.
After a few hours
of extreme effort...
Sylvie doesn't interest me.
- You know what your problem is?
You act like it's a big achievement.
-What?
To you it's a achievement.
Sex. You do it, but you¢¥re not
participating.
What do you tell me now?
-It's true.
The details of your private life
is none of my interests.
Excuse us, your honor.
-He started.
Later at the party you can continue
your discussion in the toilets.
Unbelievable.
What did you do more that I
couldn't do?
You are too old for that stuff.
I'm 2 years older than you are.
-A little bit more.
Mister starts cavilling.
You think too much about
the pleasure of the other.
You have to let yourself go lose.
-You are an altruist.
Get relaxed and think about yourself.
-That's selfish.
It's better like this.
Otherwise you get blocked.
You think too much about the
pleasure of others.
You get blocked because you
are not focusing on yourself.
In the end the pleasure of the woman,
is the pleasure of a man.
If I feel that the man isn't
enjoying...
his own pleasure...
-Wait a moment.
If I feel that the man doesn't go
up in his own pleasure...
You are not enjoying it because
I don't enjoy it?
No, I get blocked.
-What a bad thing to hear afterwards.
After all these years...
-I couldn't do it. No.
All this effort I took to
temper myself...
for hours.
I have been sweating from it.
Let me explain.
-And it was wrong? It had to be fast.
And you came two hours later,
while I was in the shower or asleep.
This is really fucked.
No, it's not like that.
-You push me too...
I wanted...
-He fucks and she comes hours later.
You can't explain.
-It's not rational.
Your problem is that you
want an explanation for everything.
But sometimes there is no explanation.
It's like that talking for centuries.
Sometimes you just have to fuck.
And afterwards everything is solved.
I don't know why.
The bodies talk.
-Don't I have to talk?
I talked during fucking.
Remember?
But the bodies.
-And everything I said got you excited.
It was just a chat.
But it interested you.
It was never a real extacy,
but once or twice...
Say it. He isn't listening anyway.
-More often.
Really? More often, mate! More often!
Mate!...more often.
You always talk like an intellectual.
-Me?
But after all it's always terra terra.
It's about sex.
That's good, isn't it?
-But you say he's an animal.
It's an essential need.
He doesn't possess the language.
"I fuck, I eat, I Marcus"
But I diverse.
I many trouble,
because I not speak the language very well.
The language.
-Come on now, "Language".
Are we there?
-I stay so I can wank myself off.
Well ok.
What a bullshit.
More often.
That's not bad at all.
Hello, Alexandra.
Pierre here. I've got car trouble.
I¢¥ll come and get you with the metro.
In 20 to 30 minutes.
I had a dream.
It was weird.
I don't have any feeling in my arm.
I walked through a tunnel.
A tunnel...
completely red...
And afterwards...
The tunnel broke in 2 pieces.
I think...
it's because of my menstruation.
Are you over time.
Remember?
A lot?
No, just a few days.
We'll see.
We had a long sleep.
We have to get up.
I have to buy a new bottle.
for the party tonight.
Pierre...
I have to be kind to him.
because in the end I stole
his wife.
What?
And I have to be too...
-No...
You didn't steal anything from anyone, honey.
I'm...
I'm not a thing.
You have not stolen anything
from anyone.
I have done it.
I have decided everything.
It's always the wife that decides.
Really.
But then again...
It's true that you decide.
By the way...
What do you get for me? Do you give
me parties with your ex?
He may be a friend.
But he is crazy about you.
He likes you.
Whatever, you will pay.
-I won't pay shit.
You decide and you pay for it.
-No, stop it.
No, wait. I'm not awake yet.
You'll pay for this.
If you hurt me, you'll pay.
You will pay.
The revenge of the elephant.
-Stop it!
Who kills children!
Stop it.
You know I don't like that.
Then I will revenge myself too.
With a kiss.
You crushed me.
-That's not true.
Wait, you...
-No.
Did I hurt you?
You're exaggerating.
You crushed my balls.
Dammit, Alex.
That can't be.
Did I hurt you?
You're a pig.
You're a dirty pig.
Then I will go away. I'll make
sone coffee. That will teach you.
Stop it.
Quit it.
I'll make some coffee.
-Make some coffee?
You know...
You should buy some booze.
Go on.
Okay.
Take a look,
I have something here that hurts.
No, really, I have something here.
Will you play some music?
No.
Alex...
- What?
I think I...
feel like fucking you in the ass.
No! I thought you were
going to say something romantic.
It is romantic.
- Oh? No, you know...
I love you.
I love you too.
And what if I were pregnant?
That wouldn't be so bad.
Yes, please.
Take a shower.
Hey, well...
I'm going to buy a bottle.
You have money?
Come on, stop it.
- What?
Do you ever have money?
Alright. Do you have some?
I'll get some from your purse.
See you later.
PREGNANCY TEST
TIME RUINS EVERYTHING
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4uwep
Help other users to choose the best subtitles