Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I will die
St. John?
I found her
at the door.
She's white as death
Hannah,
some of that hot milk.
St. John, we would
have stumbled upon
her corpse in the morning.
And she would
have haunted us for
turning her away.
- She's no vagrant.
- I'm sure of it.
There's milk for you.
Here.
Ask her her name.
What's your name?
YOUNG JOHN REED
Jane Eyre.
Tell us how
we may help you.
Your name?
YOUNG JOHN REED
Where are you?
Must hide
St. John, we must
get her warm.
ST. JOHN
Let us take her upstairs
Will she die?
Where are you, rat?
I know you're here.
If you crawl out and say,
"Forgive me, Master Reed,"
I might consider it.
Mama
John
There you are.
That book
belongs to me, rat.
It belongs to
my Uncle Reed.
Spoilt, miserable brat!
- Mama!
- For shame!
Mama!
You wretched imp
She attacked me
I hate you, John Reed!
I hate you!
Hilary, take her! Take her!
Lock her in the red room
No!
Please, please!
No, it's haunted. Please
It's haunted! No!
Please! Please
If you don't sit still
you will be tied down
What we do is
for your own good.
Pray for forgiveness,
Miss Eyre,
or something bad will
come down that chimney
and fetch you away.
Let me out, please!
Have mercy, Aunt Reed
Please
Do you know, Jane Eyre,
where the wicked
go after death?
They go to hell.
And what is hell?
A pit full of fire.
Should you like
to fall into this pit
and be burned
there forever?
No, sir.
How might
you avoid it?
I must keep in good
health and not die.
What is her parentage?
She's an orphan
Her mother was
my husband's sister.
On his deathbed
he exhorted me
to care for her.
I have always treated her
as one of my own.
If you accept her
at Lowood School,
Mr. Brocklehurst,
keep a strict eye on her
She has a heart of spite
and I'm sorry to say
that her worst fault
is that of deceit.
You can rest assured
that we shall root out
the wickedness
in this small,
ungrateful plant.
And as
for its vacations,
it must spend them
all at Lowood
You may leave.
You said I was a liar.
I'm not.
If I were,
I should say I loved
you, and I don't.
I dislike you worse
than anybody
in the world.
People think you are good
but you're bad
and hard-hearted
I'll let everyone know
what you have done.
Children must be corrected
for their faults.
Deceit is not my fault.
But you are passionate
My Uncle Reed is in heaven,
so are my mother and father.
They know how you hate
me and wish me dead.
They can see.
They see everything
you do and they will
judge you, Mrs. Reed
Get out.
- Next.
- Show me your hands.
Stop there
Very grand
Next.
Step out
of your fine dress.
Stay there
Show me your hands
My name
is Jane Elliott.
Who can we send
for to help you?
No one.
I mustn't ever be found.
Join me to Thyself
with an inseparable
band of love.
For Thou,
even Thou alone,
dost satisfy him
that loveth Thee.
And without Thee
all things are vain
and empty
Amen
Amen.
It's wonderful to see
you up, Miss Elliott
Last week we thought
we'd be escorting your remains
to an unmarked grave.
She read
The Bride of Lindorf
and suddenly it's all
woebegone maidens
and dramatic deaths.
I'm sorry to have
caused so much trouble.
Nonsense.
You're the
most exciting thing
that's happened here
since St. John's
sermon on the
fall of Babylon
I hope I'll not
be eating long at your
expense, Mr. Rivers.
Then tell me where
to place you.
Show me where to seek
work, that is all I ask.
You're not fit enough
to work. Is she, Di?
No. Stay with us
You return to your posts
at the end of the month.
What must
Miss Elliott do then?
I'll endeavor to help you,
if that's what you wish.
With all my heart, sir.
This school you
were at, Miss Elliott,
this charitable institution
what did it prepare you for?
Was it a thorough education?
Most thorough
A little wit...
will serve
a fortunate man
Again. A little wit...
A little wit
will serve
a fortunate man
Burns!
I will not have you
before me in that attitude.
All rise
I see you are mortifying
this girl's flesh.
Sir, she was not..
It is your mission
to render her contrite
and self-denying.
Continue.
The new girl.
This is the pedestal
of infamy,
and you will remain
upon it all day long.
You will have neither
food nor drink,
for you must learn
how barren is the
life of a sinner.
Children, I exhort you
to shun her, exclude her,
shut her out
from this day forth.
Withhold the hand
of friendship
and deny your love
to Jane Eyre
the liar.
How do you bear
being struck?
Miss Scatcherd hits me
to improve me.
She's tormented
by my faults.
If she hit me,
I'd get that birch
and break it
under her nose.
She'd find another
soon enough.
My father used to preach
that life's too short
to spend in nursing
animosity.
At my aunt's house,
I was solitary
and despised.
She thought I could do
without one bit of
love or kindness.
You are loved
There's an invisible world
all around you
a kingdom of spirits
commissioned to
guard you, Jane.
Do you not see them?
Jane?
Have you something
for me to do?
You're doing
something already
May I see?
These are wonderful.
St. John
No, Mary, please...
See how skilled Jane is.
Is this how
you perceive me,
Miss Elliott?
Well. How fierce I am.
Jane.
You're freezing.
Your little feet are bare.
Come into bed
and coveryourself.
How are you?
I'm happy, Jane.
I'm going home.
Back to your father?
I'm going to God
Don't be sad.
You have a passion
for living, Jane.
And one day you'll
come to the region of bliss.
Don't leave me.
I like to have you near
I will not leave you.
No one shall
take me from you
Helen!
Mr. Rivers? I wondered
if you had yet heard
of any work I could do.
I found you a situation
some time ago,
but I've delayed telling you
because the work is lowly
and I fear you'll scorn it.
I shan't mind what I do.
When I took over
the parish two years ago
it had no school
I opened one for boys
I now intend to
open one for girls.
The schoolmistress
will have a cottage paid
for by benefactors
and she'll receive
£15 a year.
You can see how humble,
how ignoble it is.
Mr. Rivers,
thank you.
I accept.
With all my heart
But you comprehend me?
'Tis a village school
cottagers' daughters
What will you do
with all your fine
accomplishments?
I will save them
till they're wanted.
They will keep.
Jane.
You will be quite
alone here.
I'm not afraid
of solitude.
This is my first home
where I am neither dependent
nor subordinate to anyone.
Thank you, Mr. St. John
It is small and plain
as I told you.
Then it'll suit me
very well.
Safe journey,
Miss Eyre. Godspeed.
Goodbye, Miss Eyre
Safe journey.
Thank you.
Bye, Miss Eyre.
Girls!
Goodbye
Thornfield, Miss.
Wait here, Miss
How do you do,
my dear?
Are you Mrs. Fairfax?
Indeed I am
What a tedious journey
you must have had.
Your hands must
be frozen. Here.
Goodness.
How young you are.
I'm quite experienced
I can assure you
Of course you are.
I'm sure we're very
lucky to have you.
Leah, would you
ask Martha to bring
a little hot port
and cut a sandwich or two?
Draw nearer the fire
John is taking your trunk
up to your room.
I've put you at the
back of the house
I hope you don't mind
The rooms at the
front have much
finer furniture,
but they're so gloomy
and solitary, I think.
I'm glad you're come.
To be sure, this is
a grand old house,
but I must confess that
in winter one can fee
a little dreary and alone
Leah's a very nice girl,
and John and Martha
are good people, too,
but they are servants.
One cannot talk to them
on terms of equality
Am I meeting
Miss Fairfax tonight?
Who?
Miss Fairfax
my pupil?
Oh, you mean Miss varens,
Mr. Rochester's ward.
She's to be your pupil
Who's Mr. Rochester?
Why, the owner of Thornfield.
Mr. Edward Fairfax Rochester.
I thought Thornfield Ha
belonged to you.
Bless you, child,
what an idea. Me?
I'm only the housekeeper
Forgive me.
There is a distant
connection between
Mr. Rochester and me
his mother was a Fairfax,
but I'd never presume on it.
Heavens. Me,
owner of Thornfield?
We shall have a cheerful
house this winter
With Miss Varens
here and with you,
we'll have quite
a merry time of it.
I'm sure that last winter,
and what a severe one it was,
if it didn't rain it snowed,
if it didn't snow it blew.
I declare, not one sou
came to the house from
November to February.
When spring finally came,
I thought it a great relief
I hadn't gone distracted.
I've had Martha lay a fire.
I hope you'll be comfortable.
Now, get that lot
turned over before
frost comes down
Do you want
the upper bit doing
as well?
Yes
We must open the
window in the study today
to let in some air
I've never seen such
an ancient old house
How beautifully
you've preserved it.
Well, Mr. Rochester's visits
are always unexpected
He doesn't like
to arrive and find
everything all swathed up,
so I keep it in
constant readiness.
Now, come and
meet Miss Varens.
Did I mention
she's French?
Will you ask her
about her parents?
Mr. Rochester
neglected to tell me
anything about her.
Her mother
has passed away.
Adèle is going to show us
her accomplishments.
Oh!
How very French.
Very good.
Now, we're going
to make a press
Shut the book up
Butterfly.
And what was it
before it was a butterfly?
Caterpillar
"I shall leave
and walk into town.'
"Do not go,"
begged her maid.
"The Gytrash roams
these hills."
A spirit of the North
that lies in wait
for travelers.
It tenants the
carcasses of beasts
possesses horses,
wolves, great dogs.
You know it
only by its eyes,
which burn as
red as coals,
and if one should
chance upon you
Nothing. A mere story
What nonsense
Whatever brings
you up here?
I've been waiting
to pour our tea.
I'm not in need of tea
thank you.
It's a quiet life,
isn't it?
This isolated house,
a still doom for
a young woman.
I wish a woman could
have action in her life,
like a man.
It agitates me to pain
that the skyline over
there is ever our limit.
I long sometimes
for a power of vision
that would overpass it
If I could behold
all I imagine...
I've never seen a city
I've never
spoken with men
And I fear my
whole life will pass
Now, exercise
and fresh air,
great cures for
anything, they say.
I have some letters to post
Will you take them?
Up! Up, you
cursed beast! Up
Stand back.
Are you injured, sir?
May I be of some help?
Where did you
come from?
Just below,
at Thornfield Hall.
I am the governess
I'm on my way
to post a letter
Can I fetch
someone to help?
The governess.
You may help me yourself.
Get hold of his bridle
and lead him to me.
If you would be so kind.
It would be easier
to bring me to the horse.
Come here.
I must beg of you
to please come here,
Miss Governess.
Hold it.
Make haste
with your letter
For who knows
what might lurk in
these dark woods.
Leah
go and light the fire in
the master's bedroom.
And tell Martha
to prepare for tea.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Rochester's here.
Go and change your frock.
He wishes to meet you.
Leah, take her cloak.
I have to change?
I always dress for
the evening when
Mr. Rochester's here.
But all my dresses
are the same.
You must have
one that's better.
He's in a terrible humor.
His horse fell
in Hay Lane, and
his ankle is sprained
He's at the doctor
this half hour
Where have you been?
Let her sit
I've examined Adèle
and I find you've taken
great pains with her.
She's not bright,
she has no talents,
yet in a short time
she's improved.
Thank you, Mr. Rochester.
You've been resident
here three months?
Yes, sir.
And from whence
do you hail?
What's your tale of woe?
Pardon?
All governesses
have a tale of woe.
What's yours?
I was brought up by my aunt,
Mrs. Reed of Gateshead,
in a house even
finer than this
I then attended
Lowood School,
where I received
as good an education
as I could hope for.
I have no tale
of woe, sir
Where are your parents?
Dead
Do you remember them?
No
And why are you
not with Mrs. Reed
of Gateshead now?
She cast me off, sir
Why?
Because I was burdensome
and she disliked me.
No tale of woe?
I daily thank providence
for sending us Miss Eyre.
She's an invaluable
Don't trouble yourself to
give her a character.
I'll judge for myself.
I have her to thank
for this sprain
Sir?
You bewitched my horse.
I did not.
Were you waiting
for your people
on that lane?
I have no people, sir
I mean for the imps
and elves and little
green men.
The sad truth is,
they are all gone.
Your land is neither wild
nor savage enough for them.
Adèle brought me these.
Are they yours?
Yes, sir.
Where did you
get your copies?
Out of my head
That head I now see
on your shoulders?
Yes, sir.
Who's this?
The evening star.
Were you happy when
you painted these?
Yes.
To paint is one of
the keenest pleasures
I have ever known.
Then your pleasures
have been few.
Are you satisfied
with them?
Far from it.
I imagine things I'm
powerless to execute
You've secured the
shadow of your thoughts.
Yet the drawings
are, for a schoolgirl,
peculiar.
Good night
Come, Adèle
Most merciful Father,
we give Thee humble
thanks for this,
Thy special bounty.
Amen
Amen.
Sit nicely, please, Adèle
Pilot
Pilot, come here!
Go on,
further down!
By the river!
He's very abrupt
and changeful.
What manner
of man is he?
He's a good master.
He's fine company,
too, when he...
Except when he's
in an ill humor.
Adèle.
I hate to reload.
On three
One, two, three
Ready?
Oh!
Think that's it, sir.
Take it down to the river.
Come on
Keep it
Take it away and
disembowel it
Beautiful.
Miss Eyre.
I'm not fond
of children.
Nor do I particularly enjoy
simple-minded old ladies.
But you might suit me,
if you would.
How, sir?
By distracting me
from the mire of
my thoughts.
That is how Maman
used to say.
Precisely
And that's
how she charmed
my English gold
out of my English pocket
Let's go and try it on,
shall we?
Your gaze is very
direct, Miss Eyre.
Do you think me handsome?
No, sir.
What fault do
you find with me?
I have all my limbs
and features.
I beg your pardon, sir.
I ought to have replied
that beauty is of
little consequence.
You're blushing, Miss Eyre.
And though
you're not pretty any more
than I am handsome
I must say it becomes you.
And now I see
you're fascinated by
the flowers on the rug
Come, speak to me
Fact is, Miss Eyre,
I'd like to draw you out
you have rather
the look of another
world about you.
I don't wish to treat
you as inferior
Yet you'd command
me to speak?
Are you very hurt by
my tone of command?
There are few masters
who'd trouble to enquire
whether their paid
subordinates
were hurt by their commands.
Paid subordinate?
I'd forgotten the salary.
Well, on that
mercenary ground,
will you consent
to speak as my equal
without thinking that
the request arises
from insolence?
I'd never mistake
informality for
insolence, sir.
One, I rather like.
The other, nothing freeborn
should ever submit to.
Humbug.
Even for a salary.
Most free-born things
would submit to
anything for a salary.
But I mentally shake
hands with you
for your answer.
Not three in 3,000
schoolgirl governesses
would have answered me
as you've just done.
Then you've not
spent much time in
our company, sir.
I'm the same plain kind
of bird as all the rest,
with my common tale of woe
I envy you
How?
Your openness,
your unpolluted mind.
When I was your age,
fate dealt me a blow.
And since happiness
is denied me,
I've a right to get
pleasure in its stead.
And I will get it,
cost what it may.
Then you'll degenerate
still more.
But, Miss Eyre
if the pleasure
I was seeking was
sweet and fresh,
if it was an inspiration
if it wore the robes of
an angel of light,
what then?
To speak truth, sir,
I don't understand you at all.
I fear the conversation
has got out of my depth.
You're afraid of me.
I'm not afraid.
I've simply no wish
to talk nonsense.
Do you never laugh
Miss Eyre?
Only rarely, perhaps
But you're not
naturally austere,
any more than
I'm naturally vicious
I can see in you
the glance of a
curious sort of bird
through the close-set
bars of a cage,
a vivid, restless captive
Were it but free,
it would soar, cloud-high.
Leah,
have you seen Mrs. Poole?
Yes, ma'am.
The master's in no mood
for any more mistakes.
Who's there?
Wake up, sir!
Wake up! Sir
Wake up!
The quilt!
Give it here!
A noise aroused me
from my sleep.
What noise?
There was someone
at my door.
Stay here
Don't make a sound.
Say nothing about this.
You're no talking fool.
But...
I'll account for
this state of affairs.
Say nothing
Yes, sir.
Is that how you
would leave me?
Jane, fire is
a horrible death.
You've saved my life.
Don't walk past me
as if we were strangers.
But what am I to do then?
I've a pleasure in
owing you my life
There is no debt.
I knew you would do me
good in some way.
I saw it in your eyes
when I first beheld you.
Their expression did
not strike my very inmost
being so for nothing.
People talk of natural
sympathies. You...
Good night then, sir
You will leave me, then?
I am cold.
Go
Has Mr. Rochester
not sent for us today?
Why, he's gone away
Were you not aware?
He left after breakfast
He's gone to the Leas.
It's Mr. Eshton's place
I believe Blanche
Ingram is there.
She's a great
favorite of his
I saw her two years
ago when Mr. Rochester
gave a party here.
She's a most
elegant girl.
They sang a duet together.
They made a lovely harmony.
I was quite surprised
he didn't make a proposal,
but she has no fortune.
In every other way
they'd make
a splendid match.
Perhaps it's his
intention now.
He's far more likely to
have gone off to Europe
He often goes
without so much
as a fare-you-well
and I don't see
him for a year.
I collected
the burnt linen
from the master's room
That's fine
Just go make up the bed.
England is
a great power, Adèle.
British ships set sail
from here to the outer
limits of our empire,
navigating the five oceans
and four corners of our world.
From Canada, here,
all the way to the
south of Africa
and the Cape of Good Hope
Across the Indian Ocean,
to Australia and New Zealand,
and on to Burma, China,
India and Malaya.
Nothing.
On these distant horizons,
you will find all
manner of men.
He's coming
back tomorrow.
He's given me
directions to prepare
all the rooms.
I'm to get more staff
from the George Inn
Miss Ingram's coming.
Supplies to be got,
the linen, mattresses...
I'll go to the George now
No, no, I'll tell Martha...
May I assist you,
Mrs. Fairfax?
Oh
South-facing rooms
for Lady Ingram
and Miss Ingram.
Colonel Dent and Mrs. Dent
must have the river view.
I reckon
master's taken a fancy
to that Miss Ingram.
He may well have
asked her already
I'll wager
he will by end of week.
You mark my words
Adèle.
What's she saying?
Mr. Rochester is here.
Everybody out.
Edward.
Allow me,
Miss Ingram.
I'd forgotten
how masculine
Thornfield is
I think
you need more flowers.
I have
the fairest of all on my arm.
Come away, Adèle
Tonight, he wants both
of you in the drawing
room after dinner.
Not me, surely.
I'm instructed to tell you,
if you resist,
he'll come up
and get you himself.
But I don't have a dress.
Don't worry, child,
who'll notice?
Mademoiselle!
I thought you
were not fond of children,
Mr. Rochester.
Nor am I, Lady Ingram.
What induced you
to take charge of her?
She was
left on my hands.
Why don't you
send her to school?
She has a governess.
Poor child.
I had about half
a dozen in my day,
all detestable incubi.
It's true.
Mr. Rochester
beware the governess
Mama thinks
they're generally hysterics.
Or degenerates.
I thank heaven
I have done with them
It's a miracle
I survived my education.
I remember
Miss Wilson screaming,
"You villainous child!"
That's right. She tried
to set her hair on fire
Frequently, I might add.
Anyway, enough
of this dreary race.
We shall have music
and a new subject.
Signor Eduardo,
what shall it be?
I give you beauty.
There's nothing
new to be said.
I give you back
male beauty.
Well,
that's my son.
Hear hear.
A man should pay
no heed to his looks.
He should possess
only strength and valor.
Gentleman or highwayman,
his beauty lies
in his power.
Then a pirate
would do for you?
Why did you
leave the room?
I am tired, sir.
Why didn't you come
and speak to me?
I haven't seen you
for weeks.
It would have been normal
and polite to wish me
good evening.
You seemed engaged
You look pale.
I am well
What have you been doing
while I've been away?
Teaching Adèle
You're depressed.
What's the meaning of this?
Your eyes are full...
What is it?
There's a gentleman
to see you, sir.
From Spanish Town
Jamaica
And indeed I think
he does come from
some hot place
because he won't
take off his coat
Mr. Richard Mason
I've put him in
the morning room.
Have I done wrong?
Bring him to my study.
Jane, this is a blow
If I were to go
to those people
and they looked at me
coldly and sneered,
and then left me
one by one,
what would you do?
Would you go with them?
No, sir.
I'd stay with you
You'd dare condemnation
for my sake?
For the sake of any friend
who deserved it.
Richard.
Fairfax.
How the devil are you?
Splendid.
I'm sorry. I see
you have guests.
'Tis no trouble. Come.
What on Earth was that?
- Where is Rochester?
- Wait for me.
I'm here. Be composed
A servant has had
a nightmare, that's all.
I must see you back
into your rooms
because until
the house is settled,
she can't be
properly looked after
Is there
anything I might do?
Miss Ingram,
ladies, please
return to your nests
like the doves that you are.
I assure you
all is well.
Noisy old house.
Come, my lily flower
I told you
it was nothing.
Please.
Come with me.
Can you clean this?
Yes
Drink, Richard
It will give you the
strength you lack.
- Will it hurt me?
- Drink!
I must go for the doctor.
Sponge the blood
away when it returns.
Give him water
if he wants it
Do not speak to him
for any reason.
And, Richard
on pain of death,
do not speak to her.
How does he?
He is sleeping.
Hurry, Carter
Be on alert.
The sun will soon rise
and he must be gone.
Let's have a look,
shall we?
Flesh is torn
as well as cut
Very, very unpleasant
Fairfax
Drive!
It's a strange night
you've passed.
Yes, sir.
You showed no fear.
I was afraid of
the inner room
You were in no danger.
Mr. Rochester,
who did that violence?
I cannot tell you.
Why do you protect them?
I drag through life
a capital error.
Its consequence
blights my existence.
For years, I've sought
to escape it.
This spring,
I came home heart-sore
and soul-withered.
And I met a gentle stranger
whose society revives me.
With her, I feel
I could live again
in a higher, purer way
Tell me
am I justified in
overleaping an obstacle
of custom to attain her?
There is an obstacle?
A mere conventional
impediment.
But what can it be?
If you cherish
an affection, sir
then fortune alone
cannot impede you
Yes
And if the lady
is of noble stock
and has indicated that
she may reciprocate...
Jane, of whom do
you think I speak?
Of Miss Ingram
I'm asking what
Jane Eyre would do
to secure my happiness?
I would do
anything for you, sir.
Anything that was right.
You transfix me quite.
I feel I can speak
to you now
of my lovely one
for you've met her
and you know her.
She's a rare one
isn't she?
Fresh and healthy,
without soil or taint.
I'm sure
she'll regenerate me
with a vengeance.
You look
ridiculous.
This game
is ridiculous.
Excuse me, sir
Does that creeping
creature want you?
Excuse me.
This is from my
old nurse, Bessie.
She says my cousin
John Reed is dead.
He squandered his fortune
and has committed suicide.
The news has so
shocked my aunt
it's brought on a stroke.
What, the aunt
who cast you out?
She's been asking for me
I parted from her badly
and I can't neglect
her wishes now.
Promise me
you won't stay long
Mr. Rochester
I've had no wages
I need funds for my journey.
How much do I owe you?
Thirty pounds.
Here's 50
That's too much.
Take your wages, Jane
I cannot.
Then I only have 10.
Now you owe me.
Indeed I do
Meantime, I shall
safeguard it here.
Do you trust me
to keep it?
Not a whit, sir.
You are not to be
trusted at all.
Jane Eye.
I've twice done
you wrong.
And I broke the vow
I made to Reed.
Please, don't think of it.
Open that box
Take out the letter
and read it.
"Madam,
"will you have the goodness
to send me
"the address of my
niece, Jane Eyre?
"I desire her to come
to me at Madeira.
"Fortune has blessed
my endeavors,
"and as I am childless,
I wish to adopt her
"and bequeath her at my death
whatever I may have to leave
"Yours, John Eyre, Madeira."
This is dated three years ago.
Why did I never hear of it?
Because I wrote
and told him
you'd died of typhus
at Lowood School.
You called the names
of the dead
down upon me.
You cursed me
I would have loved you
if you'd let me.
You were born
to be my torment.
Then love me or
hate me as you will.
You have my full
and free forgiveness.
Be at peace.
My dear uncle,
Some years ago,
my Aunt Reed mistakenly
informed you that I had died.
I am writing to tell you
that I'm very much alive
and gratified to find
I have a relative.
I look forward to
our correspondence,
hoping one day we may meet.
I'm currently living
at Thornfield Hall,
where I am governess
to the ward of
Mr. Edward Fairfax Rochester.
Ah. There you are.
Just like one
of your tricks,
to steal in along
with the twilight.
If I dared I'd touch you
to see if you were real
Come, Jane
Stay your wandering feet
at a friend's threshold.
Thank you, Mr. Rochester,
for your great kindness.
I'm strangely glad
to get back again.
There's been
nothing official yet,
but he's ordered
jewels from his bank
and he's making preparations
to travel to Europe.
Mademoiselle.
He's taken to singing,
the operas Miss Ingram
favors so well.
We'll hear
their announcement
soon, I'm sure.
You are to be married.
I see Mrs. Fairfax has
intimated my intention
to put my neck
into the sacred noose.
Adèle should
go to school,
and I must seek
another situation.
Congratulations, sir
Thornfield is a pleasant
place in spring, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
You'll be sorry
to part with it.
It's always the way
with events in life.
No sooner
have you got settled
than a voice cries,
"Rise and move on!'
I'll find you
a new situation, Jane,
one I hope
that you'll accept.
I shall be ready
when your order
to march comes
Must I really lose
a faithful paid subordinate
such as yourself?
You must.
We've been good friends
haven't we?
Yes, sir.
I've a strange feeling
with regard to you
as if I had a string
somewhere under my left ribs,
tightly knotted to
a similar string in you.
And if you were to leave
I'm afraid that
cord of communion
would snap.
And I've a notion
that I'd take to
bleeding inwardly
As for you,
you'd forget me
How?
I have lived
a full life here.
I have not been
trampled on.
I have not
been petrified.
I have not been
excluded from every
glimpse of what is bright
I have known you,
Mr. Rochester,
and it strikes me
with anguish to be
torn from you.
Then why must you leave?
Because of your wife
I have no wife.
But you are
to be married.
Jane, you must stay
And become
nothing to you?
Am I a machine
without feelings?
Do you think that
because I am poor,
obscure, plain and little
that I am soulless
and heartless?
I have as much soul as you
and full as much heart.
And if God had blessed me
with beauty and wealth,
I could make it as hard
for you to leave me
as it is for I
to leave you.
I'm not speaking to you
through mortal flesh.
It is my spirit that
addresses your spirit
as if we'd passed
through the grave and stood
at God's feet, equal,
as we are.
As we are.
I am a free human being
with an independent will
which I now exert
to leave you.
Then let your will
decide your destiny.
I offer you my hand,
my heart.
Jane,
I ask you to pass
through life at my side.
You are my equal
and my likeness.
Will you marry me?
Are you mocking me?
Do you doubt me?
Entirely
Your bride is Miss Ingram
Miss Ingram?
She is the machine
without feelings.
It's you. You rare
unearthly thing
Poor and obscure
as you are
please accept me
as your husband.
I must have you for my own.
You wish me
to be your wife?
I swear it.
You love me?
I do.
Then, sir,
I will marry you
Good night.
Good night, my love.
Good night
Am I a monster?
Is it so impossible
that Mr. Rochester
should love me?
No.
I've long noticed
you were a sort
of pet of his
But you're so young
and you're so little
acquainted with men
I don't want to
grieve you, child
but let me just put
you on your guard.
Gentlemen in his position
Well, let's just say
they're not accustomed
to marry their governesses
Until you are wed,
distrust yourself
as well as him.
Please,
keep him at a distance.
Come.
What is it?
Jane Eyre with
nothing to say?
Everything seems unreal
I am real enough
You, sir, are most
phantom-like of all.
I will be Jane Eyre
no longer.
Edward!
Move it!
Have the carriage
loaded and ready
within the hour.
Take courage, Jane
I will.
Come on
I require
and charge you both,
as you will answer
at the dreadful Day
of Judgment,
when the secrets
of all hearts
shall be revealed
that if either of you
do know of any impediment
why you may not be
joined together lawfully,
you do now confess it
Edward Fairfax Rochester
The marriage cannot go on
An insurmountable
impediment exists.
Proceed.
"I affirm
and can prove...
Proceed!
"...That Edward Fairfax
Rochester was,
"15 years ago,
married to my sister,
"Bertha Antoinetta Mason,
at St. James' Church,
"Spanish Town, Jamaica."
A copy of the register
is now in my possession
Signed, Richard Mason
She lives at
Thornfield Hall
This girl knew
nothing of this.
She thought all
was fair and legal.
She never dreamt
she was being entrapped
into a feigned union
with a defrauded wretch
Come, Jane
Come, all of you.
Meet my wife.
Get back!
Go, all of you. Go!
You're 15 years too late.
Mrs. Poole.
You ought to
give warning, sir
This is Bertha
Antoinetta Mason.
My wife.
- Antoinetta.
- It's I, Richard.
She has her quiet
times and her rages.
The windows are shuttered
lest she throw herself out.
We have no furniture,
as she can make a weapon
out of anything.
I take her for a turn
upon the roof each day,
securely held,
as she's taken to
thinking she can fly.
My own demon.
Jane.
Forgive me. I'm worthless.
How could I?
Jane.
No tears.
Why don't you cry?
Why not scream at me?
I deserve a hail of fire.
I need some water
Of course.
Jane.
How are you now?
I will be well again soon.
I know you.
You're thinking.
Talking is of no use,
you're thinking how to act
All is changed, sir.
I must leave you.
No. No
Jane, do you love me?
Then the essential things
are the same.
Be my wife.
You have a wife.
I pledge you my
honor, my fidelity
You cannot.
My love, until
death do us part.
What of truth?
I would have
told you the truth
You are deceitful, sir!
I was wrong
to deceive you.
I see that now.
It was cowardly.
I should have appealed
to your spirit as I do now
Bertha Antoinetta Mason
She was wanted by
my father for her fortune
I hardly spoke with her
before the wedding.
I lived with her
for four years.
Her temper ripened,
her vices sprang up
violent and unchaste.
Only cruelty would check her,
and I'd not use cruelty.
I was chained to her
for life, Jane.
Not even the law
could free me.
Have you ever set foot
in a madhouse, Jane?
No, sir.
The inmates are caged
and baited like beasts.
I spared her
that at least.
Jane.
I earnestly pity you, sir
No.
Who would you offend
by living with me?
Who would care?
I would.
You'd rather drive
me to madness
than break some
mere human law?
I must respect myself.
Listen to me.
Listen.
I could bend you
with my finger
and my thumb,
a mere reed you fee
in my hands
But whatever I do
with this cage
I cannot get at you
And it is your soul
that I want.
Why don't you come
of your own free will?
God help me!
Jane!
I asked how you were
I'm getting on very well.
Do you find the
work too hard?
Not at all
Is the solitude
an oppression?
I hardly have time
to notice it.
Thank you, girls
Yes, ma'am
Then perhaps
you are dwelling
on things past.
When I came to your door
I had nothing
Now I have a home and work,
free and honest.
I thank God
for the generosity
of my friends.
What you had left
before I met you,
I don't know.
But I counsel you
to resist firmly
every temptation
to look back.
That's what I intend to do.
A year ago, I was myself
intensely miserable.
I scorned this weakness,
fought hard against it
and won.
I wonder if we
do not share
the same alloy
You are ambitious,
I think.
And this little school
will not hold you for long.
Is this yours?
Yes
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Good night
Jane.
Miss Eyre.
What brings you
from your hearth
on a night like this?
There is no bad
news, I hope
How easily alarmed
you are, Miss Eyre.
Please, won't
you sit down?
Thank you, Miss Eyre
I saw an advertisement
in The Times from
a solicitor named Briggs
inquiring of a Jane Eyre
I knew a Jane Elliott.
This paper
resolved my suspicion
into certainty.
And so, I wrote to him
He told the story of
a young governess.
And her employer,
a Mr. Fairfax Rochester
Mr. Rivers
I can guess your feelings
but please hear me.
As you know so much,
perhaps you'll tell
me how he is?
Who?
Mr. Rochester.
I'm ignorant of
all concerning him.
But he has
been seeking me?
No, he hasn't.
Mr. Briggs has
And what does
he want with me?
Merely to tell you
that your uncle
Mr. John Eyre of
Madeira, is dead,
that he has left you
all his property
and that you
are now rich.
What?
You are rich,
quite an heiress.
Will you ask how
much you are worth?
How much am I worth?
Twenty thousand pounds.
If you had committed
a murder
and I'd found you out,
you could scarcely
look more aghast.
There must be
some mistake.
Not at all
You look desperately
miserable about it,
I must say
Please,
sit down
I've shocked you
Mr. St. John.
The debt I owe to you
and your sisters...
Is nothing
You saved my life.
Please write to them
This money frees us.
They will have 5,000 each
and so will you,
if you'll take it.
Certainly not
And if you would accept
me as a sister,
perhaps we could
live together,
at Moor House.
I told you the
news too quickly
You're confused
My only relative is dead.
You have family.
You cannot know
what isolation means.
And you cannot know
what it means
to be wealthy.
I have been alone always
I've never had
a brother or sisters.
Please, let me be yours.
Are you reluctant
to have me?
No, Miss Eyre
On the contrary
I shall write
to my sisters,
as you request
Brother
We are bid to work
while it is day.
For night cometh,
when no man shall work.
Help us to choose
the harder path,
for as our master
is long-suffering,
so must we be
Amen
Amen.
Good night.
Good night
Is Jane not
our sister, too?
Good night
Jane.
I go to India
in six weeks.
I can see what
your gifts are
and why they were given.
God intended you
for a missionary's wife
I want to claim you.
I'm not fit for it.
I trust you
unreservedly
And know this,
in you,
I recognize
a fellow soul.
I'll go with you
to India.
Jane.
I'll go if
I may go free.
Free?
How can I take out
to India a girl of 19
unless she is my wife?
I love you as a brother
As a husband, no
My heart is mute
Then I must speak for it
You've said you'll come.
We shall marry
And undoubtedly
enough of love
would follow.
Enough of love?
Yes, quite enough
Of love?
Yes. In all its forms.
Forgive me, but
the very name of love
is an apple of discord
between us.
My dear brother,
abandon your
scheme of marriage
Why this refusal?
It makes no sense
I earnestly wish
to be your friend
You can't give
half a sacrifice.
You must give all
To marry you
would kill me!
Kill you?
Those words are
unfeminine and untrue
I know where your heart turns
and to what it still clings.
Say his name
Say it. Say it
Jane.
Why have you not
yet crushed this
lawless passion?
Jane!
It offends me and
it offends God!
What is it?
Where are you?
Wait for me.
Why do you speak to the air?
Jane.
I am coming
Jane!
Wait, please, Miss.
Jane Eyre.
I thought
gypsies were come.
And then I saw you
and I thought
it cannot be
you are a ghost.
No one knows
how it started
I expect that Mrs. Poole
took too much of
the gin and water
and as she slept,
the lady,
Mrs. Rochester,
unhooked the keys.
She did what she failed
to do a year ago,
set the whole place
to fire.
We would have
all perished
in the smoke,
but Mr. Rochester
would not rest till
we were all safe.
Then he went
in for her
The flames were
tearing up so high
it brought men running
from the village.
I saw her standing
on the roof.
The very edge.
I heard Mr. Rochester
beg her to come down
But she jumped.
Mr. Rochester remained,
as if he would not move
until the fire consumed him.
I didn't know
it was his wife
I promise you
Why did you
run away, child?
I would have helped you.
I had some money saved.
You could have come to me.
Where is he?
Pilot.
Who's there?
This hand...
Jane Eyre.
Edward, I am
come back to you.
Fairfax Rochester
with nothing to say?
You are altogether
a human being, Jane.
I conscientiously
believe so.
A dream.
Awaken then.
Professional Translation Services
www.gts-translation.com