Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
[ Growling ]
[ Screaming ]
Okay, look, I can't believe
that I'm actually here...
and that I'm gonna get
to see them in the flesh,
because, like, Dujour is
like my most favorite band
ofall time!
Dujour!
I just want to touch them.
I don't care which one.
I don't care where.
I got all their trading cards
and all their CD's,
and all my gear is
from their clothing line,
Dujour Couture.
[ Screams ]
I mean, I straight-up love 'em,
only, you know, like brothers.
Oh, my God!
They're here!
[Screaming Continues]
Ayear ago, would you have
ever imagined number-one song,
number-one requested video?
We're numberone with a bullet,
baby,, comin'toy,ou!
Marco, there's a lady up there--
"Marry me, Marco--"
with a wedding dress.
-Keep buy,in'the records, baby,!
-Can you send it back to
all the guys in the studio?
[ Screaming ]
[ British Accent ]
All right, boys. We'll land
in Riverdale in halfan hour.
Then on to the Riverdale
Rise and Shine show.
Yeah, Wyatt, how come
my limited-edition Coke can
has me with a goatee...
when everybody knows
I shaved into a soul patch for
the Don't Tell YourPapa video?
This is wiggity-wack, Wyatt.
You're supposed to be
on top ofthis.
No, what's wiggity,-wack
isy,ourdamn monkey,.
Here wego with
the monkey, again.
Dj D.j. with the monkey,.
Yes, here we go again.
First it pooed on my incense.
Then it decided to poo
on my two little balls.
And then it pooed on my
picture ofSwami Mukananda.
Will you please tell
this man that Dujour
means hygiene?
Maybe ifyou showed Dr. Zaius
the proper respect, Dr. Zaius
will stop showin' you the poo!
Gentlemen--
I'm gonna kill you!
Okay! Now, enough ofthis.
I'm gonna rip out
your heart!
Eye contact, hand.
We'll talk to Coke
about the cans...
and try and clean up
after the doctor, okay?
Okay?
- Yo, man, I'm sorry.
My,bad.
- It's all good.
Wyatt?
Yes?
Could you maybe talk to Marco
about him always doing my face?
You rememberin the What video
lestablishedthe-- face?
Eversince then, everytime
yousee Marco, he's doing
the-- face, andit'smine.
You lookat him on TRL.
"Hi, Carson. "
Look at him on
the Kid's ChoiceAwards.
"This is ours. Thanks."
Then right here on the cover
of Seventeen magazine.
"Hi, little girl.
Beauty secrets?"
It's my face.
Travis, am l, uh--
doin' your face,
'cause-- God forbid
I'd-- do your face, 'cause
it's-- such a good face.
- That's it!
- Boys, boys, boys.
- [ Screeching ]
- [ Shouting ]
- Hold it!
- Dujour means friendship.
Thankyou, Les.
Now, listen to me.
[ Grunting ]
Let's all take a moment.
When we land, I will
call the choreographer, and
she will give you a new face.
- Too bad your mama couldn't
give you a good face.
- Take that back right now!
I'm sorry, Travis.
Thankyou.
You can have a new face too.
- Dujour means family.
- Dujour means teamwork.
Teamwork.
- So, howare we?
Are wegood?
- Yeah.
Are we happy?
Happy.
Are we dope?
Word.
Wicked.
Yo, Wy,att,
there was one more thing.
Yes?
Well, we were working
on some remixes of
the last single, right?
We heard like a really
strange background track.
We were wondering whether
or not you knew what
it was all about.
[ Voices Overlapping ]
Gee. You know,
I have no idea what that was.
Where did it come from?
I mean, Wyatt,
wejust want some answers.
The answers I will provide.
I'll be right back.
Take the Chevy to the levee.
Whoa!
Hey, that guy in the parachute
looksjust like Wyatt.
Oh, yeah?
Does he look like this?
Or like this?
- That's it.
- Break it up!
- Dujour means seat belts!
- [ Screeching ]
Dujour means
crash positions!
[Phone Dialing]
Looks like we need
to fiind a new band.
[ Phone Beeps ]
[Horn Honking]
- Thankyou, guys.
- Real nice.
Thanks for comin' out.
You're a great crowd.
[Pins Clattering]
[Man]
Okay,, girls.
We needthe lane now...
andy,ourshoes.
[Cash RegisterDings]
So how'd we do?
Twenty dollars... minus
five dollars shoe rental.
Fifteen dollars.
Each.
Five dollars.
All things considered,
I'd say this was
our best show yet.
Wejust need to
build a following.
[ Screaming ]
Look, skanky had a rock show,
and nobody came.
Didy,ouguy,sallcoordinate
beforey,ou left the house,
or are you wearing
the same thing by accident?
At least we're not
wearing stupid bunny ears.
They're not bunny.
They're leopard.
And they're not stupid.
They're special.
- We're special.
- Yeah, special... ed.
[Laughing]
Enjoy,thegutters,josie.
You'llbeplay,ing there forever.
[Laughing Continues]
[Engine Revs]
Hey,. Hey,, come on.
Who's a rock star?
I am.
That's right.
There you go.
[ Laughs ]
[Child]
Slowdown!
[Child] No way,!
[ Chattering ]
Lookin' good, McCoy!
[RecordScratches]
Alan M, what's--
What's goin' on?
Uh, the, uh, truck died.
Jump in anytime.
You can't drive this uphill
when it's hot outside.
I told you.
You don't deserve
a truck this good.
You totally take it for granted.
Um,Jose?
Did, uh--
Did you ever want to tell
someone something, but--
but you weren't sure
ifyou should, you know?
Yeah.
'Cause you didn't know what
their reaction might be or if
it was the right thing to do?
You should tell them.
You should always tell them.
'Cause there's this guy at work,
and hejust reeks, you know?
A guy?
Yeah.
Smelly guy.
Oh, God,Josie, no,
notjust smelly.
I'm talking, like,
hot, wet garbage on a sunny day.
Ithink there'saproblem.
It's like a stadium bathroom
orsomething.
No oneseems to want
to say,any,thingabout it.
I know you would say
something though, right?
Yeah. See, that's
what llove abouty,ou.
- We can just talk about stuff.
- That's what I'm here for.
- That's so cool.
- Ah!
Mmm! Good ramen.
I don't think people know
how far one pack can go.
Honk, honk.
Who brought doughnuts?
I hope you don't think
that this makes up for
your missing our gig.
Sure we didn't miss much.
Nice management skills,
brother. Build yourself
a nice fat girl group.
Hello, Alexandra.
Have you lost some weight?
Bite me, Bambi!
Okay, Alexandra, why don't
you go wait in the car?
Make me, nosejob.
Implants.
Penile-- Ow!
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's thesecondtime
today,, isn 't it?
Ow! Ow.
So, ladies,
how'd our set go?
You wouldknow
ify,ou hadbeen there.
Hey, honey, I'm running
a management company here.
I can't be everywhere at once.
Wouldn't that be cool
though ifyou could?
I could be here and in there,
and I could be
in the living room...
andin the family, room
andoverhere!
Alexander, you don't
have any other clients.
Where else do you need to be?
On the streets, spreading
the gospel ofthe Pussycats.
I'm out there working
my butt off foryou guys.
I'm handing out fliers.
I'm working the masses.
Waiting in line
for Dujour tickets.
It's for business.
I-- It, uh--
Checking out the competition.
I don't like Dujour,
like, it's Dujour.
And I could be
back in this room, and
I could go in the closet!
Hello? Uh-huh.
You want a demo tape
ofthe Pussycats?
- Your phone didn't even ring.
- It's on vibrate.
- Um, so-- so, yeah.
I gotta go right now.
- And then--
You want it right now?
Okay, yeah. So, I'll see
you guys later.
All right, I'm on it.
You guys know he's lying.
You know your fly is open.
[Laughing]
You know, you... suck!
That's perfect.
Even our manager wants
to see another band.
You guys, come here quick.
Hi. I'm Serena Altschul
with MTV News.
We havejust received
a confirmed report...
that the members of
pop sensation Dujour disappeared
in their privatejet today,
vanishing from radar
40 miles east of Riverdale.
Authoritiesarestill
trying to determine
the whereabouts oftheplane...
andifthere are any,survivors.
Dujour's label, MegaRecords,
isy,et to release a statement,
but they have
released a limited-edition
commemorative box set,
complete with a CD-ROM! history
of Dujour in stores tomorrow.
Those poor boys.
We willkeepy,oupostedas to
any, furtherdevelopments...
in what seems to be yet
another rock-and-roll tragedy.
But they didn't
say they were dead.
They said they were missing.
I say we raise money
for a search party,
and we hold a bake sale!
Yes!
[ Giggles ]
Man, that is so sad.
[josie]
It can allbe overin a flash.
You know, but at least
they had a record deal.
We can have a record deal.
It'sjust that
we can't sit around here
waiting for it to happen.
We have to make it happen.
And you know what?
Life-- Life is short.
And we-- we are musicians,
and that means...
that we should be
out there playing music.
We do play, and we rock,
but nobody shows.
Nobody cares.
I care. I do.
And you know what?
When life gives you lemons,
you make lemonade, and
when the going gets tough--
The tough make lemonade!
Right!
Good. We're all
on the same page.
Pack up your bass.
This way.
I live for these pink shoes.
Yeah, they are so much
cooler than our red shoes.
You guys,
pink is the new red.
[ All Giggling ]
Wyatt Frame.
I'm with the label.
I'm in town scouting new talent,
and I wondered ifthere was
anyone worth hearing.
I saw the card, man,
but I missed everything else.
Why don't you start over
while I change songs?
No, wait! Play this.
It's the new single
from Dujour...
recorded just a few days ago
before the... disappearance.
I'd really like
to test the reaction.
Right on.
Check this out, y'all!
I got the world premiere
ofthe last single ever...
from the late, great Dujour
just for all you in the store.
Check this out.
I love this song!
It's their best ever.
If I don't buy it,
everybody's gonna hate me.
Totally!
And, I also want
orange shoes.
Yeah!
Orange shoes are
so much cooler than
these stupid pink shoes.
You guys, orange
is the new pink!
[ Screams ]
I am sick of my Reebok sweats.
I need some Puma sweats.
And I gotta buy
a six-pack ofZima.
Dude, you don't drink.
I think I should start.
Yes, I think they responded
to that very well actually.
[Woman]
lthink thatsongsucks.
I plug my ears when
crap like that comes on.
Really? Everybody else
seemed to like it.
That's because they're mindless
drones who will gobble up
anything you tell them is cool.
I see. Wow!
You're a real free thinker,
aren't you?
I'd love to talk
to you some more.
People in the recording
industry, like me,
always want to hear
the opinion of individuals
like yourself...
to find out what
we're doing wrong.
Yeah, right.
How much time do you have?
As much as you want.
Afteryou.
Smells like teen spirit.
Well, this must be
my lucky day.
A real nonconformist.
I'm so interested to hear
what else you have to say.
Well, first ofall,
I don't understand--
Gosh, that's fascinating.
[ Phone Rings ]
- Frame.
- I'm waiting.
I'm on to it, Fiona.
You wouldn't believe this place.
It's a cultural wasteland.
Stop making excuses and get
your ass back here with a band.
Tomorrow. I'll have
a new band foryou first thing
in the morning. I swear!
Then you'll still
have a job-- maybe.
Just put this thing up?
Yeah.
Okay, girls, this is it.
Pussycats unplugged.
Let's hear it.
One, two. One, two, three!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
What do you think
you're doing?
You can't play here.
I've got things to sell.
They're new. They're orange.
- So?
- So, look at you. You're--
Who's gonna come into
my store with you outside?
The last I checked,
this was a free country.
I was calling the cops.
"Gety,ourassbackhere
with a band. "
I'd like to see her
move her ass once, just once.
Like he's really
gonna call the cops.
[Siren Wailing]
Run!
Where the hell
am I supposed to find a--
Hello, ladies.
Wyatt Frame, MegaRecords.
Girls, lcan't telly,ou
howhappy,lam
to besitting...
at this table
with the Pussy Hats.
Pussycats.
Yes, ofcourse. Ofcourse,
that would explain why
you're not wearing any.
[Laughs]
Hats.
Okay, I speak on behalf
ofeveryone at the label...
when I say that we'd love for
you to sign with... MegaRecords.
Whoa, wait, whoa.
Don't sign any,thing.
- Who is this?
- Alexander Cabot Ill.
I'm the Pussycats' manager.
I'm his sister, Alexandra.
Love the accent.
Thankyou.
I used to summer
on the continent.
Fancy a snog?
Fancy a mint?
Wait a minute.
You want to sign us?
You've never even heard us play.
Oh! Oh, oh.
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
I thought you were a rock band
that wanted to sign with
a major label. My bad.
- No, no, no!
- No!
No. No. It's--
I didn't know it could
happen this fast.
Well, that's the music biz
foryou. Ifyou wait for it to
slow down, it might pass you by.
Look what happened
to the Beastie Boy,s.
- But they're huge stars.
- I know.
Excuse me.
I have to--
- Bathroom?
- Yeah, me too.
I went before we left.
Good foryou.
You should always
try to go to the bathroom
before you leave the house,
even ifyou don't have to--
[ Gasping ]
Okay, this is crazy.
Beep-beep. Gotta gloss.
It wouldn't hide the mustache.
Honk, honk.
Alexander!
I should be here.
It's a ladies' room.
Nothing I haven't seen before.
Does anyone have change
for a tampon?
I'll be outside.
[ Slams ]
Does anyone else think
this is a little off?
Like what?
Like that Wyatt guy,
for one.
Like how he ordered
a triple cappuccino
and scooped offall the foam.
Why notjust get an espresso?
Plus how he kept folding
his napkin like he's afraid he
doesn't have any real friends?
Just people who want
to use him because
he's a big music guy.
Yeah. But I was talking
more about the whole
record contract thing.
It is super sudden.
It is.
But you said it. You said
we have to go out there and
make things happen, and we did.
I know. I just think maybe
we should think about this
for a second.
[ All Screaming ]
Gee,Josie,
how exciting foryou.
You'll get to go away and
make a record, and poor Alan M
will have to stay behind...
in Riverdale
all alone with me.
I cannot believe they let you
bring me to the city with you.
Shh.
What?
I had to tell them that
you're my guitar tech, so--
[Whispers]
Guitartech. Right.
You know what?
I still don't understand
why you're here.
- I'm here because
I was in the comic book.
- What?
Nothing.
[ Moans ]
Whoa!
[ Laughs ]
What's up, big butt?
Shut up.
Hey, you guys.
You know how people always
say that this is the life?
I think this is
when they say it.
Private plane.
Record deal.
Coasters.
Scratch that.
We still poor.
[ Phone Beeps ]
Yes?
At least I don't think
I need this anymore.
Riverdale muni bus pass.
Guy,s, y,ou know what?
We have the only,buspasses with
threepeople in thepicture.
[ Sighs ]
It's not my fault you both
jumped in on mine.
Okay, no, you both
[ Laughs ]
We should keep these.
Remind us where we came from.
Hey,, listen, let'spromise
each othersomething...
right here
and right now, okay?
No matter what happens--
Ifwe become huge stars...
or ifwe end up hitchhiking
back to Riverdale,
we will always
be friends first
and a band second.
Friends first.
I swear on my bus pass?
[ Together ]
I swear on my bus pass.
[ All Laughing ]
Don't worry, Lex.
We're not going to have
any trouble with these girls.
Oh, no.
Geez. It's so huge.
Oh, this is only
the beginning.
Arey,ousurey,oushouldbe
putting that up already,?
I mean, we haven't even
recorded anything yet.
What ifyou don't like it?
What if nobody likes it?
Don't worry.
Ifyou screw up, we'll just
put somebody else up there.
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughing Continues ]
Hey, Wyatt?
Hmm?
They've got
our nme wrong.
Hmm?
We're notjosie
andthe Pussy,cats.
We'rejust
the Pussycats.
Oh, no,Josie's the singer.
The public needs someone
out front to identify with.
Trust me.
Our studies have shown
that bands that have the word
"and" in the title...
sell twice as many records
as those that don't.
What about the Beatles
or the Rolling Stones?
Yes, ifyou want to split hairs,
yes, ofcourse, obviously.
Yes, yes, but, come on.
Wouldy,ou be more
interestedin a bandcalled
simply,the Pussy,cats,
or are you more likely to
buy a CD or read a comic...
or watch a cartoon
or go and see a movie about
a trio of luscious ladies...
called Josie
and the Pussycats?
Hmm?
It does have
a nice ring to it.
Oh, yes.
Hey!
Oh, so sorry, Valerie.
I had no idea
you weren't in here.
Ha, ha. Come on.
[Melody,]
More coasters.
[Giggles]
What did I tell you, Fiona?
It couldn't be better.
Just think Christina Aguliera
times three except one ofthem
is incredibly tan...
or else T.L.C.
with two white chicks...
or, um, Hole!
Wyatt, I get it without
the stupid analogies.
Put them in the studio tomorrow.
We'll talk later.
The feds are here
with some foreigners.
I've got to give them the tour.
- You won't be disappointed.
- I'd better not be.
We can't afford
another Dujour disaster.
- Welcome.
- [ Foreign Language ]
I'm sure you're wondering
why Agent Kelly and
the United States government...
would be so interested in what
appears to be a record company.
Well, I'm about
to showy,ou why,.
- [ Beeping ]
- [Whirring]
This... is what ouroperation
really, does.
[Woman]
Blue is the neworange.
[Fiona]
This is where itstarts--
the fads, the fashions,
theproductplacement.
From this commandcenter,
we controlthe most influential
demographic ofthepopulation.
We decide everything--
from what clothes are in style
to what slang is in vogue.
Feather tank tops,
matching pants. Kind of
a Buffy meets Chicken Run.
Feathers are
the new rhinestones.
The new word for cool
will be "jerkin'," as in,
"Dude, that'sjerkin'."
That's dirty.
[Fiona]
This is the epicenter
ofalltrends.
We turny,our worldinto
onegiant TVcommercial.
But how, you may ask, can
our operation be so effective?
Sure these kidshave brains
like Play,-Doh,just waiting
to be moldedinto shape,
but something else
must be going on, right?
The Chinese guy knows
what I'm talking about.
To answersome
ofy,ourquestions,
we've produced
a short educational film.
Lights!
[ Beeps ]
Hello. I'm Eugene Levy,
and, yes, I'm an actor.
And, I said cappuccino.
I'm here to talk to you
about something very important.
No, it's not about me
or my creer.
I'm here to talk about
subliminal messages
in rock-and-roll music...
or as it's simply known
in some cultures-- rock music.
Fory,ears thegovernment
hasbeen wisely,
coercing teenagers...
to buy,products
they,normally, wouldn 't want
just toget theirmoney,.
Fact: Kids don't
have bills to pay.
Fact: They don't pay taxes,
but they do baby-sit
and hold minimum-wagejobs...
that earn them wads ofcash as
thick as, well, my body ofwork.
But these kids today,
aren't dumb.
They,'re notgoing
to buy,just any,thing.
That's why,thegovernment has
beenplanting smallsubliminal
advertisingsuggestions...
in today,'s rockmusic.
The results?
We can nowget these kids
to buy,just about any,thing.
We can have them chasing
a new trend every week,
and that is good
for the economy.
What's good for the economy
is good for the country.
So God bless
the United States ofAmerica,
the most ass-kickin'
country in the world.
[ Beeps ]
[GermanAccent]
Howcany,ou control
the rockbands?
What ifthey, findout
about the hidden messages
in theirmusic?
Ever wonder why so many rock
stars die in plane crashes?
Overdose on drugs!
We've been doing this
a long time.
Ifthey,start
toget too curious,
ouroptionsare endless.
Bankruptcy, shocking scandals,
religious conversions.
We've created
a highly-rated TV show...
just to explain
what happens to these people.
[Beeps]
[ Foreign Language ]
[Applause Continues]
Wow.
The walls are mushy.
[Giggles]
We brought
some equipment in.
Iassume it's toy,ourliking.
They're brand new.
I like this.
It's got shiny knobs.
No. No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
That we do not touch.
It's only the most expensive
piece ofequipment
in the studio.
The Megasound8000.
Although the name sounds
ominous, it's actually
just a high-tech processor.
How does it work?
Why do you need to know that?
What is it, a big secret
or something?
A bigsecret.
Wy,att'sgot a secret.
It's not a secret. Stop it.
I'll tell you. I'll show you.
- [ Whirring ]
- Play a little something
for me, would you?
Perfect! Now, this will
just take a moment.
[ Voices Overlapping]
And now I'll play it back
with megasound.
Is that us?
It sounds so--
- I want a Big Mac.
- What?
Mel, y,ou're a vegetarian.
I know, but
suddenly I want one. Maybe
on the way back to the hotel?
Okay, as long as we can
stop by Foot Locker too.
I'm dying for a pair
ofold-school Tretorns.
Jerkin' Tretorns
are the new Adidas.
[ Clicks ]
Ladies, nowshouldldropy,ou
backat Riverdale Mall, orare
you ready,to make a record?
Come on!
[Feedback Whine]
[Drumsticks Tapping]
One, two. One, two, three.
This is the best CD ever!
Yeah, and I want
some Gatorade.
Gatorade is the new Snapple!
Idon'tget whatgoes on
in hismind
But I'm tiredofhearing
thesamestupidlines
Why do you do
what you do to me, baby
You're shaking my confidence
Driving me crazy
You know if I could
I'd do anything foryou
Please don't ignore me
'causey,ou knowladorey,ou
Can't you just pretend
to be nice
Couldy,ou at least
pretendto be nice
Ify,ou'djust
Everything in my life
would be all right
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Everything in my, life
wouldbe allright
Allright
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Everything in my, life would
be allright, allright
Oh, oh, oh, oh
[ Screaming ]
- This must be a misprint.
- [ Laughing ]
- Yea!
- Wait!
Does anyone else think
it's a little strange that
all this happened in a week?
[ Dialing ]
No!
[ Screaming ]
[Screaming Continues]
- [ Screaming ]
- Who are you?
- We know them!
- [ Panting ]
Eww! We do!
Oh, my God! We love you.
We're like your biggest fans!
[Screaming Continues]
- No, you're not. You hate us.
- Are you crazy?
Josie and the Pussycats
are our new favorite band
ofall time!
- [Screaming]
-Josie and the Pussycats
are the new Dujour!
Wanna see our
Pussycat tattoo?
Look it!
[ Gasping ]
That was way too weird.
Weird? What's the point
of being famous...
ifthe people
you hated in high school
don't want to kiss your ass?
You're lucky.
Most people have to wait
till their ten-year reunion
for that sort of revenge.
You'rejust going
to have to get used to people
throwing themselves at you.
And, talking ofthrowing,
Fiona, the head of MegaRecords,
is throwing a huge party
tonight in your honor,
a celebration
ofall thingsJosie.
- Um, Wyatt?
- Hmm?
- Don't I get one?
- Oh, that is strange.
Why don't you come along too?
There's always room
for one more.
How about us?
No.
Wow. A party,.
That's, um--
That's, uh--
That's kindofcool.
But is it as
"kind ofcool" as playing
your own stadium concert?
Oops! I promised Fiona
she could tell you. Damn.
We're playing
a stadium concert?
This weekend.
Shouldn 't we may,beplay,
somesmallclubsfirst?
Maybe do a few gigs in Europe.
Build a following.
You have a following.
Honestly, "J."
I wouldn't send you out there
if I didn't think
you could deliver.
It would only make me look bad
But this is the whole deal:
simultaneous pay-per-view
web cast, live streaming video,
millions of little people
paying good money
just to watch you.
Well, I'm sure
your bandmates are
tres excited.
Right, Melly-Mel?
Our first concert ever.
Thanks, Wyatt.
Don't thank me.
Thank Fiona.
It washeridea.
It'sbeenpart ofherplan
fory,ou from thestart.
Operation Big Concert,
where we finally take things
to the next level.
Whenjosie andthe Pussy,cats
play,theirstadium concert,
allthe kids in the audience,
as well as the ones
watching at home,
will have to purchase these.
It's the debut
of3-D-Xsurroundsound,
a newtechnology,that
makes the music feellike
it'shappeningallaroundy,ou,
Iike 3-D.
Gentlemen, a demonstration.
This is what those kids
think they're hearing
on those headsets.
Oooh, wee, oooh, wee, ooh
This is what
they're really hearing.
[Man] Conform.
Free willis overrated.
Jump on the bandwagon.
That voice.
I know that voice.
It's, um--
- It's Mr. Moviefone.
- Yes!
He does all
our subliminal tracks.
[Mr. Moviefone]
There isno suchplace
asArea 51.
Excellent work, Fiona.
These kids willnever
know what hit 'em.
- And neither will you.
- I'm sorry. What was that?
- Huh? What?
- You just said something.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
I said, "These kids will never
know what hit 'em," and then you
said, "And neither will you."
- I did?
- We all heard you.
Oh-- Well--
What I meant to say was,
"And neither will you guys."
Meaning the teenagers.
I wasjust emphasizing my point.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Great. Thanks.
That was close.
Excuse me?
I was going to say,
"That was... close...
"to being
a... really nice moment...
between the two of us."
Don't you think?
Yeah, well, I guess.
I have to be getting back
to the Pentagon, so--
[Man]
Toni Tennille andl--
we wrote allthesongs together.
Love, love will
keep us together
Captain just played the piano.
It was my idea to have him
wear that hat.
I said, "How you
gonna be a captain
ifyou don't wear a hat?"
[ Chuckles ]
We did make some beautiful music
together though.
A big song-- The one I was
mostly responsible for was...
"Love Will Keep Us Together."
Well, guess what. It didn't.
Guessaftera while, y,ou know,
they, didn 't want to share
thespotlight no more.
Sometimes that stuff happens.
I can still remember,
though, Captain always said,
"Friends first.
The band second."
I wish I'd have
got that in writin'.
Ifyou're happy
and you know it
clap your hands
Ifyou're happy
and you know it
clap your hands
[ Laughs ]
Ifyou're happy
and you know it
and you really wanna show it
Ifyou're happy
and you know it
clap your hands
[ Screaming ]
Oh, no.
That's better.
[ Giggles ]
[Knocking]
[Alan M]
It's theguy, with thepizza
The kindthat'sgoodto eats-a
ify,ou open the door
Oh, my God, I am so sorry.
I totally, totally forgot.
We have to go to
this record party thing
with the head ofthe label.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing. Itjust, uh--
You look so, uh--
You cannot make fun of me.
They sent this dress over.
I did not pick it out.
But lcut up the front,
andlmade wristbands.
It looks stupid, doesn't it?
No, no, no. No. I--
I'vejust--
I've never seen you-- Wow!
Finish your sentences.
Is that a good wow
or a bad wow?
Oh, no, no. It's, uh--
It's a good wow.
It's a-- it's a--
it's a very good wow.
Thanks.
Actually, would you mind?
There's a--
Mind what?
There's a chain thing
that I can't
figure out really.
Oh, right.
Right, um-- Okay.
Um--
That's, um--
that's down here.
A little complicated.
[ Clears Throat ]
Josie, arey,ou ready,?
The door was open. Ihope
I'm not interruptingany,thing.
- Hey, Alec N,
how's it hanging?
- Actually, it's Alan M.
Yes, what's with the initial?
It didn't work for Sheila E.,
and it doesn't work foryou.
Josie, we don't want to be late
forthe hottest andmost
exclusiveparty,ofthey,ear.
There's free cable.
Uh,Josie?
Um, I was wondering,
d-d-did you want to
do something tomorrow?
Yeah.
When?
2:00?
No can do. Taping E.
- Oh. 1 :30. 3:00.
- MTV. MSNBC.
- 4:00.
- 4:1 5.
- Sold to the young man
with no future.
Come on,josie.
There'sa limo waiting.
Goodnight, Adam 12.
- Trot on.
- Actually, it's Alan M.
[ Chattering ]
Oooh, wee, ooh, wee
Oooh, wee, ooh, wee, ooh
Ooh
Well, he looksat me
with those innocent ey,es
Andsay,s it looks
likey,ou're wearing
some kindofdisguise
Becausey,ourhair
sticks out--
[Josie Thinking ]
Look at them staring at us.
No one thinks I should be here.
That's totally
what they're thinking.
Look at them staring
atJosie.
No one thinks I should be here.
That's totally
what they're thinking.
Ifyou're happy
and you know it, and you
really want to show it
Ifyou're happy
and you know it
clap your hands
[Man OverP.A. ]
Ladiesandgentlemen,
the headofMegaRecords...
andthe host ofy,ourparty,,
Fiona.
[Woman]
Why, doy,ou do
whaty,ou do to me, baby,
-    Shakin'my,confidence
- Isn't she fabulous?
Drivin'me crazy,
You knowiflcould
I'ddo any,thing fory,ou
Please don't ignore me
'causey,ou knowladorey,ou
[Ends]
I'm Fiona.
Welcome to your party!
Enough spectacle.
Let's go be girls!
This is my girly room.
No boys allowed.
Come on, girls. Sit down.
We'll gossip.
Oh!
[Woman Singing ln French]
Isn 't hejust the cutest?
He's pretty cute.
[DoorCloses]
Pringles!
Josie!
Come on!
Oh, I am starved!
I'm such a pig.
N-No. No, you're not.
[ Sighs ]
[ Crying ]
So,Josie,
how much do you weigh?
Excuse me?
Your weight!
1 1 8.
Ha! 1 1 5.
I'm three pounds
lighter than you.
But don't worry about it.
I thinkyou look great.
[ Lisping ]
Tho pretty and popular.
What did you just say?
Nothing. I thaid
the new thong's pretty popular.
What "thong"?
The new thong.
The new thingle.
I'm thorry.
I have thomething
caught in my teeth.
[Clears Throat]
Got it.
So, who wants to
French braid?
Okay, so who else thinks
that Fiona's a freak?
Oh, my God. I'm so glad
you said something, because
as soon as you said her name,
I got the most awful
sensation,
Iike this ice-cold chill
creeping up my spine.
Oh, sweetie, that's 'cause
you're sitting on the O.
Oh.
[ Giggles ]
No. I still got
the shivers, you guys.
It's not the O.
It's her.
I don't know.
What do you think, Val?
Stuff's definitely
been... different
since we left Riverdale.
And, ifyou ask me,
some things feel like
they've changed completely.
- Wy,att.
- Hmm?
I don't like those two
pussycats. They're asking
questions, and that's dangerous.
We can't afford to take
any more risks.
I'll get rid ofthem,
have a new band by the morning.
Ooh!
Think, Wyatt.
We've already,sold
halfa million ofthejosie ears
fora big concert.
Right. Yes. So we have.
So what are you suggesting?
KeepJosie, and put those two
nosy little pussycats to sleep.
Mmmm.
I don't thinkJosie will
play without her friends.
Oh? I think
we might persuade her.
Mmm?
[Fiona]
Next, on Behind the Music,
Josiesuffersa tragic loss.
[ Laughs Sinisterly ]
[ Cackles ]
[ Chuckles Evilly ]
Ha-ha, hee-hee, hew,
ho-ho, hoo.
[ Laughs Dramatically ]
[ Laughs Loudly ]
[ Chokes, Coughs ]
[Woman]
The city,aquarium holdsmore
than 244 varieties ofsea life.
Josie, did I tell you
I got a gig tonight?
You did?
That's great!
Yeah, well,
it'sjust this bar,
but the manager--
I played him my demo,
and he said
I could have, like, almost
a full half-hour tonight.
Do you think maybe
you want to come, or--
Yeah.
'Cause I know you're
busy and everything.
Oh, my God.
Is thatJosie?
Where? Josie!
[ Screaming ]
Shapeshifter, guest lister
She'llturn around
anddesert
Gate-crasher, rehasher
Ify,ou think that's cool
well, y,ou're a fool
[ Panting ]
Thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
How am I gonna
pull this off?
Wh-What?
I'm a girl from Riverdale,
you know? I'm--
I'm not a rock star.
Jose, you've been
dreaming about this
your whole life.
I know, it'sjust--
What?
I'm scared.
Don't be. You gotta
believe in yourself.
What if I can't?
Then--
then I guess
I'll just have to
believe in you for you.
[Knocking]
Oh, wow.
[ Laughing ]
Oh, wow!
So, what do you think
we should open with
for the concert--
Spin Around,
ormay,be Come On ?
Uh, I don't know.
We could try
RolIOn, Rolly, Wheel,
but, honestly,, lthink
the ly,ricsstillneed work.
What do you think?
It's your call.
I mean, you're the boss.
No, I'm not.
Val, what's with you?
Hello, girls! Andhoware
the most beautifulandtalented
women in rock-and-roll?
Eh?
Don't you mean "woman"?
Valerie, my darling,
you're going to have to learn
to take a compliment.
I mean, what are you going to do
tonight when you go on TRL...
andCarson Daly,tellsy,ou
howmuch he lovesy,ourmusic?
Don't you mean,
what's Josie gonna do?
No, because she won't be there.
Wejust booked you and Melody.
It's time forthe world
toget to know
the otherPussy,cats.
We're gonna be on TRL ?
Mm-hmm.
Do I get to touch Carson?
[ Squeals ]
Anywhere you like.
The taping's in two hours,
unless, ofcourse,
you have a problem with this.
Do you have a problem
with this?
No! I thinkyou guys will
have a great time.
I love that show.
And-- and you don't mind
if Mel and I go without you?
Why? I don't care
about that stuff.
[ Sighs ]
Jose--
Oh, I'm so sorry!
I don't know
what I was thinking.
Okay.
Come on, girls. There are
stylists and designers
waiting in your room.
And you have homework tonight.
This is the remix
ofy,ournext single.
- I'd be very curious
to hearyour thoughts.
- Could it wait until tomorrow?
It'sjust thatAlan Mis
play,inghis firstgig tonight,
andl wannaget there early,.
Oh. Oh, I'm so sorry,Josie.
I forgot to tell you.
Alan M called my office.
They canceled his show.
- They did?
- Yes.
Why didn't he call me here?
Um, I'm sure he did.
In fact,
I'm sure ifyou go down
to the front desk, there'll be
a message waiting foryou.
Excuse me.
[ Whispering ]
Yes, there's a message
waiting foryou... now.
I guess I should call him.
Um, he also said to say
that he won't be available
for several hours,
and he'll call you
when he can.
- All that was on the message?
- Uh, yes. Excuse me.
[ Whispering ]
Yes, that's all in the message.
Anything else?
Who do you keep calling?
I'm running a label here,
Josephine.
I have other artists
who need me, other artists
who need my time,
other artists who aren't
so difficult about putting in
a little bit ofextra work.
Your level of non-commitment
is making me doubt
your commitment commitment.
So, you wanna be
a rock superstar, eh--
Iive large, big house,
five cars?
Well, you have to
do the time.
Otherwise,
[ Chuckles ]
somebody else will,
andy,ou'llbe left
to explain it all
to Meland Val.
I am committed.
I am.
Yes, I hope so,
my darling.
I hope so.
[DoorOpens, Closes]
- Val, we're on TRL !
- Hey, check out the view!
It's fake.
Wow. This stuff looks
so different on TV.
All this stuff is fake.
Where is everybody?
Where's Carson?
Yo, kitty,cats!
Howy,ou ladies doin'?
I'm Carson Daly,. Welcome.
You're not Carson Daly.
What are you talkin' about?
Ofcourse I'm Carson Daly.
Check the nails.
You need to call me.
I got plans.
All right.
Is everybody ready
to start the show?
- Oh, my God, it's Carson!
- Oh, my God, it's Melody!
Yo, man, y,ougotta
stop tryin'to be me
with the nails thing.
What you sayin', man?
A brother can't be Carson Daly?
No, that's not what I'm sayin'.
It'sjust that
I actually am Carson Daly,
so it doesn't work right now.
Who's gonna break my "gazoons,"
man? I'm Carson Daly.
That'spretty,good, man.
Who else doy,ou do?
I do Mike Tyson.
I would take a bite outta you.
Okay, what is going on?
Are you-- Is this TRL or not?
This is not
TotaIRequest Live.
It's more like
TotaIRequest Dead.
Yeah, you see, ladies, we've
only got one request today.
And that's to kill you.
[ Laughing ]
Carson said he's
gonna to kill us.
Like that's a request.
- All right, man,
I got the blond.
- He's not kidding.
Go!
[ Screaming ]
[ Ballad ]
[ Sighs ]
[Phone Ringing]
-   This is the place
Where I sit
- [ Ringing Continues ]
This is the part
where I love you too much
Is this as hard
as it gets
Um, this, uh--
this next song is
dedicated to, uh--
a friend of mine.
I kinda wanted to wait
till she showed up to play it,
but I guess she--
Whoo-hoo!
Um, the name ofthissong is,
uh, Wish You Felt the Same.
- [Toilet Flushing]
- Hey!
Shut up or hold it
till you get home!
Who do you want to kill you,
huh? Eddie Murphy?
Eddie told me,
"I want themJosie girls dead,
all right? You get them
a nurse. I want them dead!"
[ Laughs Like Eddie Murphy ]
[ Gasps ]
I can't believe
you're a killer!
- You seem so nice on TV!
- Really?
You know, lalway,s thought
you were kinda hot.
Too bad!
- Ialway,s thought
you were kinda hot too.
- You did?
What's your sign?
Scorpio.
I'm a Cancer.
[ Shrieks ]
[ Laughing ]
Da pussycats.
I gotta kill ya. Good lawd!
- What was that?
- It was Chris Rock.
That was
a terrible Chris Rock.
Why, doy,ou even bother
doing impressions?
You're not funny,.
You know who's funny?
Bill Cosby.
And he's going
to kill you...
after sticking a spoon
in your pudding.
[ Yelling ]
No way!
My, favorite movie is
Lady,andthe Tramp.
When the dogs are
eating spaghetti and
they share the same piece?
[ Together ]
And their noses touch!
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughs, Sighs ]
You know, if I wasn't
a key player in this whole...
conspiracy to brainwash
the youth ofAmerica
with pop music,
Iike, we could totally date.
- You think?
- Oh, yeah.
You know, it would be
so cool, like--
[ Yelling ]
Yeah, right.
Like I'd ever go out
with a guy like you.
Now, you,
on the other hand--
Come on.
Let's get outta here
and find Josie.
Bye.
[ Ballad Over Headphones ]
[Knocking]
[ Val]
Josie?josie, quick,
open the door!
[Knocking Continues]
Josie?
Jo-- Josie?
-Josie, we have to talk to you.
- How did they let
the two ofyou in here?
I specifically told
the front desk "no visitors."
- Are you okay?
- Ofcourse I'm okay.
Why wouldn't I be?
I have the number-one single
in the country.
You two, on the otherhand--
[Mutters]
should maybe be
a little worried.
Josie, Carson Daly tried
to kill us, and I think it has
something to do with our music.
Why do you call it...
"our" music?
Becau--
Are you even listening?
I am listening
very carefully,
anddoy,ou know
what I'm hearing?
I'm hearing someone
glomming on to my talent...
andmy,credit.
"Our" music, Mel?
I basically write all of it.
Josie, no, you don't.
We write it together.
Oh, okay.
So ifwe're all doing
equal amounts ofwork,
why isn't the band called
Valerie and the Pussycats?
I knew it.
You've been thinking this
the whole time.
I'm just-- I'm just
backup to you, huh?
Oh, but you're
a good, solid backup.
Oh, hey, Val,
who's a rock star?
Who'sa rockstar?
I am!
Josie, don't do this.
We need to
stick together now.
Oh, my God.
Melody's gonna cry.
What's the matter,
snuggle bunny--
finally realizing
the world isn't all
sunshine and rainbows?
Stop it.
Not everyone gets
a happy ending, muffin.
Stop it.
And you wanna know
what else?
Puppies turn into dogs...
who get old and die.
[ Gasping ]
Someday you'll thank me.
[ Scoffs ]
Ofcourse, by then
I won't be taking your calls.
This is theplace
where lsit
This is thepart
where llovey,ou too much
Is thisashard
asitgets
'Cause I'mgetting tired
ofpretendingl'm tough
I'm here ify,ou want me
I'my,ours, y,ou can holdme
I'm empty,andachin '
andtumblin'andbreakin'
'Causey,ou don'tsee me
And you don't need me
And you don't love me
The way,l wishy,ou would
The way I love you
[ Continues With
Static, Clicking ]
[ Mr. Moviefone's Voice ]
You are the star! Val and
Melody are mean, evil girls!
You should have a solo career!
You have the number-one single
in the country!
They're trying to glom on to
your talent and your credit!
Ifthey're doing
equal amounts ofwork,
why, isn 't the bandcalled
Valerie andthe Pussy,cats?
They'rejust deadweight,
Josie.
[ Overlapping ]
You could be huge without them.
You are the star.
Madonna huge.
Val and Melody are
mean, evil girls.
Melody,thinksy,ou can't sing.
Seriously,. She toldme.
Dump them. The are trying
to destroy you,Josie.
You'll be better off
without them.
Who's a rock star?
You are!
A great big rock star!
[ Continuing, lndistinct ]
Go,Josie, go! Go!
[ Player Slows, Stops ]
- Val!
- Oh, the return
ofthe superstar!
What's going on?
And where are Mel and Val?
Since when you do you care?
Oh, and we heard what you said,
Bitchy McBitch.
- Wish I'd said it.
- They're gone,Josie.
They,'regone,
andlhopey,ou're happy,.
No more band.
Just like the Beatles.
Just like theJackson Five.
Just like a Flock ofSeagulls.
[ Caws ]
- These are so good.
You want one ofthese?
- Okay, look,
Ineverthought
I wouldsay,this toy,ou,
ever, but, please,
would you help?
Now?
Wyatt gave me this CD
ofour song,
and it was like
as soon as I heard it--
I don't know.
What-- it sucked?
There's something on here,
I swear.
[Continues]
Okay, okay, okay.
[ Vocal Dropping out ]
[ Faint Murmuring ]
[ Mr. Moviefone's Voice ]
You should have a solo career!
You couldhavey,ourown
prime-time TVseries!
We couldcallit Josie,
andrun it right after
Will and Grace !
Oh, my, God! That's
Mr. Moviefone! Howdidy,ou
get him toput that on there?
[ Gasps ]
You slept with him!
What are you talking about?
This is on our CD
It's underneath the music.
Wyatt put them on there...
to brainwash me.
[ Gasps Melodramatically ]
Dum-dum-dum
Ooh, brainwashing!
Ooh, help!
We're beingbrainwashed!
Diet Coke's
the new Pepsi One.
"MS. " Main-- main sy,stem.
Musicsequence?
Oh, God.
Maybe you broke it.
Whoa, I didn't touch it.
[ Mr. Moviefone's Voice ]
Josie and the Pussycats are
the best band ever!
They,are totally,jerkin '!
You must buy,their CD
You have to see them in concert.
You also have to buy
Steve Madden shoes.
Heath Ledgeris
the newMatt Damon.
You're nobody, without
anAbercrombie & Fitch
vintage tee.
They're selling stuff
through our music.
Josie andthe Pussy,catsare
the best bandever!
They're selling us
through our music!
I knew there was a reason
you were so popular.
I want a vintage tee...
and Heath Ledger.
Oh, my God.
It's all my fault,
everything--
people dressing alike,
buying the same stuff.
I sold it to them.
I'm a trend pimp.
Well, it stops here!
I'm nobody's pimp,
and I'm not going to let Wyatt
and Fiona get away with this.
We're going to the police,
and we're taking this with us.
[ Grunts ]
Are you guys gonna
help me or what?
Oh, I'llhelp.
Yeah, right.
'Cause you know I'm just gonna
let you walk right outta here
and spoil everything.
All right, now the event
I know everybody's been
waiting for is finally here.
One night only,
the worldwide live debut concert
ofJosie and the Pussycats.
[ Screaming, Cheering ]
And, oh, very cool,
it's gonna be live
at the "Megarena"...
with a simultaneous
global web cast.
You can log on to mtv.com
for more details.
And remember:
You will not hear a thing
without yourJosie
3-D-X headphones,
so I urge you all
to pick some up--
I know I bought two.
[ Screaming, Cheering ]
- Hi!
- [ Chattering ]
Oh, look at the pouty girl.
Boo-hoo!
Well, you better
snap out of it, red, 'cause
you've got a show to put on!
Are you kidding?
I'm not gonna play, help you
send messages to those kids.
- Forget it. I'm done.
- Oh, look who's got all
principled all ofa sudden.
You didn't seem to mind when
your song went to number one!
You should kiss
my cellulite-free ass
for all I've done foryou.
I made you a rock star.
[ Cheering, Chanting ]
Tellmey,ou don't love that.
I said forget it, all right?
Now, find yourselfanother girl.
[ Groans ]
Yeah, see, I would,
but everybody's
already here!
- [ Chanting ]
Josie! Josie!
- Too bad.
- Wyatt.
-Josie!
- Val, Mel!
- Don't talk to her.
You're wasting your time.
Miss Diva over here doesn't care
ifyou do something to us.
No, that's not true.
You guys, just listen to me.
I didn't mean
any ofthat stuff
that I said before.
Fiona and Wyatt have put
subliminal message tracks
underneath our music--
Can it, rusty.
Your story's boring.
Wy,att, why, don'ty,oushowthese
two lovely, ladies what we have
forthem this evening?
Gladly, my darling.
- A car!
Val, I won a car!
- No, you didn't win a car.
- Oh, my God, you won a car!
- No one won a car!
The car... is about to be
a part of history...
ify,ou decide
not toplay,tonight.
Hi, I'm Serena Altschul
with MTV breaking news.
Josie and the Pussycats'
debut concert was
unexpectedly canceled...
when an automobile exploded
in the stadium parking lot.
The passengers were
identified as Valerie Brown
and Melody Valentine,
two ofthe founding members
ofthe popular rock band.
Investigators on thescene were
quotedassay,ing the two died
a slow, fierydeath...
inside the four-wheeled
hell pit.
We're toldthatjosie will
be releasinga statement...
to thepress within the hour
to comment on this tragedy,.
Yes,josie,
what arey,ourcomments?
We're allgagging to know.
Roast your friends,
or play the show?
Play,y,ourshow?
Roast the friends?
What's it to be?
All right!
I'll play.
See, Val?
She still likes us!
Mel, ofcourse I do.
You guys are my best friends
on the planet.
Look, I know that friends
don't treat each other
the way I treated you guys.
Buty,ou'vegot to believe me.
Iflcouldjustgo backin time,
I wouldtake it allback.
That would be cool.
If I could go back in time,
I'd wanna meet Snoopy.
Mel, I love that about you!
I love that you think
that everything is possible...
andthat this worldis
such agreatplace,
becausey,ou know what?
It is.
And I'm so sorry if,
for one second, I made you
think that it wasn't.
And Val-- Val,
you bought me
my first guitar.
And, you know, we may have
started this band together,
but the only reason we've
come this far is because ofyou.
Now, look.
Idon't care ifwe're
Josie andthe Pussy,cats,
or Valerie and the Pussycats
or whoever and the Pussycats.
It doesn't matter
as long as we're together.
You're my,sister, Val.
Ilovey,ou.
I love you too,Jose.
- And I love you, Val.
And I love you,Josie.
- And I love you, Mel.
And l--
I scream, you scream,
we all scream for ice cream.
Everyone loves everyone.
Now, let's get
this show started!
[ Chanting ]
We want the show!
So, what is it
this time, Fiona--
cross-trainers,
pizza bagels, lip gloss?
Oh, it's bigger--
much, much bigger.
You're gonna have a pretty hard
time selling secret messages
once your secret's out.
Oh, and tell me, cookie--
who will believe you?
Who willget behind
the ridiculous ramblings
ofonesilly,, powerlessgirl?
We will.
Who the hell are you?
Someone you thought
you'd gotten rid of.
- Oh, my God,
it's Les from Dujour!
- Les?
I tried to warn you--
the message on your mirror.
That was you?
Dujour was in my bathroom!
[ Muffled ]
I love you, Les!
-But I thought you guys were
killed in a plane crash.
-That's what I thought. Wyatt?
Oh, well, we managed
to landtheplanejust fine.
Unfortunately,
it was in the parking lot
ofa Metallica show.
Well, the fans beat
the crap out of us.
Well, you don't look
too bad.
And I thank God every day
I knew the words
to EnterSandman.
[Muffled, lndistinct]
Word, Doc. She's not
gonna get away with it--
not this time.
Let's get 'em, boys,
Dujour-style!
[ Moaning ]
- [ Monkey Screeching ]
- [Crashing]
Anyway--
- Oh, now, come on!
- [Crowd Chanting]
Boy, you almost got me.
Honestly,
girls all over the world
would kill to be in your shoes,
andherey,oustand,
runningaway, from it.
Why?
So you could go crawling back
to "Shitdale" and spend
the rest ofyour life...
being washed up
with your loser friends,
dopey and mopey there?
- [ Scoffs ]
- That's it.
[ Screams ]
Gotta be a wildone
Just stop right there,
missy.
Wyatt, you messed
with the wrong pussy.
- [ Grunting ]
-    But lkeep swingin ', baby,
I'm a real wildchild
[ Screaming ]
You bitch!
I'm a real wildone
andllike wildfun
In a worldgone crazy,
everything say,s
Yeah, I'm a wildone
- You want some?
Come on. Bring it!
- No, no!
We'regonna breakit loose
gotta keep it movin' wild
Gotta keep on swinging, baby,
I'm a real wildchild
[ Both Squealing ]
[ Yelling ]
No, baby, no! Let go!
Let go! Let go!
[ Grunts, Groans ]
Ooh!
[ Chuckles ]
What are you gonna do--
kill me with the guitar?
Who's gonna go up there
and sing? You need me,
remember?
Need you?
Doll, I created you,
and, believe me,
I can destroy you.
[ Yelling ]
- [ Feedback Screeching ]
- [ Screaming ]
- I'm sorry.
Did you need that?
- Wyatt! Fix it!
You-- what's yourjob?
Fix this!
Oh, it's too late!
They,'re already,taking off
the ears!
[ Mr. Moviefone's Voice ]
Fiona is the mostjerkin' girl
in the world!
Everybody loves Fiona!
She's got the best hair
and the most awesome clothes!
And she's so thin!
I know I want to be
just like Fiona!
That's the secret message
that you wanted to send out--
that you're cool?
What?
- That's not me, I swear.
- [Fiona's Voice]
You're not doing it right!
[Mr. Moviefone's Voice]
Hey,, that's my,job!
[Crashing, Struggling]
[Fiona's Voice, Lisping]
lfl wath aguy,,
I'dathkherout.
- Ifl wath agirl, I'd want to
be herbetht friendforever.
- What's wrong with your voice?
We'dhave thlumberpartiesand
thtay, up braiding each otherth
hairandhave tickle fights!
- [Laughing]
- Oh, thure.
Go ahead and laugh.
You don't know what it'th like
to be teathed and ridiculed
your whole life.
The thells thilver thwans
down by the theathore.
Theven thilver--
The thwims--
I tried, didn't l?
[ Sighs ]
AIllever wanted wath
to bepopular.
- Tell me, ith that tho bad?
- Lisa?
- What did you call me?
- Lisa Snyder?
"Lithping Litha"?
That-That-That wath
my nickname in thchool.
Huntington High School.
Lisa, it's me-- Wally.
"White-ass Wally."
White-ath Wally?
The albino kid?
That'th impothible.
- Firtht ofall,
he wathn't Britith.
- I'm not.
[ American Accent ]
I just started talking
like that because...
I thought it would
make me more attractive.
- He wath tho pale.
- [ Chuckles ]
Makeup.
I-l-l learned to thpeak
without a lithp.
Look!
I can't believe it'th you.
Ithn't it the thtrangetht
cointhidenth?
Wait.
[ Exhales ]
Oh, I've been holding that in
for the past 1 5 years.
This is so romantic.
Yeah, in a... creepy,
ironic sort ofway.
So, what's the moral
ofthestoryhere--
freaks should date
other freaks?
No, I think the moral
ofthe story here is you should
be happy with who you are.
This whole time we've been
spending money on expensive
clothes to impress people.
Never made me happy.
No! Happ-- Oh, my gosh.
Happiness is on the inside.
I'm not this.
I'm not what I wear.
[ Shouting ]
I'm not what I wear!
You should think about this.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, please.
Unlikey,ou bunch ofwackjobs,
lamperfectjust aslam.
Holy shit!
That girl's got a skunk
on her head!
Oh, geez.
That'sjusty,ourhair.
Sorry, but that'smessedup.
- Who are you?
- I'm Agent Kelly.
I'm with the government.
Oh, thank God!
Did you know...
that Fiona and Wyatt are using
that machine to send subliminal
messages through our music?
They're trying to create
an army of mindless teenagers,
to make them buy things and
even control their thoughts.
They what?
Oh, come on.
You knew about thith
from the very beginning.
- Gentlemen, arrest
that woman and that man...
- What?
on charges ofconspiracy
against the youth ofAmerica.
- You can't be theriouth.
- Oh, I'm serious, ma'am.
This is
a very serious offense.
Sorry, but they're on to us.
Somebody's got to take the fall.
You bathtard!
Besides, after the concert,
we were gonna shut down
your operation anyway.
We found
that subliminal messages
work much better in movies.
[Mr. Moviefone]
All right, let's go.
Well, now that you girls are
done saving the world,
I thinkyou have
a concert to play.
[Audience Cheering]
[Man OverP.A. ]
Give it up for
Josie andthe Pussy,cats!
[AudienceScreaming]
[Chanting]
Josie! josie!
[Chanting,
Screaming Continue]
[ Crowd Quiets ]
[FeedbackScreeches]
Whoa.
I'm gonna take these off.
Stop!
I know you all came out here
tonight because you heard
something you liked on our CD
[ScatteredCheers]
We're gonna play something
different foryou tonight--
something you haven't heard.
It's cool ifyou like it.
It's all right ifyou don't.
Just...
decide foryourselves.
This is forsomeone
who saidhe believedin me.
Kinda wish he was here now.
Na, na, na
Na, na, na, na
Yeah
One, two
One, two, three
Spin around, come back home
You're running out on a line
Sometimes feel
I'm goin' out of my mind
Stunned here waiting
for anyone to take the time
Spin around, weget
furtherandfurtheraway,
Smile and wave
ain 'tgot nothin'to say,
Stunnedhere waiting
forany,one to take the time
To change my,mind
this time
Well, I've been starin '
at thesun sometime
It gets dark inside
but I don't mind
And ifyou're gone
it's like I'm goin' blind
I can't get by this time
Spin around
Come down now 'cause
it's all getting clear
Everything you've
ever wanted to hear
Ifwe ever needed
anyone to change our minds
To waste our time
We're fine
Well, I'll be starin'
at the sun sometime
It gets dark inside
but I don't mind
And ifyou're gone
it's like I'm goin' blind
I can't get by this time
Josie! josie!
- Alan M!
-Josie!
- What are you doing here?
- I have to tell you that...
even though you don't feel
the same way about me...
asldo abouty,ou,
andeven though
you didn 't come to my,gig--
What do you mean?
Wyatt told me it was canceled!
That dick!
What did you mean about
the l-don't-feel-the-same-way-
about-you-as-you-do-about-me?
That's what I came here
to tell you!
Josie McCoy, l--
[ All Gasp ]
I love you!
[AudienceScreams]
I love you too!
I always have!
Hi.
[AudienceScreams,
Whistles]
Damn!
Oh.
[ Stammering ]
I love you.
La-la, la
La-la, la, la
Yeah
La-la, la
La-la, la, la
Yeah
La-la, la
La-la, la, la
Yeah
Spin around and around
and around and around
Never wanna come back down
'Cause everything we've lost
I've found
Yeah
Spin around and around and
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Whoa
[AudienceScreaming]
[Rock]
- [ Blows Raspberry ]
- [ Laughs ]
Contain the excitement.
josie andthe Pussy,cats
Why'd you have to hit me, man?
It wasjust never gonna stop.
GuitarsandMarshallstacks
Hot, sweet, supercool
Don'ty,ou knowthese kids rule
Hurry, hurry
We've beengoin'over
the masterplan
Driving in
a custom-painted van
Practicin'forhours
Don'ty,ou knowthatsoon
no matter wherey,ago
we'llbe on the radio
[FeedbackScreeches]
[ Snickers ]
Can you see me and
my nose on the microphone?
From this commandcenter
we controleverything...
except what I'm
gonna say next.
I can't even believe
that they let me bring--
[ Laughs ]
You slept with him!
You better get his mama
to get him a new face.
Ah-ah-ah.
You know my mom's dead.
That'sjust--
- [ All Laugh ]
- Next up on weather--
- [ Snarling ]
- What is wrong with you?
Goodness, won't somebody
please save us?
[ Laughing ]
Goin'tripleplatinum
Youjust watch us climbin'up
the Billboard charts
Breakin'records
breakin'hearts
Hey, those are my bunny ears!
Sh--
[Beeps]
This is what our operation--
I just spat right
in the camera.
Even though we'replay,in '
in ourgarage
Soon we'llhave
a massive entourage
Goin'tripleplatinum
Youjust watch us climbin'up
the Billboard charts
Breakin'records
breakin'hearts
Yeah, right. 'Cause you know
I'm just gonna--
[ Laughs ]
Let'sgo
Josie andthe Pussy,cats
Long tails
andears forhats
We knowjust where it'sat
[ Karate Sounds ]
-    East, west
north orsouth
- [ Giggling ]
Guaranteedto rock
the house
josie andthe Pussy,cats
[ Screaming ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Vocalizing]
They,say,this kindoflove
is wrongbuty,ou know
it feelsso right
Running my,handsacross
yourcheeks, they,'re
oh-so smooth and white
Leave the light on, baby,
andunlocky,ourbackdoor
I'llbe comin'through
that way,tonight
to lovey,ou forsure
Ly,in'ony,ourbed
Starin'up at the moon
Yougot me crazy,
Gotta lovey,ousoon
I'my,ourbackdoorlover
Comin'from behind
with the lights down low
Backdoorlover
Justy,ou andme
No one has to know
Backdoorlover
Let me meety,ou there
aty,oursecretspot
I'llshowy,ou a love
that'smore than hot
Well, he looksat me with
those innocent ey,esandsay,s
It looks likey,ou're wearin '
some kindofdisguise
Becausey,ourhairsticks up
Yourshoesare untied
Ihope thaty,ougot
thatshirt at halfprice
Andevery wordlsay,
falls flat on the floor
Itryto tellajoke
He'sheardit before
Andldon't think
that lcan take it no more
He's drivingme
right out my, front door
Why, doy,ou do
whaty,ou do to me, baby,
You're shaking my,confidence
Drivingme crazy,
You knowiflcould
I'ddo any,thing fory,ou
Please don't ignore me
'causey,ou knowladorey,ou
Oooh, wee, ooh, wee
Oooh, wee, ooh, wee, ooh
Dujouraroundthe world
Nobody, rocks the mike
like Dujour
Nobody,
Bangin' 'round
the world with Dujour
We're numberone andstay,in '
at the top ofourgame
From east to west, we know
you already, knowourname
Dujour
aroundthe worldforever
Yeah, fly,in'so high
in allkinds ofweather
We're numberone
in thisgame
Andlthinky,ou know
ourname is
Dujour
Nobody, rocks the mike
like Dujour
Dujour
Ride ony,ourmotorbike
with Dujour
I'm apunkrockprom queen
Brownpapermagazine
Hotterthany,ou've everseen
Everywhere andin between
I'm a ten-ticket thrillride
Don'ty,ou wanna come inside
A five-startriple threat
Hardest ofthe hardtoget
No one's little reprobate
Ain 'tseen nothin '
like mey,et
It tooksix whole hours
andfive long day,s
Forally,ourlies
to come undone
Andthose threesmall words
Were way,too late
'Causey,ou can'tsee
that I'm the one
[Mr. Moviefone]
Jerkin '!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org