Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Ripped by SeBaS
It's only forever
Not long at all
The lost and the lonely
No one can blame you
For walking away
But too much rejection
No love injection
Life can be easy
It's not always swell
Don't tell me truth hurts
little girl
'Cause it hurts like hell
But down in the underground
You'll find someone true
Down in the underground
A land serene
A crystal moon
It's only forever
It's not long at all
The lost and the lonely
That's underground
Underground
Give me the child.
Through dangers untold
and hardships unnumbered...
I have fought my way to the castle
beyond the Goblin City...
to take back the child
that you have stolen.
For my will
is as strong as yours...
and my kingdom is as great--
For my will is as strong as yours,
my kingdom as great--
Damn.
Oh, I can never remember that line.
"You have no power over me."
Oh, Merlin.
Oh, no, Merlin.
I don't believe it. It's 7:00!
Come on. Come on!
No one can blame you
For walking away
But too much rejection
No love injection
Life can be easy
It's not always swell
Don't tell me truth hurts
little girl
'Cause it hurts like hell
Oh, it's not tair!
Oh, really.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't stand in the rain. Come on.
All right. Come on, Merlin.
- Come on.
- Not the dog.
- But it's pouring.
- Go on, into the garage.
Go on, Merlin.
Go into the garage.
Go.
- Sarah, you're an hour late.
- I said I was sorry!
Please let me finish.
- Your f ather and I go out rarely.
- You go out every single weekend.
I ask you to baby-sit only it it
won't interfere with your plans.
You don't know what my plans are.
You don't even ask me anymore.
I assume you'd tell me you had a date.
I'd like it it you had a date.
- You should have dates at your age.
- Sarah, you're home.
- We were worried about you.
- I can't do anything right, can I?
She treats me like a wicked stepmother
in a tairy story no matter what I say.
I'll talk to her.
Through dangers untold...
and hardships unnumbered...
I have fought my way here
to the castle...
beyond the Goblin City...
to take back the child...
that you have stolen.
- Can I talk to you?
- There's nothing to talk about!
Hurry. You're gonna be late.
Listen, we ted Toby
and put him to bed.
We do have to leave now,
but we'll be back around midnight.
You really wanted
to talk to me, didn't you?
Practically broke down the door.
Lancelot!
Someone has been in my room again.
I hate that. I hate it!
I hate you. I hate you!
Someone save me, take me away
from this awful place!
What do you want?
You want a story, huh?
Okay.
Once upon a time
there was a beautitul, young girl...
whose stepmother always
made her stay home with the baby.
The baby was a spoiled child
and wanted everything for himself...
and the young girl
was practically a slave.
But what no one knew...
was that the king ot the goblins
had f allen in love with the girl...
and he had given her
certain powers.
So one night...
when the baby had been
particularly cruel to her...
she called on the goblins tor help.
Listen.
"Say your right words, "
the goblins said.
"And we'll take the baby
to the Goblin City...
and you will be tree."
But the girl knew
that the king ot the goblins...
would keep the baby in his castle
torever and ever and ever...
and turn it into a goblin.
So the girl sutfered in silence...
until one night, when she was tired
from a day of housework...
and she was hurt by the harsh words
of her stepmother...
and she could no longer stand it--
Oh, all right!
Knock it ott. Come on.
Stop it!
I'll say the words.
No, I mustn't. I mustn't say.
I wish--
I wish.
- She's going to say it.
- Say what?
- Shut up.
- Sorry.
You shut up.
Listen.
She's going to say the words.
I can bear it no longer!
Goblin King, Goblin King,
wherever you may be...
take this child of mine
tar away trom me!
- No!
- That's not it.
Where'd she learn that rubbish?
It doesn't even start with "I wish."
Toby, stop it!
I wish I did know what to say
to make the goblins take you away.
"I wish the goblins would come
and take you away right now."
That's not hard, is it?
I wish--
- Did she say it?
- Shut up!
I wish the goblins would
come and take you away.
Right now.
Toby?
Toby, are you all right?
Why aren't you crying?
You're him, aren't you?
You're the goblin king.
I want my brother back, please,
it it's all the same.
What's said is said.
But I didn't mean it.
- Oh, you didn't.
- Please.
Where is he?
You know very well where he is.
Please bring him back. Please.
Sarah...
go back to your room...
play with your toys
and your costumes.
Forget about the baby.
I can't.
I've brought you a gitt.
- What is it?
- It's a crystal.
Nothing more.
But it you turn it this way...
look into it.
It will show you your dreams.
But this is not a gitt
tor an ordinary girl...
who takes care
ot a screaming baby.
Do you want it?
Then forget the baby.
I can't.
I appreciate what you're trying to do
tor me, but I want my brother back.
- He must be so scared.
- Sarah.
Don't dety me.
You're no match for me.
But I have to
have my brother back.
He's there, in my castle.
Do you still
want to look tor him?
Is that the castle
beyond the Goblin City?
Turn back, Sarah.
Turn back betore it's too late.
I can't.
Don't you understand
that I can't?
What a pity.
It doesn't look that f ar.
It's turther than you think.
Time is short.
You have 13 hours in which
to solve the labyrinth...
betore your baby brother...
becomes one ot us...
torever.
Such a pity.
The labyrinth.
It doesn't look that hard.
Well, come on, teet.
- Excuse me?
- Oh, excuse me!
Oh, it's you.
Excuse me, but I have to get through
this labyrinth. Can you help me?
Oh, how sweet.
Fifty-seven!
- How could you?
- Yeah.
Poor thing.
You monster. Ow!
It bit me!
What did you expect
tairies to do?
I thought they did nice things
like granting wishes.
Huh? Shows what you know,
don't it?
- Fifty-eight.
- You're horrible.
Huh? No, I ain't.
I'm Hoggle. Who are you?
That's what I thought.
Fitty-nine.
Do you know where the door
to the labyrinth is?
- Maybe.
- Where is it?
Oh, you little--
Sixty!
- I said, where is it?
- Where is what?
- The door.
- What door?
It's hopeless asking you anything.
Not it you ask the right questions.
How do I get into the labyrinth?
Now that's more like it.
You gets in there.
You really going in there,
are you?
Yes.
I'm afraid I have to.
Cozy, isn't it?
Now, would you go lett
or right?
- They both look the same.
- Well, you're not gonna get very f ar.
- Which way would you go?
- Me?
I wouldn't go either way.
It that's all the help you're
gonna be, you can just leave.
You know your problem?
You take too many things for granted.
Take this labyrinth--
Even if you get to the center,
you'll never get out again.
- That's your opinion.
- It's a lot better than yours.
Thanks tor nothing, Hogwart.
It's Hoggle!
And don't say I didn't warn you.
What do they mean, "labyrinth"?
There aren't any turns or corners.
It just goes on and on.
Maybe it doesn't.
Maybe I'm just taking it
tor granted that it does.
'Allo.
Did you say "hello"?
No, I said "'allo,"
but that's close enough.
- You're a worm, aren't you?
- That's right.
You don't by any chance
know the way through this labyrinth?
Who, me?
No, I'm just a worm.
Come inside, meet the missus.
No, thank you, but I have
to solve this labyrinth.
But there aren't any turns
or any openings or anything.
It just goes on and on.
You ain't looking right. It's tull
of openings, but you ain't seeing 'em.
- Where are they?
- There's one just across there.
It's right in front of ya.
No, there isn't.
Come inside and have
a nice cup ot tea.
- But there isn't an opening.
- Ot course there is.
You try walking through it.
You'll see what I mean.
What?
Go on then.
That's just wall.
There's no way through.
Things are not always
what they seem in this place.
So you can't take anything
tor granted.
Hey!
- Hang on.
- Thank you.
- That was incredibly helpful.
- Don't go that way.
- What was that?
- I said, don't go that way.
Never go that way.
Oh. Thanks.
If she had kept on
going down that way...
she'd had gone straight
to that castle.
Toby.
I'm coming, Toby.
Give me back this!
Go on, get ott me.
Stay out of the way.
What are you talking about?
Walk, walk, walk.
- You remind me of the babe.
- What babe?
- The babe with the power.
- What power?
- The power ot voodoo.
- Who do?
- You do.
- Do what?
Remind me ot the babe.
Quiet! A goblin babe.
Well?
I saw my baby
Crying hard as babe could cry
What could I do
My baby's love had gone
And left my baby blue
Nobody knew
What kind of magic spell to use
Slime and snails
Or a puppy dog's tail
Thunder or lightning
And baby said
- Dance, magic
- Dance, magic, dance
Put that baby spell on me
- Jump, magic, jump
Put that magic jump on me
Slap that baby
Make him free
Hey, what goes on?
Your mother is an aardvark!
In 9 hours and 23 minutes...
you'll be mine.
I saw my baby
Trying hard as babe could fry
What could I do
My baby's fun had gone
And left my baby blue
Nobody knew
What kind of magic spells to use
Slime and snails
Puppy dog's tails
Thunder or lightning
Then baby said
- Dance, magic, dance
Put that baby spell on me
- Jump, magic, jump
Put that magic jump on me
Slap that baby
Make him free
- Dance, magic, dance
Jump, magic, jump
Put that baby spell on me
- You got it?
- I got it.
- Good.
- Shh!
Someone has been
changing my marks.
What a horrible place this is.
It's not tair!
That's right. It's not f air.
But that's only half ot it.
- This was a dead end a minute ago.
- No, that's the dead end behind you.
It keeps changing.
What am I supposed to do?
The only way out ot here
is to try one of these doors.
One ot them leads to the castle
at the center ot the labyrinth.
- And the other one leads to...
- Boom-boom-ba-boom.
certain death.
Which one is which?
- We can't tell you.
- Why not?
- We don't know.
- But they do.
Oh. Then I'll ask them.
No, you can't ask us.
You can only ask one of us.
It's in the rules,
and I should warn you...
one ot us always tells the truth...
and one ot us always lies.
That's a rule too.
He always lies.
- I do not. I tell the truth.
- Oh, what a lie.
He's the liar.
All right. Answer yes or no.
Would he tell me that this door
leads to the castle?
Yes.
Then the other door leads
to the castle...
and this door leads
to certain death.
- Ooh!
- How do you know?
- He could be telling the truth.
- But then you wouldn't be.
So it you told me that he said yes,
I know the answer is no.
- But I could be telling the truth.
- But then he would be lying.
So it you told me that he said yes,
I know the answer would still be no.
Wait a minute. Is that right?
I don't know.
I've never understood it.
No, it's right.
I tigured it out.
I could never do it before.
I think I'm getting smarter.
This is a piece of cake.
Help!
Stop it! Help!
What do you mean, "help"?
We are helping.
We're helping hands.
You're hurting.
Would you like us to let go?
Well, then come on,
which way?
Which way?
Up or down?
- Oh.
- Come on, come on.
We haven't got all day.
Well, it's a big decision for her.
Which way do you want to go, hmm?
Yes, which way?
Well, since I'm pointed that way,
I guess I'll go down.
She chose down.
She chose down?
- Was that wrong?
- Too late now.
She's in the oubliette.
Shut up! She should not have gotten
as tar as the oubliette.
- She should have given up by now.
- She'll never give up.
Won't she? The dwarf's about
to lead her back to the beginning.
She'll soon give up when she realizes
she has to start all over again.
Well, laugh.
Who's there?
Me.
- Oh, it's you.
- Oh, yes, well...
I knew you were gonna get into trouble
as soon as I met you...
so I've come to give you a hand.
Oh, you're looking around now,
aren't you?
I suppose you noticed
there ain't no doors.
Only the hole.
This is an oubliette.
The labyrinth's full ot them.
- Really? How do you know that?
- Oh, don't sound so smart.
- You don't know what an oubliette is.
- Do you?
Yes, it's a place you put people...
to forget about 'em.
Now, what you've gotta do
is get out of here.
And it so happens
that I know a short cut...
out ot the whole labyrinth
from here.
No, I'm not giving up now.
I've come too tar.
- No, I'm doing okay.
- Ot course you are.
But it gets a lot worse
trom here on in.
Why are you so concerned about me?
Well, I am, that's all.
Nice, young girl.
Terrible, black oubliette.
You like jewelry, don't you?
Why?
If you help me solve the labyrinth,
I'll give you this.
You like it, don't you?
- So-so.
- Oh. Okay.
Tell you what--
you give me the bracelet...
and I'll show you the way
out ot the labyrinth.
- You were gonna do that anyway.
- Yes.
That's what would make it a
particularly nice gesture on your part.
I'll tell you what--
it you won't take me to the center,
take me as f ar as you can.
- Then I'll do it on my own.
- What is that anyway?
Plastic.
I don't promise nothing, but...
I'll take you as tar as I can,
then you're on your own, right?
- Right.
Wow. Plastic!
Here we go.
Damn.
Broom closet.
Well, can't be right
all the time.
This is it. Come on then.
- This way.
- Don't go on.
Go back while you still can.
This is not the way.
Take heed and go no further.
Beware. Beware.
Soon it will be too late.
Yeah! Don't pay
any attention to them.
They're just talse alarms.
You get a lot ot them in the labyrinth.
Especially when you're
on the right track.
- Oh, no, you're not.
- Oh, shut up.
- Sorry. Just doing my job.
- You don't have to do it to us.
- Beware tor--
- Just torget it.
Oh, please, I haven't said it
tor such a long time.
Oh, all right, but don't
expect a big reaction.
No, no, no, ot course not.
For the path you will take
will lead to certain destruction.
- Thank you very much.
- Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
What have we here?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Nothing? Nothing?
Nothing, tra-la-la.
Your Majesty,
what a nice surprise.
- Hello, Hedgewart.
- Hogwart.
Hoggle!
Hoggle, can it be
that you're helping this girl?
Helping? In what sense?
In the sense that you're
leading her towards the castle.
No, I was taking her back
to the beginning, Your Majesty.
What?
I told her I was going to
help her solve the labyrinth.
A little trickery on my part.
But actually--
What is that plastic thing
'round your wrist?
Oh, this!
My goodness,
where did this come trom?
- Higgle--
- Hoggle.
It I thought tor one second
that you were betraying me...
I'd be forced to suspend you headfirst
in the Bog ot Eternal Stench.
No, Your Majesty!
Not the Eternal Stench!
Oh, yes, Hoggle!
And you, Sarah.
How are you enjoying
my labyrinth?
It's a piece ot cake.
Oh!
Really? Then how about
upping the stakes?
Hmm?
That's not tair!
You say that so often.
I wonder what your basis
tor comparison is.
So the labyrinth's
a piece of cake, is it?
Well, let's see how you deal
with this little slice.
Oh, no, the cleaners!
- What?
- Run!
You okay?
Come on!
Faster!
The cleaners!
The Bog of Stench!
You sure got his attention.
Ah, this is what we need.
A ladder. Follow me.
How can I trust you now that I know you
were taking me back to the beginning?
I wasn't.
I told him I was taking you back to the
beginning to throw him otf the scent.
Hoggle, how can I believe
anything you say?
Well, let me put it this way.
What choice have you got?
You're right.
You see, you've gotta
understand my position.
I'm a coward,
and Jareth scares me.
- What kind ot position is that?
- No position. That's my point.
You wouldn't be so brave
if you'd ever smelled...
the Bog ot Eternal Stench.
It's-- It's--
Is that all it does,
is smell?
Believe me, that's enough.
But the worst thing is,
it you so much...
as put a foot
in the Bog ot Stench...
you'll smell bad
for the rest ot your lite.
It'II never wash otf.
Here we are then.
You're on your own trom now on.
- What?
- That's it. I quit.
Wait a minute.
I didn't promise nothin'. I said
I'd take you as tar as I could go.
You little cheat.
You nasty little cheat.
Don't try to embarrass me.
I've got no pride.
Oh, yeah?
But them's my jewels!
You give 'em back.
Give them back. Give those back.
Give those back to me!
Now, there's the castle.
Which way should we try?
Them's my rightful property.
It's not tair!
No, it isn't.
But that's the way it is.
Excuse me, please,
but can you help me?
Oh, a young girl!
And who is this?
- My friend.
- Oh, yes.
And what can I do tor you?
Please, can you tell--
That is--
I have to get to the castle
at the center ot the labyrinth.
Do you know the way?
Well, yes, now.
You want to get to the castle.
How's that for brain power, huh?
Be quiet!
Ah, nuts.
So, young woman...
the way forward
is sometimes the way back.
Will you listen to this crap!
- Will you please be quiet!
- Sorry. All right.
- Okay.
- Okay!
- All right.
- All right!
- What?
- Sorry.
Finished?
Yes.
Quite otten, young lady...
it seems like we're not getting
anywhere, when in tact--
- We are.
I'm certainly not getting
anywhere at the moment.
Join the club.
I think that's your lot.
Please leave a contribution
in the little box.
Don't you dare! Them's mine.
Well, I guess I can spare this.
Oh, you didn't
have to give him that.
He didn't tell you nothin'.
Well, then.
There go a couple of suckers.
Ah, it's so stimulating
being your hat.
Why-- Why did you say that...
about my being your friend?
Because you are.
You may not be much ot a triend,
but you're the only one I've got here.
Do you hear something?
- No, it's all right.
- Friend.
I like that.
I ain't never been
no one's triend betore.
- Good-bye!
- Wait a minute.
- Keep the stuft.
- Are you my triend or not?
No, I'm not.
Hoggle ain't no one's triend.
He looks after himselt,
like everyone.
Hoggle is Hoggle's triend.
Hoggle, you coward!
Well, I'm not atraid.
Things aren't always
what they seem in this place.
Try on this for size,
you big yeti!
We've got you now,
tuzz ball!
All together now.
It only I had something to throw.
Sock it to him!
What happened? Who turned out
the light? I can't see!
- Why'd you bite me?
- Who bite who?
Who bite me? Who bite me?
- I can't see!
- What is going on?
Retreat!
Who bit me?
Oh, my aching sushi!
Now, stop that.
Is that any way to treat someone
who's trying to help you?
Don't you want me
to help you down?
Ludo down.
Ludo?
Is that your name?
You seem like such a nice beast.
Well, I certainly hope you
are what you seem to be.
Just hang on.
I'll get you down.
Just a second.
I'm sorry!
Ludo, are you hurt?
Friend?
That's right, Ludo.
I'm Sarah.
Sarah.
Here, let me help you.
Are you okay?
Sarah triend.
Now, wait. Just a second.
- I want to ask you something, Ludo.
- What?
I have to get to the castle at the
labyrinth's center. Do you know the way?
- No.
- You don't know either, huh?
I wonder if anyone knows how
to get through this labyrinth.
Get through the labyrinth.
One thing tor sure-- she'll never
get through the labyrinth.
Hey.
Where did they come trom?
What do you think?
Which shall we choose
out ot these two ugly characters?
It's very rude to stare!
I'm sorry. I was just wondering
which door to choose.
- What?
- It's no good asking him.
- He's as deat as a post.
- Don't talk with your mouth tull.
- I'm not talking with my mouth full!
- Wait a second.
- I can't understand you.
- What were you saying?
- It is so good to get that thing out.
I said, it's no good talking to him.
He's as deat as a post.
Mumble, mumble. You're a wondertul
conversational companion.
You can talk!
All you do is moan!
No good. Can't hear you.
- Where do these doors lead?
- What?
Search me.
We're just the knockers.
- How do I get through?
- Huh?
Knock, and the door will open.
I don't want that thing
back in my mouth.
- Come on. I want to knock.
- Mm-mmm.
Doesn't want his ring
back in his mouth, eh?
Can't say I blame him.
- Sorry.
- That's all right. I'm used to it.
Come on.
You're welcome.
He's a lively little chap.
I think I'll call him Jareth.
He's got my eyes.
Ludo scared.
Aw, give me your hand.
Come on.
Imagine a big thing like you
being scared.
Yeah.
See, Ludo? There's nothing
to be atraid of.
Ludo, where are you?
Hoggle, help!
- I'm comin', Sarah.
- Well, it it isn't you.
And where are you going?
Well, the little lady
gave me the slip...
but I just hears her now...
so I was about to lead her
back to the beginning...
like you told me.
- I see.
- Ludo!
For one moment I thought
you were running to help her.
But no, not after my warnings.
- That would be stupid.
- Oh, you bet it would!
Me help her
atter your warnings?
- Oh, dear. Poor Hoghead.
- Hoggle.
I've just noticed
your lovely jewels are missing.
Oh, yes, so they are.
My lovely jewels. Let me think.
I better tind 'em, but tirst
I'm ott to take the little lady...
back to the beginning ot the labyrinth,
just like we planned.
Wait.
I've got a much better plan.
Give her this.
Wha-- What is it?
It's a present.
It ain't gonna hurt
the little lady, is it?
Why the concern?
- I won't do nothin' to harm her.
- Oh, come, come, Hogbrain.
I'm surprised at you
losing your head over a girl.
I ain't lost my head.
You don't think a young girl
could ever like...
a repulsive little scab
like you, do you?
She said we was--
Bosom companions?
Friends?
- Don't matter.
- You'll give her that...
or I'II tip you straight
into the Bog of Eternal Stench...
betore you can blink.
Yes. Right.
And Hoggle...
if she ever kisses you,
I'll turn you into a prince.
You-- You will?
Prince of the Land ot Stench.
Ludo?
What's going on?
- What do you want?
- What, us?
We're just atter
having a good time.
That's right!
- Don't got no problems
- No problems
- Ain't got no suitcase
- No suitcase
- Ain'f got no clothes to worry about
- No clothes to worry about
Ain't got no real estate or jewelry
or gold mines to hang me up
- I just throw in my hand
- Throw in his hand
With the chilliest bunch
in the land
- In the land
- They don't look like much
They're so chilly chilly
They positively glow glow
Chilly down
With the wild gang
Think small with the wild gang
Bang heads with the wild gang
Like the man said,
don't lose your head.
When your thing gets wild
Chilly down, chilly down
- With the wild gang
- Hey, I'm a wild child
Let's fly with the wild gang
Walk tall.
- Good time, bad food
- Yeah.
When your thing gets wild
Chilly down, chilly down
Roll 'em.
Snake eyes!
Hey, lady!
Fore!
- So when things get too tough
- Get too tough
- Your chin is dragging on the ground
- Dragging on the ground
- And even down looks up
- Down looks up
Bad luck
- We can show you a good time
- Show you a good time
- And we don't charge nothing
- Nothing at all
Just strut your nasty stuff
Wiggle in the middle, yeah
Get the town talking, bad gang
- Chilly down with the wild gang
- Think small
Think small with the wild gang
- Bang heads!
- Bang heads with the wild gang
Hey, listen up.
When your thing gets wild
Chilly down, chilly down
With the wild gang
- Shake your pretty little head.
- Act tall with the wild gang
- Tap your pretty little teet.
- Good times, bad food
Come on!
Hey, hey!
Her head don't come ott.
Ot course it doesn't!
- She's right. It's stuck on.
- Hey, lady.
Where you going
with a head like that?
Hey, man, I know what we can do.
Take oft her head!
Yeah, let's take her apart.
Lady, that's his head.
- That's my head!
- That's a triend ot mine.
What are you doing?
Hey! Wait!
Hey, lady...
it's against the rules
to throw other people's heads.
You're only allowed
to throw your own head.
Yeah, that's right.
Where's the reteree?
We'll just take your head ott.
- Somebody stop her.
- Come back, little lady.
- Play the game.
- Yeah, we're going to throw your head.
You can't quit.
The game's not over.
- Hey, lady!
- Leave me alone!
- We get a free throw.
- Don't you want to take your head oft?
- Ot course she does.
- Grab it!
- Don't you want to look like us?
- Leave me alone.
We want her! Get us all!
It you play,
we'll take oft your arms!
- Or we'll take oft your ear.
- You don't need two ears.
- Game's almost over.
- Time's up.
- Go away.
- Hoggle, you've come to help me.
Don't kiss me! Don't kiss me!
No, no, no!
Hoggle, hold on.
Oh, my God.
Oh, what is it?
The Bog ot Eternal Stench!
I never smelled anything like it.
It's like--
It doesn't matter what it's like.
It's a Bog ot Eternal Stench.
Help!
Hold on.
What did you have to go
and do a thing like that tor?
Do what?
- You mean rescue you?
- What? No.
You kissed me.
Oh, my gosh.
Don't pretend to be so hard.
I know you came back to help me,
and I know that you're my triend.
Did not. Am not.
I just come
to get me property back.
Oh, and...
give you-- give you--
Give me what?
Ludo!
Smell!
Where's Hoggle?
Get otf ot me!
Here.
Oh, no, it's okay.
This is Ludo. He's a friend too.
A what?
Smell!
You're right.
Oh, my God.
There's a bridge.
Come on.
Watch it.
You step in this stutt
and you'll stink torever.
Stop!
- Stop, I say.
- Please, we have to get across.
Without my permission,
no one may cross.
Please, I only have
a little time left!
We've gotta get out of this stench.
Smell bad.
- Stench? Ot what speaketh thou?
- This smell.
- I smell nothing.
- Oh, you're joking.
But I live
by my sense ot smell.
The air is sweet and fragrant,
and none may pass without my permission!
Smell bad.
Oh, get out of my way!
I warn thee,
I'm sworn to do my duty!
- Come on. Let us get across.
- Hold!
Listen, I don't want to
have to hurt you.
What are you doing?
Let go of my staft, sir!
All right then.
I can conquer this mountain.
Thou must do better than that.
Give up? Huh?
Enough!
Before this day, never have I
met my match in battle.
Yet this noble knight
has tought me to a standstill.
- Are you all right, Ludo?
- Smell!
Sir Ludo, it that's thy name,
now l, Sir Didymus, yield to thee.
Come, let us be brothers
hencetorth...
and fight tor the right as one!
- Thank you very much.
- Ludo get brother.
Steady.
- Well met, Sir Ludo.
- Good. Come on.
Wait a minute!
You torget my sacred vow, my lady.
- I cannot let you pass.
- But you said Ludo is your brother.
I have taken an oath,
and I must detend it to the death.
- The smell!
- Okay.
Let's handle this thing logically.
What exactly have you sworn?
I have sworn with my liteblood
no one shall pass this way...
without my permission.
Well, may we have your permission?
Well, l--
- Yes.
- Thank you, noble sir.
My lady.
- Uh-oh.
- Have no fear, sweet lady.
This bridge has lasted
for a thousand years.
- It seemed solid enough.
- Hoggle!
Fear not, tair maiden.
I will save thee.
Somehow.
Sir Ludo, canst thou sit by and howl
when yon maiden needs our help?
- That's incredible, Ludo.
- My brother!
Canst thou summon up
the very rocks?
Sure. Rocks friends.
- Here.
- Thanks, Hoggle.
Be caretul, Ludo.
Wait tor me.
Ambrosious, it's all right.
You can come out now.
Come on. That-a boy.
My loyal steed. Steady.
Forward. Steady, boy.
Come on, Ambrosious.
Just close your eyes and go.
Let's get out of here.
Excuse us. Thank you.
I wouldn't do that,
if I were you.
Oh, please,
I can't give it to her.
Come on then. We should reach
the castle well betore day.
Look, Sarah, is this
what you're trying to find?
So much trouble over such
a little thing, but not tor long.
She'll soon forget all about you,
my tine tellow.
Just as soon as Hoggle
gives her my present...
then she'll torget everything.
Is that my stomach or yours,
Ambrosious?
Hungry.
Yeah. Well, we can't stop now.
Maybe we can tind
some berries or something.
Yeah?
Here.
Thank you!
You're a litesaver.
This tastes strange.
What have you done?
Oh, damn you, Jareth.
And damn me too.
Everything's dancing.
Yea, verily.
Whoa, Ambrosious, whoa!
The castle doth lie yonder,
my lady.
My lady?
There's such a sad love
Deep in your eyes
A kind of pale jewel
Open and closed
within your eyes
I'll place the sky
Within your eyes
There's such a fooled heart
Beating so fast
In search of new dreams
A love that will last
Within your heart
I'll place the moon
As the pain sweeps through
Makes no sense for you
Every thrill has gone
Wasn't too much fun at all
But I'll be there for you
As the world falls down
Falling
- As the world falls down
- It's falling
Falling in love
I'll paint you mornings of gold
I'll spin you Valentine evenings
Though we're strangers till now
We're choosing the path
Between the stars
I'll lay my love
As the pain sweeps through
Makes no sense for you
Every thrill has gone
Wasn't too much fun at all
But I'll be there for you
As the world falls down
Falling
- As the world falls down
- It's falling
It's falling
Falling in love
Oh, she'll never forgive me.
What have I done?
I've lost my only triend.
That's what I've done.
What was I doing?
Get oft my back!
Why don't you look
where you're going...
young woman, hmm?
- I was looking.
- Huh? Huh?
Where were you going, hmm?
I don't remember.
You can't look where you're going
it you don't know where you're going.
I was searching tor something.
Look here.
Lancelot?
Thank you.
That's what you were looking tor,
wasn't it, my dear?
Yes. I torgot.
Now, why don't you...
come in here...
and see if there's
anything else...
you'd like, hmm?
It was just a dream.
I dreamed it all, Lancelot.
But it was so real.
Let's go see it Daddy's back,
okay?
Better to stay in here, dear.
Yes.
There's nothing you want
out there. No!
Oh, what have we got here?
Lancelot.
Your little bunny rabbit.
You like your little bunny rabbit.
Don't you? Yes, yes.
There you go.
There's Betsy Bou.
You remember Betsy Bou, don't you?
Yes, yes.
Now, then, what else have we got?
What's this? Let's have a look.
It's a pencil box.
Got lots of pencils in it too.
Here's your panda slippers.
You know how much you like them.
You never wanted them thrown away.
There they are. That's right.
Okay, now then, what else?
Oh, it's little Horsey.
You love little Horsey,
don't you, dear?
And look at this!
You got a printing game, you have.
Oh, here's a treasure.
You'll want that, won't you, my dear?
Yes, go on, put it on.
Make yourselt up.
Here's dear old Flopsy.
You'll want her. There you go.
Oh, yes. Ah, oh, yes.
Charlie Bear. Right.
There's Charlie Bear tor you.
There was something
I was looking tor.
Ah, don't talk nonsense.
It's all here. Everything you've
ever cared about is all right here.
There's your little toy candy shop.
"Through dangers untold...
and hardships unnumbered...
I tought my way here
to the castle...
beyond the Goblin City...
to take back the child
that you have stolen."
What's the matter, my dear?
Don't you like your toys?
It's all junk.
Well, what about this?
This is not junk, eh?
Yes, it is!
I have to save Toby!
My lady!
Are you all right?
Fair maiden. Thank goodness
thou art safe at last.
- Where are we?
- Sarah back.
My lady, we're almost there.
Those are the gates
to the Goblin City.
Ludo, Sir Didymus.
Let's go quickly.
We don't have much time.
- Yeah.
- Right, Ambrosious.
Forward.
You know.
Open up. Open the door.
Sir Didymus, we must go quietly.
Open up. Open up right now!
You'll wake the guard.
Quiet.
Well, let them all wake up!
I shall tight you all
to the death!
Please, Sir Didymus,
tor my sake, hush.
But of course.
For thee, anything.
- But I'm not a coward?
- No.
- And my sense ot smell is keen?
- Oh, yes.
Then I shall tight anyone
anywhere, anyplace, any time!
We know!
Now hush.
Quietly.
Ambrosious, be quiet now.
I don't see why we
have to be so quiet.
It's only a Goblin City.
I smell trouble.
Come on, Ludo.
Oh, no.
What is that?
Who goes?
Watch out!
Ambrosious, will you come here?
Come here right now!
Will you please come into the open?
You're embarrassing me.
Look out!
Get out ot there.
What are you doing?
Bombs away!
That wasn't very nice.
My turn now.
How do you drive this thing?
Drop the ax!
I'm trying.
Come here at once.
What's happened?
Where's reverse?
Get out ot there, Hoggle!
Abandon ship.
Hoggle, are you all right?
I'm not asking to be forgiven.
I ain't ashamed ot nothin' I did.
Jareth made me give you
that peach.
I don't care what you think ot me.
I told you I was a coward.
I ain't interested
in being triends.
I forgive you.
You-- You do?
And I commend you.
Rarely have I seen such courage.
You are a valiant man,
Sir Hoggle.
- I am?
- Yeah.
Hoggle and Ludo friends.
- We are?
- Yeah.
Here are your things.
Thanks for your help.
Well, what are we waiting tor?
Let's get the rat
who calls himself Jareth.
Right. Come on.
Ambrosious, it's sate now.
Nothing to be afraid of.
Your Highness!
- Your Highness, the girl--
- What?
- Who ate the peach, torgot everything.
- What of her?
She's here with the monster and Sir
Didymus and the dwarf who works tor you.
- What?
- They're on their way to the castle!
Stop her! Call out the guards.
Take the baby and hide it.
Guards!
She must be stopped.
Do something!
Come on, move. Move!
- I think we're gonna make it.
- Oh, piece ot cake.
Company, halt.
Lances ready!
Cannon, tire!
Ambrosious, turn around.
Turn about.
- Quick, this way.
- All right. Charge!
No, not that way!
You're going the wrong way!
The battle's behind us!
Ambrosious, can we please
talk about this?
Sit!
Be caretul. Okay.
Through here.
Ambrosious, stand still.
Okay, come on, guys.
Ambrosious, it you don't
turn around this second...
I will never feed you again.
That's better.
Don't worry, Ambrosious.
I think we've got them surrounded.
Didymus! Where's Didymus?
Fire!
I hit something, yes? No?
We've got to tind Didymus.
Down this way.
Charge!
Tallyho!
Ambrosious, you coward.
Quick, in here.
How's Ludo gonna get in?
You in there,
you're surrounded!
Surrounded?
Get out!
Ludo, hold the roof!
- Take that!
- Hungry?
Ambrosious, unlock this door.
So, had enough, have you?
Then throw down your weapons,
and I'll see that you're well-treated.
Next time, surrender.
Good griet!
Steady, men.
Steady, men. Hold your ground.
Okay, I take it back.
Run tor your lives!
I've had enough!
I'm going to bed.
Get out ot my house!
Whoa, Nellie! Duck!
Missed!
Okay, come on.
Fire!
Hey, I just tired you.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
This way.
Now we have you!
And now you don't.
Hey, no problem.
- Sir Didymus!
- Coming!
Hi-ho, Silver!
- Whoa, boy. Whoa, big fella.
- This way.
Steady, boy.
Ah, yes. Up we go. Up, up.
Come on. Good boy.
Come on.
No.
Good boy. Come on.
-That's the only way he could have gone.
-Well, then, come on.
- I have to f ace him alone.
- But why?
Because that's the way it's done.
Well, it that is the way
it is done...
then that is the way
you must do it.
But should you need us--
Yes, should you need us--
I'll call.
Thank you, all of you.
How you've turned my world
You precious thing
You starve and near exhaust me
Everything I've done
I've done for you
I move the stars for no one
You've run so long
You've run so far
Your eyes can be so cruel
Just as I can be so cruel
Though I do believe in you
Toby!
Yes, I do
Live without your sunlight
Love without your heartbeat
l, I can't live
Within you
Toby!
Give me the child.
Sarah, beware.
I have been generous up until now,
and I can be cruel.
Generous?
- What have you done that's generous?
- Everything!
Everything that you have wanted,
I have done.
You asked that the child be taken.
I took him.
You cowered before me.
I was frightening.
I have reordered time.
I have turned the world
upside-down...
and I have done it all for you.
I am exhausted trom living up
to your expectations of me.
Isn't that generous?
Through dangers untold
and hardships unnumbered...
I have fought my way here to the castle
beyond the Goblin City.
For my will
is as strong as yours...
- and my--
- Stop. Wait.
Look, Sarah.
Look what I'm otfering you.
Your dreams.
And my kingdom as great--
I ask for so little.
Just let me rule you...
and you can have everything
that you want.
Kingdom as great?
Damn.
I can never remember that line.
Just fear me, love me,
do as I say...
and I will be your slave.
My kingdom as great--
You have no power over me.
Toby.
Here you are.
I'd like Lancelot
to belong to you now.
We're home.
Sarah, are you home?
Yeah. Yes, I'm home.
Good-bye, Sarah.
Remember, f air maiden...
should you need us--
Yes, should you need us...
tor any reason at all--
I need you, Hoggle.
You do?
I don't know why, but...
every now and again
in my lite...
tor no reason at all,
I need you.
All of you.
You do?
Well, why didn't you say so?
- Oh, Ludo!
- Sarah.
Ambrosious,
good boy, good boy.
I say, does anyone here
want to play a game ot Scrabble?
- You remind me of the babe.
- What babe?
- The babe with the power.
- What power?
The power of voodoo. You do.
- Do what?
- Remind me of the babe.
- Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
- Heard about a place today
l, I'm underground
Nothing ever hurts again
- Heard about a place today
- Daddy, get me out of here
Where nothing ever hurts again
Wanna go underground
- Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
- Wanna go underground
- l, I'm underground
- Get me underground
- Sister, sister, please take me down
- Daddy, get me out of here
l, I'm underground
Wanna go underground
Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
No one can blame you
For walking away
But too much rejection
No love injection
Life can be easy
It's not always swell
Don't tell me truth hurts
little girl
'Cause it hurts like hell
But down in the underground
You'll find someone true
Down in the underground
A land serene
A crystal moon
It's only forever
Not long at all
The lost and the lonely
That's underground
Underground
- Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
- Heard about a place today
l, I'm underground
Nothing ever hurts again
- Heard about a place today
- Daddy, get me out of here
Where nothing ever hurts again
Wanna go underground
- Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
- Wanna go underground
- l, I'm underground
- Get me underground
- Sister, sister, please take me down
- Daddy, get me out of here
l, I'm underground
Wanna go underground
Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
It's only
It's only forever
It's not long at all
The lost and the lonely
That's underground
Underground
Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
Heard about a place today
- Nothing ever hurts again
Daddy, Daddy, get me out of here
Daddy, get me out of here
l, I'm underground
Wanna go underground
- Sister, sister, please take me down
- Wanna go underground
l, I'm underground
- Get me underground
- Daddy, Daddy, get me out
Wanna live underground
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org