Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
RED: Oklahoma.
They call it the "Sooner State."
So named for those early pioneers
who jumped the gun
in the Land Rush of the 1880s.
Sooners, as in, too soon.
As in, maybe they didn't exactly
follow the rules.
l say this
certainly not to pass judgement,
for my granddaddy was a sooner,
but to suggest, my friends,
the spirit that is Oklahoma,
and thereby the heart of its people.
An ambitious bunch of independent,
strong-willed survivors
who tend to live
by the principle of feast or famine.
You see, in Oklahoma,
not all legends are about victory.
Some are less obvious.
Some you don't see coming.
Some are born out of struggle.
-
lf l don't get that pump fixed,
y'all are going to have to reside
in the bathtub.
Which will not be popular
with the owner of that bathtub
because l know y'all pee in there.
All right.
Come on.
Hey, look. it’s Charley.
Hey, Charley.
What are you doing? Bathing?
You feeling lucky?
l don't know, Barrow.
-ls your mother here?
-What the hell does that mean?
Dude, with your mom?
So gross.
Shut up.
My mother?
Billy: Pansy.
He's not worth it.
Later, sucker.
Hey, there.
Hey.
The name's Red. Yours?
l'm Cal.
l couldn't help but notice
you had a little trouble here, huh?
Oh, that. You know, it's...
it happens.
Kind of an easy target.
Maybe. But you stood up to him.
Yeah.
Any special place l can drop a line?
-Well, the fish bite better on that side.
-Ah!
Yeah, yeah. All right then. Well, l'm off.
See if l can come face to face
with one of those nice fat catfish.
- Mmm!
-Mmm.
See you again.
See you later.
"Peace, my fearless friend,
"who touched so many
with his courage and heart.
"You took it far. We'll take it from here.
"Harry Newman."
-Hi, darling.
-What are you doing?
-Just waiting for you.
-What's that?
-What?
Did somebody hit you?
Tell me who, Calvin.
Why? What are you goanna do,
pop a cap in his butt?
-l could.
-Then we'd have to move.
Where would you like to move to?
North coast of Ireland, maybe?
Come here.
Bet this never happened to Mike, huh?
l was thinking
we might get some chicken tonight.
We could.
Could a third person come along?
Who?
His name is Larry Edwards.
How come l've never heard
of this Larry Edwards?
Well, he's on his way over.
You can say hi.
What does this Larry Edwards do?
He's the assistant district attorney.
Oh! That's good. That means this guy
will be paying for dinner.
-Right?
-You would think.
-Want to come?
-No. No, then he won't pay.
When you dine with the actual
district attorney, you can let me know.
There's a few things
l'd like to discuss with him.
That's my boy.
-Hey, Ma, you heard from Mike lately?
-No.
-Why?
-Just wondering.
-What's he been doing?
-l don't know.
He's on an oil rig somewhere.
Gather up the rest of the guys
and meet over at the tool shed
in about 1 0 minutes, all right? Charley!
Charley!
Listen, l'm real sorry, Mike,
but l got to let you go.
We hit TD on this one.
Basin's slow. Looks like we're going
to have to idle one of the rigs.
l'll keep your name on file
and give you a call
when we get back up to speed.
How long?
l couldn't tell you.
Right.
-Hello.
-CAL: Hello, Mrs Charley.
Hello, Studley Do-Right. How's your day?
it sucks.
l have a meeting
for the school newspaper and a late lab.
Don't say "sucks".
l'll be home when you get there.
How was dinner last night?
it sucked. Thank you for asking.
You're welcome. l'll see you later.
Uh-huh. Bye.
l'm not sure if she bought it.
Well, since you've never actually
approximated the inside of a gym,
l would wager she did.
All right, back to starting positions.
inside pummel, inside pummel.
Everybody, ready on my whistle.
Let's go. Ten seconds.
-
-inside pummel. Work it!
There you go.
Go, Barrow. Good, good, good.
Move it forward. Move it forward.
You guys ready? Ten seconds.
Keep it going. Keep it going.
Figure eight.
Figure eight. Ready, ready. Here we go.
Nice. Lock your hands on. Speed.
Lock your hands on. Speed.
Everybody, ready?
Work it, work it, work it. Forward rolls.
Last three guys, last three.
Work at it, work at it. Sit-ups,
touch-ears, and we're done. Okay?
Nicely done, fellows.
Get to the locker room.
Get your studies done tonight.
Be good, boys. See you in the morning.
LULl: l told you. Don't bunch up.
-Whoa! Yeah, dude.
-Whoa!
This is exactly like
l was expecting it to be.
Hey! Get away from that girl!
l knew that was you.
-What'd you do that for?
-Everyone knows
that you grew melons over the summer.
You don't have to show them.
-l got reasons.
-Oh!
Anyways, they like it.
Well, what's there not to like?
No, don't... Don't do that to me.
l've known you too long for that.
ls the catfish pond pump working?
Not good enough.
We're goanna lose customers.
-How much you got?
-Not enough.
Hey, Luli, if l tell you something,
-promise you won't laugh?
-No.
l want to join the wrestling team.
-What do you think?
-Do you know how?
No, but my dad was a college champion
and my brother was an all-American.
So l figure it's in the genes.
Doesn't look like it to me.
Well, l bet he could show me
a lot of things.
Who? Your brother?
You don't even know where he is.
Yeah, l do.
Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Well.
Would you wear
those little tight-fitting wrestling suits?
Yeah, l guess so.
l'd watch you.
{OPERA Music Playing
ON HEADPHONES}
SHARON: Cal!
-
-Cal.
-Hey.
Where'd you get that scale?
Donald had an extra one.
Well, l'm not getting on.
Ma,
you got nothing to worry about.
You do know what to say.
-How much do you weigh?
-1 37.
ls that good or bad?
it’s... it’s good.
l guess.
-l got to go.
-Yeah, me, too.
TENNENT: Good, good.
Keep working it.
Keep it going. Thirty seconds!
Work it! Work it!
-Hi.
What the hell?
You here to watch
or you want to get on the mat?
-l'd like to get on the mat, sir.
-Coach Tenant.
Cal Charley.
Charley?
Yes, sir.
What's your weight, Cal?
-1 35-pound class, l guess.
-1 35? All right. We're a little thin there.
Put that down. Take those off.
Follow me to the mat.
All right, ups and downs.
Ups and downs.
-Hey, Timmy, work in with coach for me.
-Yes, sir.
Barrow, l want you to work in with...
Cal, is it?
Cal, here. Half-speed.
Work in the basics.
Cal, down position.
-This is about wrestling now, right?
-Yeah, sure thing, Charley.
TENNENT: Whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey! Barrow!
What part of half-speed
didn't you understand?
-Sorry, Coach.
-Come on, help me out here.
Charley, down again.
Come on, guys. Come on.
On my whistle.
-
TENNENT: Hey, hey, hey, hey!
-TENNENT: Come on! Come on!
-BOY: Hey, hey, hey. Relax.
What, you guys have some kind
of history between you?
Yeah, Coach. l think Charley here
is interested in my mother.
Charley, are you interested
-in Barrow's mother?
-No, sir.
At least not with all her clothes on.
No. No, gravy, Ma.
No. No, thank you.
-l joined the wrestling team today.
-l knew it.
-l knew it. Damn it. Damn it!
-What?
Scale and dieting. You're wrestling.
-l just said that.
-When did this start?
l just told you. Today.
-Why are you wrestling, Calvin? Why?
-'Cause it looks like it's fun.
No, it doesn't.
-Well, Mike wrestled.
-ls that why you want to wrestle?
No, no. l was just saying Mike wrestled.
Darling, you and Mike
are two entirely different people.
What's that supposed to mean?
it... it was in his blood.
Or whatever you guys call it.
Mike needed to wrestle. it was his thing.
-You have a lot of other things going on.
-Okay, name three things.
Geology, science club,
debating, music, catfish pond.
How many more do you want?
-And if l wrestle, l can't do all that?
-No.
Why? Will it make me stupid?
Apparently,
because that was a stupid question.
Cal, l know wrestling. it’s demanding.
it will take you away from other things.
Everything else just...
Why now?
-'Cause Mike wrestled.
-l know. You already said that.
-And Dad wrestled.
-And it ate them up.
Mike also got hurt,
and he was built like a car.
You're a beanpole.
Thanks for reminding me.
Should we pretend
you're something else?
No. They have
a 1 35-pound weight class.
Have you forgotten that?
Why are you so interested
in Mike now anyway?
l don't know.
l guess, l mean, he and Dad
probably spent a lot of time together.
And what are... What are you thinking?
He's goanna... He's goanna help you?
Help you know your father?
He won't. He will just disappoint you.
You have no idea who Mike is.
He's my brother.
Right.
One you've seen maybe...
What? Once or twice in 1 0 years.
Whose fault is that?
Pump, you are a never-ending source
of mystery to me.
LULl: Who are you talking to?
No one.
-What's wrong?
-l'm just trying to get this pump fixed.
it’s driving me crazy.
l want to wrestle, Luli.
l thought you were.
-What happened?
-l told my mom about it.
-And?
-And she just about gave birth.
Mmm.
-You wearing that outfit to school today?
-Do you like it?
it’s, uh...
-it’s different.
-Good. l was aiming for different.
So, you like it, then?
Sure.
l'd love to see you wrestle.
Who're you looking for?
Mike Charley?
Yeah.
l'm Calvin. His brother. ls he here?
Mike?
Cal. Calvin.
How'd you get here?
Bus. Then l walked.
Can l use your bathroom?
it was a long ride.
-What brought you here?
-Well, l was kind of thinking
that maybe you could,
you know, show me how to wrestle?
Just... Just sometime.
l mean, l was thinking l'd try out
at 1 35 pounds.
But l don't know much.
-l don't think l'd be much good to you.
-Well, l think l could be good
with the right kind of training.
Just the basics.
in fact, l've been studying it a bit.
About leverage mostly, seems like.
You know,
just getting the right angle and...
l don't know what l'm talking about.
Why do you want to wrestle
all of a sudden?
l don't know.
Cal, l'm just real busy right now.
Coach can teach you the basics.
That's why he's there.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Maybe we could...
We could just visit once in a while.
There isn’t... There isn’t much in my life
that you're goanna want to be a part of.
l just thought
'cause we're brothers, maybe...
Not right now.
Hey, Jim.
-Hey. How are you?
-Hey.
-Can l talk to you for a minute?
-Okay.
Cal's not interested in wrestling.
l don't know. He seems eager to learn.
He's looking for Mike.
l've already lost one kid to this sport.
l don't want to go through it again.
Sharon, l doubt the sport had anything
to do with it, one way or the other.
Anyway, it's not really up to me
whether Cal wrestles or not.
There are things about Mike
you don't know. Cal doesn't know.
You know, it turns out
he wasn't as unbreakable
as everybody made him out to be.
Nobody is.
You know, if l say no to Cal,
you're just asking
for a different kind of trouble.
l'll tell you what l'll do.
How about l watch him just to make sure
he's there for the right reasons?
And if another Mike shows up
at tomorrow's practice
willing to sacrifice everything in his life
for this,
-you're going to tell him to ease off?
-Yes, l will.
-At the cost of victories?
-Trust me.
l... l don't really even know you,
but you... You better be telling the truth.
That kid is all l got.
-Sharon.
-Yeah.
How is Mike?
l don't know.
-RED: Hey, there.
-Hey.
-How's it go?
-Catch anything?
Yeah. A nice shoe bass.
Put up a hell of a struggle.
-CAL: They always do.
-Mmm.
Want to share some
of those heavy thoughts you're carrying?
l don't know.
Yeah, l guess so.
You ever wanted something,
you know, or someone,
or wanted to get someplace,
but just didn't know how?
Yeah.
l wanted to be a Western movie star
and ride off into the sunset with the girl.
Like John Wayne.
Why didn't you?
Couldn't ride a horse.
Well, yeah.
Hmm.
All right, l'll tell you.
-l want to wrestle.
-Wrestle?
Mmm-hmm.
-What's the hold-up?
-l don't think l can compete.
You ever wrestled before?
-No. Never.
-That's your problem.
it’s foreign to you.
it’s fear of the unknown, kid.
So, who's this someone
you're looking for?
Someone?
You said something or someone.
-it’s... it’s my brother.
-Oh.
So this brother has something to do
with your wanting to wrestle?
Yeah. Maybe. Why would you ask that?
Old man intuition.
Just follow your instincts. You'll be fine.
lf you use crappie instead of worms,
you might have better luck.
Thank you. Advice taken.
-
What's the matter with you?
Hold on.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER:
injury timeout.
l'm Timmy's backup.
l'm the same weight class.
l'm next in line, four nights from now.
ANNOUNCER:
Ridgecrest wins by injury default.
1 35 pounds? Right on. it’s fate, Cal.
l can't wait.
ANNOUNCER: Let's hear it
for Timmy Hughes.
WOMAN: Hello.
-Hi. ls Mike home?
-no.
-ls this Jill?
Oh. Um...
Do you know
when Mike's going to be home?
no.
All right. Well, could you leave him
a message from me?
Yeah.
Could you tell him that his brother Cal
is going to be wrestling Friday night?
Mmm-hmm.
-Okay, thanks.
-
-Hello?
Nice girl.
Okay, guys,
let's settle down and listen up.
Listen up, everybody.
Please, can l have your attention?
We're going to be starting
with 1 35 weight class.
Visitors, 1 35 pound,
step up on the scale, please.
Mark Hayes. Come on, get on the scale.
1 35 even.
-COACH: Atta boy.
-Home team, 1 35, step up, please.
TENNENT: Riverdale, that's Cal Charley.
Cal Charley. C-H-E-T-L-E-Y, Coach.
Also 1 35 even.
Home team, 140.
The first match of the night
is the 135-pound class.
For St Paul's, Mark Hayes.
And for Riverdale,
in his very first match ever,
Cal Charley.
Riverdale will be wearing red bands.
St Paul's, green.
ANNOUNCER: Winner by fall in the first
period, Mark Hayes of St Paul's.
Don't sweat it. lt'll get easier after this.
All right? You did fine. You never quit.
-Go have that looked at.
-Okay.
Good job.
What?
l got to go.
l'll call you.
l forgot to tell you, your brother called.
He said he was wrestling or something
this week.
l saw Luli at the match last night.
l'd say she is all the girl you can handle.
Luli's not my girl.
-Does she know that?
-Ma, come on.
it’s Luli.
How is Luli? Mmm?
She's going through
an interesting phase right now.
She needs a woman in her life.
Yeah. Her mom never comes
to see her any more.
She has four brothers? Wow.
Yeah.
How fun for her.
Tell her to come see me sometime.
Are you all right?
You mean,
am l going to keep wrestling?
Yeah. l guess that's what l mean.
l don't know.
Yeah.
l mean, l can't really quit.
l'm the only 1 35-pounder on the team.
And that kid was about
the best 1 35-pounder in the state,
so l figure it can't get much worse.
Hey, Mike.
Watch yourself, boss.
Problem?
-What?
-l said, do we have a problem?
-
Hey, Donald. Do you think
l'm the worst 1 35-pounder in the region?
You haven't officially wrestled
in enough matches
to be considered the worst wrestler
in the region.
According to
the State Athletic Commission.
Do l think there is anyone in the region
you can defeat before the year is over?
it’s mathematically possible.
Oh. Well, thanks for not saying no.
Hey, dingle berries.
l heard your brother used to be the man.
-Didn't help you too much, did it?
-So?
So now he's a punk.
Losers.
-Muskogee County?
-l didn't know Barrow could read.
"Mike Charley,
a 28-year-old, was arrested
"and charged with major assault."
"Repeat offender. $5,000 bail."
RED: Hello, young fellow!
Hello.
Hey, l haven't seen you in a bit.
-Yeah.
-How'd that wrestling thing turn out?
Oh, uh...
Yeah, l'm quitting. Wasn't right for it.
According to whom?
Well, l haven't won a single match.
Not surprising.
Seeing as how a month ago,
you didn't know a wrestling mat
from a bath mat.
How's that brother of yours?
He's, uh,
not really interested.
l know a little something about brothers.
l had eight of them.
lf you need your brother,
l can promise you that he needs you.
Now, he may not know it
like you know it.
But he does.
Don't give up
on that wrestling thing. Yeah.
l have a good feeling about you.
Hey.
-What are you doing?
-l need to borrow your scooter.
l'll bring it back tonight.
-Are you in trouble?
-No.
l need you to give this note
to Coach Tenant. Promise?
Yeah.
Wow, this is exciting.
l feel like we're eloping.
Yeah, except you isn’t coming.
At least kiss me goodbye.
All right.
-Thank you. l owe you one.
-l'll be collecting, too.
And it won't be on the cheek!
All right.
LAWYER: Your Honour,
my client's altercation with Mr Brock
was a reaction to
both physical and verbal taunts.
l believe Mr Charley felt
that he was fighting for his life.
in addition, he has made arrangements
to enter into alcohol rehab
and personal therapy to address
his issues with anger management.
l would ask, at this time,
that the Court allow my client
to pursue this
under the state's supervision.
Thank you, Counsel.
Mr Charley,
anything you care to add, sir?
Your Honour,
l don't go looking for trouble.
l got put in a situation,
well, l reacted the only way l know how.
You seem to have a history of that,
Mr Charley.
CAL: Your Honour. Ma'am?
Hi. May l say something on his behalf?
Tell the Court your name, please.
Calvin Charley. Mike Charley’s brother.
Step forward. Please.
My dad died when l was young.
And my mom works a lot.
But Mike sort of took the place of my dad
after he passed on.
And he teaches me a lot of things
that my mom can't.
Your brother is in a lot of trouble.
You do realise that, don't you?
Yes. Yes, ma'am, l do.
But l think that sometimes
guys come after Mike
'cause they see him
as some kind of a target.
And he and l have this deal, right,
where l will go out with him
and l'll always step in
if any kind of trouble starts
so he can just walk away.
l just... l wasn't there this time.
Your Honour,
l'm goanna give you my word
that you won't see either one of us
in your courtroom ever again.
l need Mike.
We kind of carry each other.
He's all l got.
-You hungry?
-Yes.
l'm really hungry. Yeah.
What do you want?
l don't know. it’s been a lot of years.
l meant what do you want to eat?
Oh!
Okay. Um...
Sorry, l...
l don't know. l'm kind of having trouble
with my weight.
You know, keeping it down.
Thanks. Actually, l'm starving.
You know, Mike,
l don't want anything from you.
l just want to know you.
Cal, l been alive 28 years.
l just couldn't tell you much
about the last eight or so.
-What happened?
-l don't know.
One day Dad was there
and we had a plan. And then...
Well, then he wasn't.
Luli? Hey! l was hoping to catch you.
-Hey, Mrs Charley.
-Your old scooter finally quit?
Well, it isn’t been running too good.
That's for sure.
You wouldn't happen to know
where Cal is, would you?
-Wrestling practice, l imagine.
-No.
No. l went by the gym on my way home.
-Hmm?
-Mmm?
Yeah. He got up
awful early this morning.
Too early.
-He does like to study.
-Yes, he does.
And you're not a very good liar, darling.
Well, ma'am, l only had two ways to go.
Lie to you
or break a promise to my best friend.
Fair enough. l'm just worried about him.
One thing l know about Cal is
he'll be all right.
lf that helps.
Okay. l appreciate that.
Come by sometime. We'll do girl things.
l'd like that, ma'am.
So l won the geology essay competition
and used the winnings
to build a catfish farm.
it makes me a little bit of money
when l can actually keep it running.
Mostly l just like to go out there
and think.
Mom know you're here?
No. No, she doesn't know l'm here.
So l should probably go.
How is she?
She's... She's okay.
l think she wishes she had girls.
She misses you.
Cal, l stayed away
because...
You want me to teach you
how to wrestle?
No. No, Mike, you've got a lot going on.
it’s not that important.
Yes, l would love it
if you'd teach me to wrestle.
-l'll do the best l can.
-Me, too.
Where have you been?
Nowhere.
Just hanging out with friends.
What is this place?
Church.
You ready?
-Hey!
-Okay.
Three parts to become
a complete wrestler.
Offence, defence, and psychology.
We'll talk psychology later.
Today we're goanna work on speed.
Leverage. Knowledge and strength.
Okay.
We're goanna have to build yours.
Oh! He's back. Drinks all around.
What, did you take
a little vacation, Charley?
You wish.
Funny.
No one seemed to notice you missing.
-Why'd you bring it up then?
-Cal, l need you right now.
The rest of you circle up.
Get started on your own.
Hey, circle them up. Let's go.
Cal, we had to forfeit the match
because of you.
Now, l give each one of my wrestlers
one shot to save their ass
before l toss them from the team.
This is your shot.
l had to help my brother with something.
Screw up again and you're done.
-Do we understand each other?
-Yes, sir.
All right.
Now get out there with the rest of them.
Thank you, sir.
Lebrowski, l see you.
it’s called a watch. Get one.
Cal, get up.
Back straight. Back straight.
Move with your back straight.
That's where you get your strength.
And when you circle...
Look at my left leg.
Don't take your eyes off it. Look at it.
And when you're ready
to make your move,
halfway through, switch to the right.
Tie me up with the right.
With your right leg on mine,
you keep me from panning out,
-and take me down. You understand?
-Yeah.
Here.
So the next time, you actually
shoot for the leg you're looking at.
Or maybe you don't.
Maybe you don't look at all.
You just keep coming and juke it.
Knowledge.
-You learn quick.
-You teach quick.
Hey, l read you once pinned a guy
with a reverse cradle in a close match.
Yeah, reverse cradle.
That's not a move you want to shoot for,
especially against a wrestler
who is any good.
it’s an easy way to get pinned
if you don't know what you're doing.
-How does it work?
- Easy, bud.
Let's learn to walk
before we can run, okay?
Yeah.
Hey, did you get a job yet?
-No.
-l got you one.
Through my geology class.
l know some guys
at Sooner Pipe Works.
They can get you off the rigs, you know.
Put you in a truck.
Servicing the online wells.
Money isn’t bad. it’s pretty steady.
-l isn’t out of line about that, am l?
- No. No, l just...
l isn’t used to getting that kind of help.
What was it like working with Dad?
l tell you, man. it wasn't work.
it just seemed like Dad always knew
what to do with me.
Yeah.
-You finish your homework?
-Yep.
-Want to do mine?
-No.
Nice hiney.
Thank you. Speaking of hineys,
my mom wants you to stop by.
-Your mom wants to see my hiney?
-She didn't say.
All right. Tell me about your opponent
for tomorrow.
He's five and five.
l've never seen him before,
but he lost to a kid
who beat me 11 to two.
All right.
You know, Mom's probably
goanna be there tomorrow.
Good.
Are you goanna talk to her?
Cal, l never said anything
about going to meets.
-You understand.
-No, l don't understand.
There's goanna be a lot of folks
in that gym.
They're goanna want to talk to me
about what l've been doing lately.
instead of those trophies
l won ten years ago.
That's including Mom.
Tomorrow's about you.
l'm not going to get in the way
of your match.
-When are you going to talk to Mom?
- That's not why we're here.
No, l... l know.
Psychology.
1 29 and a half. Step down, please.
The first time you see your opponent
is the weigh-in.
Official: Next weight class, 135.
Claremore?
Step on, please.
MIKE: Look right through him.
Like he doesn't exist.
it’s a confidence game.
Somehow you are going to instil fear.
Official: 1 34 and a half.
Step down, please.
-Riverdale?
-TENNENT: Charley.
MIKE: You're thinking one thing.
That your girlfriend
is in the front seat of his car,
and if you lose,
she's going home with him.
And you think that over and over again.
You let it burn,
because it will show in your eyes.
TENNENT: Charley.
Step on, please.
You do it right,
sometimes they pee themselves.
-
-Yeah.
Mike: There's one more thing.
You got to weigh in naked.
Naked?
Well...
it’s... Trust me. it’s uncomfortable.
But it makes them more uncomfortable.
Because it shows you're proud
and it shows you've got nothing to fear.
1 35 even. Step down, please.
140?
Mike: After that,
you find a spot in that gym.
That's your spot. Your space.
You go there. Bring music with you.
Music you love.
Music that gets into your soul.
You do all those things
and that's going to give you the edge.
Okay.
All right.
Do it, Cal!
ANNOUNCER: Final score, 7-5
in favour of Cal Charley.
Team score.
Riverdale, 12. Claremore, 9.
That was Cal Charley’s first win ever
in a Riverdale uniform.
Let's hear it for our 135-pounder.
Pull it in.
You got speed? Let's see it!
-Yeah, l got speed!
-Show-off!
Mike: We're goanna pick it up a bit
for regional’s.
-More time?
- No.
-A better use of the time.
-How?
Well, you've got that week off
for spring break.
Eleven days till they start.
That's enough time to get serious.
-Serious?
- Yeah.
Serious enough to show me
the reverse cradle?
No.
You know, a good friend
wouldn't eat those in front of me.
Don't watch.
So we going to the dance together?
-Might be working.
-What?
Yes, l'm taking you to the dance.
What are you wearing?
l haven't really thought about it yet.
And dare l ask what you're wearing?
it’s a surprise.
Well, is it legal?
l'm making it.
Well, that's encouraging.
Luli, you're not still showing the boobs,
are you?
You're looking good on that mat, Calvin.
You actually look like
you know what you're doing.
Yep.
Can l talk to you for a minute?
it depends
on what you want to talk about.
l just want you to know
l'm proud of you for getting out there.
-But?
-But nothing.
l wish it were golf, but it's not. So...
Just know l'm goanna be there for you.
-Okay.
-No matter what.
l'm goanna be there for you.
You got to know that.
Just don't let it push you too far, please.
Mom, l'm having fun.
One day when we're older
and sitting in rocking chairs,
l want you to describe to me,
in a way l can understand,
how wrestling is fun.
Okay.
Hey.
Practice ends about 4:30
every day, right?
Mmm-hmm.
So what exactly do you do
for the next few hours?
l just, you know, jog.
Work on the weights. Go to lab.
Okay.
Well, it must be working. You look good.
-Hi!
-Hey.
Shit. Howdy! Who are you?
His name's Theo Henderson.
He's a big-time tiny wrestler.
We call him The Gnat.
He's the smallest guy l could find.
-it’s nice to meet you.
-What's up, man?
-How much do you weigh?
-About 145.
-Each leg?
-
Mike: Come on, come on, spin! Get it!
Switch!
Come on, Cal! Let's go!
Let's go! Beat him!
This is kind of like
that Extreme Makeover show.
Minus the boob job.
No one's ever done anything like this
for me before.
You're goanna be the belle of the ball,
Miss Luli.
-What are you wearing?
-Something l made myself.
-You do that?
-Oh, yeah.
l make sure l accentuate some areas
more than others.
How about some girl-to-girl advice?
Mmm?
Well, that would be a first.
Scotch over.
Don't sell the whole package
at one time. Give them small hints.
Keep them guessing as long as you can.
And then keep them guessing
a little more.
Let them know you have other options.
Be confident. Don't chase. Be chased.
l wish.
Well, this helps.
-Miss Charley?
-Yes?
How old were you
when you first kissed a guy?
-Thirty-two.
-What the hell?
l was 1 6.
l guess.
Was it Cal's dad?
No. But it got his attention.
He was second.
-Were you chasing?
-No.
Sort of directing.
That's what l'm talking about.
-GNAT: Good kid.
-Yeah.
He seems to know
where he's going, man.
Where have you been, Mike?
Look, l don't hear from you
for l don't know how long,
and then out of the blue?
l don't know.
You broke one of your golden rules.
You stopped moving.
You're up now. You look good.
Stay up. Keep moving.
There's your reason.
l don't know, man.
Sometimes it isn’t that simple.
Cal?
Come on.
Get down.
All right.
The reason the reverse cradle
is such a risk
is you got to trick your opponent
into thinking you're done. Okay?
-Okay.
-All right. Now, listen.
lf l know you're stalling,
l'm going for a pin.
You're goanna ball up.
So when you ball up,
l've got to press you
to flatten you out. Right?
So, l'll press you and my head will
come over your shoulder.
You see it come over
for the second time.
You got a moment.
You got to grab a headlock.
Grab it. Right there. Okay, good.
You got to roll to your shoulders,
hook a leg, and squeeze.
Roll, hook and squeeze. Go.
Lock it! Good.
Reverse cradle. No escape.
Don't mess with me.
-You want a piece of me?
-Oh, my God.
Shit howdy, you want to go?
Check it out, man.
-Now the party's started.
-Yeah.
That was nice, Cal.
You hungry?
Yeah.
BAND LEADER: Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
We are going to pick it up a little
for you guys.
# Cross l am a laying
on a wagon train... #
Hey, String fellow?
Will five bucks
get me a little private showing?
Come on, babe. l'm the only kid here
who hasn't been down Boob Boulevard.
-Sounds like a personal problem.
-Barrow, walk away.
Come on, Luli. l'm a big spender.
-Hey!
-You pervert!
-What the hell are you thinking?
-Hey, get off me!
-
-What, Charley?
What are you goanna do?
BOY: Let's go!
You all right?
Come on. Let's go.
Are you okay?
Get off me, man!
Why does stuff like this
always happen to me?
Because you're Luli.
You bring it on yourself.
-l hate myself.
-No, you don't.
Just stop trying so hard.
You're like a butterfly in a windstorm.
Meaning what?
Meaning...
l don't know what it means. it means...
it means you're special, l guess.
No, it doesn't.
They just don't like me.
They don't know you.
But you go about it the wrong way.
l think that if they knew you,
if they really knew you,
they'd like you.
l do.
Hey.
You really look nice tonight.
Thank you.
Hey. Come here.
-Hey, Mike. it’s been a while.
-Hey.
So, what are you drinking?
-Whatever's on tap is fine.
-You got it.
Here you go.
l don't want to do this, man.
l don't think you've got
a whole lot of choice in the matter.
Hello?
What?
Where?
l... l can't understand you.
Cal?
Was that Mike?
Why is he calling you?
What did he say?
l don't know. He's drunk.
No, he's not drunk.
He's in jail!
That's bullshit, Mom. He's not drunk.
How would you know?
Cal, how would you know?
Because l see him every day!
That's how l know!
We've been working on the mat
every day for the last month.
He hasn't had one drink the whole time,
so something happened.
-A month?
-Yes, a month!
And that's where you've been?
How else do you think
l've won anything, Mom?
Coach Tenant.
He's working with two dozen
different wrestlers, Mom! Come on!
How and where did you find Mike?
in his house. it’s not that hard
if you're really looking for him.
Stop it. That's not what l'm asking you.
This is me you're talking to!
You've never kept anything
from me before.
You've just spent more time with Mike
in the past month
than l have in the past ten years!
And you don't even know him
and you don't think l should know?
l didn't want it to go wrong.
-What?
-Mike.
-Why?
-Because...
Because he's my brother.
l have the right to know my own brother.
What did the two of you
talk about? Huh?
Wrestling.
That's it?
Work and school.
it’s not like we talk about the wives
or kids or our favourite colours.
l mean, l don't even know him
that well, do l?
That's not fair, Cal.
l was afraid of you and Mike together.
-Why?
-Mike is
unpredictable.
l became afraid of him. l...
l didn't know how to help him.
But you're the best friend l've ever had.
What exactly happened in the car?
Mmm.
Your dad and Mike
were headed to Eufaula
to scout one of Mike's opponents.
That's what they did.
These guys were prepared, Cal.
But there was...
There was heavy snow, ice.
Mike was thrown from the car.
Mac wasn't.
l begged them not to go.
Dad knew Mike
could take this other kid, but...
And he didn't think
they needed to go, but...
But Mike pushed it.
l remember him throwing
your dad's words back in his face.
"Take no opponent for granted."
So Mac did what he always did.
He kept his word.
Did Mike quit wrestling after that?
No. No. He got hurt a year later. But...
He really gave up
the night your dad died.
He blamed himself for Mac's death.
l think maybe...
What?
l was...
Cal, l was so lost.
l was so devastated.
And l didn't know it at the time.
But l... l blamed him, too.
And Mike felt it.
l was 1 8 when Mike was born.
Your dad and l were just kids.
He was my first.
And your first is always your baby.
l mean, you were an adult
when you came out.
l had to ask for your lD.
Then l lost both of them.
Ma, you said
that Mike blamed himself
for Dad's being killed?
l mean, did anybody ever tell him
it wasn't his fault?
l think everybody in here has a shot
at the medal round this weekend.
All right, the next couple of days,
we're goanna show them
what we're made of.
Let's get it in our heads
right now. Okay?
l'll see you guys in the morning.
Bus leaves at 7:30 sharp. Be here.
Let's get our hands in here.
Tornadoes on three.
One, two, three.
ALL: Tornadoes!
Something told me l should be here.
Why now?
Cal.
He believes in you.
And he was right.
A friend in the DA's office,
a guy l dated for about 20 minutes,
ran down the waitress
where you were arrested.
She'll testify you didn't take a drink
and you didn't start the fight.
l talked with your parole officer.
Cal needs you, Mike.
it scares you, doesn't it?
Yes.
This scares me.
But Cal really wants you
to be there for him.
And l want you to be there.
For Cal.
You know, Mike?
l've tracked you over three states.
And not a day goes by that l don't think
maybe this is the day you'll show up.
And l'm listening to Cal tell me
that you two wrestle, that you talk!
And l'm thinking, "l want that."
l want... l want my son back!
But l still don't know how!
Let's get you out of here.
LULl: Hey, Cal? Calvin?
ANNOUNCER: With that win,
Riverdale's Cal Charley
moves into the 135-pound semi-finals.
What the hell?
You don't belong here.
-Maybe l do.
-No, you don't.
No.
For all the goodness your dad brought
to your life, l don't believe
he ever taught you how to accept loss.
it was always about showing up
prepared.
l need you to show up.
Maybe l'm not right for Cal.
it’s like you said,
l just don't think l know how to lose.
You do now.
This may sound simple,
but that boy waiting for you
hasn't experienced the pain
we've been through.
l can't
breathe sometimes.
Because in my heart,
l know l blamed you at a time
when l should have been protecting you.
And l never made it right.
l am so sorry.
l'm your mother, but l was...
l was choking on my grief and my anger.
But, baby, we have to somehow
put Mac to rest.
Yeah.
l think that's what Cal is trying to do.
He's...
He's trying to help us.
Dad, he made me feel invincible. l just...
l couldn't pull him from the car.
Cal... Cal is...
ls trying to pull you out.
Let him.
Was l right?
it seems that you were.
ls he out now?
Yeah.
Beyond that,
l'm not sure.
Hopefully, he's working some things out.
How'd you do?
l'm still in it.
Good for you.
Now, go wrestle.
When you show up, things happen.
l know that's what Dad would say.
-You coming?
-l'll be there.
All right.
ANNOUNCER: Welcome to Tulsa
and day two of the
Oklahoma District Three Championship.
All coaches report
to the director's table by 10:00.
Jesuits, Lugats,
report to the scores table at mat two.
Do you know anything about Leonard?
Well, from what l hear,
he puts his pants on one leg at a time.
ANNOUNCER: All wrestlers
begin clearing the mats at this time.
135-pound semi-final match.
Hayes versus Rayber.
Red.
What are you doing here?
Well, rumour has it,
you won some matches yesterday.
Yeah.
-Where you going?
-Oh, uh...
l'm done.
l didn't want this. l was
looking for something else.
You sure about that?
Took a lot of courage to come this far.
You made something happen.
Now, l hear you're two matches away
from a district title.
l'd say that's time pretty well spent.
How come you always seem to know
what to say?
Sometimes these things
take time to work out.
But no one's asking you to win, Cal.
Just don't quit.
Hey, l'm going to grab a cup of coffee,
head inside and get a seat.
Looking forward to your match.
ANNOUNCER: Winner,
Mark Hayes, by decision.
Second semi-finals, 135-pound class.
John Leonard, North Shore,
versus Cal Charley of Riverdale.
Leonard versus Charley, centre mat.
-Hey, where've you been?
-Just wandering.
-Come on. You ready?
-Yeah.
All right, listen. Two minutes at a time.
Listen for me. Get out there.
Charley in the red anklet.
Leonard in the green.
LULl: Give him cauliflower ear!
Come on, Cal! You can do it!
-
You're okay! You're all right!
You're all right! You're all right!
TENNENT: Pace!
LULl: Come on, Cal!
ANNOUNCER: After one period,
Leonard leads Charley, five to two.
All right.
You're good. You're good. You're good.
Come on!
All right.
Get him!
Yeah, yeah. Come on, get in!
Come on! Pick it up! Pick it up!
Damn it. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, Cal!
Take him down!
-
ANNOUNCER: Winner, Charley,
Riverdale High School,
-by injury default.
-
Who taught you the guillotine?
l've been doing a little homework
on my own.
Well, that was textbook wrestling.
You showed a lot of character out there,
kid, no two ways about it.
Rest up. l'll come back and get you.
-Hey, good to see you, Mike.
-You, too, Coach.
-Hey, it's been a long time.
-Too long.
The smell of the mat
never leaves you, though.
Yeah. Listen, you're welcome
to take the coach's seat next to me
when he's up next, if you want.
-l'd like that.
-Good. l recognise the Charley spirit.
Hey, in about an hour,
l'll come back and get the both of you.
Okay.
-Everything all right?
-Yeah!
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
l had a little help.
Mom?
Okay, remember, Cal.
You're not me. You're not Dad.
You got to wrestle your own way.
Use your opponent's momentum
against him.
Use them long legs, damn it.
it’s your best weapon.
Okay.
-You got your music.
-Right here.
-You got 1 0 minutes. What you got?
-Opera.
What?
it’s like Italian opera.
Who are you?
Never mind, we're doing it your way.
-Crank it up and take it in.
-Okay.
Opera.
This is a good day.
You know our boy listens to opera?
l want you to know you are everything
Cal described, only better-looking.
-l'm Luli.
-Hi, Luli.
Could you give this to Cal
before this last match?
it’s real important.
l sure will. What is this, a Volkswagen?
Hey, Shaquille O'Neal.
That was horrible.
-What's this?
-This is a heavy present
from somebody named Luli.
"Here's your edge.
"l love you. Lu."
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
-A pump. Now that's romantic.
it is if you know Luli.
What the hell's this?
Wow!
That's Luli, too.
Hey, give us one more, kid.
We're all out there.
-l will.
-Cal.
You're already a medallist.
Let's go out as number one.
Okay.
What the hell?
Damn, Coach!
l hope the fire marshal
doesn't shut us down.
You know that guy?
That's Dad's coach.
Red is Dad's coach?
Red? That's Harry.
-Harry?
-Harry Newman.
"Peace, my fearless friend,
"who touched so many
with his courage and heart.
"You took it far. We'll take it from here.
"Harry Newman."
That guy's Harry Newman?
You know him?
Yeah. Through fishing, mostly.
ANNOUNCER: And now,
our 135-pound finalist...
Dad's here.
...representing St Paul's
with a dual meet record of 23 and 0,
Mark Hayes.
And representing Riverdale High School
with a dual meet record of five and six,
Calvin Charley.
Charley in the red. Hayes in the green.
And please welcome back
to the tournament,
past all-American nCAA finalist
and three-time state champion,
Mike Charley.
REFEREE: Here we go!
Get around him. You got to get
around him, boy. Come on now!
Get him, Cal!
Let's go.
He's setting it up.
Come on! Come on!
-TENNENT: Yes! He's out!
-Come on. Cinch it, Cal! Cinch it!
Get him!
Mike: Come on!
Go, baby. Buckle up.
TENNENT: Yes!
Mike: Come on, come on!
Squeeze it, Cal! Squeeze it!
Cal! Squeeze it! Squeeze it!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Cal, pin him!
Come on! Cinch it, Cal! Cinch it!
Come on.
Get him, Cal!
Come on!
Cal, come on! Pin him!
TENNENT: Come on! Come on!
MALE SPECTATOR: Charley!
FEMALE SPECTATOR: Cal!
ANNOUNCER: Mark Hayes,
winner by decision.
Final score. Hayes, 11 . Charley, nine.
RED: Like l said,
not all legends are about victory.
Some are about struggle,
finding out who you are
and your reason for being.
Big Mac Charley died
before he had a chance to finish the job.
That was his greatest fear,
that Sharon and the boys
would struggle on without him.
-You got heart, kid.
-Thanks.
-You thought l was done, didn't you?
-Yeah, l did.
RED: He once asked me,
if anything were to happen to him,
that l might help keep an eye
on the boys.
Mac, your boys are fine.
so is your girl
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org