In the year of Our Lord 1123,
King Louis vl, known as "The Fat",
waged war against his cousin,
Henry I, King of England
and Duke of Normandy.
Many brave knights fought beside him.
They believed in God
and the forces of Evil.
Your Majesty,
time is of the essence.
Need I remind you
we are in their camp?
Silence, Montmirail.
Love knows not haste!
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Sire Godefroy!
The English!
My vassal sees
horsemen approaching.
We are coming.
I beg of you, Your Majesty,
make haste!
Adieu, my sweet.
I must join my men.
Will I see you soon?
When my cousin,
the King of England, makes amends.
Do you love me, Kathleen?
Then accord me one last favor,
should I die.
- Hush hush...
- show me your ankles.
I beseech thee, lady-love.
Higher. Up to your knees.
My God! How beautiful!
Sire...
they're coming.
Come, sire.
THE vlslTORs
This way.
King! I capture thee!
Let me, my King!
Liar!
The King is never captured.
Not even in chess.
Toil! Never recoil!
Sound the horns! The King!
Master! You're alive!
God be praised!
I managed to save
your horse and your arms.
You managed to flee, as usual.
Castrated clod!
Sire Godefroy,
The King summons you.
Castrated clod!
Sires... the King!
My kind knight Godefroy
merits indeed
his name "The Hardy".
His baldrick was nary stuckolded.
With his sword,
he yslaked a scurvy English head.
Godefroy Amaury de Malfete,
Count of Montmirail,
of Apremont, and of Popincourt
I shall thus reward your valor.
Sire, I am your eternal servant.
I know you desire descendants.
You have one week to fetch
one of the fairest
Wenches in the Kingdom:
The daughter of the Duke of Puglia.
I know you adore her.
She is yours to wed.
How can I thank thee?
To serve my King is my Honor.
Long live the King!
- Who is he?
- Jacquasse the Crass.
My vassal.
He should be waiting outside.
He lacks grace, but he sniffs out
a trail like a good hound.
We must avoid the Forest of Malcombe,
and pass by Montargis.
Avoid the forest?
You know it's haunted, sire.
No one dares penetrate it.
Hogwash!
My betrothed must not wait!
What about the witch of Malcombe?
Ride ahead of The Crass.
She can turn an army into frog vomit.
At her touch, your skin spits pus.
And you pisseth mud.
She can damn 7 generations.
We're doomed!
Doomed!
Per Ansia
Queribus Memorium
"Halt or becometh a slug."
It's Latin and visigoth.
The Devil's drool!
A Black sabbath.
Let's splitteth!
What does she want?
To make that old hag
young again. It's impossible!
Drink! Drink!
Where is she?
Fear not.
She'll drop back in.
What a blast to have
a virgin's unpolluted body again!
She's plug-ugly!
Just like the day I married her!
It's devildom!
Surrender, she-Devil!
We'll dismember her
and slice out her tongue.
Let rats gnaw on her innards.
No lady is tortured on my lands.
Just burn her.
Thank you, sire.
Thank you. You are too good!
At last... my castle.
Unpack our best apparels
to honor my beloved.
Jacquasse, help me change.
Yes, sire.
I have no fine apparels.
She won't even see you.
My shoes and my fanciest shell.
Ganelon, sound the horn
to announce my arrival.
How thrilled am I, sire Fulbert,
that my son weddeth your sweet
and gentle daughter.
I wanted her to weddeth a Duke,
but our Fat King decided otherwise.
Cursed be love.
More wine!
Let me piss a-plenty!
Father, you promised
nary to burp for my marriage.
The Count of Montmirail!
Frenegonde! Where are you going?
Frenegonde! Come back!
Come back this instant!
No Duke's daughter runs after
a mere Count.
You look good and gentle.
And mighty uncomfortable.
Why?
Zounds!
The flask falleth all alone.
Give it to me.
My thirst needs a-quenching!
The castle!
Holy scrotums!
It swelleth like a blowfish!
It's wearing a wig!
Sire Godefroy, are you not well?
By what devil-craft?
What's wrong?
Come back, you wicked wench!
Come back!
Come back, you foul slut!
God shield!
A bear is chasing her!
My crossbow!
Come back!
There's no bear.
Steer clear, beloved!
Steer clear!
Father!
I saw a huge beast.
I'll spend my life in a convent,
faithful to you.
I can ne'er wed
the man who killed my father.
I understand, my betrothed.
I'll be faithful too.
I shall ne'er marry...
ne'er have descendants.
Don't do me any favors.
What are you up to?
I Was praying for his salvation.
Where is my father's wizard?
Eusaebius?
I found him.
He lives yonder,
not far from here.
But they say he's senile.
I can make your Duke live again.
But you must know
no fear.
Only God can do that!
You are right.
Only God can bring back the dead.
But there is another way.
Time is a mountain,
pierced by many hidden tunnels.
My magic spells can
give you access to them.
Meet Angueran.
Scarface Angueran.
At your service.
And my loyal Ganelon.
You shall return
just before the Duke's death.
If you find
enough force in yourself...
you will be able
to change the course of the arrow.
You'll wed your betrothed,
and have the lineage you desire.
It's sheer lunacy!
Where is my powder of leech?
I haven't done this in ages.
I'm a bit rusty.
He's senile!
Here it is.
If you fear not,
Godefroy the Hardy, drink.
You'll arrive in the forest
just before the accident.
Don't trust the old fool!
If sire Godefroy doesn't return,
We'll lock you in his dungeon
With your Book of spells.
Trust me.
Don't drink it, sire.
You'll turn into a frog,
or a bat, or a goat,
or a nun's ass.
Perhaps you're right.
Drink first.
Me?
I'll see if you
turn into a nun's ass.
If you do, I'll seek revenge.
Drink!
So, my Crass?
It tastes like pig excrement.
Candied concoctions
are for evil sorcerers.
Drink hastily.
I must say the incantation.
If I drank...
am I going too?
Say the incantation.
They've gone into
the Tunnels of Time!
What's that noise?
What did you step on?
Rotten eggs.
I forgot the quail eggs.
What a catastrophe!
Stand up, peasant.
Where are We?
And our friends?
This isn't my Forest.
The wizard misled us!
We have tWo legs, sire.
And tWo arms.
'Tis miracle enough.
Fetch me a horse.
Make haste!
Pugh! It stinketh!
He's crazy!
Sire! A Moor!
A Moor in the Devil's chariot!
'Tis metal,
With no oxen to pull it!
Sire, come see!
Thither, sire! Thither!
They're psychos.
Psychos!
Whose shield is this?
Lord our Father, We have sinned.
We'll bear this ordeal
to the end.
Give us the courage never to recoil.
We Will obey Thee.
Amen.
It stinketh.
We can't breathe! We're doomed!
No, I smell victuals.
More diabolic chariots!
Let's stay in the Forest.
No!
We can't fight on an empty belly.
Two burgers!
French fries and ketchup!
Yo guys!
Is it Halloween?
You're dressed to go trick or treating!
Silence, strumpet.
Take this and go your way.
Leave us be.
Holy Moses!
Are you Tv stars?
Shove off! Shove off!
I don't want to impose,
Ladies and Gents,
but since you're in show-biz,
do you know any... big-time agents?
Quiet, peasant,
or I'll smacketh you.
It just so happens
I studied song and dance.
If you could get me an audition,
it'd change my life.
What's wrong?
I'm no Worse than Madonna!
Let us leave this vile baWd.
Listen...
still hanging around, sticky fingers?
Give back the steaks!
Watch out!
I'm a political refugee!
I'm sick of your shenanigans!
Ho! Innkeeper!
You hit the fairer sex?
What the hell do
these two clowns want?
This isn't a hobo hideout!
I am Godefroy of Montmirail,
Count of Apremont
and of Popincourt.
And I lord over my property.
Mr. Vautrot! Help!
Call the cops!
The bag lady's bothering Roger again!
Murderer!
Come on, toots!
This guy is gun crazy!
Attack, sire!
On your knees, punk!
Montjoie! St. Denis!
Jacquasse! My Jacquasse!
Easy does it, hot stuff.
Attack!
Montjoie!
Asylum!
Father, I beseech
the right to asylum.
Mi... Mi, honey.
That's it.
Keep on practicing, love.
I'll be right back.
Hello, Countess? It's Father Herve.
Hello, Father.
Yes, well...
My mass was interrupted...
by a hooligan
dressed in a very peculiar way.
He claims to be
the Count of Montmirail etc, etc...
Quite frankly, he seems off his rocker.
The Count of Montmirail?
Daddy died in '81.
I know, Beatrice. I buried him. This one
claims to be called "The Hardy".
He has your family arms on his tunic.
Godefroy the Hardy?
How absurd.
Come quickly.
He looks ornery.
Hello? Hello?
Father Herve?
What is this?
It's the UNICEF calendar.
Hurry!
He's busy praying. He saw today's date
and went into a state of shock.
He claims to be born in 1076.
He's a crackpot.
My betrothed.
You are here?
Frenegonde!
My beautiful Frenegonde!
Stop!
That totally hurts!
Calm down, you brute!
It is I.
Stop. I don't know you.
Frenegonde.
The Countess doesn't know you.
You've made a mistake.
Cease, Father.
Dare I understand?
This fair dame is not my beloved,
but my descendant.
1000 years betwixt us.
Yes. I have to go.
I don't know him from Adam.
I'm from the time of Louis vl.
Help me.
Shall I call for help?
No, this very nice man
Won't harm us.
Will 50 francs do?
I must return to my time.
Know'st thou a wizard?
No. Sorry, no wizard.
I know the wizard of Oz.
Where is this "Oz"?
Don't budge.
We'll take care of you.
Thank you, my sweet.
It's a miracle.
Okay, call the police.
- It's not very Christian.
- Of course it is.
Pugh! How ugly!
Without them,
We couldn't Watch Tv. Here...
Just what the doc ordered.
Thanks, bawd. You're ugly as sin,
but good-hearted.
Ever see your nose?
When you sneeze,
is it typhoon season?
Your wine is fruity,
but a tad watery.
The wine's mine, swine.
What a raunchy eater!
You eat the plastic too?
The wizard was senile.
If I catch him,
I'll skin him alive.
Don't take it so bad.
Those pigs always get us.
Is your buddy a wrestler?
I saw him on Tv.
I wanted to be a singer...
but they're all
full of shit in show-biz.
My sire is a warrior,
a trusted aide of our King.
The Count of Montmirail.
Montmirail?
The dentist's old lady?
He couldn't marry her!
That's why we're here.
They're not married?
No kidding!
The nerve of that prude!
She acts so holier-than-thou
at the rummage sale.
What a bitch!
You came so fast.
Squadron sergeant-Major Gibon.
At your service, Countess.
I brought the National Guard.
Where's the offender?
My stars!
Your squadron is quite impressive.
He's a bit brutal, but he's just
a poor homeless person.
They're back-up.
This is Doctor Bauvin.
First we'll talk to him.
Size up the beast.
Let's go, Bauvin.
Good luck!
Where is she?
Enough!
Identity papers! Green card!
Psychology, sergeant-Major.
Hello there.
Are you from around here?
Bow down before me,
and I shall be clement.
Why the costume?
Are you an actor?
Is this for Tv?
Candid Camera?
Should I smile?
Where is my descendant?
Answer or die!
Let me, sergeant-Major.
He's a sicko!
A little shot
and you'll be good as new.
Give me your arm.
Officer, send in
your men on the double!
He's a maniac!
He took the doctor hostage!
Thanks for coming!
Montjoie! St. Denis!
Toil, toil! Never recoil!
I have a horrible doubt. This tramp
just may be part of my family.
What?
"Montjoie" is the battle cry
of French knights.
"Toil! Never recoil!"
Is the motto of Godefroy the Hardy.
It's my family's motto.
Now you have doubts?
He's calmed doWn.
Hold him down.
I'll put him to sleep.
No, my mistake!
I never saw him before.
It can't hurt.
I killed the nerve.
Jean-Pierre, come here.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'll just be a minute.
Do you remember my cousin Hubert?
Martha's son. Naval Academy.
The race car driver?
I never met him.
Obviously. He disappeared
in Borneo before our marriage.
- I think he's alive.
- What?
As wacky as it sounds,
today's Tarzan...
is probably Hubert.
He's totally changed.
You said he was a bum.
He had family air.
The sensual nose,
the large forehead...
You meet a derelict
With a shiny red schnozz, and noW...
he's a long-lost sensual cousin!
A cousin with our arms!
Don't just stand there.
Come look.
Look. The Montmirail family album.
Here's our first Count,
Godefroy The Hardy.
It's the same nose and forehead.
That's a 900-year old drawing.
What's the link with Hubert?
I'll call the castle.
When Hubert was 19,
he posed for the last
family portrait.
A wild-goose chase!
Beatrice Goulard de Montmirail
for Mr. Jacquart.
Hello, Countess. It's Frederick.
Fred, is Jacques-Henri there?
One minute. A word of warning:
He's repairing the boiler.
He's on edge.
Jacques-Henri!
Why did you jerk
the lever so violently?
You asked me to.
Spare me.
My stunning vest
is now a filthy rag.
Jacques-Henri!
Why are you shouting?
Beatrice de Montmirail.
What a ball-buster.
Jacquart?
Yes?
Boiler trouble?
The burner is ruined.
Jean-Francois yanked on the lever.
Oil spurt out.
I was nearly disfigured.
Not to mention my jacket.
No one is of any help.
At least no one died.
Thank God.
I have a problem too.
Can I ask you a favor?
Go upstairs to the Gallery.
In our last family portrait...
there's a Royal Navy cadet.
Second row. The kepi with a feather.
Do you have a Pola?
A what?
A Polaroid, Jacques.
The children threw ours in the toilet.
We have no "Pola". And my name
is Jacques-Henri, not Jacques.
Try to understand, Jacquart/
my cousin is in an insane asylum
by accident.
I can't help your cousin.
We're busy.
The Bernay and Bernay Bank
is here for a seminar.
Edgar Bernay will be
bathing in cold water.
So, even if I had a "Pola",
I wouldn't take your picture.
Okay, I'll hang up.
I'll deal with this myself.
Toodle-oo.
Good riddance.
Sir...
Yes.
The rooms are horribly humid.
Mr. Bernay is sneezing non-stop.
He wanted to relax
after his speech on sponsoring.
So he took a shower.
Ice-cold.
His head is full of shampoo.
If you can't get the hot water back,
We'll have to cut short the seminar.
Does the Instamatic work?
I'm draining Mrs. Pelissier's molar.
It'll be fine.
This is the Montmirail's house.
Take it easy!
They'll bawl us out. Stop!
They'll call the cops
for noise pollution.
Try ringing the bell.
Knock it off!
They'll kick us out!
Jacquart,
Why are you dressed like that?
Excuse our excessive chiming,
your Grace...
Lady Frenegonde!
Let me go! You're crazy!
She's my mistress!
What?
Jean-Pierre, come here.
Jacquart is calling me
"Frenegonde" too.
You slept with her?
Don't worry.
He looks weird but he's pals
With Montmirail the stuntman.
Montmirail the stuntman?
You must mean Hubert,
the race car driver.
Stuntman, wrestler...
race car driver...
same diff.
But who are you?
Jacquasse The Crass.
You don't recognizeth me?
No, I don't recognizeth you.
You're Hubert's friend?
Hubert de Montmirail, whatta hunk.
And so considerate...
like you, your Ladyship.
And he gallops
like Kerwin Costnere.
Coward that I am,
I lost track of my sire
at the inn.
They got in a brawl
at Remi vautrot's pit stop.
Whip me...
your Ladyship!
What is it?
- Jacquart?
- Thou know'st me?
What?
A Jacquart from hunger.
I'm lost.
Mr. Goulard...
Yes, hello...
He's a friend
of Hubert's. According to her,
Hubert has become
a stuntman and a wrestler.
What horrible teeth!
Let's have a look.
I'm no mule! Zounds!
That ass bit me!
I need a tetanus shot!
He might even have rabies!
It isn't Jacquart.
I did his bridge-work.
Obviously, Jean-Pierre.
He proves that Hubert is alive.
We have to get him
out of the hospital.
You banged the Countess?
Bitch.
The bum can't come.
My car isn't Noah's ark.
Open the window.
His body odor is unbearable.
He's very, very green.
Stop the car.
He's going to vomit.
Wait a second!
Hold it in!
It's coming!
He got it all over.
What a pig!
He puked on my shoes!
Your cousin is very violent.
He nearly castrated me.
Castrated clod!
What?
He saved our King's life.
Ah, my youngling.
Why did you abandon me?
Their little red balls
made me sleep.
Master! Master!
Why are you bound?
How much is the ransom?
Silence, peasant!
The "little red balls" are valium.
50 milligrams. He barely slept.
Apothecary, I demand
to be released immediately.
Calm down.
I am neither sick nor loony.
I come from far, far away.
Yes.
He thinks no one
understands who he is.
Persecution mania.
But it's true. He came from Borneo.
He had an accident during a rally.
Right, cousin Hubert?
Cousin Hubert?
Yes. Hubert de Montmirail.
It's freaky...
he has my father's hands.
You know your name.
He knows nothing.
He's completely amnesiac.
He says he's never watched Tv.
Amnesiac? How tragic!
His last remaining memories are
a few facts from History class.
Elementary stuff.
It's often the case with amnesiacs.
He speaks a hodgepodge
of Latin and Old French.
Verbal diarrhea.
Let him go.
- Pawing at him won't help!
- Compose yourself.
Will you free him?
Yes, only because
your husband is a doctor,
and he agrees to take
full responsibility.
Another relative of yours?
No, not at all.
An old friend of Hubert's.
I belong to the Count.
Souplette, sire?
Is he a foreigner?
I don't understand him.
Yes, that must be it.
Come, cousin...
Wait! If you take him,
take his outfit too.
It smells like a billy goat here.
It's repulsive.
Here, take the valium.
If he gets violent,
give him five of them.
Thank you.
Two more lunatics roaming the streets.
Sit down here.
Take care of him. I'll get the car.
Lady Frenegonde is strange.
She is not Lady Frenegonde.
She's my descendant.
My great great great
great great great granddaughter.
Your great great
great great granddaughter?
How terrible!
My Crass, we're a 1000 years old.
It's a living hell.
We must search the dungeon.
Angueran swore to lock up
the wizard and his Book.
With the book, We can concoct
the potion and go back in Time.
Drink that again? Pugh!
You'd rather stay here?
Oh no!
Is this too fast, Hubert?
Do you feel sick?
Open your eyes, sire Godefroy.
You'll get used to it.
Why "Godefroy" and not "Hubert"?
Jean-Pierre, he has amnesia.
Godefroy, Henri, suzy...
Wait. Who has amnesia?
Your cousin or that other skunk?
They both do, Jean-Pierre.
Try being more tolerant.
Their feet reek! It's revolting!
What an insufferable ride!
Please...
I didn't smell anything unusual.
Did the kids behave?
- Yes.
- Okay, toodle-oo!
Zounds! What happened to Nature?
Everything is ugly.
There's no room...
to go hunting.
The air is heavy.
It stinketh!
I'll say!
And it'll be worse
With the new highway.
Good-bye, Dr. Goulard.
Here you go.
It smells gross. Yeeuck!
Like old socks.
Could be.
See you tomorrow, Hilda.
Where is my castle?
We left the castle ages ago.
Unfortunately.
Can you imagine the heating bills?
Anyway, Hubert,
make yourself at home here.
I must go to the castle.
Yes! Yes!
That'll be tomorrow's outing!
Count me out.
I'm over-booked already.
Dinnertime!
Yes! Souplette! Good hot souplette!
Yes, Mr... Jacques Kass.
I'll make you some.
He loves soup.
You live in a pitiful dwelling.
'Tis for peasants.
True, our home is simple.
But it's cozy and has lent itself
to some marvelous evenings.
Don't push it.
We weren't counting
on having houseguests.
So go easy on us, Hubert.
You're Cousin Hubert?
O! Noble Cousin Hubert!
Now he's calling me Hubert!
They're both crazy!
Listen, peon.
I'm Cousin Hubert.
You, sire?
I don't want
to go back to the loonies.
Call me "Cousin Hubert"...
and never "sire". Understand?
Yes, sire.
Stop that, or I'll give you
the little red balls.
Leg of lamb, my sire!
Why "my sire" now?
I don't know, Jean-Pierre.
I just don't know.
Mr... Kass,
that's for tomorrow.
Tonight is cold roast beef
and a salad...
and a Cup-a-soup for you.
If you're still hungry,
you can have some left-overs.
Then a shower and off to bed.
Maybe they can start with the shower.
After such a trying day...
they'll want to wash up.
No servants?
Come wash your hands.
Bea, come look.
What is it?
Come look!
What?
Cousin Hubert, What are you doing?
Can amnesia be this serious?
They're boors!
Swimming in the toilet!
Water.
Soap.
Hot.
Cold. Okay?
Thank you, gentle Lady.
Gentle lady...
sire Godefroy.
Cousin Hubert!
Lady Frenegonde is
1000 years old too?
She's not Lady Frenegonde.
She's Lady Beatrice.
How often must I tell you?
Lady Beatrice.
The descendant.
Jean-Pierre, set the table.
The nice plates
or the normal ones?
Jean-Pierre, use mother's service.
Ridiculous.
Here. Help me, you two.
You stupid idiots!
Bea, they're retarded!
They can't even set a table!
Hello!
Don't scream.
It's Jacquart. I'm not deaf.
I'm sorry, Jacques-Henri.
Bea has some family over.
It's not easy.
Sorry to bother you.
I'm here with President Bernay
the younger of the two
banking brothers.
A charming man.
Unfortunately,
he has a festering abscess.
Due to the humidity in your hotel,
or your "Royal Raspberry" sherbet.
His face is all bloated.
I'll see your friend Bernie
tomorrow at 8:00.
It's Bernay, not Bernie.
Lady-love...
your skin is as soft as a rose petal.
Hubert!
How exciting to touch you...
to lay beside you.
Who does he want to lay?
Jean-Pierre, you're totally on time.
Let's clean up.
What were you up to?
You're kissing cousins!
- Not at all!
- Sorry!
He'll take him.
He's too bad off.
Hello?
What the shit?
Shit.
Hello, Jean-Pierre?
Is that Jean-Pierre?
What the hell?
You were sweethearts.
Not at all. He was much older!
You won't admit
you were flirting.
Jean-Pierre, control yourself!
What you're saying is totally offensive.
Is this my castle?
Yes it is.
Where's my watch-tower? My moat?
My draw-bridge?
Is my dungeon intact?
He doesn't even recognize
your castle.
Hub, it was rebuilt
after the Revolution.
The what?
Christ Almighty.
I must go in my dungeon.
Relax. You're hysterical, Hub.
We'll go tomorrow.
But the dungeon is a legend.
Father always thought one existed...
but we never found it.
It's like someone imitating a dog.
Listen. It's strange.
I don't hear a thing.
President Bernay.
Now he's gone too far!
He better not have woken
Florian and Ondine.
No! Bea! He burnt
your umbrell-Ahhhhh!
Umbrella.
In the hole.
These eardrops sting.
The dog never complained.
If President Bernay has lost...
just one percent of his hearing,
We'll sue the pants off you.
I've gone deaf.
I'm a little confused...
You're a race car driver?
A boxer? A stuntman?
A movie actor?
Who's the star of the movie?
Do I know him? And the director?
Stop the interrogation.
You're exhausting them.
Can't we talk?
Am I boring you?
Ay, indeed.
Charming.
You see.
Will this last long?
Day...
Night...
Please, Mr. Kass,
that's becoming rather grating.
Can't he join us?
It's embarrassing.
He ne'er eats amid nobility.
He is happy to munch
our left-o'ers.
Here, boy.
Thank you, sire Hubert!
He's mashing potatoes into the rug!
Enough! Come sit here.
That would upset him,
right Jacquasse?
You want to sit here?
No, sire Hubert.
In my house, we all eat together.
Nay! Nay!
Obey, peasant.
Your host insists.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org