Every journey into the unfamiliar
is an adventure.
Mine even more so.
I was in search of a
very special small boy.
I knew I wouldn't find him among
the stately mansions of the privileged.
But it was totally unprepared for the
neighborhood where my search would end.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
What kind of child could
such a ghetto melting pot spawn?
I anticipated the worst.
Good morning, Dick.
How's the boy?
No complaints.
Wish I could say the same.
Jake giving you trouble again?
Give you a piece of advice, Freddie.
Don't never ever
take a drinking man for a partner.
I won't.
Gotta see Hobbs the grocer.
See you later Dick.
See ya.
Good morning, Mr. Hobbs.
Ahh.
We booted a man out of the White House.
And what happens?
Them Republicans in Congress
are still trying to do us in.
What're they doing now, Mr. Hobbs?
Doing? Nothing!
That's what they're doing!
Never a thought
for the poor working man.
Or a small tradesmen like myself.
Oh no no..
They're too busy trying to figure a way
to let the rich stuff their pockets!
You grow up.
You be a Democrat, you hear?!
You'll be pleased with me, Mr. Hobbs.
Right.
Now what can I do for you, sonny?
Mama says kindly fill this order.
Put it on her account.
On mamaon your ma, right?
Well, have a cracker. Tit yourself
down the barrel while I see this.
Thanks.
How come Mary ain't doing the market?
She went to the factory to bring
more shirt work for my ma to sew.
Your ma is a fine lady, sunny.
Never met a dearer soul.
I guess that's why
my papa calls her "dearest."
I reckon so, Ceddie.
Keep this to yourself.
I call my ma "dearest" sometimes too.
And why wouldn't you, Ceddie?
Seeing as how she was
left a widow so young
It's kind of up to you to uhh
take your pa's place, right?
My papa has been gone a long time now.
Can't say I rightly remember him
much anymore.
Oh? He left his mark on you, you know.
You got a way of talking that
ain't exactly true blue American.
It's hardly surprising
since he was British.
I hope you will turn it against
me that my papa was British.
Seeing as how you don't
like the British for much.
By my lights, you're an American.
Whether your pa chooses to marry
a spunky American girl
and make him miss his country.
I am American!
But if you don't mind me asking, why
don't you like the British very much?
It ain't the common folk I don't like.
But them aristocrats!
Them that keeps the common folk
in servitude!!
Mark my words, Ceddie.
The day will come
when the downtrodden
rise in righteous wrath.
Blow all them lords
and earls and marquises sky high!
Maybe they wouldn't be lords and earls
and marquises if they knew any better.
Don't you believe it, Ceddie.
There's glory in it.
Have you ever known any aristocrats?
Not likely!
If one of them showed his ugly face
in my establishment, I'd heave him out!
I'll have no grasping tyrants
sitting on my barrels!
Just set your groceries
on the table, Ceddie.
All right, Mama.
Are you hungry?
Not now.
Mr. Hobbs treated me
to a sparkling apple.
A fine talk too.
I'm sure he did.
I got to your place finally.
Far too much for me to carry.
It ain't the bundles do me in.
It's them five flights of stairs.
And my little darling
did the marketing.
Mr. Hobbs asked after you.
I think he's sweet on you.
How foolish of him.
Can I go out, mama?
The boys are waiting on me.
For you. Yes, run along.
Were they pleased with the
finished waists, Mary?
And why not? Seeing you work
your fingers to the bone!
And doing such fine stitching.
Thank you, Captain.
Pardon me.
The search for the boy has led me here.
But how would the extraordinary offer
I brought be received?
Ceddie would not leave me.
Nor would I part with him.
Anger is expected, Mrs. Errol.
It's simply that the
boy's grandfather is
fixed in his determination
not to see you.
I'm well aware of that, Mr. Havisham.
My husband's father has never shown
the slightest concern
for me or his grandson.
He's an old man.
And his prejudices are very strong.
He always disliked
America and Americans.
His son's marriage to you angered him.
Hardly a revelation.
I must admit, I'm surprised
by your manner and appearances.
Pleasantly surprised.
Indeed!
However the terms of the arrangement
are not so harsh as you may think.
You're a guest in my house
and I will not be rude.
But I would prefer if you said what you
came to say and disposed of the matter.
You speak your mind,
don't you, Mrs. Errol? Very well.
Your son's grandfather the Earl
dislikes London.
He's the victim of inflammatory gout.
And intends to live
for the most part at Dorincourt.
Which is pleasantly situated
in the countryside.
Your son naturally
would also reside there.
The Earl offers you a cottage nearby.
The boy will be permitted
to visit you whenever he likes.
The Earl will neither
see you, speak with you
or permit you within the
gates of Dorincourt.
Is that all, Mr. Havisham?
Please. Surely, as a mother
you must want is best for your child.
What's best for Ceddie
is being with the dearest and sweetest
mother boy ever had!
I beg you to consider
your son's future, Mrs. Errol.
Get those kids off of the back of the
What's happening?
Get those kids off the back.
You're gonna fall.
You're gonna get hurt.
I'm sorry to make you walk
the stairs again, Mary.
But would you bring Ceddie, please?
Considering your financial situation,
I'm surprised you have a servant.
Mary isn't a servant.
She was midwife to Ceddie
when he was born.
And has stayed on out of devotion
although we could not pay her.
She's all the family
that Ceddie and I have.
I see.
You've not yet said whether you accept
the Earl's offer and all the terms.
My husband loved England.
He loved his father.
It grieved him that he was
alienated from that.
I will accept the terms.
But only because I know
my husband would wish it.
And I think I believe
it will be to Ceddie's benefit.
Your son will thank you one day.
I hope so.
However
I too have a condition
that must be met.
A condition?
Yes.
And if it is violated,
I will take Ceddie and return here.
And the condition, Mrs. Errol?
That Ceddie is not to be told.
Nor is his grandfather ever
to reveal to him his dislike for me.
I will not have my child
toward between his love for me
and the affection he should feel
for his grandfather.
You have my word.
Your wishes will be respected.
Thank you.
It will be difficult for Ceddie to
understand why we must live apart.
But if his grandfather's kind
and loving, he will accept it.
And he will be kind and loving,
Mr. Havisham?
The old gentleman would not have
sent me on this long journey,
if his intentions towards his grandson
were not the best.
That is not an answer.
But I will accept it for now.
You're a woman of considerable
strength and purposes.
I'm a mother who's giving her child
into another's care.
And that care
must go beyond material things.
Me and the boys were playing
a bangup game of KicktheCan.
This is Mr. Havisham, Ceddie.
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Havisham.
So. This is little Lord Fauntleroy!
It's long past your bedtime, Ceddie.
I know. But I've just been
trying to get it straight.
It is rather a lot
for a small boy to grasp.
Let me see
if I can explain it more clearly.
Your grandfather, whom you've
never met, is an Earl.
That's an aristocrat,
according to Mr. Hobbs.
ArisTOcrat!
His second oldest son,
your uncle Maurice,
would've become the Earl in time.
If he hadn't been killed
in a fall from a horse.
His second eldest son, your uncle
Bevis, would then have become the Earl.
But he died this past year
in Rome of a tumor.
That was papa.
So papa died too. And that leaves me.
Yes. And in time, you will be
the Earl of Dorincourt.
But until then, you're Lord Fauntleroy.
Do I have to be?
None of the other boys are.
It is a very great honor, Ceddie.
And it would make your papa very happy.
Well, if there's no getting out of it, I
guess I'll have to make the best of it.
And I know you will.
When do we have to go away?
Mr. Havisham is
making the arrangements.
And will come tomorrow
to tell us the particulars.
Mary is coming too, isn't she?
If I have to swim me way over!
That would be a sight.
I'm going to have a time now,
explaining what happened to Mr. Hobbs?
Thank you, Mrs. Grabowski.
Help yourself to a licorice there,
Ceddie.
No, thanks.
Huh?
Do you recall
what we talked about yesterday?
Uh, politics?
We also talked about Lords
and Earls and Marquises.
Recalled and entered
the conversation, yes.
Do you recall you said,
you wouldn't have a Lord nor a Marquis
sitting on one of your barrels?
I sure do. And I wouldn't!
Well, there's one sitting
on your barrel right now, Mr. Hobbs.
You got a headache?
You got a pain somewhere?
I'm fine. And it's the truth, Mr. Hobbs.
Right now, I'm Lord Fauntleroy.
But someday, I will be an Earl.
You got some story.
I best take you home.
I'm fine. And it's the truth, Mr. Hobbs.
I wrote down my grandpa's name exactly.
So I could tell it to you.
"John Arthur Molyneux Errol,
Earl of Dorincourt."
All my grandpa's sons died,
including my papa.
It looks like I'm stuck with it.
I'll be jiggered.
I'm jiggered too, Mr. Hobbs.
You've been dealt a mighty low blow,
Ceddie.
I'll be glad to meet my grandpa.
That part's all right.
But I give you my word. When I'm
an Earl someday, I won't be a tyrant.
It'll be an uphill fight.
But I reckon you'll make it.
Seeing as how your halfAmerican.
Best half, I have my lights.
Then we're still friends?
To the death!
In spite of your misfortune.
Thanks, Mr. Hobbs!
Guess this news isn't bad after all.
The Earl is anxious
his grandson should look forward
with some pleasure
to his future life in England.
And said that if he would expressed
any wishes, I should gratify them.
That much?
Oh, hardly an untoward sum, Mrs. Errol.
You must remember that a great change
has taken place in your son's life.
Maybe it won't be all that bad, mama.
Being an aristocrat.
Now if I can give Dick money
to buy out Jake.
And buy Mr. Hobbs
a genuine gold watch.
I guess my grandpas just about
the best person in the whole world.
Your grandfather will deny you
nothing money can purchase.
I'll be blowed!!
If that's not enough to buy Jake out,
I'll ask Mr. Havisham for more.
Enough? This is more than enough.
Good. Don't forget to buy
a boss sign too, Dick.
I'll be jiggered!
There's writing inside
of the genuine gold watch, Mr. Hobbs.
It says " From your oldest friend,
Lord Fauntleroy."
"from Ceddie to Mr. Hobbs."
"when this you see, remember me."
I ain't like to forget you.
I'm sorry. I won't be able
to become a Democrat now, Mr. Hobbs.
It's the Democrat's loss, Ceddie.
Well
I guess I better go.
Mr. Havisham is coming to get us.
I'll have to get dressed up proper.
Here. You take this for luck.
But it's your kerchief.
With lucky horseshoes.
You'll be needing the luck now.
You wear it when you're
with all them swells.
Thanks, Dick. I will.
I'll write and tell you how
it is being Lord Fauntleroy.
You usually enjoy
our morning stroll on deck.
Is something troubling you?
My ma told me last night
she and Mary won't be living
in the same house as me and grandpa.
They will be close by.
You be able to see
your mother every day.
I know.
That's what my ma told me too.
But I can't figure why they can't live
in grandpa's house along with me.
Do you suppose this is
the reason, Mr. Havisham?
That my grandpa thinks
I ought to have a change?
Because I've been living
with ladies all my life.
One could assume that.
Well, that's all right.
Then it's just for a while.
You think you'll be fond
of your grandfather?
When a person does a lot for you,
it means you grab part of it.
It's found to be fun.
And he'll be fond of me.
Because grandpas are always
fond of their grandsons.
That would seem a logical assumption.
Is where we're going anything
like Hester Street, Mr. Havisham?
Like Hester Street?
I doubt you'll find any place
in England quite like Hester Street.
Guess I'll have to make the best of it.
Oh I don't think you'll be disappointed.
There's no place like England.
And nowhere more fair
than the English countryside.
Is far away, Mr. Havisham?
We should be there by nightfall.
Wakeup, Ceddie.
We're here.
Ah, Dawson's here. He's the Earl's
housekeeper, from the castle.
Kindly bring in the trunk with them.
Yes, sir.
I'll keep an eye on them.
I ain't overly trustful of foreigners.
As you wish. This way, Mrs. Errol.
Welcome to Court Cottage.
Thank you.
Good evening, Dawson.
Hi.
I trust the journey was pleasant, ma'am?
It was.
And it's kind of you to greet us.
This is sure a fine house.
Dawson, this is Lord Fauntleroy.
Others bow and curtsy. Not you.
Oh. Sorry.
I guess I'll get it figured out in time.
I knew your father when he was
a little boy, your Lordship.
You're very like him.
That's what my ma always said.
Look, Mama!
Her name is Cleo, ma'am.
I thought she might keep you company.
And she shall. Thank you.
Kindly take the trunk to the bedroom
at the head of the stairs.
Yes, ma'am.
Ceddie is so tired.
Surely, he can stay here tonight?
Perhaps it would be just as well.
I'll see you Lord Fauntleroy
is put to bed.
I've been seeing to him
since he came into the world.
And I ain't about to stop now.
Of course.
Go along with Mary, Ceddie.
Good night, mama.
Good night, Mr. Havisham.
Goodnight, My Lord.
Good night, Mrs. Dawson.
Just Dawson, your Lordship.
It sure don'tit doesn't
seem very polite.
The Earl has no idea
what he's taking from me.
How... difficult it is for me
to part with Ceddie.
This is scarcely a parting.
Think of it as no more than
your son going off to a nearby school.
We both know better, Mr. Havisham.
My son will only be a visitor
in his mother's house.
Even my house is not mine.
But his grandpa's.
Will you be good enough
to tell Ceddie's grandfather
I will accept no money from him?
Surely, you cannot mean the income
that he proposes to settle on?
I do.
I must accept this house
because it makes it possible
for me to be near my child.
But I will take no money.
If he dislikes me so intensely, I should
feel as if I were selling Ceddie to him.
His Lordship will be very upset.
He will not understand.
I'm very much afraid,
he will have to understand.
I'm a good seamstress.
And intend to earn
what little Mary and I will need.
I will not take money from a man
who hates me, Mr. Havisham.
And who takes my child from me,
for whatever reason.
I don't look forward
to relaying your message.
But I shall, of course.
Is that my grandpa's house?
That's the gatekeeper's lodge.
God bless you, Your Lordship.
Good luck and happiness to you!
To you too.
Now that's what I call a fine hello.
Who is she, Mr. Havisham?
The gatekeeper. The boys are her sons.
Do you think the boys will know
how to play KickTheCan?
If they don't,
I'll be glad to show them.
I doubt that you'll
be playing with them.
Why not?
As Lord Fauntleroy,
you have a position to maintain.
Being an aristocrat sure is complicated.
Is this a city park, Mr. Havisham?
This is Dorincourt.
Your grandfather's estate.
My grandfather owns all this?
Far more!
Oh, he's loaded.
Mmmhmm.
That's what Mr. Hobbs says.
How far to my grandfather's house now,
Mr. Havisham?
You can see the castle from here.
I'll be jiggered!
Well, shall we get on with it,
Havisham?
Lord Fauntleroy, sir.
So you're my grandson?
Mighty glad to meet you, grandpa.
Did the trolley run over your foot?
Trolley?
You have to be mighty careful
getting on and off those trolleys.
Push and shove, the devil's behind you.
Well I've not been run over
by a trolley. I suffer from gout!
Let's see the boy is suitably dressed.
But I'm wearing my best new knickers.
Hardly appropriate for Lord Fauntleroy.
Mr. Hobbs says
clothes don't make the man.
But I'll wear spiffy clothes
if you want me to.
In fact, we are glad to oblige.
It's such a big house.
I guess you won't feel so lonesome
now that I'm here, grandpa.
What makes you think I'm lonesome?
I don't see how not. I know I'd be.
It'd be better if my ma was here.
She'd hardly even be noticed.
Careful.
Dugal has no love for strangers.
I'm not a stranger. I'm your grandson.
At least the boy is no coward.
As you are my grandson,
we'll just have to make the best of it.
That's what I told Mr. Hobbs.
Who is Mr. Hobbs?
He's our grocer.
He and Dick the bootblack
are my very best friends!
Grocers, bootblacks? Hardly society.
I thought a lot about you
while I was on the big trip coming here.
I wondered what you'd look like.
If you'd be like my papa.
Well? Am I?
I don't think so.
You're disappointed?
No, not by a long shot.
Seeing that you're my grandpa,
you'll be nice to me.
You think I've been nice?
Sure have!
You gave me money for Dick to buy out
Jake with the terrible profit.
And letting me buy Mr. Hobbs
a genuine gold watch.
I'd call that nice.
Your Lordship instructed me
to satisfy his desires.
And he chose to bestow gifts
on his friends.
If Lord Fauntleroy
would be so good as to give me
a few minutes alone
with his grandfather.
We have some business.
Don't mind one bit.
Lots to look at in here.
Oh my, Dugal.
Come on, boy. Come with me.
Boys and dogs have a natural affinity!
A glass of sherry for Mr. Havisham.
My fool doctor is denying me
such a pleasure.
What do you make of the boy,
Havisham?
I find him most interesting.
Clods can be interesting.
He's hardly a clod, my Lord.
Although I daresay
your Lordship will find him somewhat
different from English children.
Impudent lot from what I've heard.
American children.
Outspoken perhaps but not him.
I find him surprisingly mature
for one so young.
You call it maturity.
The Yanks call it precocity.
And I call it impudent.
The American blood will tell.
But I'll deal with it. And him.
After my own fashion.
You said there was something
you wished to discuss with me.
Please get on with it.
I have a message
from your grandson's mother.
I'm not interested in the woman
or her messages.
The less I hear about her, the better.
I'm very much afraid
you'll have to hear this, my Lord.
She refuses to accept
the income we offered.
Refuses? How dare she!
She says because relations
between you are not friendly
Does she expect friendship?
That sly conniving mercenary American.
One could scarcely call her mercenary,
since she won't even accept
the money you offer.
Done for effect, Havisham.
She hopes to make me
admire her character.
A ploy, Havie!
As the boy's mother,
she has a position to maintain.
And she shall take the money
whether she likes it or not.
Then she will not use it.
It's to be sent to her regardless.
I will not have heard telling the world
that she has to live like a pauper
because I do nothing for her.
My tenants think little enough of me
as it is.
I've got it.
She thinks to poison
the boy's mind against me.
Quite the contrary.
Mrs. Errol asks... no, demands...
nothing be said or done
that would lead Lord Fauntleroy
to understand you had separated him
from his mother
because of your dislike of her.
He loves his mother dearly.
She's convinced this
would alienate him from you.
Come now, Havisham.
Am I to believe she's told him
nothing of my antipathy for her?
Nothing. She wants no shadow
upon that relationship.
She wants the boy to believe you
the most affectionate of grandparents.
I know your intentions toward
the boy are the best, my Lord.
But your grandson's impression of you
will depend largely
on your discretion in this matter.
I must urge you not to speak slightly
of his mother in front of him.
That will cause me no hardship since I
don't intend to speak with her at all.
A glass of sherry.
But you said your doctor
I have a barbarian
to make into a Dorincourt!!
I need all the sustenance I can get.
Lunch to be served, my Lord.
I'll have my glass at the table.
Join us, Havisham?
Thank you, my Lord.
I'll help grandpa walk.
I'm much stronger than I look.
Just lean on me, grandpa.
I'll make it easy.
The boy's been well prepared
to ingratiate himself.
I doubt that it took
preparation, my Lord.
After all, he is a Dorincourt.
Not yet.
But he will be.
Before I'm through with him.
Just lean on me, grandpa.
I won't let you fall.
I have no intention of falling.
This sure would be a fine place
to play KickTheCan.
You wouldn't have to worry
about beer wagons and trolleys.
It's a warm day, isn't it??
I find it downright cruel, if you
don't mind me saying so, ma'am.
I agree.
But we can't help for it, Mellon.
Lord Fauntleroy doesn't know why
his mother can't be with him.
And he's not to be told.
That his Lordship orders.
That's a dreadful thing
to happen to her.
Keeping a widow
from her own flesh and blood.
You should've heard her talking
to the servants all last night.
She said one thing
Higgins might've liked.
Him so innocent. And like
dining with his best friend.
Best friend? His Lordship with a temper
and disposition like curdled milk.
Good morning.
Good morning, your Lordship.
I trust you slept well.
Sure did!
This is Mellon.
She's going to look after you.
Pleased to meet you Mrs. Mellon.
Not Mrs. Mellon, your Lordship.
Just plain Mellon.
You're not plain at all.
The and my friend Dick would say
you're smashing.
If you'll get up now, Mellon
will see to your bath and dress you.
And you can breakfast
with his Lordship.
I can dress myself.
And if you don't mind,
I'd as soon take my own bath.
As you wish.
Bring his Lordship
to the dining room when he's ready.
I'll just run your bath, your Lordship.
I prefer you call me Ceddie.
It wouldn't be fitting, your Lordship.
I'm not sure I'm going to take
to being an aristocrat.
Of course you will, your Lordship.
Don't you think this is a big house
just for two people, Mellon?
Oh, I'll wait till you see
the horses and stables.
Think what you'll have to tell
your mama when you see them.
It's a fact. I think
we will be great friends, Mellon.
Bless your heart, sir.
Do I have to wear this funny suit,
Mellon?
You look just elegant.
Besides, it's what his Lordship ordered.
I'm glad the boys of Hester Street
can't see me now.
How's that?
His Lordship is awaiting
breakfast for you.
And I think you best take off the cap.
All right.
What's in that room?
Your playroom, your Lordship.
You mean I have a special room
just for playing?
Mac home my friend Sam's
whole family lives in just one room.
And there are six of them.
This is all mine?
All yours.
I wasn't here then.
But Dawson says that all in this room
belonged to your own dear papa.
My own papa?
I guess my grandpa
loved my papa an awful lot.
I think we best go down, my Lordship.
The kippers not to your liking?
I never had a fish for breakfast before.
What's that?
I never had… Never mind, grandpa.
Eat your breakfast.
I guess I'm not very hungry.
Thanks for the toys and games.
What?
Thanks for toys and games!
Oh, games are important.
They prepare a boy
for the larger game of life, I'm told.
They'll prepare you to become
the Earl of Dorincourt.
Becoming an Earl is pretty important.
No need to moon about it.
I wasn't.
I was just thinking about mama.
You're what?
I never had breakfast
without mama before.
You may see your mother later today.
Pardon me, your Lordship.
The Rev. Mr. Muldaur is here.
He says the matter is urgent.
The matter is always urgent
for the Rev. Mr. Muldaur.
Show him in, Dawson.
I never met a reverend mister before..
You're safe from those occasions.
Good morning, your Lordship.
Be good enough to come closer.
I see no reason for us
to shout at each other.
Well, what is it this time?
Another complaint from the parish?
Or an appeal for yet another charity?
My grandson, Lord Fauntleroy.
Pleased to make your acquaintance,
Reverend Mister Muldaur.
And yours, your Lordship.
You've come a long way.
And many will be happy that
you've made the journey safely.
Shall we get on with it, Muldaur?
Lord Fauntleroy is very much
like his father, your Lordship.
He is his father's son.
Well. Who is in trouble now, Muldaur?
It's Higgins of Abe's farm, sir.
He's been ill himself. And his children
both have whooping cough.
He's now behind in his rent.
Your bailiff has told him
that he must pay or leave.
Higgins came to me yesterday
to ask if I'd intervene.
But I beg you to give him more time.
And also a small loan to buy
the medicine the children need.
Higgins is a bad tenant
and worse farmer.
And he's always behind in his rent.
It's true he's not a good manager
of his affairs.
But he is in grave trouble
now, your Lordship.
If the farm is taken from him,
the family will starve.
My grandpa will never let that happen.
We have a philanthropist in our midst.
One who bestows largess
on bootblacks and grocers.
A kind heart for Count Lord Fauntleroy.
In that way,
he is certainly like his father.
But unlike his grandfather?
I think you've got the kindest heart
in the whole world, grandpa.
And I ought to know.
You would help Higgins?
I can't. But I know you will.
Inform Higgins
he has two weeks in which
to pay his rent or forsake the farm.
I beg you to reconsider, your Lordship.
Good morning, Muldaur.
Good day, sir.
What is it?
I bet you have a good reason
for not helping Higgins, grandpa.
You've not yet been taught
the responsibilities
of your future position.
But when you are,
you will understand that is essential
to be firm with underlings.
What's "underlings"?
Parasites, like Higgins.
They prefer to live off charity
rather than do honest work.
Ahh.
If you have no wish for more breakfast,
we'll go to the stables.
I just got a trait.
What trait?
Why you said you are not
going to help Higgins.
Even though I know you are.
And?
Of course you are. You said it yourself.
I'm going to have
to learn responsibilities
if I'm going to become
the Earl someday.
You don't have to pretend
you're not going help Higgins
just so I can learn
responsibilities, grandpa.
Come, we'll go to the stables.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to go see mama first.
There's a pony in the stables.
Your own pony.
My own pony!
You give me everything, grandpa!
But I'll go see mama first.
Sure got lots to tell dearest.
Dearest? What's dearest?
I guess I can tell you,
since you're my grandpa.
I already told Mr. Hobbs.
I call mama "dearest" sometimes.
Because that's what
papa used to call her.
I can't wait to tell Mama about all
the things you've given me, grandpa.
I think you're the best grandpa
in the whole world!
Know what I just thought of, grandpa?
What?
What people really don't
understand about aristocrats.
I'm going to write to Mr. Hobbs
and set him straight.
I gather you're Mr. Hobbs has
a low opinion of aristocrats.
Well, he thinks they're tyrants.
That's because he doesn't know
any of them.
So I'm going to tell them
that you're the best ever.
And when I grow up,
I wanna be just like you.
It's a joy to me
now that I'm going to be an Earl.
I can't become a Democrat
or become president.
Which is what Mr. Hobbs
had in mind for me.
President?
You will go to the House of Lords!
Is it just as good as being President?
Poor child. Infinitely superior!
Go on there.
Come on. Come on.
Whoa.
I'll get out first.
Then you can lean on me, grandpa.
I'm not getting out.
You're not going to see Mama?
I've important business to attend to.
Mama will be very disappointed.
Hustings will come for you
in two hours time.
Go ahead.
Oh, Ceddie!
Mama!
Home, Hustings.
How are you?
Fine.
Did you sleep well?
Yeah, I have a huge bed!
And you're happy?
Lord Fauntleroy sits well, my Lord.
All Dorincourts sit well.
Can I go faster, grandpa?
You're not afraid?
Not by a long shot.
Let him have the reins.
Come on! Faster, come on!
Thighs in the stirrup, your Lordship.
I'm running him every time.
That will do, Wilkins!
Can I go for a real ride, grandpa?
I'll keep a watchful eye on him,
your Lordship.
See that you do.
Charlie.
Whoa.
Bye, grandpa!
He sure is spunky, your Lordship.
Get on with your work.
Whoa... whoa.
Have you had enough, your Lordship?
Not by a long shot!
Hold still.
I almost forgot my cap though.
Let's go. Come on.
You got a long way to go?
The boy lives in the village,
your Lordship.
It's him!
It's him that's come from America!
Give him a hand up on my pony, Wilkins.
Your Lordship?
He can't walk very well. And I can.
Here, ride my mount.
It's too big for him.
Give him a hand, Wilkins. Please.
What's your name?
Georgie. Georgie Hawker.
Pleased to meet you, Georgie.
So let's go.
Won't his Lordship give me what for.
Mrs. Dibble, Dibble! Look!
What? Ah, it must be him.
It's little Lord Fauntleroy!
How do?
He knows Georgie.
Can I put here?
Yes.
I'll be back in a minute.
Excuse me.
Yes?
You put things on account?
That depends on whose account.
My grandpa, the Earl of Dorincourt.
So I guess his credit's good.
The Earl?
Then you must be...
little Lord Fauntleroy!
Would I be wearing this getup
if I wasn't?
He wouldn't let the boy ride
my mount, your Lordship.
He said it was too high.
"Wilkins," he says.
"The boy is lame and I am not."
Then... he bought a crutch
for the boy from Mr. Kinsey.
And then when we got to the cottage,
he whips off his cap
and says to the boy's mother,
"I've brought your son home, ma'am."
"And the crutch is from...
my grandpa."
If you don't mind my saying so,
your Lordship,
The Lord Fauntleroy has won the hearts
of the whole village
with what he's done.
You could've knocked
me down with a feather
when he asked to buy
those crutches for little Georgie.
Such a lovely child.
He took my breath away.
He looks so like his father.
And a dearer man never lived
than Captain Errol!
I wish one of my own could live
with the Earl of Dorincourt.
Look, that's his mother.
Isn't she in luck?
Bless you, my lady.
There's no reason for you to curtsy.
But I thank you for your blessing.
It's very nice of you to be here,
Mrs. Errol.
I'll help grandpa walk.
He's his father all over again.
Everybody's sure glad
to see you, grandpa.
They're bowing to you.
To me?
Take off your hat.
God bless your young Lordship
and a long life for you.
Thanks. You too.
What is it, Higgins?
You're Higgins?
Sure pleased to meet you, Mr. Higgins.
I guess you feel a lot better
now that my grandpa said that
you can stay on the farm.
But I guess you know
how good my grandpa is.
You look poorly and should be in bed.
When you're fit again,
see that you do better with the farm.
Thanks, your Lordship.
I hope your children get over
their whooping cough, Mr. Higgins.
You sure made Mr. Higgins happy,
grandpa.
I'm sure learning how to be an Earl!
Mama and Mary came to church too,
grandpa.
Why don't we sit with them?
Our place is in the family pew.
But Mama and Mary are family too.
What's that, Grandpa?
A memorial to our ancestors.
They don't know how to spell
no better than me.
We shall now sing Hymn 298.
"Praise, my soul, the King of Heaven."
Praise, my soul, the King of Heaven.
To His feet thy tribute bring.
Ransomed, healed, restored, forgiven,
Who like me His praise should sing:
Praise Him, Praise Him.
Praise the everlasting King.
You for work?
I'm a good seamstress, Mrs. Smith.
You're his Lordship's mother!
I'm also my own person.
Of course if you have no need for help
I have this need. I'm the only
dressmaker for miles around.
What would the Earl think?
That does not concern me.
I have a living to make.
I prefer of course
to do the sewing at home.
As it's a long walk to the village.
It doesn't surprise me, my lady.
What doesn't surprise you?
That the young captain married you.
Thank you. Will you take me on?
With pleasure, my lady.
And you will do me a kindness
if you cease to call me "my lady."
I'm Mrs. Errol..
It's all the title
I want or have ever wanted.
Then Mrs. Errol, it shall be.
I took a wrong turn
on the way to the village.
Came to a sector..
I've never seen
such poverty and despair.
The houses were all decayed.
There was an open ditch
with a stench that took my breath away.
Earl's Lane..
It's where his Lordship sentences them.
It's best to stay away.
There's always terrible sickness there.
It comes from hunger and filth.
Look it over.
Fine bird, Mr. McGregor.
I'll wager you'll be pleased
to do your own shooting again, my Lord.
Keep an eye out for poachers,
Mr. McGregor.
Yes, my Lord.
I'll not have my birds in end up
on the tables of the tenants.
The signs are posted.
And all know the penalty. But
Some people's hunger, your Lordship.
Those who don't work
deserve to go hungry.
Take the birds to the kitchen, McGregor.
Yes, my Lord.
Good afternoon, sir.
Hustings.
Be good enough to inform the lady
I have no desire to converse with her.
Kindly inform his Lordship
that an exchange of "good afternoon"
hardly constitutes a conversation.
Tell the lady
that she is sadly mistaken if she
hopes to ingratiate herself with me.
Please tell his Lordship
I have no desire or need
to ingratiate myself.
He is my husband's father
and my son's grandfather.
And I merely show him the
same courtesy I would
show his gamekeeper
if the circumstance were the same.
Tell the lady
that like all Americans,
she is exceedingly rude.
Tell his Lordship that it's obvious
Americans do not have
a monopoly on rudeness.
Tell the lady she offends me.
Tell his Lordship I certainly hope so.
Tell the lady
The lady has heard quite enough,
Hustings.
I thank God each day
for the Revolution that freed us from
the arrogance and ill temper
of the British aristocracy.
Madam!!
We won that war. And I have
no intention of losing this one.
Good day, Hustings!
Shall I just drive on, your Lordship?
I want no gossip
about this conversation, Hustings.
What conversation?
Was that yours, sir?
Drive on.
Shouldn't Mama be home by now, Mary?
She must've stopped by that awful
place again to help out like she does.
Seems a mistake.
She'll come watch you when she can.
Is mama happy, Mary?
She never says.
Sure, she's happy.
Or she would pack up and go home.
But not without me.
You'd be the first thing she'd pack.
I'm sorry that I made you wait, Ceddie.
Mama!
Mary told me where you were.
New or alterations?
Alterations.
I'll fix you a cup of tea.
You look awful tired, mama.
I'm fine.
Do you realize we've
been here a whole month?
A month?
Mmmmmm.
I haven't even wrote
I haven't written
to Mr. Hobbs and Dick yet.
I'm going to do it
as soon as I get back.
Has your grandfather said anything
yet about your schooling?
He says I'm going to have a tutor.
Why can't I just finish school?
I suppose because it takes
special training to become a Lord.
Sometimes I would just as soon
not become one.
Not if we can't live in the same house.
You promised you would accept it
without question.
Someday you'll understand.
I guess. But I sure don't now.
When you're the Earl of Dorincourt,
you'll be brave and kind.
And do only good for others.
The world will be a little bit
better because a man has lived.
Good morning.
Your foot's better, grandpa.
My gout has receded.
That's fine, grandpa.
I know it must've hurt an awful lot.
I guess that's why you were
grumpy sometimes, grandpa.
Probably.
May I inquire what you are writing?
It's a letter to Mr. Hobbs and Dick.
I should've done it before.
But "Better late than never"
Mr. Hobbs says.
Quite a philosopher, your Mr. Hobbs.
That's what mama says too.
I had a fine dinner with Mama yesterday.
And you know what else she said?
"The world should feel a little
better because a man has lived."
I think the world will be a lot
better because you lived, grandpa.
Thank you.
My fool doctor tells me
I may ride again.
You will accompany me tomorrow?
That'll be fine, grandpa.
Now I'd better finish my letter.
Dugal.
"So you see, it's a mistake about
earls being tyrants.
"It's only that they are the top man.
So they get blamed a lot.
"But then you never knew any earls.
"So I can see how you wouldn't
have a firsthand idea.
"My grandpa has gout in his foot which
makes him cranky. But he is better now.
"I love him very much.
"And so do almost all
of the people who work on his land.
"Which are called 'tenants.'
"Which is different from being
a tenant on Hester Street.
Make any sense to you?
Nothing.
They call them tenants over there, huh?
It still means "them which is in
servitude to the aristocrats"!
Let me get on with it.
"The only thing is mama and Mary
don't live with grandpa and me.
"But they got a fine house
all to themselves.
"I'd as soon they live with us.
"Well, that's that.
"Please write a letter to me.
And give my regards to the boys.
"I miss you and Dick.
There is a dungeon, uhh...
under the castle.
"But my grandpa never put
anyone in there." Oh, yeah?
"Your old friend Ceddie.
Lord Fauntleroy.
"PS, I have to sign it that way."
I call it queer.
Ceddie's ma and Mary aren't
living in the same house with him.
Queer? What I call it ain't
fit for public consumption.
You don't appear to be
enjoying your ride today.
I was thinking about mama.
You're free to see her
whenever you wish.
I know.
But don't you miss not seeing mama?
Since I don't know her
I can't say I miss seeing her.
I thought maybe you'd want to.
Mama said I mustn't ask you
any questions. So I won't.
I miss her most at night.
I look out my window.
Mama puts a lamp there for me to see.
I'm a long way off. I know what it says.
It says "good night and God's with you."
That's what my ma
used to say to me every night.
We'll go to the promontory today.
There's something you should see.
All this will be yours one day.
Mine? When?
When you're the Earl of Dorincourt.
When I'm dead.
But then I don't want it.
I don't want you to be dead.
Kind of you to say so.
What's way over there, grandpa?
That's where my tenants live.
It's called Earl's Lane.
I'd like to see it.
I don't suppose I've been down there
in 20 years.
I think I better see it as long
as it's going to be mine someday.
Bless you, Lord.
And your sweet mother.
Comes like an angel of mercy.
To bring food and see to the sick.
When you're the Earl, see to it that you
are more responsible than I have been.
Whose lane is to be renovated?
Every miserable cottage.
And I've given the bailiff instructions
for that stinking ditch to be filled in.
It will improve
the value of the property.
Surely.
Hey, who'd think anyone
could sop the heart of that old tyrant.
Sopping? No. Shaming!
You wish to see me your Lordship?
This is a list of the guests be invited.
Guests? For what, your Lordship?
I intend to give a dinner party.
To mark the renovation of Earl's Lane.
No need to look as if the world
were coming to an end.
No, my Lord.
It's just that we've not
had a dinner party for 20 years.
Better late than never.
Where have I heard that before?
Lady Lorradaile!
Yes, Dawson, my sister! Lady Lorradaile.
And Sir Harry.
Yes, sir.
"No need to look like the world is
coming to an end" his Lordship says.
A dinner party here?!
What's more, Lady Lorradaile is invited.
What? They haven't exchanged
a word in 20 years!
His Lordship is proud as a Derby cock.
Thomas, the guest list.
Take it to the top stationary.
His Lordship wants the invitations
written in his best text.
Mellon, a new velvet
suit is to be ordered
for Lord Fauntleroy forthrrghtly.
The guestrooms are to be
aired and ready.
And the castle is to be scrubbed
and polished from top to bottom.
Wilkins will ensure the carriages,
horses and stables are ever good.
As for myself, I intend to lie down
to get over the shock.
"And the Queen asked the magic mirror."
"Mirror mirror on the wall, who's
the most beautiful of them all?"
"And mirror replied..."
You're wrong again. Ill show you.
You have to beat that!
Strike, Grandpa! You win.
Go fetch it! Good boy!
Come on, Dugal, come on.
Cedric is my only grandson, Havisham.
The woman is a fraud.
Quite possibly, my Lord.
But we must be certain.
Have I your permission
to use a private detective?
Dammit, man.
No stone is to be left unturned which
would expose this Minna Boggs
as the imposter she is.
To say my son Bevis married her?
Some eight years ago.
And that the child resulted from it.
Now she claims that it is her son,
not Cedric, is the rightful heir.
Wicked nonsense, Havisham!
I sincerely hope that is the case.
What manner of woman is she?
In appearance, she's handsome
in a coarse sort of way.
At our first brief meeting,
I got that she was a dancer,
who came to England
with some tawdry American company.
Uneducated and openly mercenary, I fear.
I've no doubt there may have been
an alliance of sorts.
Bevis rarely showed discrimination
in his choice of dalliance.
But marriage to a woman of that sort.
That I do not believe.
Put your investigator to work, Havisham.
Dugal finally got the hunting right,
Grandpa.
Pretty sure chewed up my ball.
We'll find another ball.
You're looking very fit,
Lord Fauntleroy.
I'm trying to be fitter.
I think grandpa looks fit too.
That's because we ride every day.
It's good for us.
Have I told you how dear
you've become to me, Cedric?
You don't have to tell me, grandpa.
I know without you're saying.
Your whole day early
for the party, Mr. Havisham.
But better early
than not at all, I always say.
Unfortunately,
I shall have to miss the party.
I must return to London.
I won't detain you any
longer, Havisham.
I wish you every success.
It will be our success, my Lord.
Lord Fauntleroy.
No stone left unturned, Havisham.
Not the smallest pebble, my Lord.
Mr. Havisham's your best friend,
isn't he, grandpa?
Mr Hobbs always says:
"When push comes to shove,
"here's nothing like having
a true blue friend in your court."
Welcome, Your Ladyship... Sir Harry.
You never thought you'd
see me come through
these doors again, did you, Dawson?
You haven't changed.
Nor have you, my lady.
Fiddlesticks! I'm like a mummy!
Where is my brother?
Waiting for you in the library, my lady.
And the boy?
As soon as you get here.
I'm to bring him to you in the library
as soon as you arrive, my lady.
Harry fears the lion in his den.
Please.
Constancia.
Molyneux.
Harry.
You look well, Constancia.
And you look better
than when I last saw you.
I was surprised to get your invitation.
But so very pleased.
I regret our estrangement.
It was a foolish quarrel
over an inconsequential matter.
For the life of me, I can't recall
the reason for our fracas.
Of no consequence.
Fables... Now tell me about the boy.
He's all Dorincourt!
And I challenge anyone to dispute it.
You're fond of him?
He's a fine boy.
Cedric! Come here!
I am your great Aunt Constancia.
I adored your father.
And you're so like him.
This is your great Uncle Harry.
Pleased to meet you, Uncle Harry.
Well, Cedric. Are you happy here?
It took a little while for me
and grandpa to get acquainted.
But we are fine friends now.
We are indeed.
You'll be amplifying the conversation
after your lessons.
I'm learning how to talk French.
It's pretty tricky.
Run along now.
You actually dote on the boy,
you old curmudgeon.
Nonsense.
Most children are idiots or bores.
It so happens that Cedric is neither.
Surely, his mother deserves
some credit for that.
I prefer not to discuss it.
Oh? I understand your tenants adore her.
It's the boy who's won their affection.
But I have to admit his mother
has brought him up well.
I should like to visit
Cedric's mother this afternoon.
That is entirely up to you to design.
What is it, Dawson?
I thought Lady Lorradaile
and Sir Harry might prefer
tea in their rooms
after their long journey.
Tea and some of those
delicious cucumber and
crest sandwiches for
which you are famous.
After 20 years, our first meeting
deserves a kiss.
There.
I share your happiness, Molyneux.
Cedric is an enchanting child.
Come, Harry.
No!
My Lord?
Cedric is the rightful heir!
I'll accept no other.
I wish you to know
that I entirely disapprove
of my brother's treatment of you.
I accept it for Ceddie's sake, ma'am.
And his father's.
I made scones.
I never understand what
folks here see in them.
But I baked a butter cake too.
And it'll be out of the oven
in two shakes.
And you'll come
and join us when it's ready now?
Right.
No English server would comport
themselves in that fashion.
But Mary isn't a servant.
She is my friend and companion.
As dear to Ceddie as she is to me.
I see.
I like you, Mrs. Errol.
Would you come and spend Christmas
with us at Lorradaile Castle?
That's very kind of you.
I promised Ceddie
I would always be nearby.
I understand.
My mother's sons Maurice
and Bevis were
bitter disappointments to him.
Wastrels enriching.
Your Cedric, your husband,
whom he loved.
Cedric disappointed him too.
By marrying me.
My brother would be not be
so prejudiced if he knew you.
I doubt that will ever happen!
Oh.
Won't Ceddie look dear in this?
He won't be test wearing it.
His mother's not attending.
My grandson, Lord Fauntleroy.
Lady Grace.
You're beautiful enough
to be a princess.
You make the most of your time,
Fauntleroy.
You'll not dare be so foolish
when you're older.
I think Lord Fauntleroy
will always say what he thinks.
So you think I'm beautiful?
Beautifuler than anyone.
Except my mama, of course.
No one should be more beautiful
to a boy than his mother.
Excuse us. Come, Cedric.
You must be introduced
to the other guests.
Freddy, my grandson. Lord Fauntleroy.
Lord Ashbey Delefante.
I knew your father, my boy.
Great Huntsman.
Ride the hounds, my boy?
I only ride to a promontory.
And sometimes the village.
You are a love.
What's that in your pocket, Ceddie?
Oh. It's a gift from Dick the bootblack.
He said I was to wear it when
I'm with all the swells.
So I guess now is the right time.
Molyneux, how do you like
being called a swell?
I daresay have been called worse.
Especially by me.
But you are a bit of a tyrant
when we were
both growing up
in this monstrous old house.
Well, Ceddie.
Are you enjoying the party?
Well. It's not very lively.
I guess is because the music
is not very likely.
Right. It's no more lively
than Westminster Abby.
Will you do something about it?
Constancia!
Fiddlesticks! Come, Ceddie.
Lord Fauntleroy has a request.
Tell them what you'd like them
to play, Ceddie.
Oh, Dem Golden Slippers.
It goes like this.
They played at the Starlight Bar
on Hester Street.
Me and the boys used to
wait in the alley and
watch the dancing girls
when the door opened.
It was sure a sight!
Sing it to them.
Then perhaps our esteemed musicians
can pick up the tune.
All right.
Oh, dem golden slippers!
Golden slippers I'm gonna wear,
because dey look so neat.
Oh, dem golden slippers!
Golden slippers I'm gonna wear,
To walk de golden street.
Shall we?
Why not!
May I?
You may.
Oh, dem golden slippers!
Oh, so, Molyneux!
The House of Dorincourt has finally
got an heir worthy of the title.
Something's troubling you, Molyneux?
What is it?
You'll hear it soon enough.
Faster! Faster!
Dammit, this isn't a funeral.
It may well be.
My Lord.
The worst possible news.
I've never known bad news
to improve with keeping.
Bevis did marry the woman
eight years ago.
She has the marriage certificate.
And it has been verified.
Much as it pains me, my Lord.
I believe her son is
the rightful heir to the title.
Bevis brought me nothing
but unhappiness in life.
And now in death as well.
There's no question about it?
Sir, the ceremony was performed
at White Chapel.
And duly registered.
Why has the woman waited
till now to make her claim?
She told me that only
recently she understood
her son could lay claim to the title.
If anyone had told me
that I could care for a
child as I care for Cedric,
I would not have believed it.
I'm not well liked... here.
He finds me a great liking.
He would've filled my place
better than I had.
He would've done honor to the name.
Bring the woman here.
And her spawn.
House them at the inn.
And thank you.
Get along, boy. We ain't got all day.
We're gonna see your grandpa, the Earl.
Commoner dirt!
Serves his Lordship right.
Treating the captain's great lady
the way he did.
You should not pass judgment.
Perhaps the woman is
not what she appears.
You don't mind the free talk,
Rev. Muldaur?
I know a tart when I see one.
Well, what's she like, Mrs. Dawson?
Think the worst.
And you'll be half right.
Let her come into the house.
And I'll go out of it.
Get me a cup of teano. A sherry.
I feel faint.
How is his Lordship taking it?
As well as can be expected.
What will happen
to little Lord Fauntleroy now?
He'll not be Earl of Dorincourt.
That's what.
I never thought I'd say it but
my heart goes out to the Earl.
I've never seen a man so shattered.
Does it mean I have to go
away from you, grandpa?
That will never happen.
Will I still be your boy like before?
You will always be my boy.
Well, I don't care about the Earl part.
I was just afraid
if I couldn't be the Earl
and I couldn't be your boy
Who would come visiting
on a raw day like this?
It's his honor. His Lordship, I mean.
Kindly come in, your Lordship.
The chair near the fire is comfortable.
Thank you. I prefer to stand.
I shall only stay a moment.
You know why I've come here.
Mr. Havisham has informed me
of the new claim to the title.
That claim will be contested.
If a contest can be made.
Ceddie will have nothing
that is not his own.
The idea that a child
of that outrageous woman should
I'm certain that his mother
cares for him as I care for Ceddie.
And if she was your eldest son's wife,
her son is Lord Fauntleroy.
And mine is not.
Perhaps you prefer your son
not to become the Earl of Dorincourt.
There was a time
when I would've been so inclined.
But there is such suffering.
Such poverty.
I know Ceddie would've used his position
to improve the lot of others.
That he would've been
decent and caring.
Unlike his grandfather?
I've not had the pleasure
of knowing his grandfather.
But I know Ceddie loves you.
Would he love me I wonder
if you had told him, I would
never receive you at the castle?
I think not.
Few women would've remained silent.
I'm an old man. And was tired of life.
Your son gave me something to live for.
It pleased me to think
that someday he would take my place.
It seems that's not to be.
I came to tell you
that Cedric will be wellprovided for,
both now and in the future.
It is your privilege.
And you may see Ceddie
whenever you wish.
I will not deny you his company.
Nor deny him yours.
Thank you. Good afternoon.
Well. Like it's been said,
pride goeth before a fall.
I'm sorry for him, Mary.
This is a bitter moment for him.
Dick!
I got a letter from Ceddie.
That's good news.
You won't think so when
you hear it what it says.
"Dear Mr. Hobbs and Dick,
"I got something curious to tell you.
And I know you will be surprised.
"It's all a mistake.
"And I am not a Lord.
And will not be an Earl.
"A lady married to my uncle Bevis
has a a little boy.
"And he comes first.
"I don't mind it all,
"Seeing as I can live
with mama and Mary now,
"and go see my grandpa every day,
"which is everything turned around.
"Isn't it?"
It sure is.
We are going to stay here because
mama knows that I love my grandpa.
"And that he loves me.
"But I'm not gonna be rich
or be an Earl.
"So there you are."
I'll be blowed.
Now wait. There's more.
"My grandpa is in a terrible state
because you don't like the lady.
"but he'll get over it, I'm sure."
Yeah I'm sure..Uhhuh. Yeah.
"I will write another letter
soon to tell you more.
"I hope business is booming.
Love from your old friend,
"Ceddie.
PS, not Lord Fauntleroy anymore."
You know what? Ceddie's been done in.
Done in proper. In my opinion,
it's a put up job.
That English aristocrat's robbing Ceddie
of his rights because he's an American.
They had a fight against us
ever since the Revolution.
And they're taking it out on Ceddie.
Look it was in this morning's paper,
including a picture.
Hmm. That's Minna!
Yeah, Minna. Minna Errol.
That's what it says.
"Daughterinlaw of English Earl."
Daughterinlaw, my foot!
That's Minna Tipton! That's who that is.
What's the matter with you?
She married my brother Ben!
Yeah, left him flat to go to London
nine, 10 years ago.
With some tinsley show.
And that boy.
He's the spitting image of Ben.
I even know where she had him too.
In Bellevue Hospital!
Well, I'll be jiggered.
There's no question in your mind?
No, sir. That's Minna all right.
Where is your brother Ben now?
Kansas City.
Had a postal card from him
just the other day.
He's running some
rinkydink show down there.
Pack up your brushes and polishes!
I'll pay the damages. Whatever!
We're gonna get ourselves a lawyer.
Faster, man! Faster!
This isn't a funeral!
It's a celebration!
A fraud! I knew it!
But what of her marriage to Bevis?
Illegal since the woman
was already married.
It seems Bevis and the lady tired
of each other quickly and parted.
What is your plan, Havisham?
How do we proceed?
I knew your Lordship
would have no objection
to my moving quickly on this matter,
so I cabled monies
to the lawyer in New York.
To pay passage for the woman's husband
and his brother Dick.
– The bootblack?
– The same.
And since Dick wouldn't come
without Mr. Hobbs
the grocer?
Precisely.
Their ship docks in Liverpool
the day before Christmas.
I've already arranged
for swift transportation to Dorincourt.
Good.
The woman is still at the inn?
Yes, my Lord. Biding her time.
She's to be told nothing…yet.
Nor is anyone to be told.
Lord Fauntleroy, not even to know
that his friends are coming?
Let it be a surprise to him.
Well done, Havisham.
Well done, indeed.
O come, all ye faithful,
Joyful and triumphant!
O come ye,
O come ye to Bethlehem.
Come and behold him.
Born the King of Angels.
O come, let us adore Him.
Well, I'll be jiggered!
Christ the Lord.
You live good if you're an aristocrat,
sir.
I wouldn't mind having
my shoe shining concession here.
You could put on a proper circus.
Clowns. Elephants. The big top.
The lady has arrived, your Lordship.
She still suspects nothing, I hope.
Nothing, my Lord.
She believes she's to take up residence.
Show the lady in, Dawson.
Mr. Tipton.
Would you be good enough
to stand at my side?
Minna! I see you've been
up to your old tricks.
This lady is your wife, Mr. Tipton?
Tied the knot nine years ago
this January.
And fathered a little feller
one year later.
Liar!
I never saw your ugly face before!
It's my Minna, all right.
Shrew and fishwife from the word Go.
Who you gonna believe?
Them shady characters or me?
Who's practically your own
flesh and blood, once removed.
My boy is you write in proper heir.
And I want what's coming to me.
What's coming to you is
the back of my hand.
You gonna let him
talk to me like that?
Me, who's the mother
of your lovely little grand son?
Save your breath, Minna. The jig's up.
And you know what!
Shut up, you worm!
Some father you are,
depriving your own son!
You dirty doubledealing spoiler!
You lost your looks.
But not your sweet disposition!
It's hello and goodbye, Minna.
Well, I ain't leaving.
I deserve something.
For the tender care I gave
your drunkard son.
Is Mrs. Tipton entitled
to compensation, Havisham?
Hardly, my Lord.
I suggest we send for the Constable.
British jurisprudence deals severely
with frauds and pretenders.
You know the way out, madam.
I suggest you take it.
I should've done you in
instead of leaving you.
I am forever in your debt, Mr. Tipton.
It's been a pleasure, Your Highness.
Dawson, kindly send for Lord Fauntleroy.
Already have, my Lord.
They're here?
Mr. Hobbs, Dick?
Never been so jiggered
when Dawson said you were here.
Not half so jiggered as us.
Up in this here castle
with an ocean voyage to boot.
Boy, you sure do look elegant
in them clothes, Ceddie.
I have to wear them. It goes
with the job of being a Lord.
Well, they're becoming, Ceddie.
Mind you, I ain't one to admire
the trappings of aristocrats.
Hey, could we see the dungeon, Ceddie?
I ain't never seen one before.
And I sure would like to
before we have to go back.
But Dawson said you won't
leave before a fortnight.
What's a fortnight?
Two whole weeks.
I hope your business doesn't suffer.
Or yours, Mr. Hobbs.
I wouldn't have missed this trip
and its consequences.
For all the tea in China, Ceddie.
Me neither.
Well, then will have a fine time.
There will be
a great Christmas party tomorrow.
And you and Mr. Hobbs
are the guests of honor.
Grandpa said for you to stay
in the house of Dorincourt.
Whatever that means.
There will be music and dancing.
And heaps to eat.
I just wish Mama and Mary
could come too.
Will have a separate Christmas party
with Mama and Mary!
We sure will.
Okay!
It's snowing!
I wonder if Mama is
watching the snow coming down too?
Wake up, your Lordship. Wake up!
Mr. Hobbs and Dick up yet?
Up and about.
They had breakfast hours ago.
And they was wanting to see the stables.
Hours ago?
Why didn't you wake me up?
His Lordship said
I was to let you sleep in.
Seeing as how
there is a big day ahead.
But we best step lively now.
His Lordship wants you
in the Great Hall.
I guess grandpa wants me
to see my Christmas presents.
What do you think of Dick?
He thinks you're smashing.
He's a cashew nut, Dick.
Here you are, your Lordship.
And you're to go straight
to the Great Hall. Don't forget.
I'm coming, grandpa!
I'll be jiggered!
Now that IS a Christmas tree!
Mama!
Custom has decreed,
that each Christmas,
a celebration should be held
in the servant's hall
for all at the castle.
This year the celebration is being
held here in the Great Hall.
By my grandson's degree.
This is a most joyous Christmas
I've ever known.
I ask you to drink to the
health and happiness...
of the future Earl of Dorincourt:
Lord Fauntleroy.
For Lord Fauntleroy!
You must respond.
This is the best Christmas I ever had.
And I don't mind one bit
being Lord Fauntleroy.
And the future Earl of Dorincourt.
Merry Christmas, everybody!
And to all the people everywhere!
Merry Christmas!
Did I do all right?
Shop this shows fashion, download the
"LookLive" app in iTunes