Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Excuse me?
I'm looking for a mechanic.
Is there one here?
Maybe I can help.
What do you need?
It has to be done right away.
You have to know
what you're doing.
I'm not that busy.
What's the matter?
I'm not sure.
Maybe you should check it out.
Maybe I bettter.
Looks ok from here.
Great customer service.
A little bit of cleaning and paint
and it'll be ready for business.
It's time for me to play
in the Super Bowl.
The guys will take you apart.
We're gonna do it this time.
You ready?
Turn back!
Here it comes!
Alright!
Suckers walk.
What does that mean, Frankie?
It means everything's okay.
How do you think I did?
Pretty good with the six-graders.
You really build me up...
What's the matter?
You don't look too happy today.
I'm missing you already.
Soon you'll see me so much that
you'll pray to have some time alone.
- I don't believe you.
- Oh yeah, believe it.
Now that's Italian!
- I have to go.
- No, Frank!
So I'm not so good against kids?
Should I try a different sport?
Yeah, golf.
Golf?
- Wanna see my swing?
- You in whites...
Like those old guys?
Can you see me on a golf course?
Good thing I've a sense of humor
or I would take that personally.
Time to go to work
Be good.
Wait a minute.
I've got something for you.
What's this?
It'll bring you luck.
That's nice.
Thanks.
I could use it.
- How was your time off?
- Great.
Did you see that game?
- I missed it.
- It was awesome.
- Was it really?
- You missed a good one, buddy.
I bet my weekend was better
than yours.
I'll bet it was.
Here you go, Roger.
How's the Diesel running, Jimmy?
Forget it. It stops, it stalls.
I don't know what to do with it.
- You got water in the fuel line.
- Open.
Are you sure?
I'd bet time on it.
- Take it off.
- Alright.
See you later, Jimmy.
- You'll get more starch next time.
- Good.
Say hi to the wife.
How are you?
Frank! What did you bring me?
Here. Kill yourself!
What about the girl?
I had one for you but the guards
liked her so much they kept her.
I knew it. I can't depend on you.
- Did you check out the garage?
- It's beautiful.
Beautiful? No garage is beautiful.
This one is. It's great.
Can I tell you something?
I'm getting out soon.
I don't come cheap,
but I know my way around cars.
If you need help, call me.
I fix them, I don't steal them.
I was framed.
What? I was framed.
What's going on?
I don't know but it's official.
Open up cell 210.
On your feet, Leone.
- What do you want?
- Take him.
You're being transferred.
Where? What the hell...
- That's not necessary.
- Step back, officer.
He's in our custody now.
You've got the wrong guy.
Transferred where?
- Move it.
- What did I do?
Open up! Get in!
What have I done? Damn!
Where are we going?
Talk to me.
Let's go, Leone.
Get his ass out here.
Come on, get out.
- Where are we?
- Shut up.
You made a mistake.
There's no mistake.
Welcome to Gateway.
- Drumgoole?
- Warden Drumgoole!
- Captain?
- Move him.
One bar of soap and two rolls
of toilet paper a month.
- If somebody steals them...
- Move!
If you lose them, you'll wipe
your ass with your shirt.
You have one uniform.
Your number is 510. Remember it!
This is C Wing. You will eat,
shower and take yard time here.
Miss a count: you're in the hole.
Miss two:
I'll put you in the house of pain.
Convict. Two things.
One: I am Meissner.
Two:
Never fuck with Meissner.
Inside.
- What about the cuffs?
- Let him get used to them.
Officer Fryberg, contact 5235.
521.
521. Open it.
You better not eyeball me, boy.
How were the accommodations
last night?
Like your mama used to do you?
- You did his mama, didn't you?
- Twice.
Open the door! You hear me?
Hello, Frank.
In the old days the warden
would come from his office,
to this chamber and witness
the putting to death of a criminal.
120 men and four women
were electrocuted in that chair.
Beautiful, isn't it?
When I came to Gateway, I had it
put back into perfect working order
to remind me
of how things ought to be.
It's been five years since
you escaped.
Yes, how time flies.
In all the years that I was warden,
you're the only one that made it.
That's what I read in the papers.
Of course you did.
You and your lawyers
did everything to make the news,
the media.
Distorting the truth,
making a criminal into a hero
and the warden into a criminal.
You took my future away from me.
Those bleeding heart politicians
politicians sent you to Norwood.
I ended up here in Gateway,
the worst shit-hole in the system.
I begged you, Drumgoole.
Do you remember that?
I had two weeks to go
and all I asked for was one hour
to visit a dying old man.
I was only doing my job.
There's a lot of ways to do it.
You could have given me
and escorted leave.
- You could've done that.
- You broke the law.
You broke the law
and I was punished.
I got five years. I paid my debt!
To the state, not to me.
But you're going to.
I only have six months left.
That's a lifetime here.
Anything can happen.
This is hard time. You have
no rights unless I give them to you.
You feel no pleasure
unless I allow it. This is hell.
And I'll give you the guided tour.
Ok, tough guy,
open your mouth.
Roll your tongue.
Are you trying to kiss me?
Show me you ears.
What are you looking at, asshole?
- Did you check his nose?
- Yes.
Good.
This is a delousing chamber.
Don't breathe.
The gas can be harmful
to your lungs.
Stand with you legs apart,
arms extended away from your body.
When I tell you, take a deep breath
and hold it for 30 seconds.
Start now.
Ten seconds.
Not yet.
He can take more.
Mr. Braden,
inmates are physically more capable
than you can imagine.
If you underestimate them,
it'll cost you dearly.
Watch out for the birds.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Billy, get that weight.
Move it, ace.
That's my spot.
That's my spot too.
- Any spot here that isn't yours?
- No.
There're all mine.
If you want one, you gotta pay.
Not so fast, ace.
I'm not gonna gouge you,
That thing around your neck
will buy a spot
for the day.
I'll put a hole in your heart.
Break it up!
Break it up, I said!
Back off!
Drop the weapon.
There's no shank here.
- Come on.
- Mother fucker.
Spread your legs.
You're making a big mistake.
You'll go in the hole for that.
Where's your witness?
Where's your evidence?
- He saw it.
- He didn't see anything.
He saw the shank, right?
I didn't see anything.
You're making a bad mistake, Braden.
Get him the fuck out.
He would have put
that shank in you.
Why are you covering him?
You have your rules
and we have ours.
I know the face,
and I know the name. Hey, Frank.
Frank Leone, right.
My name's Dallas. I was in
Treadmore, when you busted out.
You were in A Block.
Right, I was in A Block.
You have a good memory, man.
Treadmore doesn't have an A Block.
Watch your feet.
I was there on transfer.
Less than two hours,
but I know all about you.
You're looking at a devoted fan.
D.T.A.
D.T.A. Ok.
What's that, man?
Don't trust anybody.
Words to survive by. Your feet.
D.T.A.?
D.T.A.
You've got to trust someone.
I'll make it clear.
See this fat tub of shit back here?
That's Manly.
His partner's and Wiley.
They're sadistic pigs.
They are only happy
when they are hurting someone.
If the warden wants you down,
he uses them.
And the black dude in the booth
is Captain Meissner.
He runs the guards.
He's one bad dude, ok?
We already met.
I've got to work, move you feet.
Listen Frank.
When you decide
to make your break,
and I know you will,
you come and talk to me, ok?
You come talk to Dallas.
Anything you want or need,
I can get. Ok?
- No damn way.
- Come on, Eclipse.
You're always crying about needing a
man who knows his engines, Holmes.
Don't Holmes me. The only thing
you brought here is trouble.
Come on, Eclipse.
I know all about you. Your thing
with Drumgoole won't come in here.
The boys have no problems with me
and I have no problems with them.
Don't make me look bad.
I promised him a job, you owe me.
I don't owe you
or anybody anything. Hey, you!
Get your face out of that motor.
Get your face out of there.
You know nothing about motors.
Get away form it, ok?
It's been a long time
since I last saw a 365 motor block.
Take a good look. That's the
last time you'll see one here.
Frank, we can work this out,
we're all gentlemen here.
That's alright, it's his place.
He knows what he wants.
Thanks a lot,
I appreciate the endorsement.
Hold on.
You don't want this job anyway,
greasy fingers and oily clothes.
Don't worry, I'll take care of you.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Prison joke: I lost my watch.
will you help me find it?
Get your ass out of here.
You should put on a few pounds.
You look a little frail.
I meant what I said.
I'll get you something good.
Something easy, something cool.
Shut up and get inside.
Here's your shit from Norwood,
Leone.
Lock in!
Problem?
No, I have no problems.
- What the hell is going on?
- Look Miss,
he's here with 2000 other inmates...
I don't give a damn about the rest!
I want to know
about Leone and I...
Calm down, Miss.
Leone is alright.
He was a model prisoner.
Why did you bring him here?
Routine transfer.
It's hot in here.
I know. But at least it's easy.
I know, man, I'm sorry.
I didn't do too well.
Walk with me, I have to show you
something. It's important.
- No, here, you try.
- No, come on.
- You'll like it.
- I'm not into hard labor.
It's cool, it's easy.
I'm burnt out. Come on, man.
You're gonna love this.
Watch the steam, Frank.
I got these off an old trustee
plumber. They said he was a nut.
That doesn't mean he wasn't smart.
- Hurry up.
- Alright.
There are tunnels
under every cell block.
They lead to the steam plant.
I go out across the steam lines.
I'll shimmy across the steam pipes
to the sally port.
There are trucks coming and going.
I wait for my time...
and I am on a truck that's leaving.
I'm dearly departing Dallas.
Am I keeping you awake?
You're the doctor,
I want your opinion.
Let's run it backwards.
I see these trucks,
they stop running at about 9.
At 9 most of the guards complete
and all the inmates are awake.
So before you go ten feet,
every con here will know it.
And this... shimmy?
Shimmy slide.
You're going to shimmy slide across
200 yards of steam pipe at 150(?
Departing Dallas
will become Deep Fried Dallas.
- It was just a thought.
- That's what counts.
I've got a plane to catch.
Thanks a lot.
Dallas?
You got a cigarette?
This is my last one.
Here, finish that.
It's not much,
but it's the thought that counts.
Last call for the mess hall!
Looks like garbage stew,
like mom used to make.
That's why I shot her.
- Can I have some more gravy?
- Gravy?
You want some gravy?
- Here's some gravy.
- It's all over my food.
Move it!
- What's he in for?
- Murder.
He was just in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
He waited in the car while his
buddy went for beer. Boom boom!
Two guys dead.
The kid's doing the big bitch now.
Double life.
He'll make parole
when he's about 400.
Move it!
Are you a slow study or what?
Forget it.
I didn't get a chance to reserve.
Why don't we sit over there.
- What are you doing?
- I'm taking this.
- Go take something else.
- Are you looking for trouble?
- Want some cake?
- Something wrong?
I'm not hungry.
- Who are you?
- Nobody.
I'm on a diet.
Is this spot taken?
You should've hit that fat dirt bag.
Shut up. He just saved you.
What's your name?
Why does anybody need a name
in a joint like this?
It helps when you get mail.
I need a name?
They call me Killer.
That's original.
Did you think that up yourself?
I call myself what I want, ok?
Killer, this is Dallas
and I'm Frank.
What are these supposed to be?
These might be peas or
they might be toxic waste
Who cares? It's all crap, anyway.
Eat your vegetables,
- you'll grow big and strong.
- Stick your vegetables.
You know there are about
325 other "Killers" in here.
Put your leg in the aisle.
Be ready to move.
Nobody tells me what to do.
You have to be ready to move first.
You have time to get to first base.
"First Base",
there's a name for him.
It's good to be outside.
It's cold outside.
It's not that bad.
It's good keep moving.
How can you keep that "up" attitude
in a joint like this?
It's a mind set.
Your body has to be in here
but your brain doesn't.
Keep moving and you won't become
a piece of this place.
Is that guru stuff?
- Maybe I should become a guru.
- Is that sarcasm?
Fucking birds.
They don't eat in the rain.
They'll come back.
Will you save your bread for me
tomorrow?
Sure. Put that on your list.
Thanks.
Why do you talk to crazy?
It's a waste of time.
To you it's a waste of time.
To him it's all he's got.
In here you have
to respect something.
You have to protect what you have.
You don't know anything yet.
Come on, let's run.
I'm gonna get wet.
I'll send you laundry bill.
Did you feel something, Leone?
Do you want to play?
We're a man short.
I'm talking to you!
Hey punk. Go paint your nails
and answer to "bitch"!
You've got a big mouth. Shut it!
You mother fucker! I'll tear your...
You want to play? We'll play.
You talk too much. Let's play.
Goddamn right we'll play.
You and I will play later.
Give it to him!
You want more?
We have more for you.
Stay there!
That's a cheap shot!
This isn't a game, man.
This is a lesson.
- Do you have something to say?
- First down!
Fuck you, that's your last one.
You're dead, Leone.
You won't last the game!
Get in there!
Hut one, hut two,
hut three.
Don't mix it with us.
Finish him off.
Go over there. That's who
you're playing for anyway.
What took you so long?
You need the help
and I the exercise.
So, call a play.
You're dead!
What was that?
The F train, son.
Don't lay down on me.
Come on.
Come on, Leone.
You son of a bitch!
Over the tackle on "two".
Set!
You're dead!
Hut one.
Two.
Let me through.
Next time I want something,
you give it to me.
Move it, the game's over.
You don't listen, do you?
Are you ok? Come on.
Put him down.
You're not a doctor.
He's on his own.
Get inside.
You're a badass, huh?
See you inside, Leone.
You won't break me.
Still interested in the job?
Yes, I am.
You know you way
around an engine.
Who taught you?
An old man named Galleti.
Took me off the streets
when I was 14
and kept me off the street corners.
- Where is everybody?
- It's quitting time.
We've got the place to ourselves.
Did you break out for him?
Yes, I owed him.
What put you in the joint?
One night these punks broke into
the garage and beat up Galleti.
The whole neighborhood
knew about it. So did the cops.
The punks were connected
so the cops didn't do anything.
And I did.
These guys ended up in hospital
and I did 18 in Treadmore
for aggravated assault.
A little contraband?
Why not?
I see why they call you Eclipse.
You're... 6'7?
I block a lot of the sun, don't I?
Yeah, you do.
I had a guy who used to get me
good Havanas.
Not this crap.
But someday...
- Someday...
- Someday.
- That's not bad.
- At least they're cheap.
What are you hiding back there?
That's my baby.
Good body work.
- This is Mabeline.
- Hello Mabeline.
This is my baby.
Come on.
1965 Ford Mustang, 8 cylinder.
225 horse power.
When did you last turn it over?
She's been dead for fifteen years.
Nobody could bring her back to life.
I'm a body man myself.
Mind if I give it a try?
It's a dead issue, Frank.
Nothing's dead around here
until it's buried.
Save the headstone.
Nothing is dead until it's buried.
Purrs like a kitten!
A toast. Let's do the poem.
- What poem?
- The poem, man.
The jailhouse poem.
- We wrote it ourselves.
- Excuse me.
When we're in a sober mood
We worry, work and think
When we're in a drunken mood
We gamble, play and drink
But when our moods are over,
When our time has come to pas
We hope they bury us upside down
So that the warden can kiss our ass!
I like that.
It's catchy.
This is the best.
This is good, man.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
I wouldn't smoke around it but
it's as good as any dollar around.
Check, please.
When my moods are over
and my...
That's not it.
Are you married
or thinking about it?
Are you proposing to me?
I'm not married.
Will you when you get out?
That's the plan.
You know,
I had this really nice girl.
She was nice. And we were in love.
We started talking about
gettting married.
She has three brothers,
one percent retarded.
They were being on me.
Some guys don't appreciate romance.
Don't take it personally.
She wrote me for a while.
Then it just stopped.
That's when it hit me:
I'm never going to be with
a girl again. Or even see one.
I'll end up like Eclipse
kissing pictures in magazines.
There are so many things
I've never done.
I didn't learn how to drive.
What?
I never learned to drive.
I hope we don't get
a speeding ticket,
I'd hate to end up in jail.
Look wise guy, do you want
to learn to drive or not?
Cut it sharp.
That's it.
Now, left into 42nd Street.
We'll go to Broadway
- and check out the action.
- What Broadway? We're in a garage.
Come on. Work with me.
You wanna stay here
or check out the action?
I want to check out the action.
- Then left on 42nd Street.
- Okay, I got it.
The place is jumping.
Look at the action here!
Check out
those fine-looking ladies!
Hey honey, want a ride?
Hey baby.
- No reaction.
- They're not your type.
- When were you in Atlantic City?
- I've never been.
- What do you think of it?
- Do I like it?
It's the best. The lights...
The broadwalk is always jumping,
day and night.
There's hot music.
High rollers, parties.
You've got money,
you gamble.
10,000 chorus girls!
Hey honey, feel like a ride
in my new vehicle?
That was great.
You're ready for Indianapolis?
You got the touch.
Would you do me a favor?
Everything was great,
but I would like to hear the engine.
If we start the engine
the guards will come in
and we'll all land up in the hole.
Forget it.
Just for ten seconds.
It will last the rest of my life.
You are a pain in the ass.
Please let me hear that engine.
We built it, man.
Go on. 10 seconds.
Looking good.
It's beautiful, baby.
Hit it one time.
One more time!
Damn it. Frank!
Kill it, Frank, come on.
You did it. Turn it off.
Kill it, Frank.
Come on First, turn it off!
If I turn it off,
I'll never turn it on again, right?
That's right.
Turn it off, First.
I'm sorry, Frank.
Get him out of the car!
Stop him!
Stop that kid!
First! Stop, you crazy bastard!
Stop that car!
I repeat: Stop that car.
They'll kill you!
This is Meissner. Stop firing.
The warden said...
I said stop firing!
First, turn it off!
Hold it!
Look out Frank, be careful!
Get out of the car.
- They'll kill you.
- Did you see that Frank?
- Are you crazy?
- It was beautiful!
I can drive!
I can drive a car!
You're a crazy son-of-a-bitch.
Out of the way. Clear the car!
You just got yourself
a trip to the hole.
Leave Frank alone!
- Out of the way.
- Move back!
Let him go.
You have the wrong man.
Take Leone to the hole. Six weeks.
It wasn't his fault!
Save it.
I want five inmates.
Give me a bat.
I want to break up this car.
Hold him right there!
I want you to watch this, Leone.
To the honeymoon suite!
Good night.
- You should have been notified.
- Why is he in isolation?
I can't tell you.
Then I want to see the warden!
Not today.
When the light comes on, stand up
and state you name and number.
Name and number!
Leone, 510.
Face the camera.
Name and number.
Leone, 510.
On your feet. Name and number.
Give Mr. Leone half rations
for the rest of his time here.
Name and number.
Get up!
He seems a little sluggish.
Wake him up.
Cold enough?
- Wanna see my swing?
- You in whites...
Like this?
Can you see me on a golf course?
Leone, 510.
Upright. Name and number.
You'll pray to have some time alone.
I don't think so.
Trust me, I know about these things.
Leone, 510.
I need water.
Name and number.
Marilyn Monroe.
37... something.
35.
Open cell 121.
Hey, I didn't mean it!
I didn't say anything!
That's enough.
- Who ordered this?
- The warden.
Does he hate him enough
to kill him? That's not my job.
Mr. Sensitive.
He thinks we're too rough
with Leone.
Did you forget who the cops
and the cons are?
Be careful!
Stop it!
Your stick, Mr. Braden.
Pussy.
You get the hell out of my sight,
before I shine my boots with
your face, you fat piece of shit!
Your time's up.
Remember what I told you.
Roll with the system
or it's only going to get harder.
And it's gettting shorter too.
What's new, Mr. Braden?
How's the family?
How are the Jets?
Don't forget to check your bed.
Hey, Frank.
Did somebody die in here?
Not a nice welcome home, is it?
The engine block is full of sand.
That was Chink.
What are we going to do?
Forget it.
We put all we have into this car.
We can't let Chink slide.
Let it go, First Base.
Aren't you the guy who says
you have to protect what's yours?
You watch my back
and I'll watch yours?
I guess that was just jive
now that you're a short-timer.
You're incredible.
Did you think that is your car?
This is the warden's car.
Do you think Chink Weber did this?
Drumgoole did this.
Did you think that
we would take our dates out with it?
Rotate it on weekends?
Ernie, you take it on Friday, Dallas
on Saturday. And Eclipse,
you got it Sunday.
Is that what you thought?
It's his! This lift, the tools
the whole garage is his!
The whole goddamn place is his!
Remember that. Once you start
buying into the "our car" concept,
you're his too.
Just let it go.
I thought you were our leader.
I'm not your leader!
This isn't a gang!
We are convicts,
we're prisoners, we're inmates.
As long as we're here,
we'll stay his.
We're his.
Nothing will change that.
You've got to face the facts.
You guys will stay,
no doubt about it.
But I got 3 weeks
to get out of here.
In 3 weeks I'm walking.
Nothing will change that.
That's all I care about.
Nothing for nothing, man.
He's right.
Leone,
how do you like my belt buckle?
I like it too.
A little souvenir of you.
What are you going to do about it?
You mean six weeks in the hole
killed your guts and your appetite?
It ain't over, you son-of-a-bitch.
Anyone call this spot?
You guys made a reservation.
Are you on a diet?
Cutting back a little.
Here, take some of mine.
Here's some bread.
- Thanks.
- Tomatoes, celery.
I'm not playing football.
Don't worry about that guy.
He's in for life.
You only have a few weeks to go.
It's a miracle, First Base
finally learned something.
- Who's gonna say grace?
- Grace.
She was terrific wasn't she?
I wanted to rely on you, Weber.
He won't be pushed.
Because you're not pushing
in the right place.
Everyone has a weak spot.
Find his
or I'll have to find
a new yard boss.
Welcome to the Gateway races!
Let's start the race.
What's your bug's name?
Dirt Creature.
Three to two on it.
- What's yours called?
- Rear Entry.
Place your bets.
Two will get you three
and five, four.
Everything I got on Dirt Creature.
The house on Rear Entry.
All bets are in.
Gentlemen, start your insects.
I need a win.
You can't do that.
The stewards have to decide.
You can't push your bug.
Victory by rear end.
We're gonna rerun the race.
- What are you doing down there?
- Shit.
Penja, you're on the wrong detail.
Get your ass up here.
Clean up the gym.
We've got to rematch race later.
I'm getting out of here.
All bets are off.
Now, asshole!
Give me a break.
I have to put my jacket on.
Watch my bug.
I'll take care of it for you.
Delicious.
Do it today.
- Clean this place up.
- It's already clean.
- Are you deaf?
- Shut you mouth and do it.
Come on, one by one.
Get him down. Hold his head.
I told you we'd play later.
- They got First!
- I can't hear you!
- What's up?
- They got First Base in the gym.
- Again.
First!
Let me have it.
20 years old.
The kid's 20 years old.
I told you.
I know.
You want me, you got me.
You want me, you fucking Nazi.
You got me.
No.
I'll kill you!
Fight!
Get him!
I'll kill you!
You son-of-a-bitch!
Finish him off!
Do it!
Pussy face!
Go on! Drop it!
Linen run.
Get a move on,
I'm trying to make a living.
Florence Nightingale.
How are you?
Alright.
- You're out in three weeks.
- Seems like three years.
Three weeks is a blink!
What did they do with the kid?
They sent him home.
The kid told me once:
Your body has to be in prison
but your mind can be
wherever it wants.
He told you that?
Yeah.
I brought you some toilet paper
in case you want to write
some poetry or something.
Colonel Klink.
Let me out of here.
It wasn't your fault, ok?
Remember that.
Roberta, have Ms. Lowell
photograph for an ID.
I'm reinstating
Mr. Leone's privileges.
I want to make sure
Frank is alright.
He's recovering nicely.
In 3 weeks he'll be out of here and
you'll have a happy life together.
Thanks for coming.
Thank you, Warden.
Look into the light.
Hi, baby.
Hi.
How are you?
- I was worried.
- You look great.
30 minute visit.
Compliments of the warden.
- Don't waste it.
- How do you feel?
Pretty good, thanks, sweetheart.
30 minutes.
If you need any help,
give us a call.
- Are they all like that?
- Forget it. You look great.
Don't tell me what I look like.
I missed you so much.
No more separations. Promise?
Promise.
- Time is up.
- Nice...
What wrong with you?
Time's up.
The warden said half an hour.
The warden changed his mind.
What do you mean?
I want to talk to the warden.
You want is to do
is keep your mouth shut,
fix your clothes and get out.
Come on.
Don't touch her.
What did you say?
Don't touch her?
You don't learn!
I'm leaving.
Three weeks.
Come here.
Do I know you?
No, but I know you.
I was at Treadmore.
A Block?
Treadmore doesn't have an A Block.
That's right.
- We have something in common.
- What's that?
We're both getting out soon.
You in a few weeks,
and me the day after tomorrow.
What happened?
One beating too many.
I've had a hard time here.
We both have, haven't we?
You're right about that.
Can I get you anything
when I get out?
No, I'm alright.
I'm just a lucky, I guess.
I have a job lined up.
It pays a grand for two hours' work.
Not bad, eh?
What do you have to do?
Rape this bitch.
I get an extra100
for each scream.
I'll kill you!
- Chink says hello.
- You touch her, you're dead.
Guard!
Manly!
- What's your problem?
- I need to use the phone.
You know you can't.
The guy is gonna kill my girlfriend!
What guy?
The guy in the wheelchair!
- I've got to warn her!
- The wheelchair is empty.
Don't play with me, Manly.
I have to warn her.
Everybody's got problems, Leone.
Get some sleep.
God damn!
Doing some spring cleaning?
Dallas, come here!
What is it?
I need some help.
No questions asked.
You're busting out?
You only have three weeks to go.
Just help me.
It will only take a couple of days.
- I need it tonight.
- I can't do that.
When I finish it's all locked.
Listen to me.
Chink has paid a convict off
to get Melissa.
I'd love to help but I can't do
the impossible. You're hurting me.
I'll take you with me.
No shit?
What's the plan?
You'll know when you have to.
You're taking the tunnels.
Just be here, alright?
Convict, move out of there.
Use some bleach on that.
I'm coming out, Colonel.
Linen run.
How are you?
You're late. Get it done.
- Yes sir.
- Do you still make that jail-booze?
Absolutely not. I've joined
the Alcoholics Unanimous.
You talk some shit, man.
It's bad for my nervous system.
It makes me talk too much.
Hurry up.
I'll be right out.
No! Help!
Come on. Let's go.
We've got ten minutes.
Sweet dreams, Moby Dick.
Come on!
The tools, man.
You got it.
Here I go.
Oh God, I'm jumping.
There are rats in here, Frank.
No!
This way to the steam plant.
It's this way.
I remember the map, it's this way.
I'm positive. Let's go!
D.T.A., Frank.
Isn't that what you taught me?
Right on schedule.
I'm sorry.
You're my ticket out of here.
Damn you!
You had me set up the whole time?
Not the whole time.
I have 30 years to go.
The warden made me a deal.
You dumb bastard.
He made me a deal!
We don't make deals
with escaping prisoners.
What are you talking about?
You said if I delivered...
Shut up.
You're going back to the population.
Population?
You can't do this to me, warden!
I snitched on him.
They'll finish me!
Tough.
I came through, god damn it!
We had a deal!
That's enough. You'll kill him.
That's enough.
You'll get ten years
for a second escape attempt.
I knew you'd try. I told them
you were a hard core criminal
and they'll believe me now.
And you better believe me.
You'll be doing hard time here
for the rest of your life.
You know what to do.
Some deal maker.
See? Shit does float, doesn't it?
You know what else?
Don't worry about that psycho
hurting your bitch girlfriend.
We decided to keep him here.
Didn't we, officer?
She's not my type.
We'll teach you a lesson...
graduate you with honors.
Switch on the steam, Mastrone!
Put him in.
Bring him in here.
Push him in, Darrell. Do it!
Do it!
Rape this.
My face is burning!
School's out, punk.
Frank, don't leave me here.
I'm sorry.
Take me with you.
Let him go, Manly.
What are you going to do?
Are you ok, Frank?
I'm ok.
You can trust me.
Put it down, Dallas.
I won't hurt you any more.
Put it down.
You don't wanna do it.
You fat piece of shit.
Don't do it, Dallas.
Are you trying to scare me?
Don't do it!
You won't do it!
Oh yeah?
You don't have the balls to do it,
punk.
You're wrong.
Stoolie.
- Put it down.
- You're wrong!
Switch to backup.
We have a power outage in C Wing.
Go to the utility corridor.
You better have a good reason not to
tell me about Leone's escape plans.
I have a dead officer and
a dead inmate but no answers!
I was saving an informant's life
by keeping it a secret.
Why would a man
with 3 weeks to go
try to break out and kill 2 men?
We can ask him when we catch him
Defect cable
in the utility corridor.
He's going onto the roof.
Bring up zone 2.
Get more light in there.
I'm in the wellroom.
This is where he went out.
Check the far bank over there.
That's 150 meters under water.
Do you really think he made it?
Until you bring me a body,
I've got an escaped prisoner.
- This is Drumgoole. Sector 4, over.
- Meissner. Sector 4, go.
What do you have?
Right now nothing, sir.
I'm thinking of calling the local
and State Police.
No outside agencies.
This is an internal matter.
He's alive. I want him.
Arm a tactical squad
and meet me in my office.
Mr. Braden,
we will continue this search.
You won't get away with it.
You know that don't you?
I could have got out.
But I'm not going to spend my life
running from you.
Paul, look at this.
Get inside. Pull it!
You can't hold me as a hostage.
Shut up! Do you recognize the chair?
You built it, didn't you?
Get in there.
Don't think about moving.
You're gonna take me to hell?
I'll show you hell.
Move you leg.
Dallas...
was fried
the way you're going to fry.
And First Base.
You broke his neck!
You'll fry here.
It's a perfect fit.
You can't make this work.
You're too stupid.
You're scum.
Shut up! I'll show you scum.
You can't kill a man, Frank.
You don't have the guts.
10 more years, you said.
How about 20?
Or 30?
It doesn't matter how much I get.
You won't be satisfied.
You've got me for life.
Make a hole.
Take it down.
I'm not doing life for nothing!
Lean on it!
They'll break that door down.
And when they come in here
they'll break your skull.
You'll beg me to let them kill you.
- Come on!
- Meissner!
Harder!
Lean on it!
No!
Break the window!
Shoot me!
Don't shoot!
His hand's taped to it!
No!
Don't shoot!
Hold your fire.
Hold your fire!
Shoot!
Just relax.
I'm glad you're here.
It's not official without witnesses.
He wants me to accept responsibility
for his escape.
I don't want a confession.
You set everything up.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Chink Weber.
The cop that was going
to rape Melissa!
Dallas.
The killing of the kid.
Guilty on all counts.
Prove it. That's your problem.
You can't prove anything.
I don't have to prove anything.
I'm here for an execution.
I demand to be released!
No!
Don't do it, Leone!
Take it easy.
You deserve it. Pay back.
Please, Frank.
Don't kill me.
It's true.
I confess.
Mr. Meissner,
everything that he said was true.
I set him up.
Everything.
Please.
Don't kill me.
Don't...
We'll see you in hell, Drumgoole.
It works better with this.
Take him to the hole, Mr. Meissner.
Mr. Braden,
take the prisoner to the hole!
Cuff him.
Somebody get me out of this chair.
Thank you, Mr. Meissner.
I said take him to the hole.
I can't do that.
Take the warden into custody.
I said take him. What are you doing?
- Cuff him.
- Stop it!
I am the warden of this institution
and you will obey... stop that!
That was a stupid confession
to save my life.
Are you crazy, Mr. Meissner?
No, but you are.
Until this matter is resolved,
you will remain in our custody.
I'll have your ass for this.
I'll have your ass.
Move it!
I only wanted to do my time.
You'll get the chance.
Move him.
- Take care of yourself.
- You too. Thanks, big man.
Is that okay?
It's alright.
I got this one
from Fidel Castro himself.
See you, big man.
Hold it.
Crack the outside.
You know what I'll miss about you?
What's that?
Your incredible smile.
Take care of yourself, Leone.
Thanks, Captain.
Lock up!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org