Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Madeline!
Got ya.
In an old house in Paris
that was covered in vines...
lived 12 little girls...
in two straight lines.
In two straight lines
they broke their bread...
and brushed their teeth...
and went to bed.
They smiled at the good...
and frowned at the bad.
And sometimes they were very sad.
They left the house at half past nine...
in two straight lines...
in rain...
or shine.
The smallest one was Madeline.
What do you think?
It's great.
You've really captured it.
- Madeline!
- Au revoir.
The circus is coming!
Come! Come!
Come one, come all!
See the Idiots Popopov!
Experience the depths of terror...
at the sight of the man-eating tiger!
To the tiger in the zoo,
Madeline just said...
Pooh-pooh!
And nobody knew so well
how to frighten Miss Clavel.
Get down!
Take that!
Bless Lady Covington...
and protect her
that she may recover quickly...
And bless this food
we are about to receive to our use...
and us to Thy service.
Amen.
Chicken Helene.
Good night, little girls.
Thank the Lord you are well.
And now go to sleep.
Good night, good night, Miss Clavel.
Elizabeth, Veronica, Sylvette...
Marie-Odile, Serena, Beatrice...
Lucinda, Chantal, Lolo...
Victoria, Aggie and Madeline.
Especially Madeline.
Amen.
Something is not right.
Madeline's burning up!
Should we call the fire department?
No, Chantal.
"Burning up" is a metaphor.
Like " Chantal is thick
as a plank."
- Victoria.
- That's a simile.
- Go get Helene. Now.
- Ooh, my tummy!
She must've eaten something
super horrid!
We all ate the same thing!
- That means we're all gonna die!
- Girls, that's enough.
My hat! Where's my hat?
Girls, find Madeline's hat!
I'll check.
Where is it?
Think like a hat.
I'm a hat.
- Hurry up!
- Come on, everybody!
Found it! We found it!
Hold it very tightly.
That's good.
I think they'll have
to take out her appendix.
- My appendix?
- No, you'll be fine. She'll be fine.
- Just please don't hurt me!
- Just repeat atter me, Madeline.
I can do anything.
Only patients from here on, madame.
I'm sorry.
- But I must stay with her!
- Wait!
- Please!
- I'll be right outside!
I can do anything.
- Are you her mother?
- No, I'm not.
I'm her teacher.
And where are her parents?
She's a ward of the church.
She has no parents.
- They died when she was very small.
- Oh. Here.
I can do anything.
We won't be visiting for long. It's only
been a few days since the operation.
Madeline will be exhausted.
We must be gentle with her.
- Hi, everybody.
- You're okay.
Madeline, you tricked us!
Look at that dollhouse!
- Oh, girls, your flowers.
- Vicki, she's got as many toys as you.
Yes, but these aren't hers.
They're for charity cases.
Look!
- It's a crank!
- Chantal!
- Glad you made it.
- Yes, we were super, super worried.
- Was it scary?
- Did you see a white light?
They cut a three-inch hole in me...
and then they stuck their bare hands in
and pulled out my guts.
- You're so lucky.
- Please.
All right. I was asleep.
So basically, all you did
was take a long nap.
Wait. I haven't shown you
the best part yet.
Look. Come over here.
Come and look.
Look what they gave me
in exchange for my appendix.
It's not that big.
Are you kidding? It's huge!
It's gi-normous!
All right, girls.
We'll say our good-byes now.
Madeline's had a hectic
and sleepless evening.
She's emotionally drained
and needs her rest.
Bye, Madeline.
- Can we visit Lady Covington?
- Not today, Aggie.
Please report to surgery,
room 24 immediately.
Lady Covington?
Hi, there, Madeline.
- You remember me?
- Of course I remember you...
from my visit last Easter.
- Yes.
- Come in.
I heard one of our girls
was in this hospital.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, ma'am.
I hope...
they are giving you
a lot of ice cream.
They are. I hope they're giving you
a lot of ice cream as well.
Not much.
- Are you teeling better?
- Much better.
You know, Madeline,
my grandmother started the school...
and I was a student there myself
when I was a little girl.
- Can I tell you a secret?
- Yes.
When I was nine,
on the baseboard in the dortoir...
I carved my name.
You carved "Lady Covington"?
No, my name was Marie Gilbert.
- See if it's still there.
- Marie Gilbert.
Who gave you permission
to be in here?
Nobody, Lord Covington.
This is a hospital.
It's not a playroom.
You're not allowed
to just wander around.
Yes, sir.
Something is not right.
What? What is it?
We want our appendix out too!
Good night, little girls.
Thank the Lord you are well.
Now, please, go to sleep!
Good night, good night, Miss Clavel.
Wait, Miss Clavel.
But that's Lady Covington's room.
Did she get better
and go home as well?
No, Madeline.
Lady Covington...
Lady Covington passed away.
But I only just spoke to her.
She was very sick.
We'll miss her very much.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
My first husband was a truck driver.
Stupid man!
What's your name?
Is this a pet chicken?
You know the rule, Madeline.
No pets allowed.
- Then what's it for?
- What is it for?
What do you think it's for, dancing?
It's for eating.
For eating?
In honor of your return, Madeline...
we'll have Chicken Helene.
Enough is enough.
- Hello, street. Hello, house, vines.
- Take care, Madeline.
Madeline, the Spanish ambassador
is moving in next door.
Wait! Hat, wait!
The Spanish ambassador's a midget?
This is Pepito,
the Spanish ambassador's son.
We're off to the races!
No leaving the courtyard!
That boy's bad hat.
No, I don't think you should
judge people too quickly.
But I guess
I understood him quickly.
So you're Pepito, eh?
He's positively Elvis!
Don't give him any attention.
He he's bad hat.
- I like his hat,
- And, Madeline, you're so young.
This boy's got charisma.
- But is he intelligent?
- Who cares? He's got a motorcycle.
- It's a Vespa.
- He'll probably get run over someday.
He is sort of handsome.
Forget it, Aggie.
You don't stand a chance.
Nobody wants a chance, Vicki,
except for you.
"He's got charisma."
You're all googly-eyed.
I am not googly-eyed!
He'll see us!
Amen.
Tonight, Madeline, I made
your very favorite: Chicken Helene.
- Great!
- Oh, super!
- It looks great, Helene.
- Yes.
Smells gorgeous.
Oh, no. Fred.
Who's Fred?
That's Fred.
- The chicken?
- Chickens don't have names.
- How do you know?
- Madeline, aren't you hungry?
I've suddenly lost my appetite.
You see, this chicken
was a friend of mine.
I met him earlier in the car.
I think I'm a vegetarian.
This is just too idiotic.
If you knew the chicken the way I did,
Vicki, you wouldn't eat him.
Of course I would.
He's nice and crispy...
just the way I like him.
Well, I'm not eating Fred.
Fred's already dead. Look.
Well, I think
I'm a "vegetable-arian" too.
I can't eat it either.
What's going on?
Who is Fred? I don't understand.
I'm sorry, Helene,
but you killed him.
Well, I wasn't friends with Fred.
Eat it, Lolo!
Don't be one of them.
Eat it!
Everyone is entitled
to her opinion.
If Vicki wants to eat Fred...
the chicken...
May I ask what's going on?
Excuse us, my lord.
You found us in the middle
of a debate.
A debate.
Miss Clavel, I wonder
if I might have a word with you.
What's Lord Cuckoo Butt doing here?
- Lord Covington.
- Mm-hmm.
On behalf of myself
and the girls...
I would like to offer you
our deepest sympathy.
Thank you very much, Miss Clavel.
The girls.
Yes. I'm afraid
they lack discipline.
They are usually very well-behaved,
it I may say so.
You may say so,
but it is not my experience.
I've been going through
my wife's papers...
putting her final affairs
in order.
This must be a very difficult time
for you.
In 43 years of marriage...
the only thing that my wife and I
ever disagreed upon...
was her indulgence of this school.
It needed a new roof,
my wife wrote a check.
Cook needed a new refrigerator,
Trips to the zoo.
She was a wondertully
generous woman.
Well, it can't go on like this.
I'm closing the school down.
But the girls.
Will find another school to attend.
Eating chicken's not the same
as wearing leather shoes.
- Yes, it is.
- No, it isn't.
End of debate!
If you won't eat your chicken,
it's off to bed with you.
- What did we do?
- No dinner at all?
"Marie Gilbert."
- Who's that?
- A friend of mine.
- I'm super hungry.
- You're "super" everything.
It's better to be super everything
than super nothing.
I don't think I'm super,
super everything.
All right. We're all hungry.
So let's eat.
But we're not allowed.
Pooh-pooh. Come on.
I still don't think
we should do this.
In the French resistance, we knew
how to deal with a man like Cuckoo Face.
Oh, Helene, don't even joke
about such things.
Who is joking?
Shh! If they hear us,
we're dead meat.
- But we're vegetarians.
- Shh! Stop whispering!
You stop whispering!
- It's Helene's knickers.
- It's her bra.
Her booby baskets.
Boobies, boobies, boobies.
- Mmm, pickle sandwiches.
- Are dairy products all right?
Yuck. Super bad smell.
All right, who did it?
- Smells like one of Vicki's.
- I need air.
- Phew!
- Gross!
- Aggie.
- She who smelt it dealt it.
- Chantal.
- It's not me. It's this.
Nobody breathe!
It's Helene's special cheese.
- Close it!
- Give me a Jack!
Go fish!
Chicken Helene. Chicken.
Now what's for dessert?
We can bake a cake.
Come back here, you!
I don't care who your father is.
We're not in Spain.
We're not gonna take this.
If you think you scare me,
well, you don't!
- It is an outrage!
- We were just getting something to eat.
It's all Pepito's fault.
Who's going to clean up this mess?
We are, Miss Clavel.
And then what do you suggest?
We eat!
All right, but from now on
I do the cooking, okay?
Hop, hop!
Hello... A nun!
Leopold's the name.
Tutoring's the game.
I'm Pepito's new tutor.
I'm Miss Clavel
from the school next door.
Pepito appears to be
a handful.
It seems he needs an outlet
for his energy.
Well, we all do, don't we?
I thought he might appreciate this.
It's a toolbox.
Cheers.
Do you mind if we talk
a little shop?
These kids...
What do you do to keep 'em occupied,
out of your hair, so to speak?
Well, tomorrow, for instance,
I'm taking mine to the museum.
The museum.
Not bad.
What do you do on your day off?
I pray.
Despite being rather tiny in size...
Emperor Napoleon held France
in an iron grip.
I don't want you
to simply copy the painting.
I want you to loosen up.
Express yourselves. Go wild.
You have exactly 20 minutes. Draw.
Madeline, where is your drawing pad?
Oops. I left it in the other gallery.
- I know where it is.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
- Then you may go and retrieve it.
Where are you going, little girl?
I asked you a question.
What's the matter? Scared?
I wasn't scared of you, Pepito.
Were you looking for this?
That's mine!
- Hey, I know it's yours.
- You stole it.
I was gonna give it back. You should
say "thank you," don't you think?
Give it to me.
Keep it down.
Some of us are trying to sleep.
Adios, little girl.
"Beware"?
Beware of what?
Girls, we've received an invitation
from our new neighbor.
"His Excellency,
the Ambassador of Spain...
requests your presence
for atternoon tea...
to celebrate the tenth birthday
of his son."
But we can't go.
The message said "beware"!
It's a trap.
We'll never make it out alive.
Of course we're going.
We never get invited anywhere.
Vicki's right.
We can't let him frighten us off.
- It's only a boy, girls.
- Please, don't go in there!
- But they are beginning a class!
- Excuse me, Miss Clavel.
Now this is the room
that requires some attention.
- May I help you, Lord Covington?
- May I ask you what these marks are?
Those are for keeping track
of the girls' heights.
Paint them over!
Excuse me!
We have just begun our class.
Well, perhaps you'd be kind enough
to reconvene elsewhere, Miss Clavel.
Go on.
Downstairs, girls.
In an orderly fashion.
Ah, young ladies.
Right. You, paint it over.
No matter what you wear, Vicki,
you always look super gorgeous.
You can wear whatever you like
to the party tomorrow.
I know what I'll be wearing.
Don't worry, Miss Clavel.
One of us will look smashing.
Look at my dress.
Girls.
Hello.
Oh, you all look so charming!
Girls.
Slowly. Girls.
Pepito, they're here.
Ladies, may I present the reason
we have opened to you our home.
Our birthday boy...
Señor José Marco
Filippo Juan Franloco...
Lopez de Vega...
Esteban Machado...
Jorge Santiago de la Rocha...
Gaspar Carlos de Fuentes...
Coruna Diego y Sevilla.
Of course,
his friends call him Pepito.
What friends?
Señoritas, you honor me
with your presence.
Your limousine is waiting, sir.
Do excuse us.
I wish we could stay.
- Happy birthday.
- Bye-bye, darling.
- Do you have the tickets?
- Yes.
I think you look
very handsome, Pepito.
But no one told us
this was a costume party.
This is not a costume.
This is the uniform
of a Spanish toreador...
the great heroes
of the coliseums de Madrid.
He's a bullfighter.
Those must be some
pretty small bulls.
Please.
You're not a real bullfighter.
Señoritas, allow me
to show you my menagerie.
What's a menagerie?
You damn idiot!
I'll get him to the circus.
- That's not your concern.
- I don't know.
You just stick with the plan,
and we'll all be rich.
I must talk to my brothers
about this.
Look, no worries, mate.
He's as good as delivered.
Do you happen to know my uncle?
He's the British ambassador
in Madrid.
Is there meant to be a clown
at the party?
The only clown here is you.
What's in there, Pepito?
It's a surprise.
I'm not afraid of mice.
No? Perhaps you're afraid
of the snake...
that's gonna have this mouse
for lunch.
You wouldn't feed a live mouse
to that snake.
Of course not.
That would be cruel.
But what I would do
is execute him...
with the guillotine I built.
It's quick, silent and deadly.
Like Helene's cheese.
It's just an innocent little mouse!
I'll show you!
It was just a joke!
Girls? Girls?
Stupid idiot!
Look.
Come back here! I'll get you!
Drop that rat, bullfighter!
Stop it this instant!
- I'll get you!
- If you can't behave, we're leaving now.
Girls.
What about the cake?
There's only 197.
Begin again.
Thanks a lot, Madeline.
I've never been so humiliated.
Can you believe them?
And that poor carrot.
Trust Madeline to get us all
in trouble.
It was a super bad punishment.
He deserved it.
He was about to kill a live
baby mouse right in front of us.
But he did say he was joking.
Aggie.
What do you think?
I've been praying for inspiration.
- Yes. I can see that.
- You don't like it?
Listen to me.
It's not my fault.
The boy's bad hat.
How can you take his side?
Have you all gone mad?
I did the right thing.
The boy kills bulls.
He kills mice.
- He's a maniac.
- Very interesting.
I'll show that bullfighter,
that mouse-killer.
I'll fight him myself!
- Yes, Aggie.
- Take that, Pepito! And that!
- Look!
- Somebody help her!
- Help!
- The current is taking her!
You can do it!
- Keep your head up!
- Help!
Where is she?
Help!
Follow me! Girls, quickly!
Quickly!
Not too fast!
- Madeline!
- There's a dog! Look!
Thank you.
Oh, Madeline! Hold on tight.
The dog. Where's the dog?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I was so scared.
Tea, soup and covers.
I want you to stay under the covers...
eat your soup and drink your tea.
You're giving me gray hair.
- Can I see?
- No!
Stay in bed.
Bye, Madeline.
Miss Clavel, can I stay home tomorrow?
I'm feeling sick.
- No, Aggie.
- Please.
Leopold, where are my keys?
- Could you please find my keys?
- All right. Pipe down.
- Can you or not? I can't start.
- You don't need a bloody key.
- You can use a paper clip. Watch.
- Oh, yeah, right.
It worked.
You found me!
Genevieve. Genevieve.
You found me.
I never thought you would. Thank you.
Well, I think you'll find
it's in immaculate condition.
The house was built in 1852.
It's charming, isn't it?
Property's been in my late wife's family
for generations.
What a place to invite your guests.
- You don't have any children?
- No, just the two of us.
Let's start in the dining room.
If you'd be kind enough to follow me.
The house has been used for the past
few decades as a school for girls.
Hence the sensible furniture.
- What a spacious dining room.
- Oh, such a beautitul portrait.
- Is that your wife?
- It's my late wife, yes.
She was very lovely.
Yes, indeed she was.
Shall we go and have a look
at the kitchen?
It has all the modern conveniences.
Kitchens are my staff's business.
I never set foot in them.
Please, just reassure me
that you have one.
We have one.
Now this room speaks for itself.
The music room.
Yes, I think you'll agree
it has an air of real sophistication.
- Splendid.
- So, upstairs?
And have a look at these doors.
Solid oak.
They don't make them like this anymore.
Now.
And so we arrive at yet another room
with the most elegant proportions.
Think how splendid it'll be...
to see the Liberian flag
fluttering out of that window.
Indeed.
Well, Lord Covington,
I see nothing to prevent us...
from purchasing
this magniticent house.
Did you hear something, Desmond?
I can assure you,
the neighborhood is uniquely peaceful.
What is that sound?
That boy down there!
The Spanish ambassador's son.
We had a terrible little boy
next door to us in Ouagadougou.
The worst three years of my life.
He never slept.
Not ever.
I'm sorry.
This just won't work.
I should warn you
that I've had inquiries...
from a number
of other foreign diplomats.
Under no circumstances.
Never again.
I'll get rid of the boy.
He's a pest.
I'll speak to the Spanish government.
Did you know that Joan of Arc was burned
at the stake when she was only 19?
Girls, vite, vite.
Now go to bed.
Listen, everybody.
I have something to tell you.
I'm gonna be burnt
at the stake too someday.
- What a neat way to die!
- You're all nuts.
- Yeah. Cashews.
- Bless you.
No, really. This is a big secret.
The dog from the river!
Oh, look!
- I told you, you should stay.
- How sweet.
- He's so cute.
- I'll give him my bow.
So this is the big secret.
No, this is not about Genevieve.
- Great name.
- We'll never be able to keep her.
Something is not right.
I don't think she'll find her.
- What's going on, girls?
- Nothing!
We're not hiding anything!
I'll tell you what's going on.
Lord Cuckoo Face is...
- Covington.
- Cuckoo Face.
He's going to sell the school.
I heard it.
Is it true?
Yes, girls.
Lord Covington
intends to sell the school.
- But that's terrible! He can't.
- Why?
Please.
All of this is no reason for us
to stop acting like proper young ladies.
We will not fall to pieces.
We will maintain composure.
Lord Covington
is showing the house tomorrow...
and I intend for it to be spo...
spotless.
Bless you.
Thank you. Good night.
And another thing.
All of you young ladies know
that there is a strict rule...
against pets in the school.
What you do not know is that
I am highly allergic to dogs.
Your new friend can sleep
in the garden shed.
Now go to...
bed.
I can't believe she let us keep her.
- She's just a dog from the street.
- She's the most beautitul dog.
I can't believe
they're closing the school.
We'll never see each other again.
It's not fair.
Close the school.
That Cuckoo Face is super wicked.
Chantal, what are you doing?
Trying to find some way out of this.
You only just found out
how to tie your shoelaces.
Well, I think we're all being
terribly selfish.
Just think of poor,
pathetic Madeline.
She doesn't have any family at all.
Yeah, think of Madeline.
I can't believe she just said that.
She's not pathetic.
I'm sure you'll find someplace
to stay, Madeline.
I'm staying right here.
We all are.
You three on construction.
Aggie, you and Chantal
cover the kitchen.
And you two on dog patrol.
And the rest of you, fall out.
And I'll negotiate with Spain.
Hurry up.
Yes, Vicki.
Come on, Genevieve.
Bye-bye.
- You want me to go and break it up?
- No, look.
That boy is simply misunderstood.
The property's been in my late wife's
family for generations.
The house has been used for the past
tew decades as a school for girls.
Say hello to Lord Covington, girls.
Good morning, Lord Covington.
Young ladies.
Miss Clavel.
Charming.
Hear the song of the nightingale
Singing beautifully
Everyone who listens to her song
Sings along
And think how lovely it will be to have
the Indian flag fluttering on the lawn.
- Now this is the music room.
- Oh, yes.
There is good karma here.
What is that smell?
I can't smell anything.
What? Don't look at me.
Oh, come on, Gopal.
Have a look at these doors.
Solid oak, huh?
They don't make them
like this anymore.
That's probably a good thing.
Now the garden.
Do come have a look at the garden.
- Oh, yes.
- It's most delightful.
Smiling happily
lmmaculate lawns, of course.
Such peace. Such tranquility.
It's true.
Well...
Dance, you suckers!
Dance!
Look! It's Pepito!
No, please! Please reconsider!
The Uzbekistani ambassador
will be arriving soon!
I know he means business!
Please reconsider!
We did it!
It was really funny.
He was, like...
What exactly did you say to Pepito
this morning, Madeline?
All I said is that we were having some
very important guests this morning...
so could you pretty please
be very quiet at that time?
Wait! Stop the car!
If I may say so,
your little boy is a menace!
- Your Excellency.
- I want an explanation.
Why did this loco fellow
say our Pepito is a menace?
I have no idea.
Pepito is a sweet,
well-behaved child.
There's just one problem
with Pepito.
- What is that?
- He needs some diversion.
He spends all day cooped up
in the house studying.
I'm teaching him Latin.
I'm teaching him biology,
algebration...
calculometry, physiconomy
and astrology.
But he can hardly read.
No, he's taken huge leaps.
- How wondertul!
- So, um...
As a reward for all his hard work,
I'm gonna take him to the circus.
The circus?
I love the circus.
We'll all go to the circus.
Oh, great idea.
We will all go!
Look, no.
Just me and Pepito.
Damn!
Ah, Miss Clavel.
I wonder if I could have a moment.
Lord Covington,
do you have any idea what time it is?
- The girls are asleep.
- I'll be brief then.
Here are 12 letters,
one for each one of your pupils.
Kindly see that they reach
the parents.
I'm informing them I shall be closing
the school at the end of the term.
That's quite enough, Miss Clavel!
After your little act of sabotage
this morning, I am in no...
Miss Clavel wasn't the one
who did it. I was.
Go back to bed, Madeline.
Please see that those letters are
delivered tirst thing in the morning.
You can't sell the school,
Lord Cuckoo Face. You can't.
What did you call me?
Lord, um, Covington.
Oh, no, you didn't.
You called me Lord "Cuckoo Face."
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did!
Yes, she did.
I heard you!
Miss Clavel,
don't you teach your little brats...
even the slightest respect
for their elders?
They are not brats, Lord Covington.
They are young ladies.
They respect their elders
between 7:00 in the morning...
and 9:00 in the evening
when they go to sleep.
This is insubordination, Miss Clavel.
Madeline, please go to bed.
Is this your resignation?
As long as there are children here,
Lord Covington, I will teach them.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Yes?
We won't be needing this one.
Madeline has no family.
They have an animal.
Gotcha.
He's leaving!
And he's taking Genevieve away too!
Leave her alone!
Sir, leave Genevieve alone!
No, Lord Cuckoo Face, no!
Come on! I can't hear you!
Now get out of here, you beast!
Come away from the window.
We have to go get her!
- Girls, please!
- We have to get Genevieve now.
It is the middle of the night.
You are little girls and you know
I won't allow you to go out.
Genevieve will be all right
for one night.
We'll find her tomorrow.
Now, to bed.
Noblest dog in France,
you shall have your vengeance!
Where can she be?
But, Miss Clavel,
it isn't 9:30 yet.
Never mind, Serena.
We have a dog to find.
- Wait for Vicki!
- I didn't get to brush my hair.
She's about so big,
with a pink bow in her hair.
She's really brave
and a fabulous swimmer.
She runs really fast,
and she's got big golden eyes.
She's got floppy ears and...
Well, I can't tell you any more,
but please find her.
You did very well.
- Have you seen our dog, Genevieve?
- No, I haven't.
Have you seen our dog?
- She's quite skinny.
- And she's about that big.
And it's a labrador...
um, a golden retriever.
Are you sure?
She's gone. Genevieve's gone.
No, she's not.
We'll find her. I promise you.
We have to have faith.
I used to wish so hard
for my parents to be alive again...
but you can't make something happen
just by wishing for it.
Genevieve's gone.
She doesn't have a home.
She needs a home.
I know she does.
I need a home too.
Madeline, you will always
have a home.
Yes, but it won't always
be with you, will it?
Will it?
There's no place on earth I'd rather be
than with you and the other girls.
You know that, don't you?
Get your tickets now!
Last chance!
Cirque Pandora!
I was in love once
with a carnival man.
He broke my heart, you know.
And he had a beautitul
tattoo that...
Helene! Please.
All right, girls.
Everyone stay with your partners
and let's have fun!
Come, Madeline!
I want to get a teddy bear.
Oh, yeah, and then one of those games
where you go...
Bang, you're dead!
Ooh, and I want to get some candy!
I guess that means he's here.
Hello, Miss Clavel!
Up here!
Come on, Madeline.
And now, the Idiots Popopov!
They're so stupid!
That's why they're idiots.
Aggie...
I have something to tell you.
I'm not going back with you.
You're not going back?
I'm running away with the circus.
What are you talking about?
We have to go home.
I don't have a home, Aggie.
The school's closing, and it's my fault.
The circus will be my new home.
All I have to do...
is learn to juggle or tame lions
or eat fire or something.
But what about Miss Clavel?
I'll write to her,
explaining everything.
You're my best friend
in the whole entire world.
You can't tell anyone
where I went.
- But, Madeline...
- No buts. You've got to promise.
Do you promise,
Agatha Emily Walden?
I promise.
Good luck, Madeline.
No, really.
I don't want to play.
Oh, Carmen,
be a sport for once.
- Go, Mom!
- Stay.
- Whoa!
- Come on, let's go get a balloon.
- But I'm watching this.
- Come on!
- Ah, but please!
- Let me go! Let me go!
- Quiet, kid.
Oh, terrific.
It's Thumbelina.
Leave him alone, you!
I knew it.
You're not really a tutor.
Give Pepito back right now,
or I'll go get Miss Clavel.
Miss Clavel!
I'm terrified, really.
- Have you seen Pepito?
- No, I don't know!
Tie the knot, idiot!
Look, for the last time,
"Idiot" is a stage name. I'm Pierre.
You won't get away with this. My father
will send the Spanish armada after you.
Your father will thank me,
you spoiled brat!
Take that, you idiot!
I thought we were just
kidnapping one kid.
Two kids, two ransoms.
- This is the life, eh?
- Get in the truck, idiot!
And he's the smart one!
One, two, three, four, tive, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven...
Twelve. All right.
Help! Save us, somebody!
- Help us!
- Please, someone!
My coat is just dripping.
Let's go upstairs and dry off.
We don't want anyone to catch pneumonia.
- Miss Clavel?
- Aggie, what is it?
- She ran away.
- Who ran away?
Madeline. I tried to stop her.
I tried.
Please, please.
As I said before, he was with us
all atternoon, and then...
... the clown in the act,
and then he was with his tutor.
Oh, Miss Clavel!
Señor Ambassador, have you seen
my smallest one? My Madeline?
- Our Pepito's missing too.
- My baby!
Is it possible the young boy
and the young girl...
have run off together
on a romantic adventure?
- Absolutely not.
- It's impossible.
Yes. Perhaps if the boy
were French...
We are doing everything possible.
We have roadblocks everywhere.
Extra units have been called out.
The proper thing
for you to do is to go home...
and leave this
to the professionals, please.
- But, Inspector...
- Don't worry your pretty little head.
Mr. Ambassador,
we have this under control.
This kind of thing happens all the time.
Children go to the circus.
Their little eyes fill with big dreams
of the way life should be.
What happened to the nun?
... down six percent due to a lack
of consumer purchasing.
The search is on tonight
for two missing children...
who disappeared from the Cirque Pandora
carnival late this afternoon.
French police are looking for the son
of the Spanish ambassador to France...
and a local schoolgirl.
What it we never get out of here,
never go home?
Your family will pay the ransom.
So will yours.
They can't.
- I don't have a family.
- What do you mean?
They're gone.
They're in heaven.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
It happened a long time ago.
My parents probably don't want me back.
I'm a lot of trouble, you know?
You are a lot of trouble.
But you know, you have got charisma.
You think so?
I miss the girls
and Miss Clavel.
Don't worry, Madeline.
I won't leave without you.
I promise.
Thank you, Pepito.
There have been no signs
of the children.
Foul play has not been ruled out.
Authorities are asking
for public cooperation...
in the departmental-wide canvass.
Now sport.
- How could she run away?
- Do you think she's okay out there?
It's all my fault.
I should have never let her go.
You did the right thing, Aggie.
I would have done it too.
I miss Madeline so much.
So where is she? Hmm?
Where's your brother?
I don't know.
I can do anything.
Pepito, wake up!
They left us here with the knives
that they juggle at the circus.
What idiots!
On the count of three, okay?
Okay, go.
- Got it?
- Mm-hmm.
Move it!
- You're getting better.
- Move! Now!
Hurry up. They're leaving.
But we're still trapped in here.
Look! I've got it!
So?
So it's a motorcycle,
and you know how to drive one.
This is our escape.
But I drive a Vespa.
It doesn't even have gears.
This is a motorcycle.
I can't drive something like this.
Yes, you can, Pepito.
You can do it.
Look, technically, I'm not even
allowed to leave my courtyard.
Okay, give me your hairpin.
Idiots! In the truck now!
- Now! In the truck!
- Sorry about that.
Hey, wait!
Yes! We did it!
Yes!
Where are you, Thumbelina?
Oh, no! Look!
There!
- Wait! I'll drive!
- Get off!
Oh, I'm going to be sick!
Come on, Pepito!
I'm going!
Hang on, Madeline!
- Faster!
- Hey, you wanna drive or what?
Hey, who's that?
Oh, great! Miss Clavel!
- Who's Miss Clavel?
- Oh, some nun.
- A nun?
- A nun!
Hold on, Genevieve.
Don't kill the nun!
Forget the nun!
Don't kill the idiots!
Oh, no!
Yeah!
Yea, we did it!
Ha-ha! We got you!
Get 'em! Move, you idiot!
Pierre! My name is Pierre!
- Look! Look at them!
- Miss Clavel!
Hey, easy!
Are you all right?
- Mr. Ambassador.
- Not now.
- Mom, I drove a real motorbike!
- You did?
- We'll never leave you again.
- Never again.
She's here!
Madeline, you're back!
- I missed you.
- I missed you more.
Great car.
I thought you were dead.
Oh, thanks, Vicki.
Oh, super.
Tonight I'm going to make
a wonderful vegetarian dinner, okay?
I want Chicken Helene.
Oh, no.
Lord Covington, please. We were
just about to have a celebration.
Well, yes, indeed.
Young ladies.
The ambassador from Uzbekistan
has just agreed to buy the school.
What's Uzbekistan?
Very nice.
Just like in the pictures.
Very shortly, the Uzbekistani flag
will be fluttering from the root.
I'm so sorry.
The house has been used for the past
few decades as a school for girls.
Yes, as you said.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Very nice portrait.
Yes, it's of my late wife.
It was painted shortly atter
we got back from Venice one year.
It's rather a good likeness.
I'm very fond of it.
Marie Gilbert.
- I know why you're doing this.
- What?
It's because
you're all alone, isn't it?
Please, young lady,
please mind your own business.
You must have loved her very much.
She was your whole family, wasn't she?
I thought you were mean, Lord Covington,
but you're not. I understand now.
Understand? How can you possibly
understand? You're only a child.
You see, my wife, Marie and l...
This is totally inappropriate.
Please go away.
I lost my family too,
a long time ago.
But they're not really gone,
are they?
She's not gone, is she?
- She's dead. She's gone.
- No, she's not.
She's still with you,
and she's in the school too.
Please, Lord Covington.
She wouldn't want you to sell it.
My love...
no matter what happens, I'll make sure
that you and I will be together.
No, Miss Clavel.
- Yes!
- No!
The child's right.
Yes, you're right.
But the school's already sold.
There's nothing I can...
Unless I might be allowed...
Please, Mr. Ambassador.
I know the girl's school
may not mean much...
to Uzbekistan or to you, sir...
I'm not the ambassador.
I am the ambassador.
Oh!
You can keep your school.
Girls! Stay together!
Want sharper video quality? Want
clearer audio? Try GOM Player now!