Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
- Eleven days already.
- Hooray (!)
This is where the police officer rings
the bell and waits to get invited in, right?
All right, Barney.
What the hell is this?
Take it easy, Benesch.
Hell of a time in the morning
for a social call, Dan.
Now, don't complain, Barney.
We could've been here
half an hour ago.
Put your pants on,
we're taking you to Brooklyn.
- Brooklyn?
- Brooklyn.
I've been clean for two years.
- What do I know about Brooklyn?
- That's what they want to know. Move it.
- If I asked, you could show me a warrant?
- We left it downstairs with the doorman.
Watch out for my glasses.
- No gun?
- I gave them up.
What for? Lent?
Oh, you guys kill me.
I never thought you two
would try illegal entry.
Look who's talking.
- How old are you, honey?
- I am 22.
Twenty-two?
Move it, I wanna see the kids
before they go to school.
- You always were a family man, Rocky.
- That's right.
Rosita.
My jacket.
Not bad, eh, Danny Boy?
It's there for the asking.
Knock it off.
Drop the gun, Rocky.
You're out of your mind.
This is a routine check.
Cut the crap, Madigan!
Tell that wop cop it's now or never.
I said tell him to drop the gun!
Up with your hands, you bastards.
Get your hands up!
I'm never going in again.
Not with you, not with anybody.
All right, turn.
I said turn!
Your hands on his shoulders,
Danny Boy.
Get your hands on his shoulders!
Yours behind your head, Bonaro.
Right, now, walk slow.
No, you don't, Bonaro!
We're going upstairs to the roof.
Come on, move it, Madigan!
- You bum, you were looking at the broad!
- What the hell were you looking at?
He's headed for 99th Street.
Don't tell him I helped you.
He'll kill me!
- Yeah?
- Muller?
- Speaking. Is this you?
- Who do you think?
I'll see you at the same place,
only an hour later. Got that?
- Will you be able to?
- We'll both be there.
- You can count on it.
- We'll both be there. I'll meet your terms.
- And you'd better meet mine.
- Don't worry. Pleasure doing business...
Hello?
- Yeah?
- Muller?
- Speaking. Is this you?
- Who do you think?
I'll see you at the same place,
only a hour later. Got that?
[Phone rings]
- Yes?
- Good morning, Commissioner.
- Morning, Charley.
- Bad news this morning, Tony.
What do you mean, bad news?
A couple of the boys at the 23rd Precinct
stepped all over their nightsticks.
Some loser named Barney Benesch
lifted their guns and took off.
That's a hell of a thing.
Who were the officers involved?
First Grade Detectives
Daniel Madigan and Rocco Bonaro.
Damn that Madigan. He was bound
to get caught in a wringer sooner or later.
Madigan's a good cop, Tony.
Doesn't always go by the book.
I like the book, Charley.
How did it happen?
I'll have the details for you
by the time you get downtown.
Right.
Darling? What are you doing up so early?
- I couldn't sleep.
- Why? Trouble?
All kinds.
- Hello?
- Tom? Sorry to cut into your sleep.
- Can you pick me up right away?
- I'll be right there.
Thank you.
What's wrong? Can you tell me?
When I know.
Would I be invading your privacy if I
asked you what you wanted for breakfast?
Just coffee and juice.
Morning, Jim. Your heroes are upstairs.
Morning.
Oh, cheer up. Maybe a couple of my
uniformed boys'll pick them up for you.
- That'll be the day.
- Bulletin on Benesch coming through.
If Madigan and Bonaro are sick now,
they'll be sicker when they read this.
- I'll take the carbon.
- All right, Lieutenant.
You have the right to remain silent and
refuse to answer questions. Understand?
Anything you do say may be used against
you in a court of law. Understand?
You have the right to consult an attorney
before speaking to the police.
Do you understand?
- Is that a lawyer?
- That's right. An attorney is a lawyer.
If you cannot afford an attorney, one
will be provided for you without cost.
What do I want a lawyer for? I did it.
- Congratulations (!)
- Sorry to wake you up with that kind of news.
Now, don't worry about it, fellas (!)
I woke up the District Commander.
And he woke up the Borough Commander.
The Borough Commander
woke up the Chief of Detectives.
And the Chief Inspector,
I can assure you,
has already presented the glad tidings
to Police Commissioner Anthony X Russell.
Now, maybe this will wake you up.
Homicide? The first bulletin said
Benesch was just wanted for questioning.
So you two decided, huh?
To pick him up?
We knew where
we could lay our hands on him.
So you walked in,
gave him your guns and left.
- Come on, we've got enough trouble.
- Oh, that's for sure, that's for sure.
Well, what now?
- We've got a few leads.
- Such as?
Benesch has peculiar sexual habits,
to put it mildly.
So has half the population,
but you can hardly call that a clue.
Anyway, our best chance
is Midget Castiglione.
- The bookie?
- Yeah, that's the one.
Benesch robbed him
and took him apart just for kicks.
Maybe because he's a midget,
I don't know.
Anyway, Castiglione likes to know
where Benesch is at all times.
- For which I can't blame him.
- Why would he tell you?
Because he owes Dan a favour, that's why.
The sooner we get to him...
Now, look, you are not going anyplace
until I hear from downtown.
You fellas may be up for
a little vacation or worse, who knows?
Meanwhile,
you better type up your reports.
By the way, you're both automatically
fined five days' pay for losing your guns.
Thanks (!)
Thank you, Tom.
Get yourself some breakfast.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Good morning, Commissioner.
Sorry to disturb you, Sergeant.
The PC is in the building.
[Knock at door]
Come in.
- Morning.
- Morning. You the early man today?
It's more like you are.
Assistant Chief Inspector Griffen
wanted you to know he was here.
- Have him come up.
- Yes, sir.
- Good morning, Commissioner.
- Anything there can wait, Marvin?
It can all wait,
at least until after lunch.
But you may want to refresh your speech
to the police academy graduating class.
Unless he has a new one this year.
One o'clock, luncheon with Mrs Harriet
Dorrn of the Police Athletic League.
- At the Bethesda Fountain Café.
- All right.
- Three o'clock, Dr Taylor, about his son.
- I remember.
Four o'clock...
We can finish that later, Marvin.
Good morning, Commissioner.
Sit down, Earl.
All right, let's begin at the beginning.
We had a tap on this fella Muller,
George Muller.
That was in connection with your
investigation of Sergeant Shafer?
Yes, sir, that's correct.
Muller has this bar and grill
in the 18th Precinct.
We received a tip that known prostitutes
were frequenting the place.
Certain well-known suspicious characters,
who prefer not to be seen in public,
often met there.
The tapped phone was in the pay-booth
of a garage Muller had an interest in.
There were different kinds of
conversations on the tapes.
While I was running through them,
I heard this voice.
Yes, go on, Earl.
Well, as I said, Commissioner,
I heard this voice...
You know how the Chief Inspector has
a distinctive voice and a way of talking.
I felt it was my duty to bring this
matter to your attention, Commissioner.
Is there any doubt in your mind that
the voice on that tape is Charley Kane's?
Well, as I said, the Chief Inspector...
- Assuming it is the Chief Inspector.
- I just want to know one thing.
Any doubt in your mind
whose voice that is?
No, sir. No doubt at all.
I typed this transcript of the
conversation on the tape, personally.
I thought you'd like to have it.
You haven't made a duplicate
and filed it, have you?
- No, Commissioner.
- Thank you, Earl.
- Anything else you want to see me about?
- Nothing urgent.
- We're working on two or three things...
- Fine.
- Is there anything you'd like me to do...?
- No, thank you. I'll let you know.
I'm sorry, Commissioner,
it had to be the Chief.
Thank you, Commissioner.
- Nice and neat, huh?
- Yeah.
And just enough for Russell
to hang us with.
OK, we'll send someone right over.
Come on.
Take it easy in here for a few minutes.
[Phone rings]
- Hello?
- Hello, sweetheart.
Hi, Rocky. How are you, honey?
I'm fine. Fine. I'll be
a little late, we had some trouble.
- That's too bad. Sure you're all right?
- Oh, yeah, sure, sure, sure.
- How are the kids?
- They're fine.
- They get off to school all right?
- Yeah. Mario took his lunch again.
He did? Wow, that's twice this week.
I'll have to cut his allowance.
Well, I just called
because I didn't want you to worry.
All right, I've got a lot of work to do.
I'll see you later, huh? Goodbye.
[Phone rings]
Detective O'Mara.
What's your name
and where are you calling from?
[Phone rings]
- Hello?
- Did I wake you?
No, I'm up. Where are you?
I'm at the station.
There was a screw-up this morning.
- What happened?
- We picked up a guy and lost him.
Lost him?
Just lost. What's the difference?
Now we have to find him.
When are you coming home?
Don't you know?
I don't, right now. I'll see how it goes.
Well, what am I supposed to plan?
I'll try to get home and freshen up.
If you want to do something, go ahead.
What does that mean, "go ahead"?
Shall I wait for you, go out or what?
Honey, I don't know. We may get this guy
in an hour. Then again, it may be days.
Days? If this ruins the Captain's party
tomorrow, I don't know what I'll do.
- Come on, Julia.
- This is really too damn much!
Listen to me, will you?
I bought a new dress,
made a hair appointment...
We'll go to the Captain's party.
Just take it easy.
All right. For God's sakes, be careful.
Yeah, I'll be careful. I'll see you.
That's the whole story, Commissioner.
In my humble opinion,
Detectives Madigan and Bonaro
were acting like hicks in a cathouse,
and they were taken.
We know.
Plus which... these two first-class
what the Chief Inspector likes to call
"slashing detectives"
didn't even know what he was wanted for.
Come on, Hap,
you can't hold that against them.
Brooklyn was working
on the Kleyer killing.
They found out that
Benesch and Kleyer were friendly,
so they put it on the teletype
to bring him in for questioning.
Madigan and Bonaro knew him
so picked him up as a favour to Brooklyn.
Prima donnas, that's what they are.
Those "prima donnas" hold
more departmental citations
for heroism and excellent service than...
Be that as it may, they shouldn't
have gone after him alone!
While they were going after him alone,
Brooklyn found out that Benesch did do
the Kleyer killing for $1500 cold cash.
- And Benesch got both their guns, right?
- That's right.
- I'd like to hit them with a complaint now!
- For God's sakes, will you stop this?
If Madigan and Bonaro are looking for more
headlines, these'll make their head spin.
And it's not exactly the kind of image
the department needs these days.
We're not running
a public relations office, Hap.
Give them 72 hours to bring Benesch in.
As you say, Commissioner.
When the Chief of Detectives finds time,
he might assign 20 more men to this case.
Begging your pardon with all due respect,
that was done an hour ago.
- Well, thank you, Chief.
- Thank you, Chief.
- Bring him in fast. I hope nobody gets hurt.
- Yes, sir.
Now, there is a
really fine leader of men.
Two of his best goof,
and he dances for joy.
I am not at all convinced that
Madigan's one of our best men.
Haven't seen him in years,
yet I always feel he's out there
doing something
I'd rather not know about.
Such as?
When I was his captain,
he always wore better clothes than I did.
When I was grabbing a bite in some beanery,
he'd be eating at the Stork Club.
I never could figure it out at first. Then
I found out he was getting it for nothing.
"Police discount" he called it.
Sure, Madigan's always lived
a little on the arm.
On the other hand,
he's never been on the take.
- He's never given anything in return.
- You mean, he's never sold a job.
Yeah...
Yeah, never sold out.
When will you be ready to go
to those graduation exercises?
Ten minutes. I'll see you in the car.
Well, where is he? If he isn't there,
he's got to be someplace else.
Let's go.
That new secretary of Castiglione's
has got a bad case of lockjaw.
Yeah. Well, there just might be
a cure for that.
I don't know her name.
She hit me with a shoe and left.
They gotta be kidding with this 72 hours.
What are we, miracle workers?
From anyone but Russell, I'd call it
rough. From him, it's sweet charity.
Why are we important enough for
the Commissioner's personal attention?
I know him well.
He used to be a cop,
what's the matter with him?
I'll tell you what's the matter with him.
With him, everything's either right
or wrong. There's no in-between.
I remember once when he was
my precinct commander,
the wholesale butcher in the neighbourhood
gave out Christmas turkeys.
Every cop in the precinct got one.
Butcher wasn't asking for any favours,
he just had an attack of Santa Claus.
But Russell sent his turkey back.
His wife was alive at the time, they
didn't have much, like the rest of us.
But he sent his back.
What a break for the turkey.
You're smoking.
Yeah, sure I'm smoking.
You all right, Tony? You look
a bit off-key for graduation day.
I didn't sleep worth a damn last night.
Oh, your shoelaces is untied.
I haven't heard that for years.
My father used to say it all the time.
I miss him.
Especially on a day like today.
Do you remember that winter
when you and I were
nothing more than rookies
and the department had you marching
out there in the winds of Staten Island?
You froze, because you wouldn't cooperate
with the boys from Tammany Hall.
And it was Captain Kane of the old
7th Precinct that did something about it.
Two days later,
you were off Staten Island.
It was as cold in the far reaches
of the Bronx where I was,
and he didn't raise
a finger to bring me in.
I loved your father.
He was the only one I had.
I didn't mind sharing him with you.
Of course, he could see through me
like a pane of glass.
I remember one night, Tony,
the old man sat down across from me
with a bottle of Irish between us.
Didn't say anything,
so I didn't say anything.
The bottle went down,
and finally he said to me,
"Charley, me boy,
if the chips fall right,
that old friend of yours, Tony Russell,
will be Commissioner one day".
He could tell by my expression
how I felt about it.
Not all bad. Not all good, either.
Then he said,
"Don't be a fool, Charley."
"The department is big enough
for two big men,
and if you're lucky,
one day you'll be his Chief Inspector".
Of course, the old man swore one time
he saw a leprechaun in Loew's 83rd,
so I figured he was prone
to exaggeration.
- Charley...
- Yeah?
I'll be seeing Dr Taylor about his son.
Fill me in on that.
That's a sticky one, Tony.
About two weeks ago, an hysterical mother
brought her 14-year-old daughter
into the Harlem Station House.
The girl had been accosted by a boy
with a knife, who forced her into his car.
Green two-door sedan.
Two of the squad detectives
picked up Dr Taylor's son.
- Did they work the boy over?
- No, I checked on it. Didn't touch him.
You wouldn't leave me out on a limb
with this thing?
Have I ever?
Detectives Madigan and Bonaro.
Mr Castiglione isn't in, gentlemen.
Just like I told you, he isn't in.
I've no idea where he is or where he went.
Don't be defensive, Miss Newman.
You have no notion where he might be?
Off for the weekend with Buster,
and that's all I know, period, Mr Madigan.
Give us the keys to the rest of the place
or I'll tip this over on top of you.
- That's just for openers.
- There's no need... There's no...
Don't you dare! Go away!
I'll give you the keys.
I'd have given you the keys
if you'd asked for them.
I know you're friends of Mr Castiglione.
He's not hiding in there,
if that's what you're thinking.
No, no. We just wanted to make sure
in case he might've overslept.
I understood you were
two decent police officers.
When we can afford it. If he calls,
tell him Dan Madigan wants to see him
at once or even sooner.
You got that?
I'll tell him.
You do that.
- Now we're down to frightening old ladies.
- Ah, she doesn't know anything.
The Midget wouldn't tell her,
especially if he was holed up.
Yeah. Well, what's next?
I hate to say this, Danny Boy,
but you look terrible.
So do you.
- Know how long we've been up?
- Uh-huh.
- I could use a shave and some sleep.
- Let's grab a few hours.
It was a splendid meeting, Commissioner.
Thank you so much for joining us.
I should be thanking you, Mrs Dorrn,
for myself and the Police Athletic League.
We just know that the young people,
if given the chance,
would rather be playing baseball and football
than fighting and smoking pot.
- We like to think so, Mrs Hewitt.
- Goodbye, Commissioner.
I heard you mention Bergdorf's, Mrs Bentley.
I'm passing that way. Can I give you a lift?
That would be very kind of you,
Commissioner.
- This is unforgivable, isn't it, Tony?
- Horrible. In what way?
Fooling all those nice ladies
on the committee.
- If we are fooling them.
- You're a worrier.
I'm a coward.
With a very bad conscience.
My husband and children
get back on Sunday.
I know.
- What time?
- In the morning, about nine or ten.
It'll be good to see them again.
- Does that make sense to you?
- Yes, it does.
I don't know where I am, Tony.
I went home to change
and get some things this morning.
It all sort of hit me... again.
When I'm there, I...
I just want to be with you.
And when I'm with you,
part of me is always there.
This adultery is a Ionely business, isn't it?
So it is.
I find myself missing you all the time,
even when you're with me.
Because I know that some day
you'll have to go.
How was it you got around my determination
not to become involved with you?
And how, in heaven's name,
did you pick on me?
You were the only member of the committee
without a theory on juvenile delinquency.
Or maybe I fell in love with you.
(TV)...and so today, my dear,
if you will follow my instructions...
- Hi.
- Hi. I really didn't think you'd show up.
- Yep. I made it.
- You look beat.
- Can I fix you a drink?
- Yeah. Easy on the water.
- I suppose you've had your lunch.
- Well, I didn't know. You didn't call.
It's OK.
There's still some cold cuts and potato salad.
That'll be fine.
Oh, thanks.
- Helen Barry phoned a while ago.
- Yeah? How is she?
She's OK. She called to tell me
she heard about you over the radio.
"What a shame," she kept saying.
"Poor Dan."
- Did you catch him yet?
- No.
Helen has her faults, but she's a good friend.
I'd go crazy without her.
I don't mind Helen.
She's a bitch, but what the hell.
"But who isn't?"
Was that what you wanted to say?
No.
No, honey, no.
What are you going to be doing tonight?
The usual. Watch TV.
It's getting so it's coming out of my eyeballs.
- I know every commercial by heart.
- Go to a movie.
- By myself?
- Why not?
You know I hate that.
I'd rather watch TV.
That's why I've been looking forward
to the Captain's party.
We'll go.
- Want to eat now or after your shower?
- After.
The real reason Helen called was to tell me
they're buying a cottage in Breezy Point...
Have I got any clean socks?
Oh, thanks.
I didn't say anything, but why would anybody
buy a house in a place like that?
It's so common. Cops and firemen,
that's all you ever see at Breezy Point.
As if you didn't see
enough lousy cops as it is.
Except you're one lousy cop
I never see enough of.
- Now, honey, don't start that again.
- Why can't we be like other people?
My brother George and Marge
have a great time together.
- He doesn't carry a gun when he's out.
- Lucky old George.
A lot you get out of it! $200 a week!
George must be good for $30 - $40,000
a year in that bar and grill of his.
- He spends every afternoon with his wife.
- Good for him.
You could be a captain, not just a crummy
detective running around the streets.
You are smarter than most of them.
But that's not for you.
What do you care about money or respect?
As long as you're on the streets, having fun.
What about me? Think of me once in a while.
Maybe there's some kind of life I want.
Damn it, Julia.
Why do you always have to go
into that same song and dance?
[Phone rings]
- Hello?
- Hey, Dan.
Yeah?
Buster, Castiglione's friend,
didn't he have a brother?
- Worked in the subway for the city.
- Oh, yeah.
A dispatcher. Mid-town someplace.
- Check with the Transit Authority, will you?
- You got it.
- I'll pick you up in 20 minutes.
- All right. I'll see you then.
- I'll get your food.
- Honey...
I'm sorry.
You don't have anything on under that,
do you?
It's a little late for that now, isn't it?
I know Buster's no prize, and maybe
he isn't all there in the head.
- But he's my brother.
- He's not in any trouble. Don't worry about it.
We want to talk to the Midget,
and we figure he's with Buster.
I just hope you're giving it to me straight.
Mr Castiglione's been awful good to Buster.
We're giving it to you straight.
Stop dancing around and tell us
where we can find Buster.
Frankly, there isn't a week goes by
that Buster doesn't go to see our mother.
- They're very close, him and the old lady.
- Where does she live?
- Coney Island.
- What's the address?
1064 Neptune Avenue. Apartment 3.
OK. So far you've been a big help, Nick.
- But don't call her, huh?
- I never do. She's deaf.
Your son does have a green two-door sedan,
doesn't he, Dr Taylor?
David's two-door sedan is a greenish blue,
Commissioner.
Not green. I bought it for him myself.
Yet your men dragged him
to the station house,
although there was no reason whatsoever
to suspect him of this crime.
It is my understanding he went voluntarily.
And there was a reason.
Your son's been arrested twice before
for molesting young girls.
That was two years ago.
Does that make him guilty now?
Dr Taylor, human behaviour patterns
are very important in police work.
A known sex offender whose name
was on the same list as your son's
finally confessed to this crime.
Commissioner, you don't know my son.
I admit he's made some terrible mistakes,
but that's in the past.
He's a changed boy.
- Do you have children?
- No, I don't.
Nevertheless, try to understand
how I, as a father, felt,
after David told me what happened.
How he had been subjected
to the most outrageous pressures
to confess to a crime he didn't commit.
When my son came home to me,
he was in a state of complete
mental collapse and anguish.
He was given an opportunity
to call you or an attorney.
He was ashamed to call me.
- He didn't have to answer any questions.
- He was innocent.
Why should he keep silent?
Commissioner, you're known to be a man
who does not shrink from responsibility.
I expect you to punish these officers.
- Yes, Commissioner?
- Chief, come up, please.
- I'm with Dr Taylor.
- Yes, Commissioner.
Dr Taylor, the two officers involved
have been investigated thoroughly
and cleared of any suspicion
of brutality or unreasonable conduct.
Sir, I came here for justice,
and I'm going to get it.
But I don't want a policeman's idea of justice.
I want the victim's idea of justice.
From the bottom looking up,
not from the top looking down.
I think you're talking about revenge
not justice.
Commissioner, during the Harlem riots,
I was called an Uncle Tom
for using whatever influence I had
to bring about peace and understanding.
- Was I wrong?
- You were right, Doctor.
Prove it, Commissioner.
You prove it to me.
- [Knock at door]
- Come in.
- You know Chief Inspector Kane. Dr Taylor.
- Nice to see you again.
Chief, are these the facts
in the Taylor situation?
Yes, the Chief of Detectives investigated
this matter and reported his findings to me.
I want you personally to see
Detectives Bowler and Silvers.
Make your report to me.
Can I get back to you on Monday?
- I'll be expecting your call.
- You'll hear from me.
When a police officer does his job properly,
I'm prepared to back him.
When he doesn't, I'm ready to break him.
There must be one rule for every man
charged with protection of the community.
Chief Kane will tell you our men are
expected not only to enforce the law
but to live under it themselves.
That's a comforting thought, gentlemen.
No, it's OK, Buster.
- Hiya, Midge.
- Dan!
- How are you?
- Fine.
Rocky. What are you guys
doing out here in Coney Island?
Came down for a hot dog,
what do you think?
We've been looking for you.
Don't you call your office?
Why? I can read about it in the papers.
You can read your own obituary, too,
if Benesch catches up with you.
Bodyguard or no bodyguard.
One rap more won't make
any difference to him.
Yeah, I know.
I figured that, that's why I panicked.
You know I'm not the biggest coward
in the world, but that guy scares me.
I heard that bad news, so I figured I can
come out here with Buster and his mother
until you guys collect that crazy nut cake.
Well, we're gonna need a little help, Midge.
Like... you got a couple of dozen customers
who don't mind talking
to their favourite bookie.
- Sure, I can make a couple of calls...
- You're not listening.
We want Benesch now, not next Christmas.
The longer he's loose,
the shorter your lifespan, right?
Yeah, well, I know.
That punk shacked up in some pad,
tee-veeing it with a couple of broads
to take his mind of the commercials.
Somebody's gotta know something.
Some pimp, maybe,
who won't talk to us but will to you.
Time for you to come home, Midge.
You're too far away from the action.
Oh, I had it with the fresh air, anyway.
You're my friend, Dan, and I owe you.
Just make sure you give me a nice funeral
in case he makes me before you make him.
OK.
Let's go and try a couple of those
luxurious army cots, I'm beat.
You go.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know. Maybe go dancing.
You're out on your feet.
Let's get some sleep.
I'll let you know where I am.
Keep in touch.
# And how lips that taste of tears
# Lose their taste for kissing
# You don't know
# How hearts burn for love
# That cannot live yet never dies
# Until you've faced each dawn
With sleepless eyes
# You don't know
# What love is #
Hi.
- Well, at least you're alive.
- Hard to tell. Drink?
Damn newspapers. I felt so lousy.
You'd think you were the criminal.
Jonesy, you're a good girl.
Tell me more.
I'm here for comfort and sympathy.
- Do you love me just a little?
- After my wife, I love you best.
At least I haven't lost any ground.
Take it easy with that stuff, there's water in it.
- How's the world's sexiest singer?
- Great.
- Come home with me tonight?
- Oh, come on.
- You know how I feel about you.
- Yeah, I remind you of your father.
The hell you do.
You've had it, I think.
OK.
Check.
Compliments of the house, Mr Madigan.
Always a pleasure to have you here.
Thank you very much.
- Tell the boys I'm cutting out, OK?
- Yes, Miss Jones.
We got a cab right outside.
- Where am I going?
- Beddy-bye, and it won't hurt a bit.
Yeah, you're right, they shouldn't see me
like this at the station house,
when I'm supposed to be looking
for the bastard that grabbed my gun.
I'll buy you a new one.
- You can't sleep in your suit, you'll ruin it.
- No!
Clean sheets.
What time do you want the alarm for?
6.30? 7.00?
Oh, I forgot. Call Rocky at the station
house and leave this number.
- He'll call me if anything breaks.
- OK.
I promised to leave a number. He'll call me.
You know I'm not kidding, Dan.
Why can't it be like it was
before you got married?
I'm in love with Julia.
Who's asking for love?
- Where the hell have you been, Dan?
- Don't give me any trouble. Get in here.
I had to go back to the Flame Club
for the damn car.
Some jerk gave me a ticket.
- It's a great day already.
- Yeah.
OK, who's this guy who called?
Says he's a friend of yours.
Name of Mickey Dunn.
Oh, yeah. Used to be a boxer.
Haven't seen him for six, seven years.
Well, he says he just saw Benesch
in McGinty's Bar.
- You believe it?
- I'd like to.
Your buddy must be some lush, sitting
in a bar at this hour of the morning.
How can we take a chance not to check?
Can't you move this thing any faster?
You can open the other eye now,
I made the coffee.
- Did you get some sleep?
- Enough.
- You thrashed around all night.
- I did? I don't remember.
Oh, you'd make a terrible witness.
- Have you always been this hard to reach?
- I've been accused of it.
My friend Charley Kane has done me in.
Oh, Tony. But that's hard to believe.
- How could he do it?
- Ask him.
I don't know what the trouble is,
but you should give him a chance.
- He's your friend.
- One of two.
Perhaps you're being too hard
on him and yourself.
Oh, there's only one way.
- Now you sound like a cop.
- I am a cop.
No, you're the Police Commissioner,
and Charley Kane's your friend.
And friends aren't meant to be judged,
just loved.
You mean, separate rules for Charley
when I don't even have them for myself?
What about you and me in your bedroom?
Is there a separate rule for us?
I suppose not. You're right. I didn't think
we were talking about the same thing.
Tony...
Work it out with him.
It's so important to both of you.
- I'll do what I have to.
- I know, I know.
Remember, people are more complicated
than you'd like them to be.
- And that includes you and me.
- Will you be still here tonight?
I'm going to miss you.
- Hi, Dan.
- Hi, Mick.
- I hope I didn't bring you here for nothing.
- What's doing?
Benesch. He's still sitting in the bar
over there.
I've been standing here since I made
that call, and he never come out.
- Is there a back door?
- On the alley.
- You want to be a real help?
- Yeah.
You go in the front. If he's still there,
open the back door for us.
Then we'll see what happens.
Anything pops, take a dive.
Sure. I hope it's the right guy,
'cause I'm only going from his picture.
Yeah, sure. Just don't stand around
in case there's fireworks, OK?
- What do you want?
- Sorry. I thought you were from Cincinnati.
- Are you a wise guy?
- I said I was sorry.
Nobody tells me
I look like I'm from Cincinnati.
Now be a good boy and drink your milk.
Dan, I'm awful sorry
I got you out on a bum steer.
- It's OK. Let me buy you a drink.
- You don't have to do that.
I'm sorry, fellas.
I could've sworn that was Benesch.
- This is on the house, boys.
- Thanks.
- Take it easy, Mick. I'll see you around.
- You bet.
You're a sight for sore eyes, Dan.
You look great.
Oh, no. No, no, Dan.
I'm not that far down on my luck.
Take it.
Take care of yourself.
I've known those guys for 15 years.
Nice guys. The best.
Once more, eh, Chuck?
Boy, you and your friends.
Where do you find them?
They find me.
- You know what that was all about?
- No, what?
He was Ionely.
- Know what, Dan?
- What?
I got a lousy feeling our time is running out.
Yeah.
It's funny.
I was just thinking about
Russell and that turkey.
- Car one-twelve, car one-twelve?
- That's us.
Maybe it's something.
One-twelve to central.
One-twelve to central, K.
Respond to the southeast corner
of 104th Street and Broadway.
104th Street and Broadway.
See the complainant at luncheonette.
One-twelve to central. 10-4.
- Is there anything else, Commissioner?
- No, thank you, Marvin.
- [Knock]
- Yes?
- Oh, good morning. Morning, Tony.
- Charley.
This morning's case sheet.
Two bad knifings and a homicide in Brooklyn.
- Not good.
- No.
- Is the homicide a gang thing?
- Yes. It looks like that.
A jurisdictional dispute. There'll be more.
Be nice if they killed each other off.
- Anything new on Benesch?
- No. When it breaks, it'll break fast.
Bowler and Silvers, on the Taylor case,
I just had them in this morning.
Went over it thoroughly, they're clean.
They did their duty and nothing more.
I'll stake my reputation on it.
- Well, that's that.
- No...
We've still got to tell Dr Taylor something.
That poor boy of his is precious to him.
Something's eating you, Tony.
What's on your mind?
I can also play it for you.
Well...
I was afraid this might be it.
I figured that if it was,
the only thing to do was to say, "Well."
"You got caught with your hand in the till,
Charley."
And then the next thing to do
was to walk out, possibly...
Just possibly, your old friend might
let you do it with a bit of grace.
- That's the way I figured it.
- Tell me about it, Charley.
What difference does it make?
I got tapped by Griffen. There it is.
Never mind that, I want an explanation.
What's behind this?
[Irish accent] There's nothing behind it at all,
at all, me boy.
I'll just put in me papers,
with your permission, and leave quietly.
Never mind the phoney brogue.
Tell me what this is all about.
- Is that an order, Commissioner?
- Damn right it is.
What more do you want? You got the facts.
- I did a contract for Muller.
- It's your boy, isn't it?
- How in the hell did you know that?
- I guessed. I want to hear it from you.
You always had reservations
about young Charley, didn't you?
Had a couple myself,
down through the years.
But Patrolman Charley Kane Junior
is a nice kid.
And he's gonna be a hell of a cop one day.
Oldest story in the world, Tony.
He and his nitwit wife were in hock
to a loan association for $3,000.
The girl's got two fur coats.
Can you imagine that?
A 21 -year-old girl with two fur coats.
Anyway, Muller knew he needed the dough,
so he passed it to the boy...
...in return for keeping the Vice and Gambling
Squad from raiding Muller's premises.
When the kid couldn't keep the bargain,
Muller threatened to turn him in
for accepting a bribe.
Muller's no fool, he knew
the kid would come to me.
- Pretty smart for a punk like Muller.
- Yeah...
- Go on.
- Nothing.
Fourth generation of Kanes...
...and I'm the first one to get himself
kicked out of the department.
That's one thing the old man
didn't see in that bottle of Irish.
- What kind of money are we talking about?
- $3500.
- Why didn't you just give it back to Muller?
- He wouldn't take it.
Your boy couldn't do his dirty contract,
so you did it for him?
- You might put it that way.
- How would you put it?
Well, that's easy, Tony.
I wanted to save the kid's neck.
You've sold yourself, the department
and me down the river
in the name of fatherhood?
What in the living hell
do you know about fatherhood?
Nothing. But I do know Earl Griffen.
You think he'll cover for you or me
in front of a Grand Jury?
My ears are still pretty good.
You don't have to shout.
What am I supposed to do with that?
Commissioner, I thought you'd never ask.
I've been waiting for you.
Can I get you an egg cream?
Never mind the egg cream.
What have you got?
- See the movie house down the street?
- Yeah, we see it.
OK, left side of the aisle,
ten rows from the back,
you'll find a young boy, Hughie.
He's wearing a black jacket,
green corduroy pants,
a gold sweater and a head full of hair.
- Kind of pretty, ain't he, Buster?
- Hughie what? Do we know him?
No, he's nothing. But once
he drove a car in a heist for Benesch.
Being a cute fella with the ladies,
he helps Benesch out with a few girls.
Sounds all right, Midge.
- What's he doing in there this time of day?
- Waiting for night.
- Thanks, Midge.
- I done good, didn't I?
If it works, it's good.
If it doesn't, it's lousy.
Yeah, you're right, Dan.
Hughie?
Who are you?
Police, Hughie.
Detective Madigan.
That's Detective Bonaro.
- What do you want with me?
- We want to talk to you.
- I'm watching the show.
- We know you're watching the show.
- Come on.
- What is this? I ain't done nothing!
Come on, move it.
Sit down.
So your name is Hughie, huh?
Haven't we seen you before?
No. I ain't never been busted.
Don't get excited. Nobody's gonna bust you.
We want to talk to you
about Barney Benesch.
You've no rights to do this. I want a lawyer!
- What did you do that for?
- Do what for, huh?
Come on, Rocky.
Give the kid a break.
Come on. He wants to cooperate.
Don't you, Hughie?
You see, I was just trying to explain
a little law to him, that's all.
Cigarette, Hughie?
Now, listen, Hughie.
You forget that partner of mine.
It's just you and me.
You tell us where we can find Benesch,
you'll see the rest of the show
in no time at all.
I know nothing about Benesch
and I ain't no stool pigeon!
I know you're no stool pigeon.
You're a pretty straight guy, I can see that.
Even though you did help Barney
on a little job a while ago.
Right?
Yeah... I mean, no!
I don't know what you're talking about!
Hughie, either you talk to me
or Rocky Bonaro. Which do you take?
Wait, Mr...?
Madigan.
- Just call me Dan.
- Well...
Well, Dan.
Honest, I don't know much.
- You don't, huh?
- No.
Let's do it this way. Let me ask you one
or two things. You give it to me straight?
- Yeah.
- We know you sent Barney a few girls.
Huh?
- Well, I didn't want to.
- No?
But this guy Benesch calls me at my house.
He's always saying why don't I fix him up.
He's a freak!
Always saying
why don't we get together with some girls.
- So you did, right?
- Yeah, I sent him a few, once in a while.
It's the only way to keep him off my back.
When I say I don't know where Benesch is,
this just ain't talk.
Because he moves all the time.
He wants a girl,
he says send her here, send her there.
The next time, it's someplace else.
- What about a girl he might be with now?
- Honest, I don't know.
- There's this girl named Rosita he likes.
- We know her. Who else?
There's this other one, a junkie.
Name of Sarah.
I don't think he likes her so hot. Junkies
are too dead. That was three months ago.
- Who else?
Who else?
There were these sisters,
named Stella and Doreen.
They always hang out at the Bongo Club.
Something new for Benesch, sisters!
Then there's this other place called
the Pale Moon. They work both places.
- Where do they live?
- Honest, I don't know!
They hang out at these two clubs
starting 10 o'clock every evening.
- They call you once in a while, right?
- Yeah, to find where the action is.
- Where do they call you?
- Home. Where else?
All right, Hughie.
Write your address
and phone number down, will you?
- Don't worry about him, Hughie.
- You been a good boy, Hughie?
Sure he has, Rock.
He's gonna give us a little hand tonight.
We'll pick him up 10 o'clock
and go for a little ride around town.
You live at this address all the time, Hughie?
Yeah, most of the time.
I move around a little bit, too.
This your place or you live with somebody?
It's my old lady's place. My ma's.
Hughie, if you had any brains,
you'd spend more time with her after this.
- Yeah, I know.
- After tonight, he means. See you later.
Hope you didn't miss too much of the movie.
Yeah. I've seen it before.
That kid needs a haircut.
[Knock at door]
Come in.
You forgot your shield.
How could I have done that?
When I'm ready to pick it up,
I'll let you know.
See you tonight at the Captain's party.
- Good evening, Mr Madigan.
- Hiya.
- Soon as I find a sitter for Julia, I'll buzz you.
- Wait a minute.
- What?
- I still think you're nuts for going.
Suppose somebody sees you?
Like some of the top brass?
They wouldn't believe it.
- Good evening, Mr Madigan.
- Good evening.
Nice to have you with us. Mrs Madigan
is in suite 1004. I'll think you'll like it.
- Good. Have you got a extra key?
- Oh, certainly, Mr Madigan.
- If there's anything we can do, let us know.
- Thank you very much.
- Dan!
- Hi, darling.
Well!
That feels good.
I've been on a starvation diet.
- Where have you been keeping yourself?
- Oh, you're comical.
- Did you find him?
- Who?
- The man you lost.
- Uh-huh.
But I have to leave early tonight.
There may be a break in the case.
Early? What about me?
Don't worry,
the party will be full of friendly bachelors,
good for a few extra dances
and a ride back to the hotel.
- Fine. We can shop for him together.
- Not bad for free.
Not bad.
- I guess they want to keep our business.
- I guess so.
What'll you have? Apples? Pears? Bananas?
Scotch? Bourbon? Or just plain ice?
[Scottish accent] I'll have you, with a wee bit of
Scotch, not on the rocks.
Better be careful.
Hotel rooms do something to me.
I know.
- Let's make it a good party, starting now.
- OK. I'm for that.
- Cheers.
- What did you do today?
- Oh, nothing much.
Wow.
That's nice.
- Did I ever tell you I was hooked on knees?
- Only mine, I hope.
Only yours.
How much time do we have?
Not too much. I have to clean up.
Settle you down at the party.
Get back on the job before Russell sees me.
Oh, damn! Damn Russell!
I'm sick and tired of you and Russell.
I'm fed up with the name Russell.
Who is Russell?
A shanty Irish nobody from the slums!
I could scream!
Calm down. Take it easy.
I want to go to a party.
Who gets in? Russell!
I feel like going to bed. Who gets in?
Russell! I'm sick of Russell!
Now, hold it.
You've got a pretty dress to wear,
you look great, you'll be a knockout.
You know I shouldn't be going to this thing,
but I don't want to disappoint you.
Disappoint me?
For the 10 minutes you're there?
Come on, Julia, be a sport.
I'm up to here in it!
If we don't get a break,
it'll be over our heads.
As far as I'm concerned,
it's over your head right now.
Good evening.
Thank you.
Honey...
- A gun under every tuxedo.
- That's right.
Are we just gonna stand here
or are we going in?
Wait a second. Just a second.
- Hey, Ben.
- Dan!
- How are you?
- Good.
Good to see you.
You know my wife, Ben?
- How do you do?
- Having a good time?
- Oh, just great.
- Who are you with?
- Nobody, I'm batching it tonight.
Is that a fact? Well, you're in luck.
- Where's your stub?
- My stub? What stub?
- You just won the door prize.
- Oh, Dan...
I got a bad leg, it's very bad,
and Julia's dying to dance.
- Say no more. My pleasure, Julia.
- Good. Have fun, honey.
Oh...
- Good evening, Commissioner.
- Hello, Dan.
I'm fine, thanks, Commissioner. I'm just fine.
I just left the wife... I just left her.
As a matter of fact,
I'm on my way uptown right now.
I didn't want her to miss the party.
She's been looking forward to it...
- I was just gonna call my partner.
- I see.
I thought for a minute I didn't have a dime,
and I was wondering
where I could get change,
but it turned out I had a dime after all.
Interesting.
Well, good to see you, Dan.
Sorry, sir.
- Anything new on Benesch, by the way?
- No, sir. Not yet.
But something's bound to break pretty soon,
I'm sure of that.
I was just on my way to call my partner.
So you said. Goodnight.
Goodnight, sir.
179th and Amsterdam, 10-21 in a collision.
179 and Amsterdam.
Something wrong?
Man tampering with an auto.
267 West...
Stop the car, Sam. Watch yourself.
This might be Benesch and it might not.
Hold it a minute, fella.
Hey, Julia.
What do you say we get out of here?
I know a noisy little place
where we can have a quiet little drink.
Sounds fun.
Just one more dance
and then we'll go, OK?
OK.
How long has he been in there?
A year, I think.
What are you doing, Hughie?
What am I doing? Nothing.
Doreen and Stella been around?
- Maybe they're at the Bongo.
- Nah. Been there.
Hey, Hughie? We're going on
to a couple of places. What do you say?
Nah. I'm going home.
- You find him, Hughie?
- No. But I think I got something.
Ross the bartender ain't seen
Stella and Doreen since Friday night,
but he heard they were gonna meet
Barney Benesch for a party.
- He say where?
- No, that's all he heard.
- He asked around. Nobody's seen him.
- You leave word?
Sure. Just like you told me.
If they show, they got the word
to give me a ring.
All right, kid. Don't get too much sleep.
You got a lot of nosying around to do,
till we turn up those sisters.
- You understand me, don't you, Hughie?
- Yeah.
- Gee, but I ain't no cop!
- Now don't get smart.
Right now, you're a cop
whether you like it or not.
Now stay down.
We'll drive you to your house.
[Siren winds down]
- Why haven't you taken him in?
- Bullet grazed his windpipe.
I had to make sure he could breathe
before we moved him.
Commissioner Russell, son.
You and your partner performed bravely.
Commissioner...
How's Phil?
You don't have to worry about him.
Lift him in.
Commissioner. Chief.
Detective's special.
Looks like Benesch dropped it.
Recognise this, Dan?
Yes, sir. It's mine.
Easy now.
How about a kiss?
One more time.
Easy now. That's the kid.
Now...
Oh, yes.
Oh, baby, baby.
Hold me.
Come on, let's go, huh?
Let's go, baby.
Come on, my place is just
a few blocks from here.
We'll be there in a jiffy, come on.
Come on, let's go.
Come on.
Let go.
- Oh... no.
- What do you mean, no? You want to...
No, I can't!
I can't!
I thought I could.
I was mad at him, but I can't. I can't!
Sure you can, honey. Sure you can.
I'm sorry, I can't.
Please take me back to the hotel.
I think I'm going to be sick.
Please.
OK, Julia.
OK.
- Come on, let's get in the car.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- It's all right. Let's get in the car. Come on.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, Dan, you want cheese or jelly?
- Anything you got.
Oh, Dan, there's a phone call.
A guy named Hughie.
- Hughie? Dan Madigan.
- Stella's with me now. They're with Benesch.
He sent her down for a bottle of vodka,
and she called me.
- Benesch has still got Doreen.
- Take it easy, Hughie.
Take your time. Where are you?
100 Street and 2nd Avenue.
Two blocks from where he's holed up.
- Where's that?
- East River Hotel. 102nd Street.
His apartment's on the top floor,
facing the alley.
- Stella says he's got six guns.
- All right, Hughie.
Don't stay there.
Go across to the Washington Houses.
I'll meet you at the south end.
And hang on to the girl, right?
Yeah, man, yeah.
Your wife called.
I told her you were on the phone.
- Thanks.
- She got home OK, and she loves you.
- Jim, we got Benesch located.
- Where?
East River Hotel.
We ought to pass the word downtown,
looks like he wants to go all the way.
- This is exactly the way the apartment is?
- Yeah, that's it.
What about my sister?
He said he'd kill her if I don't come back.
We'll take care of him. She won't get hurt.
Here. Take Stella to the movies
till this is all over. Get going. And thanks.
Lieutenant Price, 23rd Squad.
- Where is he?
- Here, I'll show you.
The top floor, last window on the right.
- Did you cover the front?
- Yes, sir.
- Did you evacuate the top floor?
- No, sir.
- Do it now.
- All right, men, go ahead.
- There's a girl with him?
- That's what they tell me.
It's gonna make things a little tougher.
No tear gas or smoke if we can avoid it.
- Here's the layout.
- Good.
- Who's going in first?
- I am.
- I go in first. I'm the senior badge.
- By only two days!
Dan, go in first. Rocky, cover him.
Don't use that shotgun unless you have to.
I know you have a personal score to settle,
but don't let it make you reckless.
Good detectives are hard to find.
Good luck. God be with you.
Thank you, sir.
To hell with these vests! Let's go.
Never mind the dog. Get going.
This is the last of them.
We've evacuated the whole floor.
Come on, pop.
Barney, you haven't got a chance.
Get some sense in your head and come out.
I still got one of your guns, Danny Boy!
You want it with a Detective's special?
It's all over, Benesch.
Come out or we're coming in.
What are you waiting for, Bonaro?
You and Madigan lost your nerve?
Just the lock. There's a girl in there.
- Dan, cover me and let me go in first.
- Knock it off.
- Keep him talking.
- Right.
Barney? Barney, send the girl out.
She can't help you.
How do you know? I might get bored!
Oh, come on, Barney.
She has nothing to do with this.
- Let's talk.
- I'm all through talking with you bums!
Send me somebody important!
The mayor here yet?
Sorry, he couldn't make it.
He's busy with the budget.
You're a funny man, Bonaro!
You want her alive, come and get her
before I put a bullet in her dumb head!
[Girl screams]
I killed him, didn't I, Rocky?
Dan?
Dan!
Dan...
I'm... I'm hurt bad, Rock.
Sergeant, get these people out of here.
Clear the way.
Get back. You, out!
- You're gonna be all right, Dan.
- Thanks, Commissioner.
Save your strength. You'll be at the hospital
in two minutes.
- I'd like to go with him, Commissioner.
- Go ahead.
Price, get Mrs Madigan... and a priest.
Rocky...
Yeah, Dan?
Did we get him?
Yeah, we got him, Dan.
You're gonna be all right.
Where's Julia?
Julia...
Hey, she's on her way, Dan.
She'll probably be at the hospital
when we get there.
Too... late.
Come on, clear them away, huh?
Let's go, fellas, let's go!
I'm so very sorry, Mrs Madigan.
I don't see why, Commissioner.
Just another lousy cop.
- Are you sorry you killed him?
- Mrs Madigan, please...
I'll take you home.
What the hell do you care
about Dan Madigan?
What do you know about him anyway?
Except he was one of your lousy cops!
- I am very sorry...
- I don't want your sympathy!
Julia, Julia...
You're a self-centred murderer,
and I don't want anything from you.
Except I want Danny.
I want my Danny back.
Your car is this way, Commissioner.
There's never any right thing to say,
is there?
No, never.
Oh, Charley, about that other thing...
We'll face Earl Griffen together.
I think it'll work out.
Anyway, I threw a raid
into Muller's place last night, Tony.
- We'll see what happens.
- Good.
- See you downtown in the morning.
- Yeah.
Oh, Tony.
What are we gonna do about Dr Taylor?
I don't know, Charley. That's Monday.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3tfdf
Help other users to choose the best subtitles