Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Order in court!
Counsel for the defense
of Mrs. Victoria Thompson.
Thomas longwood, m.P.
That's one of the most expensive
lawyers in New Zealand.
The crown against
Victoria Thompson.
Victoria, voice-over: Perhaps
this is the way my story began.
Perhaps this is the way
I came to be here--
Awaiting my judgment.
I've imagined it many times,
the different ways
it might have been.
The different ways
As I've told you in my letter,
the child's father
is unknown to me.
It was my express wish
not to know his name.
My daughter wanted
to keep the child.
You understand that
is impossible.
Naturally, I want the child to
know nothing of this arrangement.
She will be well cared for.
You may be sure of that.
Yes, but of course that
is a comforting thought.
I was sure it would be so.
You haven't told me her name.
Her name?
Yes. What is
the little one called?
I don't believe she has a name.
Victoria?
Victoria, somebody's
here to see you.
Are you a relative
of mine, a relation?
Do you know me?
My name is Oliver Thompson.
I'm a merchant.
I've, uh...
Chain of shops.
It is a small chain,
but, uh...
In 10 years' time I
expect to turn a profit.
They, uh...
They told me of you.
Uh... Won't you, uh...
Won't you sit down?
Victoria, have you...
Have you ever
considered marriage?
In sickness and in health...
To love, cherish,
to love, cherish,
and to obey...
Till death us do part.
I'd never pictured
myself as a bride.
When the matrons
arranged this marriage
when the matrons
with Oliver, I was
determined to do my best,
but we had been taught
that it was a woman's end
to be a wife.
But I was shocked to learn
that although I was wed,
I was not yet free.
You know, Victoria, my dear...
This is where
we must part for now.
You must go back to school.
Back? For how long?
Well, until you come of age.
It's just
a short while, my dear.
It's how it's done.
I'm afraid, my dear,
we should both have
to reconcile ourselves
to this period of waiting.
At last,
by the end of the summer,
I left matron and everything
I had ever known
and set sail
for my new married life
on the north island.
Very tightly, George.
You never been to
the north island, ma'am?
You travel to join your parents?
No. I'm going to my husband.
Um... My new husband.
Mr. Oliver Thompson?
Of tamarind grove.
The town has grown of late.
I don't know
the place very well.
Nor do I.
I've only met
Mr. Thompson twice.
Enjoy your stay, ma'am.
Good evening, Mrs. Thompson.
Good evening.
The master is not
at home, madame.
He's not here then?
He's had to visit
his sick father in woodford.
It was only right.
Woodford.
Ah...
Is that far from here?
It would take 5 hours at least,
I should say, with fast horses.
Did the mas--
Did the master leave long ago?
This morning, madame.
He left something for you.
If you'd do me
the kindness of following.
Master likes to save a penny.
There it is, madame.
A present.
He was sorry not to be here.
Perhaps you'd like
to go and rest, madame.
You must have had
a tiring journey.
Ah! Uh!
I shall take you around
my shops every so often
so you can see what I've
created with these hands,
what I've given up my life to.
George, get over there!
Come on!
That's my brother George,
my wife Victoria,
my parer burley.
My parer burley.
Keeping busy, are we,
brother Georgie porgie?
This cheese will be moldy
before we can sell half of it.
Nah.
Just let me get my hands
on the man who made the
mistake on this order.
Well, it's too late for that.
What's the wholesale price?
5 for 1 and 8ths.
And sale? 3 shillings.
We'll send everything to shops.
Special price. Half a crown.
Oliver, there's
not enough transport
to get all of this to the shops.
Surely, we should hire more porters.
Not enough transport?!
Get 10 of those black laggards
from the street corner,
give them a few pence each.
They can carry the bloody
barrels on their back.
Rat! Rat!
There he goes!
Aah! Aah!
All right! Kill the dumb...
How about that one?!
That's a championship rat!
Well, you were very happy there.
Well, I know. They told me.
Yes.
Tis true. We were all happy.
It's not what
I'm trying to say, um...
When you're dropped there,
you learn not
to think of happiness.
Just as I never thought
you'd have a father
or a brother.
Mmm. Brother.
Ahem.
Ahh.
Has Oliver arrived?
He asked me to tell you
he'd be along later.
It's beautiful.
Perhaps you'd like
to see the dogs.
I was going to feed them.
Oliver is very proud
of the puppies.
Phoebe, Phoebe, Phoebe.
That's Phoebe.
She's my favorite.
She had a hard time of it.
Does he ever let them free?
Simmons runs them every
morning, once a day.
Like clockwork. That's
the way Oliver likes it.
What's the point?
Why does he have them then?
Why do you think?
Come on, Phoebe.
Come on!
That's it. There you go.
Come on, Phoebe!
Is that scream still
necessary, my dear?
I mean, we have been...
Man and wife
for over a month now.
I thought I'd pick some
flowers for my hair.
I should think we could dispense
with some of the notions
the good matrons taught you.
You put on airs, Victoria!
I prefer it to jewelry.
Victoria?
If you could...
These hairs have grown out.
Who did this before I came?
I went to the barber's
more frequently then.
Why don't you go frequently now?
What a fine lady,
you are, Victoria.
Well, this isn't a kennel.
Who brought this dog in?
Get it out!
You heard father.
Simmons, George, anyone,
get this dog out of here!
Victoria, this is
my father, Mr. Thompson.
Uh-huh.
I think it's time
to send burley down
to Christ church,
have him open the next store.
Mmm?
Tired of working
with him anyway.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Try this. Cheese, father.
You'll like it. No.
The rats do.
I'll take some.
I read a fine joke
in the newspaper yesterday.
This one gentleman wants to--
Ah!
I don't know
what sort of customs
you're used to, Mrs. Thompson,
but in our family we like to
show some respect for old age.
Thank you. Right. So...
He wants to challenge
another one to a duel.
See? So, he says to him,
see? So, he says to him,
"I'll trouble you
for your card."
Says the other one--
Victoria, get that bloody door!
Shut--shut the--
It's all right,
George. Sit down.
Sit down, George!
Go on, son! What did he say?
Yeah, right, so...
He says...
"I'll trouble you
for your card."
And the other one says...
"So you can put it
on your mirror
"in your drawing room and boast
that you have gentlemen
visiting you."
That you have gentlemen
Visiting you!
Oh, yes.
Don't you think it's funny?
I used to hide from them
in here when I was a boy.
I'm still hiding from them.
Shh.
You're not going
out in this wet.
You'll stay the night.
No arguing about it.
Bloody rain.
Patty will be knee deep
in mud in the morning.
Last time it rained like this,
the dogs were brown
from head to tail.
The dogs were brown
Not a spot of white on them.
Ha ha ha! Took Simmons
about a month
to get him clean again.
Give him a bath,
a big beast like that.
You best be off, son.
Got work to do tomorrow.
We shall bid
a fond farewell for you
to, uh...
Uh, Victoria,
whatever her name is.
Yes. She's probably
retired to bed
with a book if I know my wife.
Ha ha ha! And I believe I do.
Mrs. Simmons!
Yes, sir.
Find out what
the missus is doing.
Ask her to come down.
The mistress is not
in her room, sir.
She's what?
She may go into the kennels.
That's where she often goes.
She's taken such
an interest, father.
Mmm. Hmm.
You really should wait
before you judge.
Indeed?
Victoria?!
You out here?!
Aah!
Victoria?
She's not there.
She's nowhere in the house.
You're not worried, shorty?
She'll be back?
She'll get cold and wet?
Like you are?
Come back repentant?
She doesn't know
anyone in the area.
I think you treated
her too roughly.
Ahh.
A little lesson won't
do her any harm.
You don't know women, son.
They're all the same.
All of them.
Exceptin' your mother,
of course.
Lord have mercy on her soul.
What was I saying?
Good morning to you, sir.
Joseph, my father's asleep.
The mistress was kind enough
to give me a gold sovereign.
Where is she?
She told me to give you
that there piece of paper, sir.
For god's sake, Joseph,
what's the meaning of this?
I did everything
the mistress told me to, sir.
Hey, what's going on?
I'll take care of this, father!
I was driving
to woodford and she said,
"we ain't going to woodford.
We're going someplace else."
Well, where did you go?
Come on, where?!
The docks, sir.
Why the docks?
I'll shake the living
daylights out of you!
Why the bloody docks?
Don't hurt me, please.
She gave me a gold sovereign
and told me to give you
that there piece of paper.
What is it? What is it?
It's a pawn broker's receipt.
She's pawned the horse and
carriage for 100 pounds.
Ah. I warned you about
making this arrangement.
Oh, father, be quiet!
All we can do now is find her!
Here! Right here!
Where's the ticket office?
Just down there, sir.
Come on.
We go left, son.
Wait for me, Oliver!
I want to be in the world.
I want to know all
that I can know.
I want to know!
I'd have died if I'd
stayed in that house.
Did any ships leave
this port last night?
Several.
Do you have any lists
of the passengers?
How can I help you?
Lists, registers, names,
bloody passengers!
Just wait quietly, please.
I'll need to see the--
Thompson, Thompson.
Thompson. A lady named Thompson.
Uh!
Thompson! Now what's this?!
That's the George Washington
sailing for America.
It's the only one that's--
Good god. America?
Where is this ship?
Further down the dock.
Why did he come for me there?
How did he even know
that I existed?
He kept all that
a secret from me.
I felt helpless.
Uhh!
Aah! Uh!
Oliver!
Watch out, son!
You've killed him.
Come on.
You killed my brother!
Father, take her away!
Guess what?
George is still alive.
Yeah?
Ohh.
How is she doing?
She won't speak.
Not a word.
It's all over.
I've taken care of everything.
Cost you a pretty penny.
Luckily, the ship
was about to sail.
His body is...
No one will ever know.
We shall say
he sailed to America,
we never heard from him again.
You are a very fortunate girl.
We saved you.
Don't frighten her, father.
No.
He was always different
from his brothers.
The runt of the family.
I shall forgive you, Victoria.
Everything will be
different now.
"He leadeth me beside
the still waters.
"He restoreth my soul.
"He leadeth me in the paths of
righteousness for his name's sake.
"Yea, though I walk
through the valley...
"Thou preparest
a table before me
"in the presence
of mine enemies.
"Thou annointest my head with
oil, my cup runneth over.
"Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life.
And I will dwell in the
house of the lord forever."
Aah!
Got to get this plate in.
All right. Think you
can handle that?
Just press when you're
ready, all right?
Come on, Nicholas.
Get the old face around.
Ha ha!
So you see,
they had arranged everything.
I was pregnant
with Oliver's child,
he was full of pride.
And our life together
went quietly forward,
the way he had
always foreseen it.
All right now.
Let's give you this...
Little bunch of flowers.
Yeah, it's lovely.
What happened that night
was never mentioned again.
But they had made it clear to me
that were it not
for their generous protection,
I would surely have
been held for murder.
Once more.
Now, do it again, my dear.
Ah, father.
What do you make of that?
A ghost.
If she were to discover--
Don't talk nonsense, father.
She believes he's dead.
I hear her scream in her sleep.
You must destroy it.
Don't worry, father.
Haven't I handled
everything so far?
You want any of that cheese?!
Do you want any of that cheese?!
Have you no relatives,
no family solicitor, my dear?
No one?
No. That is why
I have come to you.
I've written to the head matron,
but I've heard nothing in reply.
I truly doubt that there's
anything I can do for you.
Is this your first child?
There must be something
you could tell me.
From what you've told me,
assuming your
information is correct,
the convent arranged
for you at age 18
to marry a gentleman who,
by your own account,
does not beat you,
nor starve you,
nor deprive you of his respect.
And yet you cannot
remain another moment?
I...
I'm afraid.
No one will believe me.
No one will understand.
If every woman in the
antipedes with the vapors
decided to divorce her husband,
there would be no children,
no mothers.
You have a long life
ahead of you, my dear.
That is... Is just
what terrifies me.
I must... Must do something.
I must... I must save myself.
And she went in?
Like I said, sir.
She went in and stayed in.
Rather than having
2 hands or 2 feet,
to be cast into
the everlasting fire,
and if thine eye offend thee,
pluck it out
and cast it from you.
Beloved brethren,
let us recall that
we are all one body,
body of Christ.
And all those near to us
are members of that body.
Blessed in the lord,
let us look round
with great attentiveness...
For the eyes and
the hands of the devil...
Are everywhere.
A fine preacher.
Yeah.
It's no doubt
they added precious.
If you can find--
Be careful, my love.
I just want you to know that...
I know where you have
been in the town...
And how long you've been there.
Not just it, my dear.
You see, Victoria,
I know now that
I cannot trust you.
From now on,
you will be accompanied
wherever you go by Simmons...
My faithful servant.
And he will report to me...
Your every thought,
your every thought,
your every movement.
At least until
our child arrives.
Aaah!
"Yea, though
I walk through the valley
"of the shadow of death,
"I will fear no evil--
"for thou art with me,
"thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me.
"Thou preparest
a table before me
"in the presence
of mine enemies;
"Thou annointest my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
"Surely goodness and
mercy shall follow me
"all the days of my life,
and I will dwell in the
house of the lord forever."
And I will dwell in the
Come on.
Let's go.
Don't let yourself...
I shall take you home.
Why didn't it happen to me
what happened to that child?
It's better to die
in a mother's womb
than to live and never see her.
God has cursed me now.
God would never
judge you for this.
My one weakness.
Only one?
Well, I prefer to think so.
I hope not.
This is very curious.
You're a minister,
and yet you show
such an interest
in pagan objects.
Is this not used
in human sacrifice?
Hmm.
This is an amulet.
For love sickness.
Would you like
something to drink?
Yes.
I think I should
let you wait on me.
Victoria!
If you're not doing anything,
perhaps you could help me
with the scissors.
My, uh...
Whiskers.
You know.
Where are they?
Oliver!
Where did you leave them last?
My dearest friend,
after all I had suffered
and believed for months
you cannot imagine
my profound shock
at what I was to find that day
hidden in Oliver's drawer.
Victoria!
Coming!
No, not that one, Simmons.
Reverend Wilson's are
in the other box.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, yes, try one
of mine, Thompson.
What? Why?
Thank you. Don't mind if I do.
Ha ha ha ha!
It's an improvement, you know?
I have them sent from London.
Ohh. Quite right.
Always get the best I say.
I was thinking more
about our supper.
You've made a difference
in the kitchen, my dear.
I shall like to go to London.
I've imagined it many times.
Ohh, you wouldn't like it.
Nope. More than enough
for a lifetime...
Right here,
lifetime? Mm-hmm.
Do you think?
Mm-hmm.
You take my word
for it, right, Wilson?
Mmm. A lifetime.
Now...
You want excitement,
you should come down
to the shop.
Both of you. We've had more
business than we can handle.
It's been an excellent autumn,
if I don't say so.
Excellent winter, too.
You do say so, don't you?
Someday perhaps we shall
have that holiday
I mentioned to you.
Or perhaps we could
go to the cottage.
No, no, no, no.
Too busy at the shop right now.
Well, later then.
Perhaps we could all go.
In the gloom, he charmed her.
So she put her mark upon
his forehead, an ash,
so that the next day
she might recognize
her chosen lord.
Well, if he was so charming,
then why would
she not recognize him
whether he had
a mark or not? Hmm?
The next morning...
She was disgusted to see
her chosen husband.
The other chiefs were outraged.
Kiwi, the handsome chief,
together with his friend wecca,
took the princess and ran off
with lord howell in pursuit.
Is this a true tale?
Lord howell killed kiwi.
Wecca and the princess ran off.
When they reached the
edge of a steep cliff,
wecca hurled the
princess over the rock,
into the black chasm below.
Into the black chasm below.
Her last words were...
"By the darkness
I was confounded."
It's not a true story,
to answer your question.
A true feeling.
But not a true story.
"And then providing
the subject indicates
"a propensity for
indirect influence,
combined with--".
Oh, Victoria.
Where have you collected
all this rubbish?
Reverend Wilson gave it to me.
It's a very famous book
by Dr. Franz mezmer.
You haven't forgotten
what you promised me.
Let me just finish
this chapter, Oliver.
No.
It's very interesting
if you just listen
and let your mind flow.
Let your mind flow?
Is that another
of your doctor's teachings?
"Combined times with
actual physical connection
"combined times with
"between subject and teacher
"that enables a direct
magnetic flow
"to exist between their
respective unconsciousness.
"To be more precise,
"if during the course
of experiments
the teacher were to hold a
shining or bright object..."
Oliver, shall we try it?
You know what I'm waiting for.
And I've been waiting here
for an hour or more.
Ohh. Just let's try it, Oliver.
Promise. I'll do anything then.
All right.
"And it will greatly aid
in the transference
"and it will greatly aid
"of the teacher's will into the
unconscious of the student.
"In so doing, it creates a link
"between the two that
proves impossible to sever.
This link provides--".
Victoria's been reading to me.
Victoria's been reading to me
from one of your scholarly
books, Wilson.
It's not all wives that...
Read entire books
to their husbands.
Did you enjoy it, Oliver?
What book was that?
Dr. mezmer's theories
on the unconscious.
That's it.
That's the one.
I should think
that would be a bit...
Modern for you, Oliver.
Perhaps, uh...
Perhaps you'd like
to try to hypnotize me.
Nah, I should be glad to serve
as one of your subjects.
Oh, no. I don't think you'd make
a very good subject, Oliver.
You're too full of...
Life forces. I don't think
I could capture them all.
Why don't you try anyway?
Yes. Do try.
All right. Perhaps this once.
This is a very new and
revolutionary science.
No one knows how
or why it works.
Too little is known
of its effects.
Ha ha ha ha!
There. You see.
No wonder. You're too strong.
I shouldn't think you'd
say that about me.
Wouldn't I?
Do try it.
It's extraordinary.
It's amazing.
What'll happen now?
What do you want to happen?
Do you want to kiss her?
Victoria?
Kiss the man you love.
Should we ask for more?
No, no, don't.
You can retire if you like.
I shall stay with
Victoria for a while.
I must break the trance then.
Surely you don't think a husband
is unable to take care
of her adequately?
That's hardly the point.
Wilson, she's my wife.
I'll believe I'll take a stroll
before bed if that's all right.
Victoria, my dear...
I've always longed for...
For...
Right. Uhh!
Go on. Give me yours then.
Come on!
Give me one of those rigs.
Give it to me!
There's none left, sir.
Then give me yours then!
Sure you'll be all
right, Mr. Thompson?
Never you mind about me, mate.
I wanna be in on this.
You just light it, sir.
Go on. Light it.
Light it!
Aah! Uhh!
See one over there!
I see it, sir.
This should get rid of them.
Rat!
There's a whole batch of
the beggars here, sir.
The master's not well.
Is there a doctor in the area?
Yes, madame. There's
a new doctor.
Dr. Finch in clarendon,
but I don't know
anything about him.
Shall I send the husband to
fetch doctor Finch, madame?
Yes, yes. Do that.
No. Perhaps I better go myself.
I'm awfully sorry,
Mrs. Thompson,
but, uh, would you mind if I had a
private word with your husband?
But, uh, would you mind if I had a
It's all right, my dear.
I must ask you a rather...
Personal question, Mr. Thompson.
For the sake of your health,
I would be grateful
if you answered me honestly.
Please bare in mind
that I am a physician.
Fire away.
Have you ever, or rather
have you in the recent past,
have the misfortune
to catch a, uh...
A man's illness?
You see, there are symptoms
of poisoning here.
Probably by Mercury,
which as you know is used
to kill venereal disease.
Doctor, I've never been down
with any illness in my life.
Man's or otherwise.
You have my word.
Well... My diagnosis
is poisoning.
At this moment, I cannot
establish the cause.
But fortunately, the state
of illness is not serious.
The medicine I'm prescribing
should set it right,
very shortly.
I assume you've told Dr. Finch
about the rats, Oliver.
The rats?
Oh, yeah.
In my storeroom.
Hundreds of them.
Brought in some men
to get rid of them.
Look at these rats!
I caught a whole
bloody tribe of them!
And you were present on
this occasion personally?
Of course I was.
I wasn't going to stand by
and let the beasts eat
my entire stock.
You should have mentioned
this in the first place.
It confirms my diagnosis.
Please follow my instructions...
Exactly.
A few days, Mr. Thompson,
you'll be as fit as a fiddle.
I'll call again the day
after tomorrow.
In the meantime, you know where
to find me, Mrs. Thompson.
And in the future,
I'd advise you not to poison
your rats personally.
Your life is more important
than your goods surely.
Is he better?
Yes. Getting stronger
and stronger every day.
You must have been frightened.
The doctor says there's
always a danger of a relapse.
But surely under your care...
What?
He's improving so quickly.
Yes.
Perhaps this is
too tiring for you.
Simmons could push
this bloody chair.
It's good exercise...
As you've spent
the whole month indoors.
I'm taking steps
to make it easier,
I've asked my father
to come stay with us.
Your father?
Mmm. Be good company.
But do you think it wise?
Uh, yeah.
You're not strong enough.
Well, he's grown very
fond of you, my dear.
He'll come here as soon as
his affairs are settled.
Looking forward to it.
If we were to go away,
if we were to travel,
he'd be alone in a big house.
No, no. Don't
you worry, my girl.
You've done enough.
You seen how big
the puppies have grown?
I shall put them out
to stud this spring.
Ha ha ha ha.
George, voice-over:
I cannot express
how happy I was
to learn at long last
that you were all right.
I know that it is impossible
for you to correspond with me.
I hope at the very least
that you will receive this.
I was saddened to learn
that you suffer so greatly.
If there was any possibility
of my sending for you now,
you must know I would move
heaven and earth to do so.
I can only hope and dream
that Providence will find
a way to unite us one day.
You are always in my thoughts.
Mrs. Simmons.
The doctor has prescribed
a special diet.
Oh. Very well, madame.
I shall do it myself.
You may go now.
I felt them bite out my throat!
I shouted and screamed!
I couldn't move...
As they bited me more and more!
I was suffocating!
You got to help me,
doctor, please!
It's quite understandable, Mr.
Thompson.
You've had a sudden
high temperature!
Such--such dreams
are quite normal.
So take me.
I was better but now
I'm weaker every day.
Life is losing its grip on me.
Please, don't worry,
Mr. Thompson.
It's just a temporary relapse.
It is unexpected.
These things happen.
My teeth are loose...
And my gums are bleeding.
You haven't been poisoning
your rats again.
I swear, doctor.
I've never been ill in my life!
Why don't you try and get
some rest now, Mr. Thompson?
And, uh...
I'll, uh...
I'll leave you
another prescription.
Hmm?
Ohh.
Oliver's strength slowly waned.
And it was necessary
for the young Dr. Finch
to attend to Oliver,
and even on a few nights
to remain at his side.
One night, as I watched
from the window,
I knew the doctor was puzzled
by Oliver's lack of response
to treatment.
By Oliver's lack of response
But I knew that I alone had
the power to comfort Oliver,
to calm him, to make him sleep.
Please try to keep calm.
I-I know that it hurts.
But it is necessary if you're
to return to good health.
Patience, please.
It won't be long now.
Aah!
Please accept my deepest
condolences.
I'm truly sorry.
This is a great shock.
Oliver... Business...
To think...
This year we were going to open
a new shop in christchurch.
What have you done...
To my son?
Ahh!
Even if god forgives you...
I never shall.
I shall make quite sure
that I see you hanged for this.
Yes, I will.
This is odd.
The lamp. Lower the lamp.
Good god.
Chloroform.
Thank you for waiting.
And so, dear George,
they came for me that morning.
It is over now.
And I willingly accept
what lies before me--
Whatever that may be.
The earth trembles beneath me.
If I had not stepped
in when I did,
there was every likelihood
you would've been
detained without bail.
Everything is being done,
I assure you.
Your defense is
in the best of hands.
I--I did not.
My dear, if
you're trying to tell me
whether or not
you murdered your husband,
I must ask you to stop.
You see, I prefer not knowing.
It's much more
satisfying that way.
Now, to go over
it one more time--
Have you spoken to our minister, Mr.
James Wilson?
He would defend me.
He knows how Oliver
and I've lived.
I tried to get
an appointment with him,
but I'm afraid it was too late.
Too late?
He'd already left.
Left? What are you
talking about?
Your friend, the minister
Wilson, has gone.
Left town the day
you were questioned.
He's been transferred
to Japan... I think.
You did not know?
Order in court!
The crown against
Victoria Thompson.
But can you say what was the
subject of the conversation?
All I heard was the
minister Wilson laughing.
That was just as I
went past the door.
When I'd brought the tea in,
it had gone quiet again.
Mr. Wilson was standing
by the piano...
With his head in his hand
in a rather peculiar way.
Then I heard voices again.
Mr. Wilson's voice mostly.
But I don't know
what he was saying.
The lord's prayer probably!
Moreover, even
the smallest quantity
would cause damage
to the windpipe.
And there is absolutely
no evidence
that chloroform
passed into the stomach.
The throat of the deceased
was not damaged.
And yet your examination
showed an enormous amount
of chloroform in the
stomach of the deceased.
I can't--
I cannot give an
explanation of this fact--
Neither I nor
my learned colleagues.
I'm sorry,
but there simply
isn't an explanation.
Surely though, an explanation
must exist, doctor.
If one excludes
supernatural forces.
It would please us
if you kept
to the facts, doctor,
not supernatural forces.
My apologies.
Did you notice the
presence of chloroform
at any time in the house
of the deceased?
At any time in the house
Yes, I...
I saw a bottle
of chloroform there,
but there were other chemicals
and disinfectants, too...
Used in treating the dogs
as I recall.
And could you state
how much chloroform
was in the bottle that you saw?
You're a doctor.
I can tell you the truth.
When Oliver fell ill,
he began to behave
very strangely to me.
He began to behave
It's beyond my power.
He was so...
He was so frightening.
And his mouth...
The reverend Wilson...
He's a good friend
of mine, of ours.
We love each other
like brother and sister.
I...I...
I asked him to get me
some chloroform
so that I might quiet Oliver
when he got too insistent.
Quieten him?
How?
I...
I-I-I applied
a drop to his face,
on a pad of cotton while...
It always sent him
to sleep, though,
there was no harm done.
Do you have the bottle?
Yes.
In the future, Mrs. Thompson...
You must leave
the treatment to me.
As far as I can recall,
there was some 4,
possibly 5 fluid ounces.
Certainly more
than half the bottle.
And where is this bottle
now, Dr. Finch?
It was dropped... And broken.
Gentlemen of the jury...
Experts appointed
by the court...
Experienced physicians...
Have informed us that
medicine cannot explain
how a poisonous substance
could have found itself...
In the stomach
of Mr. Oliver Thompson.
We live in an enlightened age.
So we are bound to listen
to what the wise
and learned have to say.
And what they have to
say is the following--
We do not know...
How Oliver Thompson died.
And if, gentlemen,
we do not know this,
how can we possibly give
the blame for his death
to a frail woman?
Is that you?
Yes.
How can we expect
that such a woman
has committed a deed...
That has baffled the
wise and experienced?
Read to me.
If you like.
Do you remember where we were?
Yes.
Our law specifies
the benefit of the doubt always.
And in this case,
there is evidently
great room for doubt.
"Lady mader is a gliding woman.
"Years ago when a tall girl
at a boarding school,
"she was informed
by the drilling master,
"an ex-yeager,
that she was a gazelle.
"He meant a giraffe,
"and she owed the
compliment, if it was one,
"to his imperfect
knowledge of English.
"It is an axiom, I believe,
"among polite lovers that
nothing is so effective
"as an unintentional compliment.
"Herr winning's unintentionality,
as he would have called it,
"was most effective.
"The gazelle, miss spofkins,
"forthwith set herself
to study and imitate
"the habits of her namesakes.
"She applied for information.
"She was not unsuccessful.
"And in due time,
glided into matrimony
"with sir John mader,
"a gentleman who
had been baronetted
"for some excellence so deep
"that it was altogether
beyond the will of Ken.
"She was want to boast
of having been married
"just out of the school room
"and there is still a boarding
school flavor about her.
"Lady mader, nee spofkins,
is always almost a lady.
She is now gliding about in
society with 2 daughters."
It is important that you know
what transpired
that fateful night.
Oliver sank
into a deep trance easily,
for the hypnosis
was now our custom.
And while in that state,
I gave him chloroform.
He swallowed it all...
Without a moment's pain.
I do not know
what will become of me now,
but I know that I will never,
ever forget you.
I remain, your servant,
Victoria Thompson.
Uhh!
Ahh!
Ohh!
The jury requests permission
the jury requests permission
to ask one additional
question of Dr. Finch.
Is Dr. Finch present?
If so, the court
gives permission.
Doctor, if the chloroform
were applied
to the deceased
against his will...
By force...
Would it leave traces?
In my opinion, yes.
And no traces were found?
No.
Absolutely none.
We have no more questions.
Order!
Gentlemen of the jury,
have you considered
your verdict?
We have, your honor.
Do you find the defendant,
Victoria Thompson,
guilty of the crime
imputed to her...
Or nay?
Not guilty.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5tadh
Help other users to choose the best subtitles