Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(NUMB/ENCORE PLAYING)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, darling.
Two Bacardi mojitos and a gin and tonic.
Lemon or lime?
Lime.
Where you from?
Lisboa. That's in Portugal.
But you got your tan in Miami?
What's your name?
-Rita.
-Rita. Sonny.
See you later, Rita.
Hey, Michael.
-Neptune.
-Here are your dates.
Hey, baby.
Here you go.
-Let me hit you now.
-No, no, no. Please, put it away.
-Be cool.
-Come on.
Hit me later.
What's with number three?
She's sick, man.
SWlTEK: That's cool. I'll go with two.
Let's go, sweetheart.
NEPTUNE: Do you know how much
I'm losing tonight?
HAlTlAN GlRL: No.
(NEPTUNE SPEAKlNG CREOLE)
BOUNCER: Where you going?
SONNY: Easy. Easy.
Neptune should ease up
on the merchandise.
Flip the girls upstairs and we got him.
His day will come.
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Hello?
-ALONZO : Sonny?
-Yeah. Who's this?
Sonny?
Alonzo?
Alonzo, I can't talk.
We're in the middle of a deal right now.
Take care of Leonetta for me.
Ask Ricardo to do that.
I gave up nothing on you.
They're on their own.
It's all their deal, anyway. Fuck them.
Alonzo, what are you talking about?
I'm falling by the house,
and then I'm gone.
So whatever you can do for her,
okay, Sonny?
Alonzo.
Goodbye.
-What is it?
-Alonzo Stevens.
Something's wrong.
He told you to look after Leonetta for him.
(TELEPHONE RlNGlNG)
FBl AGENT: FBl Miami.
This is Detective Crockett, Miami-Dade PD.
Patch me through to your SAC.
(TELEPHONE RlNGlNG)
Leonetta, it's Rico.
Give me a call back
as soon as you get a chance.
(ANSWERlNG MACHlNE BEEPS)
This is ASAC John Fujima.
Detective Crockett.
What's your Miami-Dade badge number
and date of birth?
447-Charlie-1 292.
-447-Charlie-1 292.
-SONNY: 07-02-70.
OFFICER ON PHONE: Miami-Dade PD Tech.
Bobby G., it's Rico.
Hey, that transponder we had
on Alonzo Stevens' Bentley, it still running?
When's the last time we used it?
I don't know.
We ain't worked him in six months.
Okay. So?
SONNY: One of your deals
may be going bad.
Confidential informant
we cut loose to you guys.
Cl's name is Alonzo Stevens. He called us.
We haven't spoken to him in six months.
How do I discuss this over
an open phone line?
How the hell do I know?
We got the phone call from Alonzo
on an open line.
That is the hand we have been dealt
at 1 1:47 on Saturday night.
Now, I do not know what case
you have him on, but whatever it is,
it is going bad, and it sounds like
it is going bad right now.
It's a preliminary meet and greet.
RICO : Meet and greet?
You flash me yours, I'll flash you mine?
FUJIMA: Who are you?
-Ricardo Tubbs.
-My partner.
Yeah, deal goes down another time,
another place.
-So, what? No HRT weapons team out there?
-That's right.
Colombians? Russians?
White supremacists.
And that tape
is not gonna look good in court.
Aryan Brotherhood? Mongols?
Nazi Low Riders? What?
We think Aryan Brotherhood,
but we don't know for sure.
-What's up?
-Get Michael out of there.
-What about Neptune?
-It's Neptune's lucky night.
What else did Stevens tell you?
He said that it went bad,
that he didn't give us up. Told us goodbye.
ZITO : Rico, we got the Bentley.
Hey, he just got on the 95 southbound
from the 195 causeway.
We got meth, ice, glass, Es, Ks, ex,
Mitsus, Ames, Colombian H.
Ice.
Party down with the coke.
You're looking at 92% pure.
Not like that jumped-on powder
they sell up in Nuyorico.
(SPEAKlNG FORElGN LANGUAGE)
Never seen green?
You got the green. We got the goods.
We party.
Larry'll call you in the a.m.
about quantity and money, time and place.
Hey, lvan!
My brother.
How long have you been working
with the FBl?
Alonzo, pull over!
Pull over!
Stay back!
What'd you do?
I fronted their undercover team
to these guys like usual, you know?
They're Feds, Russian speakers.
I was the middleman.
-What, 15%?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, to set up the meet.
They grabbed Leonetta.
They took Leonetta.
I gave them up, man.
Gave up the Feds. Everything.
Everything I knew. Rico, I got to go home.
Got people there now.
-How did they get onto you, Alonzo?
-How the hell do I know?
They knew one Russian was FBl
from the get-go, so...
They knew I knew.
-Rico, I gotta go.
-RlCO: Alonzo. Alonzo.
(RlCO DlALlNG PHONE)
-Rico, I got to go. I got to go.
-Alonzo. Alonzo!
-I gotta fucking go!
-Hello?
(TURNlNG OFF CELL PHONE)
RlCO: You don't...
You don't...
You don't need to go home.
They said they wouldn't hurt her, man.
They lied.
-Alonzo!
-No!
Prints on the fridge.
Hold on.
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
Yeah.
CASTILLO : Where are you?
What's your QTH?
Just a couple blocks away.
We can see the lights.
Turn around.
Turn around? Look, we know these people.
Meet me in 15 minutes, Standard Park.
-What the hell just happened?
-RlCO: What was that?
Who's this?
He needs to talk to you.
I'm Fujima. We talked on the phone.
-So, this was your operation?
-Yes, at command level.
We trusted our informant, Alonzo, to you,
and you got his whole family killed?
What, did you jump some amateurs
into a game they ain't ready for?
-What the fuck happened, man?
-Three men got killed!
-SONNY: And so did our...
-Cool down.
They discovered my guys were undercover,
and we don't know how.
This was an interagency task force,
DEA, ATF, U.S. Customs.
The leak could have come
from any one unit.
I gotta assume
my operational security is compromised.
Compromised? Your whole op sec is blown.
You're stone cold dead in the water.
Meanwhile, it does not track.
White supremacist gang?
White prison gangs is tweakers
and meth labs and trailer parks.
Bouncing the old lady around
until they get busted back.
And how did they get all high tech
with sophisticated counterintel?
And what we here
talking to you for, anyway?
Miami-Dade wasn't part of the task force.
Oh.
They don't know you.
So, you want to recruit us?
Identify them. Who are they?
-How did they cut into us?
-How do we cut into them?
How do we get
all close and personal with them?
Make a buy. That worked well.
Sell to them? We supply them?
No, they got a steady stream of supply.
Colombian named José Yero,
midlevel trafficker.
Okay. So what about Yero?
Can we get to them through Yero?
-FUJlMA: Possible.
-What does he need?
-Money laundering? Transpo?
-FUJlMA: Transpo.
He outsources his transportation.
Okay.
Do we run an undercover on José Yero?
So we transport a load for Yero
into this group?
So can we run a load for Yero
into this group? It's a question.
He transships out of Haiti.
Flies his product in from Colombia,
hires someone to run it from Haiti into here.
This is a FLlR image of someone's
go-fast boats running in a Yero load.
AWAC shot it.
That's all we got.
All right. If they do this,
I'd like them deputized as federal under
OCDETF for the purposes of this case.
Fine by me.
Because your op sec is blown,
your agency can't know anything about
how they do whatever it is they do.
That's why I came alone. Thank you.
Sorry about your men.
CASTlLLO: What'd you spot?
Go-fast boats running that close?
On radar they look like one, not two.
Total darkness?
Man, those are skill sets.
Plus, who runs four 250 Mercs
off a deep-V hull?
Sal Maguda.
-He that good?
-Oh, yeah.
SONNY: Bleaching it down.
Must have just unloaded.
-Who are we?
-How's your Creole?
(RlCO SHOUTlNG lN CREOLE)
Do you know whose load this is?
What are you doing?
(TELEPHONE RlNGlNG)
Hello?
Hey, Nicholas, my ace. What's up?
Everything's good. You?
We good. We all good.
As a matter of fact, we're looking
to charge up your cash flow. Hold on.
-Nicholas, how you doing?
-Sonny. What's up?
Somebody's something's got to go
somewhere, some when.
Not too distant in the future.
Except he had transpo problems.
RlCO: Call Colombia.
-Man, that's José Yero.
-RlCO: Really?
NlCHOLAS: He is AUC, you know.
Colombian right-wing paramilitaries.
You know who they are?
They are vertically integrated. They are...
You mean, they walk around
with constant erections?
No. They farm, process, produce, export...
I know what it means.
No, see, it gives them attitude.
A player negotiates too hard
and you never hear from him again,
'cause these guys kill everything!
I gotta know what's the skinny.
-It's none of your fucking business.
-lt can come back on me, baby.
It can't come back on you, baby.
-Am I assured of that?
-Hey, sunshine.
When has Rico or Sonny
ever lied to you, huh?
I mean, when has anything Rico told you
not happened exactly like he said?
RlCO: You saying I lie to you?
NlCHOLAS: No, I'm not saying that...
TRUDY: Yes, you are.
NlCHOLAS: It's just there's variables,
you know?
Randomness, see? That's why.
-"That's why," what?
-Well, why, like, if you can't deliver,
this group goes from zero
to high-order violence like that.
You made a 15% commission
off three money-laundering prosecutions
I put you into,
you know, which is why you live
in your $4 million condo.
And you question Rico and Sonny?
Fuck that. I will cap your skanky ass
and throw it off that goddamn balcony.
Yeah, then we can kick back and
watch Marlins highlights on this 65" plasma.
After we clean this place up.
Don't you ever put anything away?
Plus he's gonna commission José Yero
for putting you to José Yero.
Anybody looking at his ill-gotten gains?
IRS looking into his shit?
SONNY: Any reason
this does not go down?
That's the sound of air rapidly filling
the vacuum created by your departed body.
On account of how fast I remanded your ass
back into custody.
Why is this happening to me?
Because you lead a life of crime.
Can't do time, don't mess with crime.
SONNY: He's cool. He'll make the call.
Hey, you.
Wake up.
What happened to you?
Aren't you excited to see me?
I can't talk about it.
-Mmm-hmm.
-This is all right.
I'm just joking.
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep right here. That's it.
-Any word?
-RlCO: Nothing.
"Hey, Trudy." Hey, Sonny.
Hey, Trudy. How you doing, darling?
Who are we here?
It's the same fabricated fundamentals
as before.
Rico.
3-to-5 on assault, Folsom B-wing,
Pelican Bay.
Sonny, Marine Corps,
Chicago, and 10 plus weapons.
Five out of eight, and jumped parole.
Pelican Bay, where you guys hooked up.
And then it goes cold,
'cause presumably you're both too smart
and too fast to get jacked again.
What about this place?
It'll show up
leased under these aliases.
How'd they test?
-And who tested them?
-Helene in NYPD.
And she worked through
your false identities,
and then she found your deeper, hidden,
more criminal selves.
-SONNY: Yeah.
-He's in.
You're on. The meet's in Haiti.
He'll negotiate the price
in person.
Call me after you've landed
in Port-au-Prince,
'cause only when you're on the ground
will he tell me where you are to go.
Be careful. Be cool.
Approaching. Turning to heading 340
down to 6,000 feet.
Clear to the lLS runway 1-0
for the approach to Port-au-Prince.
Why do I get the feeling everybody knows
we're here 15 blocks out?
'Cause everybody knows
we're here 15 blocks out.
Sit.
José.
Sonny Burnett.
That's my partner, Ricardo.
Thank you for coming down.
So, let's lay it out.
Nicholas say you run a tight group.
That's nice, 'cause we got product
that's got to move.
-Real tight. We move as fast as FedEx.
-Move to where?
To New York, through South Florida.
-SONNY: Move when?
-Right now.
That's kind of all of an instant.
RlCO: That means only one thing, real fast.
So, the price, is it right?
Price is right.
But how I know if you any good at this shit?
What's that?
Yeah, your business.
How much volume you do?
Whose product you move?
Who you work with?
Other than Nicholas,
who the fuck knows you?
Well, my mommy and daddy know me.
And we don't talk about who we work with.
And we didn't come down here
to audition for business.
Business auditions for us.
And knows all about us,
before they call Nicholas.
That way we don't waste avgas
or our motherfucking time.
SONNY: You want us to be telling you
about our shit?
You can't find out on your own?
Why do I not buy that?
You with DEA? The Feeb? What's up?
They targeting our transpo line?
You with the Man?
You wearing a wire?
RlCO: I'm gonna tell you
what's gonna happen.
People gonna come in here,
and you know what they gonna say?
They're gonna look around
and they're gonna go...
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
"That's some crazy
motherfucking wallpaper. What is that?
"Jackson Pollock?"
"No, viejo. That was José Yero,
who got splattered all over his own wall."
So, we can close each other's eyes
right now, real fast.
But then ain't nobody
gonna make no money.
ISABELLA: José.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
So let's talk equipment.
Adam A500s, carbon composite,
real stealthy.
1,400 nautical-mile range, low and slow.
We like Caravelles and 727s
to move the product from source countries
to transshipment places like here.
Big loads, we like containers.
Smaller loads into South Florida,
we do go-fast boats.
So, what's the weight?
-First, let's talk logistics.
-Okay.
You pick up a load, you fly it in the hole,
we tell you the drop point,
and our people then move it on up the road.
Now, not so fast. People at the drop point
are our people, not yours.
You know, so there's no tweakers, dopers,
first-timers, people we don't know.
They didn't do time with us,
they ain't doing crime with us.
Once we pick up the load,
the next time you hear from us
it'll be a date, time, and a place.
Like, "There's a 18-wheeler in a parking lot
in north Miami with the keys in the ignition."
You pick it up, you drive away.
Smooth, that's how we do it.
So, when you looking to move it?
Never.
'Cause how you drop loads, I don't like,
so maybe this don't work.
Then it don't work.
Red light, green light, José.
They also call me Cochi Loco.
That means "crazy pig."
'Cause I run security and counterintel.
I get people to tell me
what they don't ever want to say.
And I have eyes everywhere.
That part of what I do,
you never want to find out about.
Other people negotiate money,
and go and no go.
Yes, no, maybe so.
Not me.
So, what the hell are we talking to you for?
-I had to lay my eyes on you.
-SONNY: Why is that?
To see if you go meet the Man.
And?
You seem okay.
But him,
I don't like how he looks.
Do you want to fuck my partner,
or do you want to do business with us?
'Cause I don't give a shit
how you think he looks.
Wait by the phone in the hotel.
You get a call, or maybe you don't.
And then you can piss off
back to where you come from.
Yero said New York
through South Florida.
Then this load
does not go to the Miami group.
That may take load number two.
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
(SPEAKlNG CREOLE)
That was fast.
Four hours. They're dicking us around.
Call it.
That's it.
Let's go.
ISABELLA: Put your guns on the table.
We didn't bring you here to kill you.
If we want you dead, you'd have been
no longer drawing breath in Miami.
$3,000 a kilo on small loads.
SONNY: Thought we had
to meet the Man.
You do.
-When is that?
-Right now.
Full signal, no service.
They're jamming the phones.
This is the type of stuff the ClA does.
In Baghdad.
Yeah. What's it doing on a dope deal?
Out of the car.
(SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH)
MAN: See the three trucks?
Move there now.
SONNY: Where'd all the people go?
Ready, boss?
Excuse me, because I am very busy.
I have many things to do,
so this will be brief. Yes?
I will try you out on one load to build trust.
1,000 ki's out of Colombia.
Your end is $3 million.
In all matters, when you work for me,
you must do
exactly what you say you will do.
In this business with me,
I do not buy a service. I buy a result.
If you say you will do a thing,
you must do exactly that thing.
Then you will prosper beyond your dreams
and live in Miami millionaire-style.
You will contact and work
through José Yero
on logistics, communications, security.
To do with money and terms,
you will work through my lsabella.
I look forward
to our doing more work together.
Whether we do or do not,
it is unlikely that we will meet again.
I extend my best wishes to your families.
Thank you for making this trip to see me.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
Flight 000 is airborne.
ZITO : This is November 1206 Sierra.
Roger that.
CONTROLLER: Good afternoon.
Radar contact. Climb and maintain 7,000.
November 636
is coming your way from the northwest.
636.
CONTROLLER: Opa-locka Departure,
good afternoon.
Radar contact. Climb and maintain 7,000.
King Air 1 206 Sierra,
you see anything off your right side?
This is November 1206 Sierra.
Negative, Opa-locka.
I got a double hit.
I think there's another plane there.
SUPERVlSOR: Let me see.
CONTROLLER 2: Go down to 220.
Ghost. One blip, one plane.
(TELEPHONE RlNGlNG)
Yeah.
Oye, Burnett. Our client got delivery.
Product's on the road. Good work.
Yeah, but we had a problem
before your client showed up.
Somebody tried
to rip off the load.
You know a detail shop
on Second and Overtown?
I do.
Across the street we found a stash house.
10: 00 a.m. Be there.
Here we go.
ZlTO: Only two.
RlCO: They tried to jack your load.
We brought him home and discovered this.
YERO: Haitians stole this two weeks ago.
That's my load. This is my product.
RlCO: How'd they know where the drop was?
-How'd they know?
-I find out.
See you later.
I see you,
I see a load we lost two weeks ago
all in the same place.
Well, you don't like us finding your load,
we can go ahead and lose it all over again.
What other suspicions
did you mastermind today?
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
We want our product back.
Sure.
How much?
How much...
-For what?
-For recovering that.
Nothing.
Nothing?
Consider it an investment
in the future of a fine business relationship.
That is because it's yours.
What's yours is yours.
So is this a one-time deal?
Or is something else coming up?
Give them the shipment on the 17th.
-RlCO: Conveyance?
-By ocean. Out of Barranquilla.
José has details.
Lay it out.
You're gonna get the longs and lats
for a transshipment point.
Ma'am.
-Do me one favor.
-Yeah?
In return for the risks we took
in recovering your load,
allow me to buy you a drink.
How fast does that go?
Goes very fast.
Show me.
Where would you like to go?
What do you like to drink?
I'm a fiend for mojitos.
I know a place.
RlCO: Partner.
I know what I'm doing.
All right. The secured satellite comms,
Iongs and lats for the transshipment points,
that's all cool.
But I need a vector, not a location.
Ships move, that's why they call them ships.
Ship stops, it's trying to impersonate
an apartment building.
At sea, that is very suspicious.
Brings about attention.
AWACS, Coast Guard, U.S. Customs,
that's all bad.
I take you to the best place for mojitos.
Where is that?
Bodeguita del Medio.
Oh, the Keys?
Havana.
Havana?
Cubans don't like my business.
-And they don't like my passport.
-It's okay, the harbormaster is my cousin.
Grab the wheel.
You do business in Cuba
with your husband?
I never do business in Cuba.
And Jesus is not my husband.
I'm a businesswoman.
I do not need a husband
to have a house to live in.
(BAND PLAYlNG CUBAN MUSlC)
-You like the mojito?
-Mojito's great.
Do you dance?
I dance.
(lSABELLA SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
You will like it.
Allman Brothers.
You know Allman Brothers?
No.
Lynyrd Skynyrd? Free Bird?
-No Skynyrd.
-Well, that was the music back then.
And he played all those Atlanta bars.
But his luck was...
Well, my dad never got lucky,
so he started trucking.
Yeah, I didn't see a whole lot of him.
But we were close.
-You look like your mother?
-Why?
She died in Angola when I was 16.
She was a translator.
I show you photograph. It's from wedding.
This is a bad idea.
This is past a bad idea.
And it has no future.
That's right.
So, then there's nothing to worry about.
Come here.
See?
Lucinda somebody's wedding.
Everybody is with couples.
Husbands and wives, they all pose.
But she is the most special.
Let's talk a different kind of deal.
You pay us zero.
Is it December?
Why?
Did Christmas come early this year?
No.
We become partners on the loads we run.
What we want is 25% of that load in product.
And why, you're thinking,
would I be crazy enough
to cut in these gringos like that?
It's because Sonny and Ricardo
can deliver to me what no one else can.
We guarantee loads.
Comes up short, we make good.
Your operation will run
from now on out risk-free.
And you are the 25% partner?
You?
What if I tell you
your ideas are too big for your skin?
And merely to propose this
is a dangerous thing.
Then I would say to you, this has been fun.
Okay. So?
Think of the cash you don't have to front.
Cash is not difficult.
Seventeen.
I would say you're five percentage points
away from a deal.
Maybe I'm only one.
You've convinced me.
(TELEPHONE RlNGlNG)
-RICO : What's up? Where are you?
-I'm on my way back.
RlCO: The meeting with Castillo
is in 45 minutes.
-What's up, Sonny. You okay?
-Fine, darling.
RlCO: So, where you been?
Hit a couple of jazz clubs,
fell back to her place.
-Where?
-Vedado.
-Where's Vedado?
-Suburbs outside Havana.
-You went to Havana, Cuba?
-No, Havana, Louisiana.
Don't we have a meet?
You making moves on Montoya's woman?
-No.
-You're not making moves on her?
-We're making moves on each other.
-Oh, so that's supposed to make it all right?
Something like that.
-So what happened to the first load?
-Went to Dominicans in New York.
We think load number two's going
to our guys. South Florida. Their big buyer.
-Okay, that's great.
-Yeah.
But we wanna go beyond load number two.
-Why are we going exploring?
-Who's the "we"?
Only thing you've contributed so far to this
is bad intel.
-How's that?
-José Yero, cocaine producer?
Yero's middle management,
part of a bigger transnational operation
run by Arcangel de Jesus Montoya.
Montoya's the new news. Globalized.
Moving?
Colombian coke and H,
arms from the Ukraine,
E from Holland,
pirated software from China into Brazil.
What's this got to do
with the price of tea in China?
We're seeing their ops.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5cr6j
Help other users to choose the best subtitles