Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(WHlSTLES)
(MAN YELLlNG lN lTALlAN)
Here we go.
Come on.
(NElGHlNG)
Come on, seven !
What are you doing
at the house of God?
This is where l grew up.
Mott Street.
I'm CharIie Luciano.
ln my neighborhood
there were two dons.
Two bosses, each fighting
for control of New York.
And sometimes innocent people
got caught in the middle.
l got a right to drink
a glass of wine!
l got a right
to find work
that uses my brain !
You clean the fish
and the calamari,
just like me!
What are you saying?
'Cause l'm a greasy immigrant,
all l can do is clean fish?
That ain't enough, Pop!
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHlNG)
(SPEAKlNG lN lTALlAN)
You come in my house?
You tell
the son of a bitch
Faranzano,
the miserabile bestia,
l give him. . .
Don Faranzano.
Faranzano.
Faranzano,
l no mean
what l say.
You have been very loyal.
Done favors for me.
Always made your payments
on time.
Now you've stopped paying.
l have to ask myself, "Why?"
No, no. Faranzano,
mia piccola bambina,
she's sick.
l no have the money.
l no got the money.
FARANZANO: Fat pig.
When l came from Sicily,
you went with me.
Now you're drifting back
to that fat pig, Masseria.
No! Faranzano. . .
You are, l see.
No, no, no.
(GROANS)
l can't take chances.
lf one man can desert me,
everybody can. Understand?
Yes.
lf you have to sell
your daughter,
you will pay!
You have a pretty wife.
Usually, after children,
they get fat.
(WOMAN SCREAMlNG)
(SPlTS)
Nice, sweet taste.
(SHOUTS lN lTALlAN)
Get out of my house!
l felt your balls,
so l know why
she needs her own.
(ROSALlE SPEAKlNG lTALlAN)
Put down the knife.
You'll have your chance
one day.
(CRYlNG)
That was one boss.
Don Faranzano.
Some things change
your life forever.
Yeah, l know.
l know. Loyalty.
My father
sweated blood for him.
CHARLlE: The guy with me here
is Frankie Costello.
Loyalty, Frankie, yeah?
He and Joey DeCarlo
were my two best friends.
That Joey?
But on these streets
friends were hard to keep.
Don Masseria!
(SPEAKlNG lN lTALlAN)
Look at this.
(GASPS)
Joey!
Terrible what these
niggers are doing.
They come down from Harlem,
kill my own nephew.
Right in front of my face.
(SPlTS)
WOMAN: (CRYlNG) My son !
Oh, no! No, no!
My God !
My son !
Joey!
Joey! My God ! Joey!
CHARLIE: That was
the other boss.
Don Masseria.
Some way, some time,
no matter how long it took,
I knew what I had to do
to both bosses.
He kills
his own blood,
you know?
l mean, his own nephew.
What kind of man is that?
And on top of that,
he pays
some lrish to do it.
CHARLIE: The law of the street
was take or be taken.
Everybody fought everybody.
Irish, Italians,
Germans, Jews.
But this was different.
This was that Irishman
who killed Joey.
Beating up on
this skinny Jewish kid,
Meyer Lansky.
And the Jewish kid
wouldn't stay down.
Meyer wouldn't give
no matter how bad he got it.
You had to respect that.
Meyer's big pal
was Benny Siegel.
Leave him alone,
you fucking mick!
CHARLIE:
Benny loved a good fight,
even a bad fight,
but they wouldn't let him in
on this one.
What is it? You in love
with the little Jew boy?
No.
Joey was a friend of mine!
Meyer!
(SlGHS)
What the hell's
everybody looking at?
He just saved your life.
CHARLlE: Come on.
Let's get the fuck
out of here.
CHARLIE:
So that's how we started.
Two Italians and two Jews.
Funny combination.
Frankie, he liked to worry,
so he paid off the cops.
Benny liked to brawl,
so he was our muscle.
And me and Meyer,
we were both the leader.
At least
it started out that way.
Just four mugs off the street.
At first we were penny-ante,
but together we grew.
Thing that worries me is
things is going too good.
Relax.
How can l relax?
When everything's going right,
you know it's gonna go wrong.
We can't keep operating
like four kids running around
the neighborhood.
That's what l mean.
lf we're going to expand,
we need a leader.
And who's that
gonna be, huh?
Tommy's meeting us
over here. Come on.
After you.
Please, be my guest.
Thank you.
WAlTER: l got 'em coming up
right now, sir.
Do like l said
with the kid.
Okay.
What is this?
You'll see.
Charlie, come sta?
How's everything?
Meyer.
Good to see you.
l got everything
ready for you
in the back.
What do you got
to show me?
lt's a little experiment.
You asked me a question.
l'm gonna answer it.
Come here.
Yeah.
Watch.
He's telling this kid
there's a guy here,
very powerful, successful,
who's got a job for him.
Easy money.
You got that?
Good, get out of here.
Let's go.
Now he realizes.
Bugsy didn't tell him, right?
Me or you.
Got a job for me?
You just did it, kid.
Get lost.
Now do you see?
Between you and me,
we're equals.
But other people,
they look to you.
What are you saying?
l'm your front man?
No.
This ain't a con, Charlie.
You're it.
You're the one.
Tommy Reina,
Charlie, Meyer.
Good pal, gonna even be
a better partner.
From your mouth
to God's ear.
He's got a line
on the good stuff.
How good?
Bottle in bond scotch whiskey.
l got a friend got a boxcar
sitting on a spur in Philly.
He wants 35 G's.
l only got 1 0.
Who's this friend?
Arnold Rothstein.
No disrespect, Tommy.
Why would Rothstein
wanna do business
with bums like us?
'Cause some of us
are Jewish bums. Right?
You'll find out Monday night
when you go to his hotel.
No one ever called
you all bums.
Come on.
lt's very good stuff.
TOMMY: Come on in, fellas.
l want you to meet the genius
who fixed the World Series.
Mr. Arnold Rothstein.
This here's Charlie Luciano,
and Meyer Lansky.
Tommy, thanks.
Yeah.
Sit down. Sit down.
Mr. Luciano,
you're walking
down the street.
Suddenly you realize
you're being followed.
lt's a hit.
Walking toward you
is a second gunman.
You have time to fire at only
one of them. Which one do. . .
l don't accept the question.
To live, l got to
kill 'em both.
Next,
your wife comes. . .
l don't have a wife.
Why not?
Emotion is dangerous.
Aren't you human?
Would it help?
Next. l have ships
and distilleries in Scotland.
l need distribution
in New York.
Masseria? Faranzano?
They'd kill me.
l won't?
You have Jewish partners.
Maybe l'd kill them too.
You can't afford to.
You're in the squeeze.
Masseria has 700 soldiers.
Faranzano, 600.
Either one realizes you exist,
they'd squash you like an ant.
Unless l get
a powerful friend.
Exactly.
Next.
What's the secret
of America?
What's the matter with
this guy? l'm 24 years old. . .
Money!
Everything is money,
Charlie.
Don't ever forget it.
But you, you'll never
make any money.
Why's that?
You dress like a schmuck.
(LAUGHlNG)
(EXCLAlMS)
Let's do some business.
Check it.
ROTHSTElN: (LAUGHlNG)
lt's raining money.
We got money to burn, Charlie.
Wanna burn some?
Want to? Want to?
All right!
Be my guest.
Everybody ready?
The party.
Our first million.
You ready to make some money?
l'm ready.
l'm always ready.
Just don't hog all the broads.
l can't help it.
They're all over me.
Tell us something
we don't know.
Gentlemen, before we go,
let's have a toast.
Our first million dollars.
Say this bottle
is bootleg business,
greater New York.
This is our business
when we started.
Nobody noticed us,
nobody gave a shit.
Now, this is our business
right now.
lt's big enough for us
to have a party.
Big enough for
other people to notice.
This is where we want
our business to be.
But the bigger we get,
the more we're taking
from other people.
Thanks.
Masseria's already calling us.
Faranzano, calling.
You see what l'm saying?
Yeah. l didn't get
no whiskey.
l'm saying this.
lf we're not careful. . .
We're all bums
when the wagon comes
l mean this joint
is jumpin'
Charlie!
Hey.
l got the room
in the back for youse.
Father, how are you?
Tommy, you bum,
you look beautiful.
Grab a jug
and cut the rug
How you doing?
Good to see you.
Check your weapons
at the door
Be sure to
pay your quota
CHARLlE:
The table looks beautiful.
Giovanni !
The neighbor's knockin'
We're all bums
when the wagon comes
I mean this
joint is jumpin'
MEYER: People
will love to play numbers.
lt's smart business.
Somebody hits big,
you got to publicize.
All right. l'll get
somebody downtown.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
(MEYER CLEARS THROAT)
Anna Citron,
these are my partners.
Frank Costello.
ANNA: Hello.
MEYER: Benny Siegel.
ANNA: Hi.
And these
are their girlfriends.
ANNA: He has two girlfriends?
At least.
(TOASTlNG lN lTALlAN)
Charlie, this is my girl.
l want you to meet
Anna Citron.
My goodness, l'm honored.
Sit down.
You met my priest?
Anna Citron,
this is Meyer Lansky.
Hello.
This here is
Father Bonotto.
(GREETlNG lN lTALlAN)
Father!
Tommy, you stupid bootlegger
from the Bronx.
Charlie,
l want to talk to you.
You see, this is why
alcohol is outlawed.
You son of a bitches.
They're threatening us.
Then talk to the bosses.
You mean buy ourselves
some time.
Exactly.
l agree.
Frankie. We made it.
Let me tell you this.
Watch your back, all right?
Good.
Yeah.
So, you talked
to Rothstein?
Yeah.
He worries too much.
So do l.
Faranzano wants to meet
in the morning.
l think
we should go.
Not yet.
Let him beg.
He is begging.
(SCREAMlNG)
(YELLlNG)
Meyer!
Stay down !
(GROANlNG)
Move! Move!
(ANNA SCREAMS)
You okay, Meyer?
Anna?
Yeah.
That's twice
l saved your life.
You're telling me.
l hate owing somebody.
Listen, we're meeting
Faranzano in the morning.
Whatever you say, Meyer.
Good.
You all right, Anna?
Don Faranzano.
Have we met?
Maybe around the neighborhood.
When l was a kid.
This is my associate,
Meyer Lansky.
l don't talk business
with Jews.
You talk business with me.
lf Meyer works with me,
that ain't your concern.
Let's be blunt.
lf you go with Masseria,
maybe he wins.
lf you go with me,
maybe l win.
This seems to give you
a lot of power.
So what are you offering me?
Masseria's the boss
of all bosses.
l respect him.
(CHUCKLES)
He's a fat pig.
l offer you this.
Join my family.
We combine all operations.
You'll get 1 5 percent.
Yes?
lt's a very handsome offer.
We have to think it over.
That means no.
Means what it means.
We have to talk
with our partners.
Show them out.
Fifteen percent, huh?
You know how much money
that is?
l don't,
and neither do you.
But it's a hell of a lot.
Fifteen percent?
As soon as
we sold to Faranzano,
he'd knock you off.
Why would he do that?
You're Sicilian.
One day you might
wanna be boss.
lf he iced you now,
there would be a stink,
but if you're working for him
when it happens,
who's gonna come after him?
Who is gonna give
a fucking shit, except us?
And we'd be history.
He's right, Charlie.
That's why
we're in partnership
with these Jews, Frankie.
(MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Excuse me.
How are you, Charlie?
Right this way.
MAlTRE D':
Show Mr. Luciano his table.
Charlie!
Nice to see you.
Good to see you.
l heard you
told Faranzano
to go fly.
l told him
l'd think it over.
Always so polite?
Now you come to see Joe,
the boss?
lt's a very smart move,
Charlie.
Everybody needs protection.
Even me.
Where is he?
He's up on his balcony.
You ought to come aboard,
Charlie.
We're just
one big pasta-eating family
over here. All right?
l'll see you later.
All right.
Hi.
Jeez.
(MASSERlA CHUCKLES)
l don't believe my eyes.
lt's me.
Charlie!
Come on, sit down.
l send messages, send flowers,
and you don't come to see me.
l had some things
l had to straighten out
with Faranzano.
l heard.
You won't marry him.
That's beautiful.
Still, you won't
go to bed with me,
and l'm so gorgeous.
l know. l've always held
a warm spot for you, Joe.
Your nephew Joey
was a friend of mine.
(SlGHS)
lt's too bad, Charlie.
Charlie, you belong
in this family.
Someday l will join you, Joe.
You don't like today?
No. No, l don't like it.
lt's too bad, Charlie.
l've seen a lot come and go.
Guys just like you.
The ones who come,
they come to me.
The ones who go. . .
l'm the guy
who sends them off.
You want a little broccoli?
No. No, thank you.
Come on, it's full of garlic.
lt looks wonderful,
but l got to get back
downstairs.
Enjoy the show.
What do you think?
l don't trust him.
You don't trust anybody.
l doubt that you trust me.
He's stringing us along.
Yeah.
(DANCERS EXCLAlMlNG)
Hi.
You boys enjoy the show?
Park it here, baby.
How you doing?
Great. Couldn't be better.
Got a light?
A light? For you,
l'd burn down
this whole joint.
Excuse me, Joe.
l hate to interrupt,
but can l talk to my sister?
This is your sister?
Yeah.
Go ahead. Be my guest.
lt's nothing. Just relax.
Thanks.
No problem.
lt's not really
my favorite part of the job.
l could see that.
lt's a nice outfit.
Thanks.
What's your name?
Mara Motes. Somebody said
you're Charlie Luciano.
Let's just say l'm somebody
who believes in his friends.
Good.
Maybe you and l
can be friends sometime.
Yeah. Yeah.
l could pick you up
after the show if you like.
You sure you wanna do that?
Well, l mean. . .
lf you want to be
somebody's friend,
it takes time, doesn't it?
l guess it does.
l should really get back.
Okay.
Bye.
(SlGHS)
Friends.
(RlNGlNG)
Yeah?
Charlie, it's Meyer.
We got hit.
We got no shipment
New Year's Eve.
We got to see Rothstein.
Right.
Now.
We're supposed
to meet Mr. Rothstein.
Yes. Of course.
You know where to find me.
l'm Benny Siegel.
You heard of me?
No, not really.
What do you do?
l kill people.
Who hit us?
Masseria or Faranzano?
Probably Masseria.
But who knows?
Could be either one.
Wait a minute.
l'm the first guy to worry,
but doesn't everybody
get hijacked?
You think this was business
as usual?
l shouldn't have to
explain this to you !
Next week, our customers
will be buying
our scotch from them.
ln a month,
l'll lose my distillers
to Joseph fucking Kennedy,
and we'll all be
out of business!
We got to get tough.
Yeah !
Only we can't afford a war.
They got armies.
We don't.
Happy New Year, honey.
Balls and brains.
You got 'em,
you don't need an army.
A hundred years ago,
Austria was run
by a prince named Metternich.
Austria was weak,
its neighbors strong,
but Metternich was
a cold, calculating fox.
lf one country got too strong,
he organized
an alliance against it.
He would bring Europe
to the brink of war.
Then everybody thanked him
when he kept war
from happening.
He barely had an army?
But he had Europe
by the kishkes.
We gotta send a signal.
Nobody messes with our stuff.
We have a shipment landing.
Cape May, tomorrow night.
This is a perfect opportunity
to set a trap.
(YELLlNG)
Cowards!
Try this again,
l will kill your mothers,
fuck your sisters
and turn your brothers
into eunuchs.
l think
you've made your point,
Benny. Let's go.
Tony No Nose.
This is a surprise.
Give our regards
to Don Faranzano.
Who's next?
You wanna start a war?
l don't mind.
l do. Sometimes you're
so stupid l can't stand it.
Let's go.
Move it. Move it.
(lMlTATlNG GUN FlRE)
l knew it.
You had to kill him,
didn't you?
ln 24 hours,
Faranzano comes after us.
So?
So? We can't fight him.
We ain't got the guns.
Masseria does.
Masseria?
We're going with Masseria?
He ain't so bad.
He's a fat, stupid fuck!
Other than that,
l guess he's swell.
Frankie, right now,
this fat stupid fuck
can save our lives.
Remember,
it's only temporary.
A few more stupid moves
like that, they'll knock us
over like bowling pins.
lt's time to play
with the big boys.
Yeah, l used to be
skinny like you.
Hey!
Pay attention !
l'm talking for a reason here.
l used to move fast,
jump fast, dodging bullets.
Fourteen !
Fourteen with my name on it.
Yet, never a scratch
on this beautiful body.
So l realized, l can't be hit.
So, why be skinny?
Eat! That's what
we are here for.
What are you here for?
l wanna talk details.
Yeah, l hear you
got some trouble.
You hear wrong.
l hear you got to join
my family to stay alive
another 24 hours.
l don't deal from weakness.
You sit down.
(MASSERlA CHUCKLlNG)
l like you,
up to a point.
What are the details?
l'm number two,
above everybody.
lncluding Catania here.
We get a fair piece
of all the action,
and everything from me
and my associates
goes into the pot.
Everything.
Except whiskey.
The booze stays with us
and Rothstein.
So, my family
shares in everything,
except
the whiskey.
Right.
You sucking bastard !
You son of a
flea-bitten bitch !
(SHOUTlNG lN lTALlAN)
Thank God
l can't kill him now.
He made such a tough deal.
He's no phony.
You and me together,
Faranzano is a dead man.
ln six months,
you pass the whiskey to me,
or l kill you.
(COOlNG)
You're part of the family.
That's my boy.
lt's not a question
of numbers.
Anyone can rack up numbers.
lt's how you do it.
lt's a question of style.
l don't kill with style?
You don't know
how to kill at all.
Gentlemen, sit down.
Very interesting
to see
you again, Mr. Coll.
Again?
About three years ago,
you ambushed me
and Meyer here.
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
By the old way
of doing things,
l should let Benny
shoot you in the head now.
But l'm not gonna
do that.
So, you're not gonna
kill me.
So?
So, we have a problem.
Name him. He's dead !
(LAUGHS)
Our problem is you.
See, you freelance.
When you hit people
on our turf,
it upsets the cops.
No!
Plus, you're very,
very good
at what you do.
l figure,
l upset
somebody else,
you don't miss
a second time.
That's my motto.
Nothing so pretty
as the back of a man's head.
(COLL LAUGHlNG)
What, you want Mad Dog
to go back to selling argyles?
No, we want Mad Dog
to move his operations
out west.
Los Angeles, San Francisco.
We promise to keep you
very, very busy.
Out west?
l'll think about it.
l'll let you know.
Gentlemen.
(CHUCKLlNG)
Maybe we should
just kill him.
No.
He could be useful.
Let's just see
if he leaves town. Okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
(CHATTERlNG)
Glorious!
Hi !
Mara.
Yeah?
Could you come out here
for a minute?
Sure.
Hi.
Let's go upstairs.
Gambling doesn't start
till midnight. Okay?
Okay.
Come on.
l'm sorry l haven't been
in to see you. l had business.
lt doesn't matter.
lt doesn't?
No. l knew you'd be back.
You believe in fate?
l don't know.
l do.
Some people are born to be
chorus girls and dog-catchers,
and other people,
people like you,
have something
they don't even realize.
What don't l realize?
l can't tell.
Wouldn't be fair.
There's another
kind of fate.
Between two people.
l mean,
why did l meet you?
You're very gentle,
you know that?
l am?
Very.
Most guys, tell 'em
you want to be friends
and they skip town.
But you really can,
can't you?
Can what?
Be my friend.
l'd like to be.
l got to ask you a question.
Not that l'm complaining,
but if we're gonna be friends,
why did you kiss me?
lf somebody's your friend,
you can trust them, right?
With anything?
Yeah.
Do me a favor?
l would do anything for you.
Don't forget we're friends.
Once you throw sex
into the kitty,
guys forget their manners.
l won't forget mine.
Or they start getting
all goo-goo
and talking about love.
Love is a very confusing thing
which l personally
do not understand.
Neither do l.
Can we do this again?
l gotta go to work.
l don't mean right now,
l mean. . .
Sure. l can do it
as often as you can.
Probably more.
l'm sure.
l'll see you later.
Okay.
Don't fall asleep.
l won't.
How's it going?
Lansky's inside.
He is?
What are you doing?
Drinking.
Straight?
Yeah.
Beauty.
l got a serious question
for you.
Ask away.
You wanna sleep with Anna?
What?
My girl, Anna.
l'm offering her to you.
She's very beautiful, Meyer.
l happen to think this.
But she's not
my type.
She's not your type?
Why isn't she your type?
Because she's your type.
You're turning down
this offer?
That's right.
l'm marrying her next week.
Or month.
We're not gonna rush it,
but l'm gonna marry her.
Congratulations.
Maybe you'll stop
with all these
ridiculous questions.
Friendships, Charlie,
they never get tested.
You and me,
if we're gonna stay
in this business,
we gotta know
we can trust each other.
So you're. . .
You're getting married?
There's this
Yiddish expression,
"A wedding is like a funeral,
but with musicians."
The reception
should be an excellent
business opportunity.
Meyer, what if l'd
said yes about Anna?
That you wanted
to schtup her?
Yeah. What if
l'd said that?
l would've killed you.
You would've tried
to kill me.
No. l would've done it.
All right.
Let's just say
for friendship's sake that
we're both equally strong.
And we both would've died.
Okay, for friendship's sake,
l'll say this.
Even if it ain't true.
(THUNDER CLAPPlNG)
(WHOOPlNG)
(MUSlC PLAYlNG)
(ALL SlNGlNG)
Smile.
(ALL EXCLAlMlNG)
God.
l'm gonna get sick
from this goddamn wine.
Why don't we get some Corvo
or something like that?
Excuse me, Mr. Siegel.
Have you met
my daughter Rachel?
No, l haven't.
She was voted
the prettiest girl
in school.
Very pretty.
She's not a bad cook,
either.
Ooh, that's important.
They got those things
called kreplach.
That's like ravioli.
And they got this thing
called a blintz.
lt's like manicotti.
l love manicotti.
Yeah, right here.
Then they got that.
That's matzo balls.
lt's like a big hunk
of soggy bread.
God, that looks
like brains.
Yes.
No, l don't want that.
Charlie?
How's family business?
lt's up 35 percent
since l came on.
That's good.
See if you can get
someone to get me
some of that
ravioli crap.
l got some.
Prohibition. . .
Ain't gonna last forever.
Yes.
We're gonna go with booze
and smokes best we can.
l got this crazy idea.
The big plan is this.
We're gonna take
the unions.
The unions.
Garment workers.
The longshoremen.
Not just
New York unions.
Chicago.
The whole fucking country.
The West Coast.
What are you
gonna do about. . .
Don Masseria?
He's an old man.
Masseria?
What are you worried about?
l just wanna run things.
l'm not worried.
A little
more control.
You gotta
watch your back.
Masseria? What should we
do about him?
l think it's very tricky.
Yeah?
You should consider
many things with him.
You have something
in mind, l hope?
Yes, we do.
(WHlSPERlNG)
SONNY: Rothstein's behind it.
Then Rothstein must die.
Cash, money, unions.
l see what you're doing.
lf l see, Masseria sees.
Everybody dies,
Charlie.
l know.
This thing will blow up
in your face.
When?
l don't know.
You give me such naches.
Naches?
lt's like pride,
when a son makes
his father proud of him.
Look at you !
You're bigger
than me now.
When war comes,
and it'll come,
the winner will be the one
who gets his enemy
to trust him.
How do l do that?
You save his life.
Crew's taking steam tomorrow.
Boss wants you there.
Nobody's bigger
than you, A. R.
Seven-card stud.
Let me ask you something.
You ever dream about
this game?
l do. Every night.
Nightmares.
l got jacks up.
l'm looking at kings up.
l got four aces.
l'm looking at
a straight flush.
Looky here, looky here.
Looks who's high.
A thousand.
Come on, come on.
You in or out?
l'm in.
lt's my turn now.
You in or out?
Are you in?
What's the matter?
Did l make a wrong bet?
(COLL LAUGHlNG)
My number two.
Sit down and get wet.
That was
a beautiful wedding.
Always makes me
cry like a baby.
Young people madly in love.
lsn't it funny?
l mean,
isn't it funny to hear
things that
you can't believe?
Like, l've been hearing,
Charlie, you've been
talking to people
about the unions
and all that dog shit,
horse shit, pig shit!
l'm just trying to make
money, Joe, for you.
How come l ain't heard of it?
All the guys
you was talking to
thought you was
talking to them, not me!
After all,
l am your number two, right?
Holy Christ, screw 'em.
We could be bigger
than the Jews,
bigger than the lrish.
We could run
the whole fucking country.
You could be the next
John D. Rockefeller,
if you let me do it for you.
See, Joe,
it's what l told youse.
lt's terrible what happened
to Rothstein, isn't it?
Yeah, fucking terrible.
He got hit
in his own hotel room.
lt's scary.
Who. . . Who did it and why?
Who knows? Gambling debts,
mad-dog killer.
Who knows? lt's. . .
We're all shook up
around here.
You know, Charlie,
you're a swell guy.
But from now on,
you look the wrong way,
you fart
in the wrong direction. . .
Joe, you're always complaining
l don't eat.
lf l don't eat,
how am l gonna fart?
Yeah.
He's funny!
(ALL LAUGHlNG)
Yeah, he's funny.
MAN: l told youse, five G's
on Sonny Boy in the fifth,
five G's on Star in the sixth.
Off the phone.
l'm making a bet!
Beat it!
TOMMY: Charlie,
you know who hit Rothstein.
We gotta kill him.
l always said
you was the one, Charlie.
But if you're gonna
take him down,
get a price from Faranzano.
l always thought
your loyalty was to Joe.
l love Joe,
but this is business
and Faranzano's gonna win.
And if you do this,
you can write your own ticket.
How do we set the meeting?
l won't go to Brooklyn.
He won't come here.
Pick a neutral territory.
Staten lsland,
Profaci's turf?
Perfect. l'll set it up.
Okay.
l always knew
you was the one, Charlie.
lt's like Joe Profaci's
inviting me into his home.
Right.
lt's like a bar mitzvah.
Look, if you told me
something because it
was Jewish knowledge,
l'd say okay.
But now you've
gotta say okay.
This is between ltalians.
l've known Profaci 20 years.
l'm safe on his turf.
When things
are between ltalians,
one of the ltalians
ends up dead.
Relax, Tommy Reina
will be there.
Tommy's my pal.
Will you shut up?
Listen,
at least take Bugsy
and l along.
No, no. l take you guys,
it's a sign of distrust.
l want Faranzano to trust me.
FRANK: Charlie's right.
lt's true, ain't it?
You changed. You're not
listening to your friends.
Listen to you !
You let Mad Dog Coll live.
He's already killed Rothstein,
and who knows who's next!
You blame me
for A. R.'s death.
l don't blame you.
So what then?
l make one mistake.
Suddenly you
know everything.
You're getting
a swelled head.
l see it. l do!
Meyer, don't ever
point your finger at me.
Excuse me, Mr. Bigshot!
Please, Charlie,
l need you alive.
l chose you
as our leader, remember?
Remember that.
You chose me?
That ain't what l remember.
What l remember is,
you didn't have it.
l didn't have what?
l didn't have the guts?
l didn't have the brains?
Don't make me say it, okay?
Fuck you.
You got something to say?
Fuck you ! You fucking got
something to say to me?
l could've let you
die in the streets.
Come on, say it!
That's your second mistake,
you fuck.
Charlie, come on.
Meyer, come on.
(ALL YELLlNG)
All right!
Look, you're brilliant, okay?
But you ain't ltalian.
You don't understand ltalians.
Without me,
you don't last two weeks.
Yeah, because l would
screw up some Sicilian !
Yeah, but
you said it yourself.
l got it, whatever it is.
Now l'm gonna use it.
You got it! You got what?
At least l've got the brains
not to make a fatal mistake.
Anna. You care about her.
You married her.
lf you were out front,
she'd get hit.
And as tough as you
say you are,
you would never recover.
You see what l'm saying?
Without me, you are a loser.
Go on, then, Charlie.
Kill yourself.
(SPEAKlNG lTALlAN)
lt's been too long.
Profaci?
l told him
it was postponed
till tomorrow.
He talks too much anyway.
This is just you and me.
Thanks for
setting this up, Tommy.
You're a pal.
FARANZANO: Charlie,
you understand business.
l'm a business man myself.
l. R.S. came last week.
Eighteen hours,
they found nothing.
So, strictly business.
l hope you
can appreciate
some facts.
Conditions have changed.
Some people
have gotten
too powerful.
l'll take care
of Masseria.
Personally.
l want you
to do it yourself.
That's not all, though.
Lansky and Siegel.
l know you've always
gotten along,
but Jews,
they're different.
You cross 'em one time,
fight with 'em one time,
and they're gone.
l know this.
l've heard.
CHARLlE: Heard what?
They're a
different race, Jews.
You take Communion.
l take Communion.
They don't even
believe in sin,
for Christ's sake.
They're gonna
betray you,
just like they
betrayed Jesus Christ.
You join my family,
they die.
No one will even
know you approved.
Looks like
l don't have
a choice, do l?
(CHUCKLES) No.
Either l agree
to kill my friends,
or you kill me.
That's right.
l don't accept
the choices.
Charlie, Charlie!
Tough little bambino.
(LAUGHlNG)
(SPEAKlNG lN lTALlAN)
He's got balls. . .
Don't talk to me!
Rocco.
(SPEAKlNG lTALlAN)
What is this loyalty?
We're going to
kill them anyway.
All this is for nothing.
(CHARLlE GRUNTlNG)
Well?
l don't bend over.
lt's too hard
to stand straight again.
(GROANS)
Long run, short run,
you have no choice.
Salvatore. . .
Don't start.
(LAUGHlNG)
Tough guy,
isn't he, Tom?
Hi.
Hello.
How you doing?
l look beautiful, huh?
You look like shit.
lt's good to see you
with your eyes open.
Everybody's still
talking about you.
They say it's a miracle.
First time somebody got taken
for a ride and lived.
l guess l'm just lucky.
Yeah, lucky.
That's you,
Lucky Luciano.
So what about Joe?
Masseria.
He's confused.
He don't know
if you're working for
him or Faranzano.
He's gotta be pissed,
but he ain't lifted a finger.
He can't figure out
why Faranzano didn't kill you.
He needs me.
He can't get close enough
to Masseria to do it himself.
He wants me to kill him.
What's wrong with that?
Sicilian law, Benny.
Kill a don, you can't
never be a don.
We have to start a war.
Make those bastards
fight each other.
The only way to do that
is to kill somebody important.
Have 'em blame it
on each other.
Reina.
Tommy?
Faranzano will think
Masseria ordered the hit
'cause Tommy changed sides.
The Bronx is at stake.
He'll have to strike back.
You're talking about
a friend of mine, Meyer.
Anybody touches Tommy. . .
No, it's done.
lt's not done.
Benny,
Reina set me up.
When he went with Faranzano,
the don made him pay a price.
Me.
l just don't believe. . .
l mean, Tommy would never. . .
Meyer, from now on,
you and me, we gotta agree.
So if l start getting
a swelled head,
just shoot me.
lt'd be a lot less painful.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You guys gotta
get out of here.
MEYER: Take care of yourself.
FRANK: See you, Charlie.
See you later, Frankie.
When the war comes,
you're gonna be in danger.
Danger's not for girls?
Maybe you ought to
leave town for a while.
You don't understand
anything, do you?
l'm with you now.
Okay?
Okay.
You get some sleep.
Yeah.
(SlGHS)
TOMMY: Benny.
Tommy.
Come here.
How you doing?
We gotta talk, Tommy.
Where's Short Stick?
lt's his day off.
He's at the dog track.
How's Charlie?
Charlie's tough.
Faranzano had no right!
He had no fucking right!
lf l'd have known,
l'd have done something.
lt wasn't
your fault.
That's why l'm here.
l wanna show you
there's no hard feelings.
l got something.
Take it.
What's this?
This was,
l swear to God. . .
A friend of
Frankie's pinched it.
The personal property
of Benito Mussolini.
ll Duce.
Shit.
lt's a nice gun.
(GUN COCKlNG)
(GUN CLlCKlNG)
Hmm.
We've been friends
a long time, huh, Tommy?
A long time.
Yeah.
You know what Charlie
always says.
How this is America,
and everything is money.
Yeah, l think l. . .
l think l remember
hearing that somewheres.
But this ain't money, Tommy.
This is friendship.
This is too big to
pay off the goddamn judges.
lt's great that the bosses
are trying to
knock each other off,
but they can't seem
to get the job done.
Take it easy.
Then we'll have to
do it for them.
Masseria?
Yeah.
There's just
one problem.
How do we get him
to trust us again?
l know.
We save his life.
How's it going, Joe?
How many times
you gonna fuck me, Charlie?
l got eyes, l see.
l got ears, l hear.
l even got a brain.
Whatever you think,
l've already thought it,
ten times over!
So then why suspect me?
Staten lsland?
You were pissed at me,
so l thought,
l'll tell Faranzano
l'm gonna make
a deal with him.
He admits it.
How else can l set
a meeting with this guy?
How else can l get
close to him?
There's one thing
you haven't thought about.
l am going to kill Faranzano.
lf l live, he dies.
That's what l went to
Staten lsland to do.
Obviously
it didn't work out
as l planned it.
You got 48 hours to kill him.
(CHUCKLES)
Mr. Lucky Luciano!
You know, what's great is that
there's no hard feelings.
l. . . l'll take you guys
out to dinner tonight.
Where you wanna go?
Anyplace you wanna go.
l mean, it's on me.
(MACHlNE GUN FlRlNG)
(SHOUTlNG)
(GUN COCKlNG)
Frankie!
Where's the car?
Staten lsland.
You enjoyed Charlie
getting tortured, didn't you,
you fucking shit?
Yeah, but. . .
But you said all was forgiven.
lt is.
Come on, Joe.
Get away.
That's 1 5 times.
l told you, Charlie,
they will never kill me.
Never.
By the way, thanks.
Sorry what l had to do.
(LlON GROWLS)
Why do they call them
king of beasts?
They don't hunt.
They don't kill.
All they do is eat,
shit and fornicate.
Just like some
fat people l know.
(CHUCKLES)
Let's talk business.
The only way
l can kill Masseria
is if you lose the war.
Masseria has to
think he's won.
l give you a week.
One more thing.
Don't ever,
ever touch my friends.
Your lives will
be your own.
Let's go.
(EXCLAlMlNG)
We did it.
We did it!
We won !
l knew we would, Joe.
So, when do we
wipe out Faranzano?
This week? Next week?
Next year.
What's the hurry?
Right.
Let the fucker sweat.
That's right.
lt looks good.
Not bad. Wait.
Try this. Salsiccia.
Tell me something, Joe.
What do you love?
What do l love?
What kind of question is that?
Conversation while we eat.
What do you love?
l love food.
l love pussy.
You know.
Young pussy.
But
most of all,
l love to destroy people.
Anybody?
The bigger the better.
But anybody.
Makes me feel good.
There's something
l've been meaning to ask you
about your nephew, Joey.
He was a pal of mine.
Your namesake, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. He was a. . .
Good kid.
Yeah, he was.
You forgot this,
but l was there
the day he got killed.
On the street?
Yeah.
You see,
l've been wondering. . .
Why'd you kill
your own blood?
Some kind of family dispute.
l don't remember.
We're family, ain't we?
Yeah.
Family.
Mmm-hmm.
l gotta take a leak.
(CLOCK CHlMlNG)
(GUNS COCKlNG)
Joe, this ain't number 1 6.
Come on.
My friends!
Honorable men !
l welcome you today
as your Caesar.
The boss of all bosses!
(SPEAKlNG lN lTALlAN)
To give impartial leadership,
l have turned over
my interests to
other members of my family.
ln return, l will receive
a fair share of the proceeds
from all the families
across the country.
From now on, we will be
divided into five families,
and the capo from each family
will report to me.
Mr. Thomas Gagliano.
(APPLAUDlNG)
Mr. Joseph Bonanno.
Mr. Joseph Profaci.
(APPLAUDlNG)
Mr. Vincent Mangano.
And Mr. Charlie Luciano,
(APPLAUDlNG LOUDLY)
who will supervise
the entire operation
under my direction.
Now l ask you to come forward
and pay respects,
not to me,
but to the office l hold.
(SPEAKlNG lN lTALlAN)
MAN: lt's a great privilege,
Don Faranzano.
(CHATTERlNG)
Excuse us.
Ready for this?
Faranzano brought in Coll
to ice you.
What?
Know what we have to do?
Have a
good day,
Mr. Coll.
(YELLlNG)
You guys are so stupid !
The problem is,
l don't feel it.
All this blood,
l don't feel a thing.
The way l see it,
we got two problems.
Getting past his outer guards
and having him invite us
into his office.
l could pay some cop
to kill him.
Give me the money
and l'll do it.
No, no.
Brains, not brawn.
This is something
we need to do ourselves.
Pride.
That's his weakness.
Don't people say you look
more like a bookkeeper
than a gangster?
So? You look like
a second baseman !
You see,
Faranzano's the only mug
l ever heard brag
about being audited
by the l. R.S.
He came out clean,
so he figures
his shit don't stink. Right?
His shit don't stink. So?
Seeing as how he enjoyed
the experience so much,
why don't we give
it to him again?
(SlGHS)
l'm scared.
Huh?
Everything l want
is right here.
All l have to do
is take it.
Morning.
Mmm.
(MARA GlGGLlNG)
(GASPlNG)
(GRUNTS)
(GUN FlRlNG)
Jesus Christ.
Name it, Frankie.
Anything.
Whatever the department
can do.
The body goes
out covered.
So far as the press knows,
it's Charlie.
You got it.
Benny.
Those bastards!
FRANK: They'll pay.
lt's like you told me,
Charlie.
lf you loved her,
it was a mistake.
You gotta come
out of it, Charlie.
This is the moment.
This is the test.
They're the ones
who made the mistake.
Shut up and give me the don.
Don, Don, Don.
You got the dough?
Charlie's dead?
Deep frying in hell.
You want the other
three to join him?
Come on over.
l'll pay you for this.
Give you instructions.
l'll be over.
Mad Dog Coll's coming
over to get paid.
When he walks in,
put him on ice.
My pleasure.
MAN 1 : Here's my key. 31 2.
MAN 2: Yes, absolutely.
Mr. Coll, l sent
your room service.
lt must be on its way.
l don't know.
You don't know
if it's on the way up?
l'm sorry, Mr. Coll.
Give it to me again.
l want two eggs up.
l want a rasher of bacon.
l want a pot of coffee, black.
And l want it now!
Right now, or l'll. . .
Room service.
lt's about time.
Bring it in.
What's your handle?
Because l wanna talk
to your boss, that's why.
l just want your
undivided attention.
Son of a bitch !
MAN: My God. Jesus!
(HONKlNG)
l. R.S. raid. Get going.
l said get lost! Now!
(GUNS COCKlNG)
Anybody else got
any bright ideas?
Now, beat it!
Nice work, Cliff.
Okay.
Mr. Faranzano?
lt's the l. R.S. again.
Show them in.
(YELLS)
Don't even think about it.
You want it in the eyeball?
Drop it!
Heaters on the floor! Now!
Siegel, drop it!
All right, Lansky,
over there.
You too, Costello.
Over with your Yid friends.
(CHUCKLES)
This is pretty.
Kill 'em !
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How much is it worth?
Anything ! Hundred grand !
You don't like yourself much.
Two hundred !
Five. Come on, say it!
Five!
All right, five.
Truth is, l like my work.
l would've done it
for nothing.
Okay, boys.
(SCREAMlNG)
(YELLlNG)
That's number three, Meyer.
This time l want you
to thank me.
Thank you.
No, you crazy Jews!
Remember this?
Sicilian law, remember?
You kill a don. . .
All right.
Just do like l said.
Slow.
What are you doing?
Why slowly?
'Cause l tortured you?
No, no, no.
lt's what you did
1 5 years ago.
Jesus! You want revenge
after 1 5 years?
l've been busy.
Get up!
At least tell me
what l did 1 5 years ago.
No!
CHARLlE: Want me to tell you?
Wanna know what you did?
Tell me, what'd l do
1 5 years ago?
You destroyed my father!
Your father?
l don't even remember
your father!
Exactly.
Charlie.
No, no, please!
No!
(SCREAMlNG)
(EXCLAlMS)
Lucky.
Sit.
l want to thank Mr. Capone
for hosting this meeting.
Sit down and shut up,
will you?
There ain't gonna be a boss.
You all know how l got this.
Maybe Joe Profaci here. . .
Wait a minute.
What are you saying?
Don't worry.
Maybe you knew it was
gonna happen to me,
maybe you didn't.
But by the old way
of doing things,
if l become boss now,
l have to hit you
in case you knew.
And all of you shrug, right?
Except some of you
are friends of Joe's.
And one day
l might do something
that upsets you,
then you'll hit me.
Then you become boss.
My friends, they hate you.
Somebody else becomes boss,
and on, and on, and on.
Know what l call that?
Stupid. Very stupid.
So, if you ain't doing it,
who's gonna be. . .
Nobody.
We're all bosses here.
What then, Charlie?
We're gonna vote
on everything?
That's right.
Everybody here is equal.
Corporations have
a board of directors.
So will we.
A commission.
Now, l have friends.
They're not from Palermo,
not from Sicily. . .
They're not even ltalians.
They're Jewish.
And l trust 'em.
Anybody have a problem
with that?
You say there's gonna be
no boss, but you're starting
to talk like one.
l've learned.
Every organization
needs somebody
standing out front.
Call it a figurehead,
a leader, whatever.
lt doesn't much matter
to me who does it.
l say we make Charlie Luciano
head of our
national commission.
Who agrees?
You want it, Al?
lt's yours.
Hell, no.
l want you to do it.
lt's just Julius Caesar
never took no vote.
That's why Caesar ended up
dead in the street.
Any other business?
(LAUGHlNG)
Friendship.
(COLL LAUGHlNG)
Shop this shows fashion, download the
"LookLive" app in iTunes