Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
As I leave....
MICKEY: What kind of pies do you have?
We got apple...
...pecan, cherry, key lime.
MICKEY: Which do you recommend?
The key lime's great, but...
...it's an acquired taste.
MICKEY: I ain't had key lime pie in 10 years.
When you had it, did you like it?
MICKEY: No, but I was a completely...
different person back then.
Let's give that key lime pie a day in court...
...and a big glass of nonfat milk,
if you please.
Should I make that two pieces?
MALLORY: No, no, Rosie.
My name's not Rosie, it's Mabel.
Whatever.
EARL: Goddamn, this son of a bitch...
is running hot.
Go on in. I'll check it out.
SONNY: All right.
I’ll get a cold one for you.
[ROCK MUSIC OVER JUKEBOX]
What the hell is that?
That is a bitch out of hell, son.
Take a run at her, kiddo.
Miller, Mabel.
- Coming up.
That's one sweet piece of meat.
MICKEY: Her name's...
...Mallory.
Mallory. Whatever.
Who gives a shit?
I call it pussy.
[LAUGHS]
Don't stop, darling.
I'm just getting started.
OTIS: I think she's sweet on you.
Are you flirting with me?
Beep, beep.
[MALLORY LAUGHS]
You want a piece of the guy?
Do you?
Your move. Your move, fucker. Go.
This stinking....
You son of a bi--
It's not polite to point.
[WHIMPERS]
Because she's mopping the floor
with your buddy...
...is no reason for you to join in.
[GUNSHOT]...
[GLASS BREAKS]
How sexy am I now? Huh?
MALLORY: Flirty boy. How sexy am I now?
[OPERA MUSIC]...
[SCREAMS]...
[SNAPS NECK]...
[SINGING LT'S 'SHITLIST']
Honey. Come on, he's dead.
No.
There is no escaping here.
MICKEY: Who's the lucky one?
Eenie-meenie-minie-moe
Catch a redneck by his toe
If he hollers let him go
Eenie-meenie-minie-moe
My mama told me
To pick the best one
And you are...
...it.
MALLORY: When they ask, you tell them
Mickey and Mallory Knox did it.
Say it.
Mickey and Mallory Knox.
I love you, Mickey.
I love you, Mallory.
[BALLROOM MUSIC]...
[MICKEY AND MALLORY WHOOP]
NARRATOR: Stars are coming out.
Look up in the brassy sky and there...
they are, like loony pocket change.
You bet on something you wish
you had $10,000 to bet on.
Something where the odds are good.
Betting all those stars don't mean shit....
MICKEY: Whoo-hoo.
[MALLORY GIGGLES]...
[MICKEY URINATES]
Whole world’s coming to an end, Mal.
That's the angels, Mickey.
They're coming down for us from heaven.
And I see you riding a big red horse.
And you're driving the horses,
whipping them...
...and they're spitting and frothing
at the mouth.
They're coming right at us.
And I see the future.
There's no death.
Because you and I, we're angels.
MICKEY: That is poetry.
I love you, Mal.
I know you do, baby.
MALLORY:
I've loved you since the day we met.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]
MALLORY: Hi, Dad, how was work?
What work? I'm unemployed.
ED: Where the **** have you been?
You look nice, Mallory.
Yuck. You look like....
[BELCHES]
Thanks, Mom.
I'm going now. I'll be back
at midnight, okay?
Are you wearing
a broomstick and a trash bag?
Why don't you put some meat on you?
Any lighter, you'll be Miss Ethiopia.
ED: Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to the John Lee Hooker concert...
with Donna. I told you yesterday.
First off, you don't tell me.
You ask my permission.
Second, you're not going out in that dress.
You'll end up peddling your ass,
you stupid bitch.
You're not going out at all.
You didn't mow the yard.
That piece-of-shit lawn mower is fucked.
That's the way you talk in front of
your mother? You stupid bitch.
You watch your language.
Or I'll kick the shit out of you,
like I do her.
If your ass is in this house...
...it's my ass.
So move it upstairs and take a shower.
Make sure it's a good shower.
Because I'm coming up after
to see how clean you are.
Mommy.
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]
Weren't you a little hard on her, Ed?
I'll show her a little tenderness after I eat.
When I get up there,
she won't see my face for an hour.
I think you should speak nicely
in front of Kevin.
Don't think. You're a ******* idiot.
What am I, a bad guy?
Did I ever ask you to **** my friends?
And don't tell me what to do.
If it wasn't for me, you'd still be...
slinging hash and fucking your boss.
[DOORBELL]
- That must be Donna.
I'll tell her the bad news.
Don't let your macaroni get cold, Ed.
[DOORBELL RINGS]...
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]...
Yes?
- Delivery for Ed Wilson.
What on earth is it?
It's beef, lady. Fifty pounds of beef.
Wait right here. I have to have
a word with my husband.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Who are you?
Mickey. Who are you?
I'm Mallory.
MICKEY: You ought to change your name...
to Beautiful.
AUDIENCE: Aww.
You a big...
...meat-eater, Mallory?
I could be.
You always dress like that?
Or you just...
...waiting for me?
Why would I dress like this
for somebody I don't know?
Maybe something inside you told you to.
You know?
Like fate.
Do you believe in fate, Mallory?
Maybe.
You don't look happy.
Wanna go for a ride? Talk about it?
MOM: Ed, you promised your doctor...
no more meat.
I eat what I want. So what?
This fucking food here,
you pray after you eat it.
I don't want you to clog up your
arteries and keel over at the table.
Don't ******* cry, it turns me off.
I haven't cried in 15 years,
and you still haven't touched me.
How about him?
You were drunk, and you thought
you were in Mallory's room.
That's why we have Kevin.
You mean Mallory's my mom?
I'm sending the meat back.
I don't care what you do to me.
You know what I'll do to you.
- Ed, look.
What's it say?
'Out with the meat man.
Back before dawn. Love, Mallory.'
That stupid bitch.
Is that your car?
My car?
That meat man cocksucker.
I broke her in, and he grabbed her.
I'll fix his ass. Call the cops.
[SIRENS]...
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDS]
MICKEY: Everything I see, I see you, Mal.
I know, baby. I'm going crazy too.
Even ugliness looks beautiful
because of you.
Even though I'm in here,
I visit you every night.
Listen, Mickey.
My daddy, he's gonna move us away...
...so that you can't never find me,
and I'm scared.
He can't keep me away from you.
He said if you ever show up...
...he's gonna kill you.
Kill me?
When's this supposed to happen?
Can I help you?
He won't leave me alone.
He keeps fucking touching me...
...and I can't take it.
I have to go.
If he finds out I'm gone,
he's gonna beat me.
I just wanted to tell you
I love you and I miss you.
Don't forget about me.
You won't forget me?
- I won't forget about you.
It's cool.
No matter where he takes you...
...Timbuktu, it don't matter,
because we're fate.
Nobody can stop fate. Nobody can.
One of these nights soon...
...I'll be coming for you.
I gotta go.
I love you.
[HORSE WHINNIES]
Tornado.
WORK BOSS: Move. Move. Move.
You guys get on the goddamn bus. Now.
MICKEY: Haw. Haw.
Stop or I'll shoot.
[HORSE WHINNIES]
MICKEY: Yee-haw.
[CAR ENGINE RUMBLES]
ED: Break his arm.
There's no action.
Am I watching two fags?
Kill him. Kill the fucking Indian.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going out.
You ain't going nowhere.
Hey, Jack. Mickey's back.
Just the prick I wanna see.
ED: All right, fuckface.
I'll take your eye out and show it to you.
[SCREAMS]
MICKEY:
You been fucking the wrong woman.
'You stupid bitch.
You stupid, fucking bitch.
You will shut up.
You will eat your food.
You will listen to me.
Are you clean?
Are you soapy and wet?
You stupid bitch.'
He's dead. He's dead.
Now, where's the old bag?
He's dead.
Hi, Mom.
[LAUGHS]
You never did nothing.
[WHIMPERS]
Wait.
You're free, Kevin.
MALLORY: Wherever we go...
...or whatever happens, Mickey...
...when I look up at the stars...
...I'll know you're looking up
at the same ones.
Same ones, baby.
You make every day feel like kindergarten.
MICKEY: All right.
Let's get a whole bunch of stuff,
because I need a whole new wardrobe...
...because I'm a new woman now.
I'm a new woman.
MICKEY: She's a new woman.
MICKEY: Past is behind us now.
It's time to grow up.
We have the road to hell in front of us.
Mal?
- Yes?
Will you marry me?
Of course I'll marry you.
MALLORY: I've been waiting for you...
to say that for so long.
Where we gonna get married?
Right here, Mal.
This is our church.
I got a perfect thing.
Give me your hand.
That's not what I had in mind.
Fuck you.
Ow.
Put them together.
MALLORY: It's very romantic, baby.
We'll be living in all the oceans now.
MICKEY: God, before you and this river...
and this mountain...
...and everything we don't know about...
...Mickey, do you take Mallory to be...
...your lawful wedded wife, to have and...
hold and treat right until you die?
I do.
MALLORY: Oh, baby.
Do you take Mickey to be your--...
[MEN SHOUT]
Won't murder anybody
on our wedding day.
MALLORY: Fuck you.
God.
I do.
For all eternity...
...until you and I die...
...and die and die again.
Till death do us part.
Baby, by the power vested in me...
...as God of my world...
...I pronounce us husband and wife.
WAYNE ON TV: After that, there was...
no stopping Mickey and Mallory.
They tore up the countryside with
a vengeance right out of the Bible.
WAYNE:
Tonight I'm standing on Highway 666...
...running through towns like Cortez...
...Shiprock, Sheep Springs
and ending in Gallup, New Mexico.
To some, a beautiful stretch
of the American landscape...
...but to Mickey and Mallory Knox,
who are still at large...
...it is literally a candy lane
of murder and mayhem.
Patrolman Gerald Nash...
...was the first of 12 peace officers...
that Mickey and Mallory murdered...
Gerald and his partner,
Dale Wrigley...
...were parked at this doughnut shop.
Alfie's Donuts, when....
This 1970 Dodge Challenger pulled up...
across the street.
DALE: Gerald, only three weeks out...
of the academy...
...walked out with a coffee...
...and my bear claw.
Driver asked him a question.
Where's Farmington?
DALE: Looked like he was giving
street directions.
Take it over to 66...
...and Farmington's up, 65 miles.
Quick ride.
You going there?
DALE: When he finished
and waved him thanks...
...then up come that shotgun.
You cop-killing cocksuckers.
MALLORY: Whoo-hoo.
[GUNSHOTS]...
[SIREN]
WAYNE: In the ensuing chase...
...a tragic murder occurred.
American bronze medalist
marathon bicyclist....
MALLORY: I always wanted to shoot...
at one. They're not so easy to hit.
We raped and pillaged
the first show to do this.
We changed the order so it's less obvious.
It needs a new intro. You can't
cannibalize yourself all the time.
WAYNE: Repetition works.
You'll wind up with shit.
- Repetition works.
You think that those nitwits...
in zombie-land remember anything?
It's junk food for the brains.
Filler. Fodder. Whatever.
Just build to the interview.
Keep saying that word,
'Live interview with Wayne Gale.'
Anticipation.
That's what it's all about.
Mickey and Mallory?
- Hot.
They're hot.
- Totally hot.
I love Mickey and Mallory.
They're so cool. They're so great.
[CHEERING]
They're the best thing to happen
to mass murder since Manson.
But way cooler.
MAN: Take great figures from the States:
Elvis. Jack Kerouac.
James Dean.
They are super cool.
[IN FRENCH]
MAN: Jim Morrison, Jack Nicholson...
...add a bloody pail of nitrate
and you got Mickey and Mallory.
KID: I don't believe in mass murder...
...or that shit.
Don't get us wrong.
We respect human life and all.
But if I was a mass murderer,
I'd be Mickey and Mallory.
[PATSY CLINE SINGS]
MALLORY:
I haven't seen a cop for 10 minutes.
Is there such thing as a copless town?
That'd be paradise, wouldn't it?
Shangri-la.
Want a hostage?
No.
What about her?
From here?
Too heavy? Too fat?
What's the matter?
Do you think I'm still sexy?
We might have to find us
a motel here soon.
When I see one that looks nice...
...I'll put my honey-bunny bride
down on the bed.
Tie her up.
MALLORY:
Wanna go out and get something to eat?
No.
We'll stay in.
We got plenty of action here.
Know what I've been thinking about?
Course I know.
You're thinking about rolling around...
in that sunflower patch...
...outside of Tulsa.
MALLORY: How'd you know?
And you been thinking about
cutting your hair short.
And you been thinking about us
settling down on a boat...
...in a big lake,
with a dog and a jukebox...
...and a 26' Sony Trinitron.
I love it when you can read my mind.
I bet I know what you been thinking about.
I been thinking about why...
they making all these stupid movies.
Anybody out there in Hollywood
believe in kissing anymore?
Love you, baby.
I love your knee.
Love your thigh.
Love your stomach.
Love your finger.
Where is it?
Goddamn it, Mickey.
I just took it off so I wouldn't
snag my hair when I washed it.
Okay, baby, look.
Even if that ring pulls out every hair...
on your head, it stays on.
If it tears out my eyeballs,
it never comes off.
Every great thing we do starts with these.
MALLORY: All right.
Since you put it that way.
Why are you looking at her?
I'm going for a ride.
Baby, hold on. I thought maybe...
we could just throw her into the mix.
MALLORY: Shut up. Shut up.
Quit being so fucking cute.
You can be cute by yourself.
Little Mickey,
you're so fucking pretty.
You go fuck her.
MICKEY: Maybe I just will.
[SCREAMS]...
[GUNSHOTS]
MALLORY: Fill her up.
MALLORY: Can I look at that car?
ATTENDANT: Go ahead.
ATTENDANT: That'll be 17 bucks, lady.
MALLORY: That's a nice Vette.
Wait a second.
Don't I know you?
I don't think so.
Do you want to touch me?
Yeah.
Tell me you want me.
I want you.
Tell me I'm beautiful.
You are beautiful.
Am I beautiful?
So beautiful, I can't stand it.
Am I sexy?
Yes.
You're sexy.
Go down.
Holy shit.
You're Mallory Knox, ain't you?
It's the worst fucking head
I ever got in my life.
Next time don't be so fucking eager.
JACK: It's called Scagnetti
on Scagnetti, in your bookstore.
Go buy it.
- I will.
SHERIFF: An author too, huh?
My wife could never wear these.
Now that is a perfect ass.
It's nice.
JACK: There's her arm.
Her head.
Dry saliva drops.
See?
[MALLORY MOANS]
That's my type of girl. I like her.
Let's see what we got here, scooter.
Give it up.
Mallory Knox...
...meet Jack Scagnetti.
Exactly where do you expect us
to be going?
Where are we supposed to be?
What town is it that's out here?
MALLORY: Fuck, it's the fucking cheese.
MALLORY: Quit looking
in the rear-view. Sit back.
Put the lighter on the floor.
Put it on the floor, Mickey.
MICKEY: Bury the bag.
Mal?
- What?
MICKEY: Would you relax?
Turn left. I think there's a town.
All I see is desert.
MICKEY: That's right, Cochise...
...go eat some more fried bread.
Give me some 'shrooms, Mal.
Mine ain't kicking in yet.
[CAR SPUTTERS]
MICKEY: Turn left?
Turn left to what, you stupid bitch?
MALLORY: 'You stupid bitch.'
'You stupid bitch'?
'You stupid bitch'.
Mickey, that's what
my father used to call me.
Thought you'd be more creative than that.
You're losing it, Mickey.
You're losing it.
Snakes and birds.
Ain't nothing out here.
I'd go down on a lawman
for a gallon of gas.
Let me tell you something.
This is the 1990s.
In this day and age,
a man has to have choices.
A man has to have variety.
MALLORY: What do you mean, 'variety'?
Hostages? You want to fuck
some other women now?
Is that what you mean?
Why'd you pick me up?
Why take me out of my house...
...and kill my parents with me?
Ain't you committed to me?
Where are we fucking going?
Relax. It's me, your lover...
...not some demon,
not your father.
MALLORY: No, you're not
my fucking lover. You're not my--
You've been fucking loving me?
You been loving me real true.
[SHEEP BLEAT]
Listen, we got tobacco,
lots of tobacco.
You got any gas we can buy?
MALLORY: I don't think he speaks English.
Push comes to shove,
we can snatch...
that donkey and ride out of here.
Come in.
Come on in.
[SNAKE RATTLES]
MICKEY: Oh.
MALLORY: Oh, my God.
Friendly snake?
It's a rattlesnake.
My name is Mallory.
This is Mickey.
How...
...you doing?
[IN NAVAJO]
We're not from here.
[IN NAVAJO]...
[IN NAVAJO]
This is like The Twilight Zone.
Is that your wife?
Oh.
[IN NAVAJO]
MALLORY: He died?
He was your baby?
[FIRE CRACKLES]
Feel the demons here?
I think we're the demons.
[RATTLES]...
[GRANDPA CHANTS]
MICKEY'S DAD: Who are you fucking?
Your father.
- Bitch.
[MICKEY GROANS]
I said shut up.
Come here, pecker-head.
MICKEY: No, don't hit me.
[GRANDPA LAUGHS]
I hate you, you little asshole.
[MICKEY SCREAMS]...
[GUNSHOTS]
This is so bad. What did you do?
I didn't mean it. I didn't mean it.
MICKEY: Oh, my God.
Bad, bad, bad.
Come on, Mal.
- Bad, bad.
Okay, okay.
Get it together now.
It's okay.
We're out of here.
Come on.
[YELLS]
MICKEY: Come on, Mal.
Let's go.
Come on.
Why? Why?
What did you do that for?
It was an accident.
This whole thing is crazy.
There are no accidents, Mickey.
I'm human, and I made a mistake.
You gotta--
You are sick.
You killed life. He fed us.
He took us in there.
That's a harsh indictment.
[SNAKE RATTLES]...
Hold it. Hold.
- Leave me alone. I'm going.
No, hang on.
[SCREAMS]
I got bit. I got bit.
Hold on, Mal.
[GUNSHOTS]...
Hold on there, Mal.
- I think there's more.
Hang on.
- Mickey, there's more.
MALLORY: Oh, shit.
MICKEY: They're out there.
MALLORY: There's more.
MICKEY: What have we done? Hop on.
Ah.
You know something?
Badasses don't die.
MALLORY: I'm seeing things.
Make it stop.
It's okay.
Just dreaming.
It's just a dream, Mal.
My name's Pinky.
JACK: I remember now.
PINKY: My brother gave me this name...
when I was about 6.
He said, 'You're as big as my pinky.'
I don't like cheap motels.
They give me the creeps.
JACK: Yeah, me too.
You a real cop?
Yeah, I'm a real cop.
PINKY: You won't hurt me?
JACK: I've never hurt anybody
in my whole life. I'm the law.
I'm your protector.
Come on over here.
Come here.
Take off them shoes.
You're pretty.
Step up on the bed.
Real slow.
That's nice. Move around.
Move around for me.
Yeah, like that.
Come on down here.
Real slow.
Give me a kiss.
Give Big Jack a kiss.
JACK: Like me?
- Yeah.
I like you. Come on, Pinky.
Ever been strangled?
JACK: Hey, come on.
Give me a kiss.
JACK: You're pretty.
[PINKY WHIMPERS]
I said come on.
JACK: This is a sick joke.
I'm just kidding, all right?
Ahh.
Bitch.
Mickey.
I'm coming to get you.
I'm not gonna make it.
I feel so cold.
You're gonna make it. Get mad.
Go get the stuff then.
All right.
WAYNE: They were average, living
drab, nothing-ever-happens lives.
But then these sweethearts began
a cross-country murder spree...
...which has lasted
only three terrifying weeks...
...but has left 48 known bodies in its wake...
...including...
...Mallory's own mum and dad.
Oh, shit.
MICKEY: Excuse me.
Aloha?
Chief?
Rattlesnake took a chunk
out of us a ways back.
Me and my wife are pretty sick.
Could be dying, you never can tell
about these things.
How's about you ungluing your fat ass...
from that boob tube...
...and getting us some snake juice...
...pronto.
WAYNE:
- -depraved and sick actions.
Found it yet?
They stormed in with shotguns...
...and after liberating the place of
all the firearms they could carry...
...and various personal
idiosyncratic knickknacks...
...they killed every customer...
...without hesitation.
MICKEY ON TV: Money. Faster.
WAYNE: But they always leave
one clerk alive...
...to tell the tale of Mickey...
...and Mallory.
I'll be damned.
Mal.
You piece of shit.
MICKEY: Mal. Cops.
I'll meet you out front with the car.
Get the car. I'll get the juice.
CLERK: No, please.
That's sweet.
Snake juice?
- The back.
We don't carry it. Hospital.
This shit keep you hard?
I'm the only clerk left.
You're forgetting something.
- What's that?
If I don't kill you...
...what is there to talk about?
Fucking squealer.
MALLORY: I forgive you, baby.
MICKEY: Fuck you.
Fuck you.
JACK: You stupid bitch.
JACK: Shut the fuck up.
MALLORY: Kill them all.
You bonehead sissy,
this is Jack Scagnetti.
JACK: Put that gun down.
Fuck you, Scagnetti.
I'll cut her tits off.
Go ahead, Scagnetti.
I'll get her silicone implants.
I swear to God, I'll cut her tits off.
Go ahead. You ain't got the balls.
Don't give up. He won't do it.
- Shut up.
JACK: Watch this.
You like that?
Okay.
JACK: Put that gun down.
- Don't cut her.
Put your hands where I can see them...
and step in the light.
Kill them all.
All right, I'm coming out.
JACK:
Hands where I can see them. Good boy.
Step out in the light. Come on.
Step outside, big shot.
All right.
Someone come get this bitch.
Get this bitch.
Come get the big bad wolf.
JACK: Come on.
JACK: You're in my light, motherfuckers.
Hold your fire.
Oh, God, my eye.
JACK: Hold your fire.
No. Do not kill him.
MICKEY: One camera all you can muster?
MICKEY: You ain't that big
a star yet, cocksucker.
You and me, one on one, let's go.
JACK: Fuck you. Bring it.
JACK: Fry this cop killer.
[GROANS]
JACK: How's that, big shot?
JACK: Cop killer.
MICKEY: Fuck you.
Hey, Mickey. Want a drink?
- Just joking.
Where is my baby? Where is she?
Let her go. Let her go.
You okay, baby?
[MALLORY SINGS 'THESE BOOTS
WERE MADE FOR WALKING']
FEMALE DEPUTY: No pictures. No pictures.
Always wanted to meet you, Scagnetti.
I really respect you.
You know what?
I even bought your book.
I read the whole damn thing.
How about an autograph?
WURLITZER: Warden...
...Jack Scagnetti.
DWIGHT:
Dwight McClusky.
Welcome to hell.
JACK: Great to meet you, warden.
How are my two favorite assholes?
We got them two in there.
Wanna see them?
JACK: Why not?
DWIGHT: Come on.
I seen you on TV. I even read...
your goddamn book.
I'm impressed.
Surprised Hollywood ain't found you.
Your story would be
a better movie than Serpico.
In all of my days in the penal business--
And that ain't no small amount, right?
Mickey and Mallory are
the most twisted, depraved fucks...
...I have ever laid my damn eyes on.
These two motherfuckers
are a walking reminder...
...of how fucked up the system is.
Don't get me started,
okay, warden?
Dwight.
You call me Dwight.
They killed inmates and guards?
Three inmates, five guards...
and one shrink. Open that damn gate.
Psychiatrist?
Mallory strangled him when he made the...
mistake of asking about her parents.
She done it shot up on tranquilizers.
Ain't love grand?
Ain't that the truth?
It's like that other big lie:
'Love makes the world go around.'
How did you get to be
a specialist in psychos?
I'd recommend having
your mother killed by one.
After that, I developed a keen interest.
What happened?
- I was born in Texas.
You don't have an accent.
I don't want to talk like those asses.
My mother was from Texas.
- I mean the other asses.
The ones who beat me up.
Anyway, when I was 8 years old...
...my mother took me to the park.
It was the same day Charles Whitman...
...climbed the University of Texas Tower...
and started shooting.
You was with her?
- Sure was.
I didn't hear any of the shots.
I'm with my mother and suddenly...
...chest explodes. She falls,
and I'm just looking at her.
Her arm flies off, her hip explodes.
And I'm not hearing any of the shots.
Boom. Her chest exploded.
I was lying on the grass being
eaten alive by ants, thinking:
'What happened to my mom?'
Since then, I've had a strong opinion...
...about the psychopathic fringe that...
thrives in this fast-food culture.
I don't show the self-discipline
becoming of a peace officer.
You got it right, Jack.
You don't mind if I call you Jack?
DWIGHT: We got an army of shrinks.
Talks about mania...
...and schizophrenia and multi-phrenia...
and obsessions.
And it makes me sick.
It's arrogance, bullshit. Mickey and
Mallory are not the sickest I've seen.
Open it.
- Yes, sir.
JACK: Why me? What's this really about?
DWIGHT: Can you feel it?
Silence in the air?
You don't want it in a prison.
Silence.
You boys okay?
What the fuck is you looking at?
I said what the fuck you looking at?
DWIGHT: Drop it.
Try this on, big boy.
You son of a bitch.
Come on up here.
Get your ass over here.
Come on, goddamn it.
By God. Stick his ass in the block
then bring him to see me.
You all right?
Jesus Christ, you could be on
American Gladiators.
30 minutes a day.
It doesn't take much.
Someone goes for you,
go for their throat.
DWIGHT: One chop paralyzes them.
Mickey and Mallory got
my whole prison worked up.
WURLITZER: Like sharks to chum.
Smell of blood drives them nuts.
- 80% are violent offenders.
We're over 200% capacity.
This ain't a prison,
it's a time bomb.
Fry the pricks.
- We tried.
But they kill somebody new, and we...
gotta start the process over again.
JACK: Like a hemorrhoid
you can't get rid of.
We're sending them for testing to Nystrom.
JACK: Lobotomy Bay.
DWIGHT: Vegetable Land.
Home of the criminally insane.
That hasn't been done.
- The ruling won't stick...
...with the shrinks here, but they'll
be in your control for a few hours.
Then what?
You're a celebrated lawman, public
loves you. 15 years on the force.
Bestseller out in paperback.
A modern-day Pat Garret
with a deadly ax to grind.
That is why you have been chosen
to deliver Mr. and Mrs. Knox.
We know once you're on the road,
if anything happens--...
An accident.
- Fire.
Escape attempt.
- Anything at all.
Jack Scagnetti will look out
for his public's best interest.
I get the picture.
Nobody in their right mind will cry
if these fuckers take a little lead.
A lot of lead, Jack.
Write the script, call it:
The Extermination of Mickey
and Mallory Knox. I don't care.
You'll have my two best men:
Kavanaugh and Wurlitzer.
We got a special disliking
for these punkolas.
Have we found our man?
DWIGHT: You know her...
...you love her, you cannot
fucking live without her:
Mallory Knox.
[MALLORY SINGS 'BORN BAD']
DWIGHT: Hey, Knox,
somebody out here...
wants to meet you.
Jesus Christ.
She always does this.
JACK: She ain't changed a bit, huh?
Where's the other half?
In the deepest, darkest cell in the dungeon.
You can't see him now.
He's got a special visitor.
Who's that?
- Wayne Gale.
Wayne Gale? The TV scumbag?
We call them media.
Don't you like the media?
A worm in my blood is more attractive...
to me. He fucks cops over.
Can't say no to the media.
You want this job?
You come say hello.
WAYNE: I have a television show.
Every few weeks, as part of
our thing on current America...
...we do a profile on a different serial killer.
Mass murderer.
Whatever you want.
The episode on Mickey and Mallory...
was one of the most popular.
Ever do one on John Wayne Gacy?
- Yeah.
MICKEY: Who got the higher rating?
You blew him away.
What about that crazy fucker,
Ted Bundy?
That crazy guy? You got the larger
Nielsen share. You're big.
WAYNE: What I want to get--
- What about Manson?
Manson beat you.
It's hard to beat the king.
Anyway, Julie, my producer, and I...
...have been waiting to do a follow-up...
piece on you, and that time has come.
I feel it's apparent to anyone
who's hip to what's going on...
...that the prison boys
have violated the Constitution.
You and Mallory may be killers,
but nuts? Insane?
WAYNE: Today they wipe
clean your mind...
because they feel you're dangerous.
They might clean my mind
or dump me into syndication...
...because what I say is dangerous.
Where does it end?
WAYNE: I have interviewed the prison...
board and psychiatrist, Reingold...
...and with Warden Dwight McClusky,
and I tell you, they look bad.
If you give an exclusive...
...to Wayne Gale,
we are talking a media event here.
Promos on the Super Bowl.
The network will cream for it.
What a great idea, Julie.
We are talking about nothing like it...
...in television history.
The first in-depth interview...
...with the most charismatic
serial killer ever...
...one day before he's shipped away...
to a mental hospital...
...for the rest of his life.
This is Wallace and Noriega.
This is Elton John...
...confessing his bisexuality
to Rolling Stone.
This is Maysles brothers at Altamont.
This is the Nixon/Frost interviews.
What do you say?
Why are you letting him do this?
- Relax.
If I don't, we'll be excoriated.
If I do, they won't clear it for weeks.
Legal, appeals.
M & M will be toast before that
ever happens, right?
Nobody's gonna give a flying fuck
about two dead losers.
WAYNE: What are you saying?
DEPUTY: Time, motherfucker.
Leave him alone.
He's a human being.
WAYNE: Wait a minute. Let him answer me.
Time's running out, mate.
What's the answer?
I say go for it.
[LAUGHS]
WAYNE: Well, in any case, he says yes.
DWIGHT: Thought he
would. Keep contact...
with the population to a minimum.
WAYNE: Give me a room, I'll take it...
from there. We're stealth journalists.
You should worry more about the promos...
that start to air next week.
You'll be a national face,
a real hero to the American public.
It's true. You could even launch
a new career here.
DWIGHT: No.
WAYNE: Julie will fax you
in the morning with the details.
I must get back. I'm doing a benefit...
for the homeless transsexual veterans.
MICKEY: Dearest Mallory...
...you once told me I had no feelings.
You were right and wrong.
I got more feelings now
than I ever had before.
I've been reading a lot
and doing yoga with this guy...
...but he pissed me off.
He's not around anymore.
At night...
...I pretend you're lying next to me.
I lie in my cell...
...imagine kissing you...
...not making love...
...just kissing for hours and hours on end.
I remember everything about our time.
I remember every secret you ever shared.
I remember every single time you laughed.
And your dancing.
My God, your dancing.
I lie on my bed and go over every day,
every minute of our happiness.
I take it all as it comes...
...and I live that day again.
That way, when I get to our first kiss...
...they're not just memories.
I feel that joy again.
WAYNE: Dr. Reingold...
...are they insane?
Insane?
No.
Psychotic, yes.
It's right after the Super Bowl.
We got them in their homes,
the game sucked...
...they want to see Mickey.
EMIL: Mickey and Mallory have shocked...
a country numb with violence.
These guys wanna tear
their wives' heads off.
But, Sullivan--
EMIL: Mickey and Mallory...
...know the difference
between right and wrong.
They just don't give a damn.
WAYNE: This will be the most talked...
about event in television history.
WAYNE: Is it true they were sexually...
abused as children?
I can't imagine.
I don't think that it's....
I would say no.
When you said to marry your daughter...
after I got her pregnant...
...that's exactly what I did.
Now you listen to me.
WAYNE: If you blow this...
...CBS will eat your lunch next season,
and I'll be with them...
WAYNE:...because I'm out of here.
I'm out.
Mallory Knox has said that
she does want to kill you.
I never really believe
what women say to me.
Margaret, darling...
...whatever you think you found,
it's not what you think.
MAGGIE: Tell me who the hell Ming is.
Ming? There's no Ming.
That's a fucking restaurant.
Why are you going through my drawers?
I don't go through yours.
WAYNE: It looks like it was cut with...
a meat cleaver.
Where's my close-ups?
Listen, less of the shrink.
Keep the teens, keep the long hairs.
I love the cop.
I love McClusky. Cut in on
the middle of that horrific laugh.
Freeze-frame on it.
Then cut to me at the trial.
WAYNE: Their subsequent trial...
...turned into a sick,
pathetic circus.
The nation caught Mickey...
...and Mallory fire.
Mike ******* Griffin is who these
misguided ***holes should revere.
Mike Griffin was killed in the line of...
duty by these scum-sucking...
...degenerate ******bags.
What do you think of the turnout?
- I've never had more fun.
Scumbag.
Ming, first of all, slow down.
Speak English.
MING: -All right, English.
- You're paranoid.
She knows.
- She's not onto us.
I don't give a fuck what the I Ching says.
Just don't put anything down
on paper, ever.
WAYNE: If she calls back...
...you say, 'Hello,
Ming Dynasty Restaurant.'
What do you have to say to your fans?
You ain't seen nothing yet.
JACK: How'd you let this show go live?
DWIGHT: Just got out of hand.
Doesn't change a thing, though.
I'm moving those scumbags tomorrow.
When I do these douche bags, I'll go...
right up there with Jack Ruby.
JACK: World famous, huh?
Hall of Fame.
You'll be bigger, Jack.
Lee Harvey Oswald was a pussy.
Maybe, but he was a great shot.
- Hear it?
[SILENCE]...
Hear what?
DWIGHT: It's dead quiet.
It's dangerous when it's dead quiet.
[CROWD CHEERS]
Okay, testing, one, two, three.
How goes it, brother?
Doing some hard time?
What'd they get you for?
Murder.
- That's a rough one. I'm with you.
Showtime.
TV ANNOUNCER 1: And
the Dallas Cowboys...
are the Super Bowl Champions....
TV ANNOUNCER 2:
After the game, stay tuned...
...for a special American Maniacs
on WATCH.
Mickey Knox is the most
dangerous man in America.
But Wayne Gale isn't afraid
to meet him one on one...
...to learn what 48 people died for.
Is he insane, or does he belong where...
he sent so many others: in the grave?
Mickey Knox, thank you for this time.
I'd like to start with a few questions,
if you don't mind?
That's ******* nice, Wayne.
When did you first start thinking
about killing?
Birth. I was thrown into a flaming pit...
of scum, forgotten by God.
[CHUCKLES]
What do you mean?
I mean, I came from violence,
it was in my blood. My dad had it.
MICKEY: His dad had it. It's my fate.
Do you believe in fate?
My fate.
- No one is born evil, you learn it.
WAYNE: What about your father?
How did he die?
You were only 10 years old,
and there's a lot of speculation.
I didn't kill my father,
and I don't want to talk about it.
WAYNE: Watch it. Watch it.
It's all right. It's okay.
Go on to something else.
Please, let's do.
WAYNE: Tell me, how can you look at...
an ordinary person,
an innocent guy...
...and then shoot him to death?
I mean, how can you do that?
MICKEY: Innocent?
Who's innocent? You?
I'm innocent of murder, definitely.
It's just murder. All God's creatures...
do it in some form or another.
MICKEY: I mean, look in the forest.
Species kill other species.
Our species killing all species...
...including the forest, and we just
call it industry, not murder.
MICKEY: But I know a lot of people who...
...deserve to die.
WAYNE: Why do they deserve to die?
MICKEY: I think everybody got...
...something in their past.
Some sin. Some awful, secret thing.
MICKEY ON TV: A lot of people walking...
around already dead...
...just need to be put out of their misery.
That's where I come in.
Fate's messenger.
Except a corn or wheat
falleth to the ground...
...and die, it abideth alone.
But if it die...
...it bringeth forth much fruit.
The theory that everyone meets
a serial killer halfway?
The wolf don't know why he's a wolf.
God just made it that way.
You're saying that
the world itself is predatory.
When a lion takes down an elk,
it's the elk’s time to go.
And the B.S. liberal agenda
about saving the herds...
...only serves to overpopulate
the balance of nature.
Maybe you're right.
I don't think so,
but maybe you are.
Corporate and environmental predators.
Nuclear predators. Life is a hunt.
I've seen it, I was there.
When the **** hit the fan at Grenada.
I saw it all...
...go down at Grenada.
So tell me, Mickey, any regrets?
I mean, three weeks,
50 people killed.
Not too cool, Mickey.
Fifty-two, but I don't spend
a lot of time with regret.
It's a wasted emotion.
You must have some regret.
Rack your brain.
I wish that Indian hadn't got killed.
Bad, bad, bad.
One of your last victims.
Man had a rattlesnake sitting in a corner.
A rattlesnake?
He could pick it up, pet it.
He saw it.
He saw what?
The demon. He saw the demon.
The demon?
WAYNE: What demon?
Everybody got the demon in here.
The demon lives in here.
It feeds on your hate.
Cuts, kills, rapes.
MICKEY OVER TV: It uses your weakness,
your fears. Only the vicious survive.
We all told we're no good pieces
of shit since we could breathe.
After a while, you kind of become bad.
But after the Indian,
we were gonna quit killing.
The old man took it out of us.
What happened?
It was all just a mistake, you know.
Man tried to help us.
You know, pet us.
Same dream I've had
since I was a kid. I just....
Running, running with the animals
in the darkness.
Mr. Rabbit.
Bloody fangs.
Christmas hat.
Little...
...madness going on,
we're just running....
I'm just....
I'm Mr. Rabbit.
I'm eating every other animal in the forest.
Death.
Death kind of becomes what you are...
...after life became black.
You know about realization, Wayne?
I mean, all this is just...
...an illusion.
Mr. Rabbit says,
'The moment of realization....'
'The moment of realization...
...is worth...
...a thousand prayers.'
You're crazy.
I don't think I'm any crazier than you are.
I'm extremes, dark and light,
you know that.
I'm light with Mal.
Mal.
That's your shadow on the wall.
MICKEY: Can't get rid of your shadow,
can you?
You know, the only thing that kills a demon:
Love.
That's why Mallory's my salvation.
She was teaching me how to love.
MALLORY: I forgive you, baby.
It was just like...
...being in the Garden of Eden.
Only love can kill the demon.
Hold that thought.
[CRUNCHES SNOW]...
[GRUNTING]
If these guys are in your eye line, I'm sorry.
You want some powder?
Mmmm.
Rise and shine, Mallory.
GUARD: Turn around and face the wall.
Relax, we want to have a talk, is all.
GUARD: Don't get too close
or she'll kill you.
One way or another, she'll kill you.
Relax. Read my book.
I met some unruly crocodiles...
...but she's got a sweet streak for me.
Take that. It's okay.
We're not allowed....
- It's okay.
It's okay, guys.
Smoke?
I know you smoke.
I'm not here to hurt you.
I want to be your friend.
If I ever met a girl who needs a friend...
...it's you.
You're a very pretty girl.
Remember the last time you got fucked?
Remember?
I want you to close your eyes...
...and remember the last time
Mickey gave you the hard one.
Thinking about it?
[MALLORY LAUGHS]
Forget it, because it's never
gonna happen again.
When they get through
with all the electroshock shit...
...Mickey ain't gonna be worth a shit.
Was it worth it?
Was what worth it?
Was massacring those people worth...
being separated from your love forever?
You mean, was an instant of my purity...
worth a lifetime of your lies?
Explain where's the purity
you couldn't live without...
...in the 52 people...
...who aren't on this planet
because they met you and Mallory.
What's so ******* pure about that?
How do you do it?
MICKEY: You'll never understand.
You and me aren't even the same species.
I used to be you, then I evolved.
From where you're standing,
you're a man. To me, you're an ape.
MICKEY: Not even an ape,
you're a media person.
Media's like the weather,
only it's man-made weather.
Murder? It's pure.
MICKEY: You're the one made it impure.
You're buying and selling fear.
You say, 'Why?'
I say, 'Why bother?'
Are you done? Great.
Now let's cut the B.S. and get real.
Why this purity that you feel about killing?
Why, for chrissakes? Don't lie.
You just gotta hold that shotgun in
your hand, and it becomes clear...
...like it did for me the first time.
That's when I realized
my one true calling in life.
What's that, Mickey?
Shit, man...
...I'm a natural born killer.
JULIE: And that's commercial.
Did you get that?
INMATE: All right, Mickey.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Great. Great, man.
LEROY: There's a riot going on here.
Shit.
Thanks.
Every fucking moron in the world
just saw that, mate.
LEROY: We got a riot going on here...
that's out of control. We need help.
God Almighty shit,
Leroy. Where at?
In the rec room, B wing.
We're outmanned, we need help.
You mobilize the men. I'm on my way.
Mr. Gale, close them cameras down.
We got a riot going on in B wing.
It's live, for chrissakes.
- You're finished.
Millions are watching.
- They got guns, hostages.
Close those cameras, now.
Turn them off.
- We'll be famous.
You stay here and shut up.
I must find out what's going on
before I let you film anywhere.
The world is watching.
We'll never get this chance again.
Fuck you.
He can't tell me
what to do in my jail. Fuck him.
WAYNE: Fuck you.
DWIGHT: Keep your fingers on the...
trigger of your shotguns and follow me.
This is a tough room.
All right, one more.
MICKEY: Mother says to Sister:
'You can go to the drive-in with Bobby,
but you got to take little Johnny.'
Sister goes, 'Okay.'
They go, they come back.
Mother takes Johnny aside
and says, 'What happened?'
Little Johnny can't talk.
She says, 'They went to the drive-in.
What happened then?' Johnny goes:
[KISSING NOISES]...
'They were kissing? What else?'
You heard this one?
'What else?'
Little Johnny goes:
'He felt her up?
What else?'
Little Johnny goes:
'They took off their clothes?
What else?'
Little Johnny goes:
'They did that?
What the hell were you doing?.'
Little Johnny goes:
'Little Johnny, no.'
DEPUTY: Shit.
Drop it.
The gun, goddamn it.
Smart move.
Empty the shells.
MICKEY: Hurry up.
Where are you?
I'm all right. I'm okay.
All right, new friend,
get your camera.
Where's Roger?
- Right here.
WAYNE: Where's Scully?
- He's hit. I think he's dead.
Shit.
Put the shells on the table.
Drop your belt.
Hands behind your head.
Got the camera going yet?
They're both shot to shit.
That's too bad for you.
Wait, I got a remote Beta.
I can get an image up.
Very innovative. Put it on.
Everyone's going to follow me out of here.
One big, happy family,
shooting everything I do.
MICKEY: Kavanaugh, get up.
Take me to Mallory's cell
and hope she's in one piece.
Everyone get behind Kavanaugh.
Press up against him.
Let's go. Young lady,
come along with us.
MICKEY: Hustle it.
Stay with me.
[GUNSHOTS]
That's my camera.
Now I remember you. You're Jack.
I'm not really as bad as they say I am.
I'm actually a really nice person.
Yeah, I know.
I've done some bad things myself.
I killed somebody.
No shit.
Know what I think about?
Sex.
Fucking.
I think about hands on my tits.
And I think about flesh against flesh...
...and sweat.
My mind drives me crazy.
Sit down.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to kiss me
and squeeze my nipple.
You're so specific.
Squeeze it.
You like a little bit of pain?
Harder.
How sexy am I now, fucker?
You stupid dick.
GUARD: Shit, what happened?
MALLORY: You want a sexy little whore?
GUARD: I'm trying, I'm trying.
Fucking bitch broke my fucking nose.
Give me that gun.
I'll fucking kill you.
GUARD: No gun. Put it away.
JACK: Give me your Mace.
You want to play, bitch?
You want some?
How about this?
MALLORY: Don't do that.
You like it?
TV ANNOUNCER: Now a special report...
from Channel 6 News.
Are we on?
Good afternoon,
I'm Antonia Chavez.
This is a WATCH special report.
I'm told we're taking you right now
live to Botongo Penitentiary...
...where Wayne Gale continues
his interview...
...in the middle of a riot.
Wayne, can you hear me?
What's happening there? Are you safe?
This is Wayne Gale, resuming live.
You can tell from the blood
and carnage all around...
...that the final chapter of Mickey
and Mallory has yet to be written.
Are you in danger?
Can you tell us?
War has broken out here,
unlike anything I've ever seen.
But we'll stand alongside them.
CHAVEZ: What's happening?
WAYNE: Botongo, Botongo, Botongo.
JACK: Don't you like this?
MICKEY: Hey, Jack...
...Mickey's back.
[GUNSHOTS]
JACK: Drop the shotgun.
We got us a Mexican standoff.
We've had this date from the beginning.
Slide that shotgun here.
Put your hands behind your head,
your forehead on the floor.
Or what? You wound me?
I can blow you in half.
I never wounded anything in my life.
I got you locked right between the eyes.
I've had you locked
from the jump, you phony.
MICKEY:
You got me locked.
Take your shot.
Okay, Jack, you win.
[JACK GROANS]
Oh, baby.
Ladies and gentlemen, this kiss
has been a year in the coming.
They're doing what everyone said
they'd never do again.
At this moment, they are
the only two people on earth.
[JACK GURGLES]
WAYNE: Shut up, Jack.
[GUN CLICKS]
Losing your touch, Jack.
I was out of shells.
[GROANS]...
[COCKS GUN]
You still like me now, Jack?
What's this?
WURLITZER: List of prisoners.
What the fuck?.
I asked for a list of hostages.
WURLITZER: How should I know?
- Just get it.
Do I have to do everything?
Jesus Christ.
What are those guys right there?
DWIGHT: Close 1, 2, 3.
DEPUTY: Still jammed open, sir.
- Well, jam them shut.
There's a fire.
- I see the goddamn fire.
The psych unit looks like a zoo.
Informants are being tortured.
What is it, Natapundi?
- Napalatoni.
I don't care what your name is.
Mickey and Mallory Knox are loose.
Scagnetti's dead.
They're live on network TV.
Live on network TV?
Jesus Harold Christ
on a fucking rubber crutch.
Is this happening to me?
[GUNSHOTS]
You fucking sick motherfuckers.
Come on.
Yeah, come on.
OWEN: Come on.
Come on, Mickey. This way.
MICKEY: Who are you?
My name's Owen.
MICKEY: What do you want from us?
I want you to take me with you.
MICKEY: Where the hell are we?
It's a place I come to think
when things get hectic.
Call them.
MICKEY: Let's go, Kavanaugh.
OWEN: Follow me.
MICKEY:
Now we're in B wing.
Where we going?
Out. Through. Down.
MICKEY: Hold up.
Okay, Kavanaugh....
Don't shoot.
Don't shoot. Wayne Gale.
Motherfucker.
How you doing, Wayne?
I'm fucking great.
You got the feeling?
- I'm alive for the first fucking time.
For the love, thanks to Mickey.
Let's kill all these motherfuckers.
Give me that.
- Why?
You're not centered, Wayne.
Here, shoot with this.
Let's go.
Kavanaugh, stop slacking off.
[GUNS COCKING]
End of the line. Drop him.
MICKEY: One move and he's dead.
He's already dead, dickweed.
You got shit. Fire.
You shoot, I'll blast him. Back off.
Shut up, Gale, you prick.
Mickey, Mallory, just let me say--
Put your hand up.
[GUNSHOT]
Shut up.
Mickey, I made a place. Come, come.
MICKEY: Come on, move. Let's go, Mal.
WAYNE: What is your bloody problem?
Sixty seconds and I'm coming up.
MICKEY: Think, think, think.
Fuck.
[PHONE RINGS]
WAYNE: Yes?
Hello, Margaret.
How are you doing?
- I'm all right.
You're doing good, baby.
MICKEY: I want you to know...
...no matter what happens...
...I love you.
I love you more than I ever loved myself.
I know that, Mickey.
I'm never coming home.
Don't you get it? I'm alive for
the first time in my life. I'm alive.
Because I don't love you anymore.
I love Ming.
That's right, Ming is not
a fucking restaurant.
I don't care. Take the money.
It's all yours anyway.
And one more thing: Piss off, you cunt.
It's good to be with you.
You do a lot of good for people.
The joint's exploding, and...
you're diddling around with these two.
We have more important things to do.
These two die today. You hear me?
I'll wipe that fucking scum
off the face of the fucking earth...
...if it's the last fucking thing I do.
You know what I say?
I say...
...to hell with going to our cells.
MALLORY: Let's go out there...
...and run down the stairs
and go out in a hail of bullets.
And then we'll die.
Then we'll really be free.
That's poetry.
But we'll do that when all else fails.
I just left her.
That's right.
Put a bottle of Dom on ice.
Get some ecstasy.
I'll come put a hot pepper up your ass.
MING: No, you're not.
I love you, Ming.
- Sorry, Charlie.
Ming?
MICKEY: Hold this.
You married?
God, I don't wanna die.
I don't wanna die.
That wasn't the question.
Yes, I'm married.
Do you have children?
A boy and a girl.
DUNCAN: I don't wanna die.
MICKEY: Mal, come here, please.
The only way we'll get out that front door...
...is if they don't wanna kill you two
more than they wanna kill us.
Mr. Journalist.
Okay, hold that.
Duncan Homolka, Wayne Gale.
How are you?
MICKEY: You want reality? You got it.
My name is Wayne Gale.
I am the star of American Maniacs,
watched by 40 million people a week.
I am a respected journalist, winner of...
the Ed R. Murrow and the Golden Globe...
...to name a few.
I've been shot. You're on camera.
We are live.
If anyone fucks up our escape...
...I'll make it my mission to put
Warden McClusky out of commission.
I will do exposé after exposé,
revealing the inhumanity, brutality...
...and conditions that exist here.
You, back up. Back up.
My name is Wayne Gale.
I'm the star of American Maniacs.
You are on camera. We are live.
Just how far do you think
you're gonna get?
MICKEY: Out the front door.
That will never happen.
MICKEY: It is happening.
My name is Wayne Gale.
I'm a friend of Bill Clinton's.
If anybody puts me in danger....
You open that gate.
My name is Wayne Gale.
I am the star of American Maniacs.
I will personally hunt you down,
blow the head off your whore wife...
Don't disrespect my man.
...and plant your sick ass
in the ground all by myself.
Another day, perhaps,
but not today.
[INMATES YELL]...
[GUNFIRE]...
[DWIGHT SCREAMS]
This is Wayne Gale,
unfortunately no longer live.
I am wounded. All my crew is dead.
I have left my wife,
and my girlfriend has left me.
MALLORY:
Don't look that glum. That was good.
Mickey Knox's plan worked.
We walked out the door into...
my news van and made our getaway.
When we were followed by patrol cars...
...Mallory shot Deputy Sheriff
Duncan Homolka...
...and tossed his body out.
MICKEY: Show them your ear.
MALLORY: Oh, my God, that is so gross.
Why helicopters were not deployed.
I don't know.
I guess it happened too fast
for arrangements to be made.
We've pulled to the side of the road...
to do this interview.
Tensions run high as we--
MICKEY: We don't got all fucking day.
So without further ado: Mickey and Mallory.
So, Mallory,
after Mickey's incredible rescue...
...what did you think next?
I was wondering how long it'd be...
...until me and Mickey could be alone,
and if I could wait that long.
Did you have anything to do with the riot?
We didn't have nothing to do with that riot.
You know, that was....
Whatchamacallit?
Fate?
- Fate.
If they wanna say we masterminded...
the whole fucking thing, let them.
It's not like it's gonna keep us up
at night and stuff.
But the truth is...
...it was...
...fate.
Fate it was. You saw it right here
on American Maniacs.
You believe in reincarnation, Wayne?
Yes, I believe we've all lived many...
times. So what's next for the Knoxes?
I'm thinking we can lay
in a big king-size bed...
...and sleep...
...for two days, and I've been
thinking about motherhood.
So I think me and Mickey are gonna...
get started on that...
...as quickly as possible.
Gotta go.
- Wait.
How do you intend to disappear? You're...
the most famous couple in America.
There's the Underground Railroad,
when during slave times--
Let me swing the camera around...
...and do my wrap-up,
then we're off.
We're gonna do a wrap-up, all right.
But it won't be you staring
in the camera, looking dumb.
You'll be staring down the barrels
of our shotguns...
...and we're gonna be blowing
your brains all over that tree.
Wait. Time. Cut, cut, cut.
It's a fucking joke, right?
[GUNS COCKING]
WAYNE: Don't fucking shoot me.
During this escape,
a bond developed between us.
Not really. You're scum, Wayne.
You did it for ratings.
You don't give a shit
about anybody except yourself.
So nobody gives a shit about you.
That's why helicopters weren't deployed.
Wait a minute, you hypocrite.
What about the Indian?
You said you were done with killing.
That love beats the demon.
You said that love beats the demon.
I am...
...and it will.
It's just that you're the last one.
No, don't kill me.
This is not about you, you egomaniac.
I kind of like you.
But if we let you go,
we'd be just like...
everybody else. Killing you...
...and what you represent is...
...a statement.
I'm not sure what it's saying...
...but, you know, Frankenstein
killed Dr. Frankenstein.
[MICKEY COCKS GUN]
Have some dignity.
All right.
So I'm a parasite, so what?
Life is cruel,
and no one said it'd be easy.
The day you two killed,
your ass belonged to us.
To the public. To the media.
We are married, right?
The point is...
...what do we do next?
I say we do a Salman Rushdie-type thing.
Just books, talk shows. We lay low,
we jump up, we bob and weave.
We get rid of them.
We do Oprah, Donahue.
Do you have any idea
how huge we could be?
Let's make a little music.
Wait, wait.
Don't Mickey and Mallory always leave...
someone alive to tell the tale?
We are. Your camera.
Okay, fuck.
[CHANTS]...
[GUNSHOTS]
I'm gonna miss him.
Let's go.
Okay, baby.
CHAVEZ: I can't hear him.
I'm not getting anything.
Oh, my God.
A bride and groom's wedding reception...
turned into a nightmare.
My dad....
People....
Because it would end in sex.
He punched me, he slapped me again.
I just wanna say,
you know, can we...?
[NINE INCH NAILS PLAY]
Ready?
[ENGLISH SDH]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4w84y
Help other users to choose the best subtitles