Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Turned left on 14th street...
copy that Foxtrot..
crossing 14th..
Turned left on the 18th street...
copy that Romeo..
crossed Broad Street now...
copy that Bravo..
All teams we have him!
Open stretch approaching..
Take him down now!
Mo?e.. move..
Go.. go!
Hands up... FBl! Get out of the car!
- What l ha?e done?
Get out of the car...
Up against the car now..
John... frisk this guy!
Stay against the car!
ls he clean?
- He's clean.
Bring him back...
Open it...
This is not mine
l don't own this taxi..
Bingo boys we got him!
- This is not my cab.
They're not yours? You're driving
around with weapons in your taxi..
and you don't know whose they are..
- No... they're not mine...
We know who owns the cab..
Get rid of him...
Sir... there has
been some mistake sir...
some confusion sir...
Sir l finished work at 9'o
clock in the night sir...
and l went straight up from work...
l have no idea...
l've been arrested for what sir?
On what charges sir?
Omar Aijaz...
So you're from Delhi?
Sir you don't need to do
these bonding exercises with me
Sir.. l don't have a clue how
that stuff landed in my cab...
or who put it there...
why am l here?
This is an FBl lnterrogation room...
and it's me who asks questions...
When did you first visit America?
l want a lawyer.
You're not getting one.
What?
- You've been detained...
Which means that you may
want to talk to someone...
but you can't...
you're not allowed to.
The Patriot Act empowers
me to detain a suspect
in order to prevent
an act of terrorism..
Terrorism?
What does that mean?
What do l have to do with terrorism?
We'll soon find out...
So start talking... when was
your first visit to America?
September 1 999.
99... exactly two years before 9/1 1 ?
What do you mean?
Just answer the question...
Why did you come to America?
l got a scholarship...
For my Masters at New
York State University...
Two years at the university..
you must have had friends...
Name them.
Yohann... Anil...
Kevin.. Sarah... Harminder..
And...
And?
You forgot one.
Who?
Sam... your dearest friend.
Why did you hide his name?
l didn't... l just
did not remember him..
Didn't remember?
You've been brought here
only to talk about him..
How can you force me?
l hope it doesn't come
down to that, my friend.
l need a lawyer.
Forget it.
- This is illegal!
You must remember
one thing my brother..
you're not talking
to a damn policeman..
you're dealing with the FBl...
lf we need to break the law...
for this country's safety..
we do it..
Okay...
We have recovered AK-47s..
and plastic
explosives from your taxi...
so you don't talk about legality...
That is not my stuff...
Then prove it!
Sir... please... listen to me...
Tell me about Sam...
What does Sam have
to do with all this?
l haven't seen him in 7 years...
Why haven't you seen him?
l haven't seen a lot
of people in 7 years..
And what is it that you
want to know about him?
Every damn thing...
Let's start from the beginning...
and try not to
forget anything this time.
l was born in Delhi...
No... no... cut Delhi...
cut lndia...
Start from America...
My first day at the university...
New York State Uni?ersity...
Thank you...
- Sure... have fun...
lt was my first trip out of lndia...
l was nervous...
l didn't have a clue
who to talk to...
or what to talk about.
This was a different world for me...
Hi... l'm Maya.
Hello...
You are Omar... right?
How do you know my name?
And you're from lndia...
How do you know all this?
l also know that
you're one semester late..
that's late lateef in Hindi, right?
You speak Hindi?
l speak Hindi...
l even watch Hindi films..
don't like them much
but l have to..
my mother you know...
she'd dump my dad in a
second for Shah Rukh Khan.
Anyway... you're looking
for your lecture room..
come with me...
Thanks...
Let me introduce myself again.
My name is Maya, and l'm
your student counsellor..
that's how l know all this.
l had your admission file.
But there are so many people here...
How did you find me?
lt's not that
difficult really to find..
a good looking lndian
boy fresh off the boat..
a crisp shirt neatly tucked
into his terricot trousers..
l'm kidding.. your
file had a photograph.
See you later Matt..
Where are all these guys going?
The annual challenge...
- What's that?
lt's a college
tradition where a new student..
challenges the college champion..
in a bizarre race.
Why bizarre?
See for yourself...
and meet the challenger...
He's our classmate...
and loves to be the
centre of attention... c'mon..
The race starts as soon as the
clock tower strikes twel?e...
no one has e?er completed the
race before the twelfth gong..
come on!
come on Sam!
That's right! That's right!
One..
Two..
Three..
Four..
Five..
Six..
Seven..
Eight..
Nine..
Ten!
Eleven!
Twelve!
Woo.. Sam!
Hey man!
So cool!
Dude... l told you l'd win...
Aren't you happy?
- Of course...
Then give me a hug...
Ah... have a shower first..
Sure... come baby...
Keep dreaming dude...
come... you give me a hug...
Hi l'm Sam...
Hi... l'm Omar... l have just come...
Really... with just a hug?
c'mon... give him a break...
Just kidding Omar..
Welcome to New York
Thank you.
- c'mon...
How was he as a student?
lmpressive... good at sports...
spoke well... got good grades...
he had just one problem...
people found him arrogant...
Arrogant?
l guess he was...
How did you become friends?
Maya reached college at 7.50...
l would get there 5
minutes before her and wait..
l used to look out for her..
and we went to class together.
Hey Omar!
After a few days,
this became a routine..
l liked spending those
1 0 minutes with her...
Just her...
Maya..
Now what?
Every time l ask you about Sam,
you start talking about Maya.
Sir... you said... you
need all the details...
l'm doing just that...
Ya... go on... continue...
Hi... what's going on?
What else... the attention seeker
seeks attention... and gets it..
Sam plays chess?
Yup... thinks he's a grandmaster...
claims that no one can beat him..
that's his challenge...
checkmate!
Do you want to take three
moves back and play again?
Three moves back?
l'm giving you a chance...
Show off...
You still win...
c'mon guys... anybody? c'mon...
can l try?
Sure...
Are you sure?
check...
l don't need the third move Sam...
checkmate!
Dude... How did you do that?
Superb man!
Show me.. show me again...
- Our friendship started with chess...
and soon l became
a part of his gang.
Yes!
Touch down!
Hey Friends..
lets live this moment
to it's fullest
lt seems now
Our time is about to come
Hey friends..
if you belie?e in yourself
then life is beautiful
Tomorrow beckons you
Hey Friends..
lets live this moment
to it's fullest
it seems now
our time is about to come
Hey Friends..
if you belie?e in yourself
then life is beautiful
tomorrow beckons you
We have passion..
Great run... Omar...
we have passion in our li?es
Dude... you're learning fast...
Nothing much to learn...
just catch the ball and run...
Fine... you start this time...
What kind of game is this...
You hold the ball in your
hand and call it football..
who the hell piles on like that...
all on one guy...
you're not playing kabaddi.
Honestly... e?en l find this
game very strange but Sam likes it..
That's why he gets
everyone here each weekend..
Yeah... he almost
got me killed there..
No. He likes you. He doesn't
ha?e too many lndian friends..
Why?
He's just so American in his ways.
He's been living here
since he was 4 years old.
His father is a professor...
an expert on lndian culture...
that's why he's so fluent in Hindi...
otherwise he would ha?e
been totally American..
Like you?
l look American to you?
You surely look American...
your attitude is definitely American
but you manage to
speak decent Hindi...
Mom...
She spoke only in Hindi
to me since l was small...
she loves to talk about lndia...
ln fact... you should
come home sometime..
she'll really like you...
Somewhere.. a certain
melody begins
Along our paths look..
there are marvels in all their glory
Us.. just us in this world
Everywhere
To brighten our dreams
we have found a reason
Somewhere.. a certain
melody begins
Along our paths look..
there are marvels in all their glory
Us.. just us in this world
Everywhere
To brighten our dreams
we have found a reason
What if this..
is not true
what is it then..
that is true
Hey friends.. on your own terms
on the pages of your hearts
come.. lets write a new chapter
Hey friends.. to worry about results
ls not what this age does
then why have any fear at all
We have passion..
We have passion in our lives
We have passion in our hearts
We have passion..
check out those broads... dude...
Broad... what a strange word...
l mean... doesn't broad mean wide...
then how can that be a girl?
Okay... what do you
call sexy girls in Delhi?
We call them Maal... Katto...
That sounds pretty cool... Katto...
Katto!
Totta...
Tota... But Tota is a parrot...
Not tota my dear... totta... totta...
Totta.
Hey guys... what's up!
Totta...
lf ever.. we meet
along the way
ln a moment.. it will erupt
that laughter of old
then say.. what would you say
to me then
how will you veil those moist
eyes of yours
lf ever.. we meet
along the way
ln a moment.. it will erupt
that laughter of old
then say.. what would you say
to me then
how will you veil those moist
eyes of yours
Do you know
this that happened
Do you know why
then say it loud
Hey Friends.. lets live
this moment to it's fullest
lt seems now
Our time is about to come
Hey friends.. if you
belie?e in yourself
then life is beautiful
Tomorrow beckons you
We have passion..
we have passion in our li?es
we have passion in our hearts
We have passion..
we have passion in our li?es
we have passion in our hearts
l don't know how those two years...
flew by with Sam and Maya...
time just went by..
That's Zaheer... from Pakistan...
came from Quetta...
stayed there for two years...
and has been in
New York for 8 years..
he's an illegal immigrant...
Malik... also from Pakistan..
came via Germany..
Yaqub... from Bangladesh...
Yaseer... Afghan... he's a mute.
All are suspected terrorists...
members of a South
Asian sleeper cell..
we found clues from a hard disk...
that we got in a
Middle East operation.
Why are you showing me all this?
Because they all work
for the same person..
you've been working for...
Your friend... Samir Sheikh..
for whom you were transporting guns
in your taxi yesterday.
Am l right? Am l right? Am l right?
You're mad!
This is what you show me
after all that bullshit..
Samir's a terrorist..
l'm a terrorist..
and you are completely crazy!
you admitted that this
man is your friend..
he runs a sleeper cell in New York...
you are and always have
been his accomplice...
We recovered arms from your taxi..
You're talking nonsense...
neither was l transporting guns
in my cab..
nor can Samir be
running a Sleeper cell..
You have lost it...
you've gone mad...
Where were you transporting
those guns and explosives?
prepare an answer to that question
in your 6 by 6 cell tonight..
or you're in deep shit my brother.
Sir... listen to me...
You're framing me...
l'm not a terrorist..
and neither can Sam be one...
Where were you transporting
those guns and explosives?
prepare an answer to that question
in your 6 by 6 cell tonight..
The Patriot Act empowers
me to detain a suspect
l want a lawyer.
- You're not getting one.
We have recovered AK-47s and
plastic explosives from your taxi..
so you don't talk about legality...
for the same person you've been
working for... Samir Sheikh...
Your friend... you admitted
that this man is your friend..
he runs a sleeper cell in New York...
you are and always have
been his accomplice...
Why haven't you seen him in 7 years?
Welcome to New York.
Omar... Omarr...
One more... one more...
c'mon Another one...
Sam... c'mon... Sam... photo...
Sam... dude...
Sam...
Totta...
Totta?
Keep at it dude... Totta!
c'mon let's go...
c'mon, c'mon let's go..
What happened?
Nothing...
Then why did we come out
so suddenly..
l didn't like the music..
ls that all...
Life is just a dream..
And in a dream.. what's a fantasy...
and what is real..
Look... lt's raining...
lt's cold.
Whatever my heart..
told me to do.. l did
just that
Whatever my heart..
told me to do.. l did
just that
Someday at leisure l will wonder
was it wrong or right
What?
can you help a poor
man with some change?
Ya sure...
Omar, what are you doing?
Let's leave.
Your bag and earrings... quick...
Give me your bag and earrings...
quick...
What the hell do you
think you are doing?
l think l need to ask
you that question...
Don't mess with me man...
Omar... grab him from the back..
l'll get his hands..
Hey what did you say?
- Sam... Maya's with us..
Sam! Hey!
There's nothing in that bag...
Sam..
Sam...
Oh my God! Sam... are you okay?
Omar listen... call somebody..
call an ambulance..
Wake up Sam.. please wake up!
l love you Sam!
Listen to me..
Stay with me okay.. stay with me..
Baby.. l love you baby.
Why do you do these things..
Because l love you Maya..
l love you too baby.
What you never uttered..
is what l always heard..
for no reason
l began to weave dreams..
What you never uttered..
is what l always heard..
for no reason
l began to weave dreams..
Don't know how
our lives got torn apart..
this town of mine..
was no longer mine
Away from my love
- Omar.
l kept walking away
for no reason
l began to weave dreams..
Are you alright, Omar?
l didn't see you after that night.
You disappeared from the hospital.
Yes... sorry. college
is coming to an end..
l had to pack some things...
You know when l met
Sam for the first time..
l found him rather odd...
He thought the world of himself...
but then, l don't know how,
l started to like him..
and l realised it
that night when l saw
him in that state...
l think l'm in love with him...
Yes, l heard they discharged
him the next day... that's great.
You haven't met him yet?
No... like l said...
l was packing some stuff..
What are you packing that
doesn't let you meet your friends?
Maya... l don't belong to
this place... like Sam and you..
l must keep everything
with a lot of care..
..and in any case you're
here to take care of him..
Why are you being so strange Omar?
l'm sorry... l'm in a strange mood...
college is about to end..
that's why maybe..
Only college is coming to an end..
not our friendship...
Yes... but l don't
know why l feel like
a lot more is coming to an end...
lt seems that night
really shook you up..
Yes Maya, it sure did.
Listen... its okay.
l know Samir is a little crazy but...
You always called him
crazy and l thought that..
What?
Why didn't you tell me Maya..
that you and Sam..
Omar... you?
lt was chaos!
Oh my God!
A plane had crashed into one tower
of New York's World Trade centre
lt was chaos!
We just saw another one..
Another plane just flew
into the second tower.
l can't believe this.
This raises.. this has
to be deliberate folks..
Oh my God!
Skyline of Manhattan
has changed forever..
New York's twin towers are gone.
This is awful..
We have passion.. we
ha?e passion in our lives
ha?e passion in our hearts
No one realized it at that time...
but that one day
changed our lives... fore?er.
l left New York that evening..
and moved to Philadelphia...
l don't know where
Sam and Maya are...
They're married now...
and they have a son...
l want to belie?e you...
but then l can't deny the truth...
Truth is... that neither me
nor Samir are terrorists...
Sir, by now you should know
that he wasn't like that...
Don't defend Samir...
just speak for yourself...
we have enough evidence
against him...
Then why don't you go and get him...
why have you kept me here?
l've told you a thousand times...
those are not my guns...
lt doesn't matter if you tell
me a hundred thousand times...
or you shout all day...
who is going to hear you...
how are you going to prove it?
Okay...
then someday you will
find yourself blindfolded...
seated in a plane...
And dumped in a
prison in some place...
that you will never know about...
which country, town or
jungle that's going to be...
will be a mystery for me as well...
What do you want?
l want to help you...
you're not letting me...
lf you can't help yourself,
no one else can..
How? l swear l don't know a thing...
Why don't you arrest him...
l honestly don't know...
You can do one thing...
Why don't you go back
to Sam... as a friend...
...but at the same time work for
us... give us information about him.
This is probably the only way
you could prove your innocence...
this is the only chance.
Oh... so that was your idea...
that's what you want me to do...
that's why you planted
those weapons in my cab...
l'm sorry...
l won't do it... is that clear?
You have no idea what
these people could do to you...
You're in detention...
soon you will forget how to
walk straight or talk right...
you will want to sleep
but won't be allowed to...
is that clear?
l won't betray my friend...
l'm not asking you to betray anyone...
l'm just saying co-operate with us...
if you do, you will be
helping this country...
then l can tell my seniors
that they should be lenient
with a boy who is helping
us unco?er a sleeper cell...
are you getting me?
Spare a thought for
your 70 year old father...
all alone in a single room at
Lajpat Nagar... do you
realize what might happen..
when the news spreads in lndia
that Omar Aijaz is a terrorist?
What he will go through?
What about Maya?
That poor girl doesn't
even know that her husband is a...
Don't you want to help her?
Think about it...
l'll see you tomorrow.
The usual.. make it double...
Thanks.
You think this idea of
yours is going to work?
Maybe... are you scared?
Are you what?
Scared...
You know Roshan, its been fifteen
years and l still can't understand..
that damn accent of yours...
l'm on this case
because l'm a South Asian...
so you need me to
speak the way l do...
and Gibson... fifteen years...
1 5 years.. you can't
say my name properly.
lts not Rowshaen... its Roshan.
Ya... Ya...
You know... l've put my ass on the
line for this crazy idea of yours...
if this goes bad... it means there
will be a terrorist attack that
we knew about and did nothing...
that makes us accomplices...
Look at it this way...
if it works...
you become a hero.
And what if it doesn't?
Then we both are screwed...
What?
Screwed... as in...
ls anybody there?
can you listen to me?
Hello! l need to speak to somebody...
c'mon get somebody here...
l want someone right now...
right here...
can you listen to me?
Why the hell are you
screaming at this hour?
l need to speak to the officer.
You gotta wait till the morning.
l can't wait...
l want to speak to him now...
Why me?
lf you need an infiltrator
to go to Sam....
...you have your people... why me?
ls this why you've
called me at this hour?
Yes.
Who do you think
could stay with Sam and
Maya in their house... besides you?
What am l going to tell them?
where was l for 7 years...
what was l doing...
And why have l come to them now?
You're friends with Sam and Maya...
they have no reason to doubt you...
we'll give you a back story...
a new identity...
so don't worry about it...
you just have to say yes...
Alright...
Yes?
Alright... l'll do it.
Good... good...
Now let's go to sleep... ya?
Just a minute officer...
l have agreed not because
l'm keen to help the FBl...
it's only to prove that
Samir and l are not terrorists...
Works for me!
Thanks...
What a friendship!
You must have fired many guns?
Oh yes... l would shoot
balloons during Diwali fairs.
Then you must be a good shot.
Relax! Relax your elbows...
control your breath when you fire...
l'm going there as their friend,
so why do l need all this?
Because... when you tell him
that you want to work with him...
he will definitely test you... and
l don't want you to fail the test.
No one in the FBl
knows of this operation...
besides me and my senior.
Hi... we booked a room
in the name of Omar Aijaz.
Let me check sir...
Are you with Northwest chemicals?
That's right.
Okay..
Omar... it's very
important for this mission..
that you stay in Samir's house...
l don't want you to appear hasty...
but shift in with them at
the first opportunity...
Okay... so two of my
men will come to you..
at 1 0 tomorrow morning...
they'll take you to a school...
Sam and Maya's son
goes to that school...
Maya will be there to pick him up...
Here... spare keys... just in case...
You do have a driver's license...
right?
No... can we cancel the mission?
Don't ask me stupid questions...
Do you see those kids at the gate...
What else will l see there?
No, the boy with the
blue and yellow bag...
that's Maya's son...
She'll be at the entrance
after she parks her car...
you'll see her as she
comes to the entrance...
she's there... she's there...
can you see her?
There she was...
revealed to me again
Memories came rushing back
My eyes began to water
with the smoke of yesterday
Your condition is nothing like mine
Why in this joy
am l still feeling pain
why am l beginning to again create
that world
That world
away from where
l had long walked away
Once again these memories
have made a new beginning
A moment of the past
Still made my heart ache
for no reason
l began to weave dreams..
What you never uttered..
is what l always heard..
for no reason
l began to weave dreams..
Have you lost your mind?
lf he backs out... l'll
hand over the case to you...
l'll give you all the
evidence l have on Samir Sheikh...
l'll shoot that terrorist...
and l will do it like tomorrow.
lf you're right about
Samir running a sleeper cell...
Then?
Then... you have to
promise me something...
What promise?
That... you won't kill Samir...
lf you can convince
him to surrender...
then l can promise you that...
l guarantee that.
Okay...
let's do it.
Hello...
Yes..
Hello..
Make a turn ahead and try again...
and keep talking to me
on the phone...
Yes... l just made a turn...
she's coming towards me...
lf she doesn't see you... at least
she'll recognise your voice...
Ya... she's right in
front of me... relax...
Oh yeah... l'll see you this
evening... for sure... l promise...
She didn't see me...
c'mon speak louder on
the phone... concentrate...
Listen l'm trying my best...
give me one chance... please...
Omar... Oh my God! l can't believe
it's you... what are you doing here?
Wow! lt's been so long...
l know!
Oh... this is Danyal... my son...
Are you serious?
Hi Danyal... l'm Omar...
Hi Omar.
His looks just like Samir...
he has your eyes...
but otherwise...
he's just like Samir...
Really?
- Ya!
But l didn't marry Samir...
Look at your face!
you're talking like you were at our
wedding... you just disappeared...
Where is Samir?
l can't believe l let
you talk me into this...
Stop walking around
on this damn thing...
Mark... l brought you up
here to show
you how much effort
goes into this...
Six of my men will be
sticking to your
walls for the next six days...
6 days? l' can't have
these spidermen
crawling around my
windows for 6 days...
Why don't you hire more boys?
More boys means more money Mark...
Your rates are too high...
Nobody does as
complete a job as us Mark...
you know that. Think about it.
Alright... just get me
down from here alright...
Excuse me...
Yes Maya...
Samir... l want you
to talk to somebody...
Hi Samir...
Who is this?
How are you buddy?
Omar!
Sam... everything had
changed after 9/1 1 ...
you know how it was...
people stared at me on the
streets like l was a terrorist...
l was scared... after
that l went back to lndia...
when l tried to return...
l was denied a visa...
they didn't like
my name it seems... Omar.
l tried for months...
then l just gave up...
and now l'm finally here...
after years.
That's great.
And the moment l reached...
l bumped into you guys...
lsn't that strange?
Very strange.
l'm doing fine at the hotel...
and anyway my company will give me..
a service apartment in
two weeks... l'm okay.
Nothing doing...
you're going to stay
right here with us...
at least till you
get your apartment...
No Sam... l'm good at my hotel...
Okay... do as you like...
l can't force you...
come on... now you're upset.
Okay fine... l'll stay here.
No... if you're happy there then
l don't want to disturb you...
What happened?
Omar doesn't want to stay with us...
he's happy at his hotel...
- Really?
Hey... Now both of you are upset...
okay fine... l'll
shift here tomorrow...
Good... so it's final...
you're gonna stay with us.
come now... it's 1 o'clock...
let's go to sleep... we
all have to work tomorrow...
Not yet... l need to
settle an old score with him...
come on... You can't
take so much time...
What is going on here?
This is the limit now...
something is happening everyday now...
when the hell will
you guys stop all this?
You guys... what do you mean?
You guys... you Americans...
when will you learn that
this is not the way...
You seem to be very
interested in these issues?
Why wouldn't l be? lt
affects all of us...
don't you get affected?
Yes l do Omar... but what can we do
about it? lt's not in our control.
come on... l think if we want to...
then we can do a lot...
and l don't believe that
you're talking like such a loser...
Loser?
Yes! You had strong opinions
about things in college...
you took a stand on everything...
even when it was not necessary...
and look at you now...
What are you trying to say... Omar?
That we should go and
fight for these issues?
Are you crazy?
Sometimes l feel like...
Like what?
That one day... l'll just lea?e aside
everything and... just one day Sam...
One day... what?
Forget it... lets go to sleep.
come...
And this...
This? We can finish
this in the morning...
anyway you were losing...
Omar... my office is a block ahead...
yours is two blocks away...
Omar... come over if
you're free for lunch...
Sure... What about you Sam?
l'm sorry guys...
l have a lunch meeting.
Hey Maya, by the way...
what exactly do you do?
Let's meet for lunch...
l'll tell you everything... See you...
That's my office building...
Which floor?
- 1 8th...
Nice... let me come with you...
l have time for a cup of coffee.
Let me settle in first.
l mean.. l'm just 3 days old there.
l'm still an outsider...
you know what l mean...
Okay, never mind.
See you this evening.
See you... bye.
- Bye.
Good morning Mr. Aijaz... Your 9.30
appointment is waiting for you.
Ya... l'll just be there.
What happened Sam?
You forgot this in the car...
Thanks... how about coffee?
No... your appointment
waits for you... See you..
Tota!
Welcome back Omar...
Too much cheese on pasta.
My wife is an ltalian..
20 years... l have been telling her..
don't overdo the cheese...
l hate pasta...
there are some things in life
that you just cannot digest...
can you come to the point please.
Oh... you want me to
come to the point?
Ya...
This... take this with you when
you shift to their house today...
keep one in the living room
and one stays in your pocket...
What is it?
Micro transmitters.
This degrading job of
spying on my friends...
either l do it my
way or no way at all...
first your James Bonds
in those black SUVs...
and then this...
whatever you call it.
We can call it quits
right here right now...
Go ahead... arrest me...
slap me with your charges...
and get one of your own
cronies to do this job... l mean it!!
You could have said this without
smashing those transmitters...
They were Americans...
FBl... l was blindfolded...
it was a 9 or 1 0 hour long flight...
then a two hour drive...
then they stopped... got us down...
that's what l remember...
l had to climb a lot of stairs...
after which l was left alone...
..then some people came
and untied my blindfold...
come... it's okay.
Please continue Zilgai.
Three months later l was dumped...
at the detention centre right here.
What did they do to you
in detention?
What else... they would
forcibly strip us naked...
and assault us.
They would handcuff
us to the ceiling..
and keep us hanging that
way for up to 40 hours...
then... they would put
a hood on us...
and urinate on it... on our face...
they didn't let us go
to the toilet...
We were forced to relieve
ourselves... in our clothes...
Then... they'd say - your mother...
your sisters... are whores...
they would abuse us...
Then they would get a dog collar...
and tie it around our neck.
They would pull us by that leash...
all day long...
and grill us for 20
hours at a stretch...
cooperate with us... cooperate with
us... that's what they would say...
or else we'll send you to a place
from where you will never return...
Who was this man, Maya?
Zilgai... works with Samir...
Thanks.
he is a suspected terrorist...
l mean.. he was..
they illegally
detained him after 9/1 1 ...
His statement has been
presented at least 5 or 6 times,
but no one has bothered.
We're representing his case
against the government agencies...
he's pretty distressed...
You are doing a great job Maya...
But... there's injustice
happening against people..
and we human rights
workers can't stop the damage...
it gets pretty depressing sometimes.
Sorry.
'Trouble'
Hello... - Hey! You're
ha?ing lunch with Maya...
That's great... isn't it?
How do you know that?
Never ask an FBl
officer that... okay...
remember the gun l gave you...
don't forget...
you remember what it's for, right?
Yes, l remember...
l'm at your hotel.
l've made the payment.
So you can check out in the evening.
Wow
- Danny... Danyal...
cool... right dad?
Danny!
Where did you find this?
Go play with Mummy! And listen...
don't tell her about the gun...
okay?
Okay...
- Go.
What's this Omar?
Where did you find it?
l found it in Danyal's hands...
What is this doing here?
Relax Samir... it's mine...
Relax... what do you mean relax...
why do you need a gun?
l don't feel safe here Samir.
lt's for my safety.
Safety? What are you
talking about Omar?
You wouldn't know
what l want to do...
What?
Relax Sam... l still
ha?en't done anything...
What are you talking about Omar?
But yes... given a chance
l will go that way... once...
Have you gone crazy...
What are you guys doing?
l've been waiting for you...
dinner is ready...
Danyal's hungry and
l'm hungry... c'mon...
Get rid of this Omar.
l've hinted to him that
l want to be a terrorist...
yesterday l planted
that gun at his place...
he reacted like he's
ne?er seen a gun before.
Predictable...
he'll do exactly that...
Why? lf he is
operating a sleeper cell..
then wouldn't he say
something to me...
and even in his house there's
nothing remotely suspicious...
What do you think... he'd have
a jihad poster on his walls?
Have you met any of his friends yet?
What friends?
The ones whose
photographs l showed you...
No! that's exactly what l'm saying...
this is all nonsense...
Samir is not a terrorist...
please leave him alone... and me!
Do you think it's easy to
infiltrate a sleeper cell?
lf you were not his friend...
he wouldn't have let you
come even this close to him...
FBl has great
expectations from your friendship...
give one more push.
Thanks Bill. l'll send
you the memo tomorrow.
Let's go.
Thanks for coming Samir...
or l would have lost my way...
You're welcome... but why does your
company have a warehouse
at such a strange place?
Warehouses are
usually at such places...
just had to check it out once...
Omar l'm worried about you...
you talk about strange
things these days...
Hey man... you guys
want to buy some stuff?
No... we are fine...
l've got some pure cocaine...
and l'll give you a
really good deal...
No... we are good... excuse us...
come.
l said take it man...
Okay... give me some...
What's up with you guys?
first you say you don't
want it then you say you do...
Nothing mister... l just want to
buy some stuff and carry on...
l want no trouble.
You are shady man.
Are you with the cops man... huh?
Are you with the cops?
No relax... l'm not...
l'm not a cop...
c'mon gi?e me all
your money... c'mon...
Ok... Ok...
Both of you...
c'mon... let's go... c'mon...
Shit! Wha...
What the hell is wrong with you?
You killed him?
How long will we tolerate all this?
Tolerate what Omar?
He was a mugger...
But why did he only stop us?
Because... we were the only two
idiots there... don't you get it?
No Sam... it's not that simple...
l don't know man...
Are you out of your mind Omar?
Look Omar... l don't know
what you're up to...
or what you've gone through...
but l don't want this in my life...
l have a family...
Samir...
You'll have to leave my house...
Samir... what are you..
- Tomorrow.
l will explain to Maya that
you had to leave for training.
but you won't return after that...
l don't want you in my life Omar.
l don't want you.
c'mon... c'mon... get up...
O?er acting fool!
c'mon run, run... Maya... ball...
c'mon... c'mon...
l did it...
Ready?
- Ready...
And it's a strike! You're out...
No... but you were throwing so fast..
and it went down before
l was close to the ball...
it was like... you threw it...
...and it went pfuuuu...
right under... - Okay...
You know... in
college l always thought...
you'd be the first
amongst us to get married.
That could have happened had
l run after that villain...
What?
Don't you remember
that Hindi movie scene?
No?
The villain snatched the heroine's
bag... the hero chased him down...
so the heroine went with the hero...
and here l am...
still a secondary hero...
c'mon catch it...
No...
No..
Yesss...
Hey l saw that... don't spoil him...
Sorry to be a spoilsport Omar...
it's time to leave for the airport...
Why do have to go on a Sunday?
Leave tomorrow...
l have to go Maya...
l have a meeting tomorrow...
But l'll be back soon...
come back soon.
Bye!
Bye daddy!
- Bye sweetheart. Bye
What is this place Sam?
That's Zaheer... from Pakistan...
Malik... came via Germany
Yaqub... a Bangladeshi...
Yasir... Afghan...
You know how close we've
come to our mission...
why didn't you buy
the detonators from...
who you were asked to buy them from?
lf l give five hundred
thousand dollars to somebody...
Then l keep track of
what he is doing.
Who are these new suppliers?
They're Russians...
l'll return the money...
l had to give it back to someone
or they would have killed me...
l'll pay it back l swear...
lt's not about the money Yaqub...
your stupidity has got your
Russian friends curious about us...
they're asking about us
all over town.
lsn't that dangerous?
Samir... please don't do this..
l'm sorry Samir.. l'll pay it back.
Samir..
l'm..
Sorry..
listen to me.. Samir
Kill him Omar.
Shoot him.
Or else watch television and
keep cursing all your life...
Shoot him Omar.
You wanted a chance right?
Here's your chance... come
see this world closely...
Shoot him.
l said shoot him Omar.
What are you thinking?
How this all American dude like me..
became a terrorist..
Omar, 9/1 1 changed the world..
So how could it spare me..?
Ten days after 9/1 1 ..
l was on my way to
meet Maya in Washington..
Mr. Samir Sheikh..
Yes..
- Please come with me..
What's this about?
lt's just routine sir..
please right this way..
l've got a train to
catch in 1 5 minutes..
We're aware of your schedule sir..
Where exactly are we going?
Right around here please..
How can you.. how
can you do this to me?
Who are you? Give me
my clothes back!
Did you take these pictures
in August?
Screw you.. l'm not talking..
Did you take these pictures
in August?
How did you get these?
What's this about?
What specific reason did you have..
taking pictures of
the World Trade center?
These are for my paper on
architecture at the university.
They're pretty specific photos for
a school paper.. don't you think?
They're supposed to be..
they're supposed to be!
And we'?e got you
purchasing an online ticket at the..
Kiosk at Kinkos on 20th Street
on the 5th of September.. right?
Yes.. that's for my cousin..
what does that ha?e to do with this?
Mr Sheikh.. we think you're a
suspect in a terrorist attack.
What! Are you insane!
What rubbish is this?
l want my lawyer..
Answer what's being asked..
You can't do that!
Listen to me.. please understand..
l'm an American..
l want my lawyer..
l want my lawyer.. now!
On the basis of some photographs...
...l had clicked of
the World Trade centre..
during college and one airline ticket
they tried to label me a terrorist..
l never knew then..
but the FBl had detained
1 200 people..
like me and put them
in different jails..
We had just one thing in common..
Our religion..
Who did you take
these photographs for?
l told you..
ask my professor..
Who did you take
these photographs for?
They would beat us..
and scream at us..
over and over again..
Listen to me.. this is a mistake..
l'm an American..
Leave the cloth on him
for the night.
No.. no.. don't leave me
like this.. take this off..
take this off.. take
this off.. take this off..
you bastard take this off..
take this off..
lt seemed we would
ne?er make it out of here..
for months we lived in that
detention centre like animals..
Listen to me.. this is a mistake..
Wake up.. here's your food..
Don't you want to
fight for your dignity..?
When you get out of here,
go to the Brooklyn market..
and ask for New
York's best brown bread..
Brooklyn market.. New York's
best brown bread.. remember this..
Lights out.
And finally.. nine months later..
l was one of the four people..
released by the FBl
for lack of evidence..
come.. walk along with me
Why do you seem so frightened
come let me hide you
in my arms
come let me build a dream
in your eyes
Now that l'm beside you
and l'm one with your soul
l'll pick the agony from your way
Every passing moment
This love deepens even more
What happened?
Let's get married.
What..?
Will you marry me?
No.. Maya.. what are you..
c'mon Sam
This is the first time in history
that a girl is down on her knees...
asking a boy.. please
don't spoil the moment..
Why not..?
Because l'm not the same person
that l used to be in college..
l don't care Samir..
l will be viewed with
suspicion all my life..
because of what happened to me.
l don't care..
l don't care.. what happens to me..
as long as we're together..
Don't stop as you walk along
lf you are stopped tomorrow
by the shadows of the past
l'm with you always
You are never alone
ln your loneliness
Don't stop as you walk along
lf you are stopped tomorrow
by the shadows of the past
l'm with you always
You are never alone
ln your loneliness
Now that l'm beside you
and l'm one with your soul
l'll pick the agony from your way
Every passing moment
This love deepens even more
come.. walk along with me
Why do you seem so frightened
come let me hide you
in my arms
come let me build a dream
in your eyes
Now that l'm beside you
and l'm one with your soul
l'll pick the agony from your way
Every passing moment
This love deepens even more
Now that l'm beside you
and l'm one with your soul
l'll pick the agony from your way
Every passing moment
This love deepens even more
Maya tried her best..
but something had died inside me..
l couldn't remember anything..
couldn't concentrate on anything..
l would tremble while speaking..
l was good for nothing..
l didn't know what to do?
Alright.. and there you go.
Hi can l help you..
Hi.. can l have two
turkey sandwiches..
Sure.. would you like
white or brown bread?
White or brown bread?
**When you get out of here, go to
the Brooklyn market and ask for..**
New York's best brown bread..
Don't you want to
fight for your dignity..?
Brooklyn market and ask for
New York's best brown bread..
Thank you..
l want New York's best brown bread..
3.45..
Yes?
l want New York's best brown bread..
New York's best brown bread..
3.45..
Thank you..
How much for this?
But l went back..
again and again..
New York's best brown bread..
3.45..
Thank you..
New York's best brown bread..
3.45..
Thank you..
New York's best brown bread..
3.45..
Who told you about the bread?
l was at the metropolitan detention
center and this old man was there.
What old man?
l don't know his name.
He never spoke except once when
he told me about the brown bread..
What took you so long to come?
They kept asking me questions..
and l kept answering them..
l told them everything..
they had a different world..
they had another motive..
but they were giving me a
chance to fight for my dignity..
and that's what l was
looking for.. that's all l needed..
l decided to tell Maya everything..
l had decided my course of action..
and she was free to choose hers..
But when l got home..
l'm pregnant. l'm so excited!
That moment l decided at
that l will keep Maya..
and my child away from
this new world of mine..
l became the Sam
from college for Maya..
because Samir had
found his purpose..
Yes Maya..
No.. Omar's meeting got cancelled..
we're coming back together..
Yes.. we're coming home.. okay bye..
Maya doesn't know anything?
She shouldn't either..
But that guy Zilgai.. he was
with Maya.. is he with you as well?
No.. he's just
employed in my company..
he's extremely emotional..
not quite the right man
for such work.
c'mon let's go home..
Shoot him.. l want my lawyer.. now!
Shoot him Omar..
they hit us all night..
how did he become a terrorist..
how can you do this to me..
they kept shouting.. again
and again.. like animals..
Why would you do that?
You are providing the
technical know-how and the workers..
and you want just 30 per cent of
the profits. What's the catch?
Let's just say l'm a man
in a hurry..
l need to be at least 1 0 years old
in this business..
to even qualify for the bidding..
and l'm just 4 years
into this business.
But your company has been
around for generations..
and you've got a clean reputation
So l become your front?
And make money and
bounce back Steve..
let's face it.. the
recent accidents on..
..your site haven't been
great for your business..
you are on the verge of a shutdown..
this is your chance to get back..
You are not doing this to help
me out.. so what's the real deal?
These buildings are
prestigious Steve..
they mean more than
money to me in the long run.
l pay 70 per cent of the costs..
you keep 70 per cent of the profits..
can't get better than this.
Okay Sam.. l'll call you.
You did the right
thing at the right time..
Right thing.. l killed a
man who l didn't even know..
how is that the right thing?
lf you hadn't.. his own
people would have killed him..
if they spared him.. we
would have killed him..
because had he been alive..
he would have been responsible for
many deaths.. and you know this now.
Why didn't you tell me that you
had detained Samir.. for 9 months?
Because l didn't want you
to sympathise..
..with Samir when you met him..
because nothing..
nothing justifies terrorism.
How easily you said that..
do you ha?e any idea what
these guys went through?
And after all that..
9 months later you tell them..
sorry kids..
we made a small mistake!
lf someone commits a mistake..
does that justify Samir
becoming a terrorist? ls it?
After being tortured the
way they were in detention..
no sane man can
remain what he used to be.
Precisely..
that's what l'm saying..
Samir was not a terrorist..
but he is one now.
Yes..
but it's you who have
made him a terrorist.
Him and all the others..
ha?en't you?
Omar.. l am a Muslim..
and it hurts me to see
another Muslim go astray..
this clich has been repeated over
50 times that lslam favours peace..
but in reality if you favour lslam..
then you favour peace.
Yes l agree that this country
has committed a lot of excesses..
a lot of mistakes.. and we must take
responsibility for these faults..
but you cannot overlook the
positive values of this nation..
l'm a Muslim and
yet l have been given
responsibility for a
sensitive case like this.
That is only possible here..
you shouldn't forget that we
arrived here as immigrants..
and now we have found a place here..
we've got our freedom..
and its to protect this
freedom that l'm doing all this..
Omar.. we have come half way.
This hostility towards Muslims..
that you sense in this
corner of the world..
or probably any
other part of the world..
it's now up to a Muslim to transform
that to sense of goodwill..
maybe you and l are
here to do just that..
Alright.. is your crew ready?
- Yes..
we'll get a third level
up on the scaffolding..
get your guys working
on the brick today..
there are those 20 windows
for you to do right over here..
you guys can handle that today?
we need to scale it back down..
otherwise we're going to
overshoot everything..
so dig up this foundation..
get back to work on
this section right here..
Samir.. yes l'm done
with the meeting..
l will see you in 40 minutes..
okay cool.. bye..
Don't fail us..
find out what is
their plan.. and when..
l don't know what or when it is..
but l know Samir..
whatever it is and
whenever it happens..
it will shake up all of you..
Sam.. Steve here..
Hi Steve..
Listen.. l assume you heard
about the accident on my site today?
Yes Steve.. l know
you're servicing those..
important buildings very soon..
l'll send my workers across to you..
Sam.. listen it's the only
opportunity l ha?e left..
l'm counting on you..
Trust me.. l won't let you down..
Ya and l'll give you
all the details of..
the workers for that
building's security clearance..
l'll personally supervise
the job.. See you soon..
Who are you talking to..?
l'll have to call you back..
ya.. thanks.. ya..
Russians. They're saying that
Yaqub gave them two instead of three.
Tell them they will get
the remaining money today..
l want to meet them today..
do you understand..
Show me your phones guys..
show me your phones..
we've been planning
this for five years..
and now we're really
close to our objective..
From now on l'll handle
all the dealings, you got it?
Omar..
your phone..
these phones are really dangerous..
anyone can locate us.
l'll give you new
phone numbers tomorrow.
You got the money?
You said 300 thousand dollars
and my man gave you
that money in cash.
Now you want more?
Last week.. gas sold
for 4 dollar a gallon..
this week it's 4 dollars and a half..
you still buy, don't you?
So prices change.
They told me.. you
guys are a dedicated lot..
you could spend any amount of
money to further your cause..
go to any extent.
Yes.. you are right..
we can go to any extent.
Don't shoot him!
He will guide us to the detonators..
How could l call you when
he had thrown away my phone?
And you told me not to
keep a record of your number..
l have not sent you
there to sleep at night..
if the police get a whiff
of what he did last night..
then our whole operation is
finished.. we're finished.
Why has he changed your phone..
what is he up to?
l don't know..
Then please find out.. quickly..
and tell me..
and don't call me with your new
phone.. Samir could be tracking it.
That's great.. you track my old
phone.. he tracks the new phone..
what the hell do l do
with these goddamn phones?
This was a small example..
what we will deal with is
going to be way more powerful..
And executed just as easily.
With this phone.. but how?
Exactly how l showed you Zaheer..
don't ask me dumb questions.
These phones will be
used as detonators..
when c4 plastic
explosives are stuck on them..
then l can trigger
these with my phone..
and this phone stays with me.
But why?
But where and when?
You don't need to know
that right now.
Zilgai don't worry..
we'll take this case further..
they cannot deport you..
this is just a normal routine.
No Maya.. this is
neither normal.. nor routine..
this is happening because
my skin colour is different..
my face is different
and my name is different.
Don't be silly Zilgai..
all of you have developed
this persecution complex.
l know they have been
wrong with you once..
but that doesn't mean
they are your enemies..
Those circumstances were difficult.
Am l responsible if the
circumstances were difficult..
you are lucky
if you think that way..
but l have to live and
face this insult everyday.
At times..
l feel like..
Feel like what.. Zilgai?
There come the bastards..
goddamn cops..
to harass us.
They won't do any such thing..
don't get excited..
Must be a routine check
or something.
Why were you driving so fast?
can l have your name please?
Mohammed Hanif Zilgai..
Father's name Latif
Mohammed Zilgai.. anything else?
License and registration
please sir..
Why officer...
we do no any mistake...
Zilgai... just do as he says...
Maya.. l know the
worth of these bastards...
Excuse me sir. Licence
and registration please...
Sorry officer... what's this about?
l'm just doing my job ma'am...
you guys ran a traffic light...
Would really appreciate if your
friend here would just cooperate...
Uh.. okay.. sure
Here.. take this..
l told you.. they'll
harass us.. bastards.
Don't overreact Zilgai..
just shut up.
Sir.. would you please
step out of the car please..
What's your problem now..
leave me alone..
Out of the car and keep your
hands where l can see them.
Officer.. is this really necessary?
l think you are over reacting.
What the..!
Ma'am l advise you to stay
in the car.
Maya.. stay in the car..
l'm used to this..
Why are you used to it then?
Officer, is this really necessary?
Listen he doesn't
understand English!
That's fine.. turn around
face the car.. do it now!
Why did you come out?
Shut up Zilgai.. now
let me do the talking..
just doing my job ma'am..
you had to go and turn
this whole thing around.
She's clear..
can we go now officer.. please.
l'm sorry..
Bye baby.
- Bye.
Bye
- Bye..
Just a week after the
mayor had released..
reports showing a decrease
in crime related incidents..
in downtown New York,
a police officer has
been murdered in the city.
ln a shocking incident,
a Sergeant..
of the New York Police
Department was found..
dead last night under
gruesome circumstances.
Apparently his neck was broken.
The motive is unknown.
What happened Maya?
Omar..
Oh God!
Zilgai!
The commissioner has promised
to track down the killer..
Within the next 48 hours.
What?
Zilgai!
Hey!
Get down on the ground!
Stop!
Freeze!
Get down!
Down!
Stop!
Freeze.. He's over here..
Just relax..
get down on your knees..
Keep your hands where
we can see them.
Just relax..
No!!
How the hell did this happen?
Where's Maya?
She's at the police station..
for some questioning..
The mission is off.
- What?
There's no other option..
Zilgai was employed in
my maintenance company..
Maya was also
fighting his legal case..
would you want the police to
arrive here in their investigation..
while we're planting bombs..
it's risky to do
any such thing now..
instead we'll begin
work on the new contract..
of that building starting tomorrow.
Mission cancelled!
You're joking right..?
Wrong.. it's me who
has become a joke..
for days l've been
spying on my friends..
l've been lying to them..
l've even murdered a man..
to uncover something that
will never be revealed now.
We've made a mistake
once by detaining him..
if we arrest him this time
without foolproof evidence..
the human rights people
will create a huge scene..
that's why l need you
even more than before.
l think now Samir will wait.
For what..?
For the NYPD to cool down..
this country has forgotten
even the Kennedy assassination..
this guy was just an ordinary cop..
and after that..
Samir will rise again.
Excuse me..
l'll pay the bill and come.
Omar.. Omaaar..
Sorry Maya.. l'm in
an office meeting..
l can' talk..
Taxi!
Maya?
Who are you?
You scared me Maya..
Who are you..?
Maya.. you know who l am..
give me the gun..
Are you here to hurt Samir..?
Why would l hurt him?
What will l achieve by
doing that? Sam is my friend.
Omar.. stop it! Stop pretending.
We both know who Sam is
and what he does.
What..?
Yes Omar..
l know what Samir is doing..
Does he know that you know this?
No.. answer me first.
Why did you lie that you
were not on the 20th street..
who was that man with you..
he's with the cops right?
l saw him at
Zilgai's accident site too..
Maya listen..
What do you want to do to Samir?
Maya.. first let's get out of here..
l'll tell you everything..
No.. tell me now..
Maya.. do you honestly
belie?e that..
l will let anything
happen to you or Sam?
No.. let's get out of here and
l will tell you everything..
Maya l promise you..
You can't do this to me..
Please.. l beg of you..
Please put the gun down..
please..
You have to trust me Maya..
lf you knew.. then why
didn't you stop him?
Because Samir didn't tell me..
l found out.
l always felt that if he's
not sharing it with me..
then he'll give it up
one day and come back..
each day l lived with the
fear that he would tell me..
because as long as he hides it..
l have a hope that he
will one day leave it all..
and that's the hope that
l have been living on..
and l can do anything for it.
Then help me Maya..
we can bring him back.
How can l help you?
You work for the FBl, the same people
who stripped Samir of his dignity.
Please Maya.. Samir has aborted his
operation after Zilgai's incident..
this is our only chance..
We can get him off this track..
Maya.. trust me.. please.
How can l trust you?
Why should l trust you..?
Because.. l..
you know how l feel about you..
and l don't want anything
to happen to you or Samir..
Maya.. please trust me..
l'm here to help Samir..
Please trust me..
Help me.
l need a guarantee.. in writing..
from the FBl..
that they won't kill Samir.
How could you tell his wife?
What kind of undercover operation
is this.. undercover from who?
The only people who don't seem to
know what's going on here is us..!
Gibson.. he had to tell her..
And now you want
amnesty for this terrorist?
When he's called off the
attack he was planning..
FBl can't kill him for nothing..
Look sonny.. you don't tell me
what FBl can and cannot do..
That's the problem with you
Americans.. you just don't listen to
anyone.. What's he saying? - Nothing..
You have my personal guarantee..
you will get that letter..
but Maya will have to come to the
FBl office tomorrow to meet me..
Look Roshan.. you better
know what you're doing..
Ya.. she's coming to meet us.. ya..
Okay.. happy..?
l don't trust this man..
Okay.. and now let's see how much
you can eat.. wow.. you like it..
see this.. ya.. c'mon c'mon..
suck it in..
lt's okay Maya.. it's okay..
Don't worry.
Poor Zilgai..
couldn't handle the pressure..
Ya..
Where's Omar?
l don't know..
Dad made me pasta mamma..
He loves his pasta.
Hey.. there you are..
where were you?
Ya.. l went to the police
to find out about Zilgai..
And what did they say?
lt's an open and shut case for them..
a frustrated illegal immigrant commits
murder in a moment of madness..
that's just about it..
Okay.. Danny.. time to sleep..
Night-night mamma..
Mommy is coming in 5 minutes.
That's the aeroplane..
Say goodnight..
Goodnight Danyal..
- Night-Night mamma.
Good night my lo?e..
Maya you will have to
go to the FBl office..
tomorrow to meet their
senior officers.. okay
Why?
Maya they want to meet you
before giving the guarantee letter..
Samir has cancelled the mission..
this is our only chance..
we can show him the letter.. maybe
he gives it all up when he sees it..
Maya.. did Samir tell you about..
the new project that
we're starting tomorrow..
Really?
- Ya.
That's great.
l'm really excited about it..
for a new project..
for a new beginning..
That's true..
- cheers!
a new beginning.
Morning..
- How you doing?
Good.
- Alright..
Hello Steve. Hey it's William..
are you sending up
any new guys today?
Okay.. okay.. thank you.
Go ahead..
This is what makes our
company special Omar..
we clean everything from
the roof to the sewer..
Morning
She has to understand this..
She's here..
Hi Maya.. l'm Roshan
lt was you that day.. with Omar.
Ya.. it was me..
Eric.. Danny.. you guys take
that side. We will take the front.
This is it.. the main
drainage pipe of this building..
You're sure..?
We'll know soon..
What's that? - This brush basically
cleans up all blockages in the pipe..
But.. so far he's done nothing
that makes him a terrorist..
and it's possible that he
may never do any such thing..
you're just assuming
that he is up to something.
Had it been just an assumption
l wouldn't have called you here..
lt's more than a guess, Maya.
That's why we need your help..
l'm ready to help.. but l need a
guarantee that you won't kill Samir..
l'm prepared to give
you that guarantee..
What was that Zaheer..?
You get the letter.. l'll sign it..
Alright..
Samir is a genius.. that's a brilliant
way to send up c4 explosi?es..
What does that mean..?
That means.. that the
plan was never cancelled.
What building is it?
That, only God knows..
No, l need to know
which building it is.
Stop..
Ya..
- Samir is doing something today..
there's a bomb planted in
a building somewhere here..
Hello.. Omar.. hello..
Hello.. hello..
Hello..
- Yes..
What building is it? - l don't know
which building it is...
but there's a bomb planted
in a building here somewhere..
Hello.
- Omar..
Yes Maya..
- l saw Samir here...
What?
Where did you see him?
- At the FBl building...
What!!
Omar.. hello?
c'mon Omar.. tell me.. tell me..
l know which building it is.
Sir! Sir.. stand back..
l need to meet agent Roshan..
Tell your guards to let me in first..
We don't have time.. tell me quick!
l just need to meet him
for a minute..
What is he saying?
Let me in first..
l don't have time.. tell me..
FBl Headquarters!
All of you are sitting on the bomb!
We are the target!
What?
We have to evacuate.. now!
Move! Move! Go.. go!
How do you know it's this building?
Because Samir is in this building..
he's cleaning your windows.
And he's using the same
phone bomb l told you about..
Send snipers.. we'll shoot
him before he blows us..
Shut up Gibson!
l can stop Samir.. if you give me
a chance to speak to him please..
Why will he listen to you..
Because he doesn't know
that Maya is also here...
maybe if l tell him
that he will believe me..
..please don't waste time..
Okay.. let's go.. come on..
Move it!
Sam..
Omar..
You can't press that trigger Samir..
What are you doing here?
Sam.. l am an undercover FBl agent..
What?
- l will explain everything...
just give me the trigger..
we don't have much time..
What happened to you before won't
happen again.. please trust me..
Trust you?
l could have planted these bombs
anywhere Omar.. on any soft target..
l need the choppers
in here right now..
l need the snipers
in here.. let's move!
But my fight is with the FBl..
so that they think
twice before labeling..
..just about anyone a terrorist..
How will that help Sam?
You'll blow this building up..
and they will detain ten more
Samir Sheikhs in that investigation..
and they will undergo
exactly what you went through..
this will never end Sam.
What did you do Omar?
Sam.. give me the trigger..
l promise you nothing will happen..
Yes Omar.. nothing will happen..
but only till the time
that l have this trigger..
they know if they shoot me..
l will press the trigger.
you screwed it all up Omar..
you screwed it all up.
No Sam.. l have a letter..
Yes.. and these are your postmen..
don't be stupid Omar..
you know how this will end.
Sam you can't press the trigger..
l promise nothing will happen Sam..
Maya is in this building Sam..
Sam..
Give me that trigger..
l know everything.. whatever
it is.. we'll make it alright..
we'll figure it out.. together..
please.. l promise nothing is going
to happen.. give me the trigger..
l kept you away from this
world for so many years..
only to be able to come back
everyday to you and Danyal..
l know.. l know.. baby please..
come back.. come home..
Just come back.. just
leave this.. please..
That's what l wanted Maya..
to come back home for good..
to you.. l didn't want you to know..
Sam you haven't done
anything so far..
Sam listen to me..
look at me.. look at me.
No Maya..
there's nothing left for me now..
Nothing's over baby..
nothing's over.. please..
just leave this.. all
of this.. listen to me..
Danyal needs you..
l need you.. please Sam.. Sam..
l'm sorry baby..
l love you..
Sam..
Sam!
Fire!
No!
That jersey no 3.. your
son plays like a real pro!
Man!
Thank you.
Safe!
For how long will
you not speak to me?
congratulations.. l read in the
papers.. you got a commendation..
Omar.. it's not me or
you that killed Samir..
the path that Samir chose is
responsible for his death..
And Maya..? What was her fault?
No one was at fault Omar..
everyone was right
where they were..
its just that the time
was not right.
And in such times people make
wrong choices and so do countries..
Both suffer, the
people and the country.
That's what happened.
What did we get out of this
undercover operation of yours?
Two of my friends end up dead..
and you get a medal. What else?
The day you have an answer
to this is the day we'll talk.
The answer is in front of you..
A Muslim boy whose
father was a terrorist..
is playing in an American team..
and they're hailing him as a hero..
that's what we got..
that's what we achieved.
This is a new generation Omar..
it's come away from
the memories of 2001 ..
and l think we should also move on..
it's high time.
l told you.. l'm the champ!
Yes champ.. you are the champ.
Give me a five..
Who's that?
He's an old friend.
Who.. your friend or Papa's friend?
Well.. let's say..
l'm your friend champ..
High five?
Are you hungry champ?
Yeah.. let's go..
Alright let's go then..
Aren't you coming?
Of course Danyal.. he is coming..
Great.. lets go..
Do you like Pasta?
What baby?
- Do you like pasta?
Yeah..
l love Pasta baby!
l love pasta..
Let's go..
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/mmjc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles