Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Ladies and gentlemen!
Please welcome the man who knows
what you're gonna do before you do it!
The amazing,
Frank Cadillac!
This is for the world peace.
Good evening. Welcome to the
beautiful downtown Las Vegas.
How many people are here
from the orient? Raise your hands.
You, sir...
Where are you from?
No, wait, wait...
Don't tell me.
I'm sensing,
you must have soul.
You're a soul man.
Why don't you share with
everyone where are you from?
- Korea.
- How about that, folks?
May I assume
this charming young lady...
...is your daughter?
- She is my wife!
Well, of course she is!
What happens in
Vegas stays in Vegas.
- What's your name?
- Yhun-Kihong.
Yhun-Kihong.
Would you be kind enough to join
me up on the stage please?
Are you serious about this guy?
This is a joke?
Going behind some mimes
and clowns while we're in it?
Yhun-Kihong.
What if I told you that
that pretty necklace your wearing...
...has a broken catch and on my count
of three, will fall in your drink.
Wouldn't that be something?
Wouldn't that just blow your mind?
- Yeah.
- Yes. Wouldn't it blow all your minds!
Three, two, one...
...now.
Somebody said "spooky"?
Wait a minute, look at your glass.
Where did it go?
Yhun-Kihong, why don't you
look inside my pocket?
Reach in. Dig deep.
Let's have a big hand
for Yhun-Kihong.
Well... that's magic folks.
And that's why I'm here.
They probably seen
a lot of those shows.
Mentalists,
magicians, illusionists...
It would be shocked to know
that sometimes...
...not often, but sometimes,
it's the real deal.
Masquerading as an act...
...hiding behind
a few 50 dollar tricks...
...hiding in a plain sight.
Because if the magician
doesn't do that,...
...the alternative is impossible
for others to live with.
Anyway. Wednesday nights
The Back Page doesn't pay very well.
So I gamble.
But I don't play against other people,
only against the house.
So, no mega Jack Pots,
no wash outs.
The idea is to be unnoticed.
That way I can keep coming back.
I'm not a God.
I can't see everyone's future,
only my own.
And only within 2 minutes,...
...except for when I saw her.
But we'll come back to that.
There is no pattern to this guy,
he is all over the map.
He's not counting,
not enough the top of that deck.
Wait a minute.
Isn't it that "Two Bit Magic Act"
that called Back Page.
- What's his name?
- Cadillac.
Yes, Frank Cadillac.
Is he pulling tricks on us?
Is that legal?
He can't trick the deck.
I'm telling you. That little prick
knows what's coming.
If he's really knocking a system
why's he not betting more.
That's gonna be my second question.
Look at that.
He is looking at us.
It's like he can hear us.
- What table was that?
- 27.
It's Roybal, send security to table 27!
Coming right now!
Your bets please.
Here is the thing
about the future.
Every time you look at it,...
...it changes.
Because you looked at it,...
...and that changes
everything else.
Nine thousand and seventeen.
Empty the drawer.
Move!
Drop the gun, now!
Nine thousand and seventeen.
Drop the gun, step back.
Its his gun.
He's gonna shoot you people.
Step back,
we'll decide this right now.
What's he doing?
Security the doors, elevators, escalators
every way out of this damn place, now!
Clayman! Seal off the Black Jack tables!
Sullivan, linkup with Roybal!
- We are on the floor! On the floor!
- Bring the view of the cameras!
That way! This way!
He's right next to
the ten dollars slots. Aisle 14.
There he is! Behind you!
Your left. Turn around!
He's right between you.
He's in the mensroom!
Near the Gameshot! Gameshot!
Davis, where the hell is he?
Black t-shirt, straw hat,
heading towards the entrance.
Come on, let's go.
Call Vegas PD.
He just stole a silver Charger,
tag 585-G4S.
- Drop the gun, step back!
- It's his gun.
He was in the top of gambling bureaux's
wish list about 2 months ago.
And what he does
has nothing to do with luck.
It's a definite ability. Look at him!
He knows exactly what to do not get caught.
Can you explain that to me?
No, I can't explain it, Kelly,
nor do I have the time.
The Russian Federation has a 10 kiloton
nuclear munition, unaccounted for...
- I understand that.
- I'm not sure you do.
We need every agent available
beating the street.
That bomb was stolen
5 weeks ago.
We have just been informed of it now.
Which means it could be parked
under this truck for all we know.
I need actionable intelligence.
Not paranormals
and bullshit magicians.
With all due respect sir,
this bullshit magician...
...achieved paranormal advanced awareness,
it's statistically impossible.
You let me bring him in,
and you get what you want.
5 days, Kelly.
That's it.
Get me the head of casino security.
- You ROYbal?
- It's RoyBAL.
- Whatever.
- Who are you?
Cavanaugh, take a walk.
Hey, Roybal. This isn't
a pissing contest. Come on.
What did you do?
You bought a new car?
- Stole it.
- Oh, look it is.
20 minutes to walk 20 steps.
Well, that's what you get
from two packs a day.
I got you two sandwiches.
Two sandwiches?
That's plenty grand.
Come on, take it. I love you.
Oh, Jesus.
How can I repay you?
Must be a big
to drive this thing.
Chief Roybal,
Special Agent Ferris.
I'm sure Agent Cavanaugh
has explained to you...
...everything you say is has been
concealed. You only admit...
...it can be used against you.
Do we understand each other?
Sure.
- Tell me about Cris Johnson.
- I don't know who that is.
How about Frank Cadillac?
You chased him in the casino tonight.
- He stole a car from valet parking.
- Yes, yes I know Cadillac.
I thought he was cheating us at cards,
the next thing I know...
...he's tackling some guy waving a gun.
- The gun wasn't his.
The man he tackled was
one of the two casino killings in Reno.
He is in custody now.
Come on, I'll show you something.
You remember this?
Oh, yeah, of course I do.
We were saying that
he was looking right at us.
- How did you get this?
- Now think carefully.
What were you talking about
when he looked up?
We were saying if he has a system
why wasn't he betting more.
You sure you weren't doing
or saying anything else?
Just going down and pick him up...
And right then? That's when
he looked up? Very specific.
That's what I said.
He looked up. Really.
So he doesn't have to be there to do it.
Once you entered his consciousness,...
...he can pick it up.
Is that to work the system?
Thank you.
We're finished.
Done some good here, Mr Roybal.
None of these up for the discussion.
As far as your concerned...
...Chris Johnson never existed.
That's going to be difficult, considering
a hundred cameras saw him at the casino.
Don't worry.
The tapes have been destroyed.
Hey! Is she single?
Chris, you can keep stealin' cars
and have been chasin'...
...but that's not a life.
And you gotta forget this girl
that you keep seeing in your head.
No, I am not going anywhere
until I meet her.
What supposed
she doesn't show up?
She already did.
At the diner.
10 min. after 8.
You've got a couple of hours.
How about a game of pool?
Allright, Irv.
We'll shoot some pool.
We timed every hand
in the Black Jack.
The longest was 89 seconds
and Jonhson pulled 6 cards 21.
So we know he can stay
at least a minute and a half ahead.
I had a text from a radio
frequency spectrum analysis.
He came up dry.
He is not receiving
any form of electronic help.
At one point there was a
2 minutes and 16 seconds delay.
He never backed.
Just got up and walked away.
Maybe 2.16 is too long
and he can't see that far.
Narrows the window
a little bit any way.
We got him.
Vegas PD got a lo-jack hit
on the stolen vehicle.
Listen.
About that girl.
When you looked at the clock,
did you happen to see a calendar?
Because...
...its could be 10 years
from now she gets hungry.
It's gotta be soon.
I never seen further ahead
than two minutes.
Except for her.
And what do you think
the reason is for that?
I don't know.
Maybe she doesn't scare easy.
Maybe she is the one.
Well, when you get like this...
...there is no talking to you.
- She is almost here.
- What happened to the diner?
Somebody else. A cop.
A cop?
Well, then you gotta go.
Wait, I wanna see how much she knows,
what she wants from me.
Chris Johnson.
Still here huh?
Where else would I be?
Special Agent Ferris.
Next time steal a car without lojack.
Can we speak privately?
It's ok, Irv, go ahead.
Thanks.
I'm sure you know why I'm here.
Cause you're the man who knows
what I'm going to do before I do it. Right?
The show, right. Right.
I saw you there.
- Wonderful. Do you like magic tricks?
- Yeah, yeah I do. Like your...
...magic tricks, clairvoyance,
whatever you callin' it.
Let's talk something hard.
A stolen nucleur munition has being smuggled
into the U.S. and may -in fact- already be here.
I want you to look ahead and tell me
where it is gonna be deployed.
I think you got the wrong guy.
It's a magic act.
You gonna stick with that story.
Because millions of lives are at risk and
you could maybe prevent a major catastrophe.
On a practical note. We are standing
in front of a stolen vehicle...
...and you are wanted for assault
involving a weapon at the casino.
That was an accident. He had a gun
and he was going to shoot two people...
Yeah?
How did you know that?
The deed goes unpunished, does it?
I can fix your legal problems
but first you gotta step up...
...otherwise your next magic show
is gonna be in Fulsom State Prison.
It's ironic but...
...people like you who try to help
had been torturing me.
In the full sense of the word
since I was 3 years old.
What do they call it?
Oh, yeah.
Observed play therapy.
Featuring a marathon 36 hours...
..."can you guess
the next flash card" game?
So, please,
leave me alone...
...and let me live
some semblence of a normal life.
I would love to indulge
your feelings. But I'm dealing...
...with a slightly larger picture
right now.
Now you can exercise your responsibility
to help your fellow men...
...or I will exercise that
responsibility for you.
You're right, I gotta go.
He's gone, right?
I missed him by seconds tonight.
Excuse me honey,
can you get off my car?
Yeah. Thank you. Jesus.
- Sr. ROYbal?
- It's RoyBAL. Can I help you man?
I have a few questions
if this is a good time?
Gaming Commission is after hours,
you guys should be in a strip club, come on.
What can you tell us
about Chris Johnson?
I don't know
who your talking about.
Let me rephrase the question.
- Here you go, honey.
- Thanks.
Excuse me.
Hello!
I noticed you're alone too.
Do you mind if I join you?
Actually I do.
Sorry to bother you but I have
a question about the coffee,...
...the bean they use...
Isn't that something you should
probably ask your waitress?
Yes, it is.
Excuse me, do you have a light?
I don't smoke.
- Here you go, honey.
- Thanks.
Please. Don't.
- Hi, Liz.
- Did you follow me here Kendal?
No, no. I just thought
we could talk.
You know we got
really nothing to talk about.
And I told you that
3 weeks ago.
Liz, come on. I had an off day,
just give me another shot.
It's not gonna happen, OK?
So maybe you should just go.
Do you know how hard
it was to find you?
I was at your apartment,...
...I tried the Starbox in Lexington,
I was at the dry cleaner...
All I'm asking for is a few minutes
of your time, so we can work things out!
Ok, Jesus!
You're stalking me now.
Don't! Don't say that, please.
That's a terrible thing to say...
Let go of me, Kendal.
Look, I just... I thought we can talk.
You know, maybe we can take a drive...
...and now your ruining it.
Your hurting me.
Kendal?
I think your having another off day.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm her future.
Really?
Hi, my name is Chris.
You okay, Kendal?
The thing is I feel connected to you
and I don't know the reason why.
Now listen.
I think it's only fair that
you pay for the lady's breakfast.
What are you having?
Pecan pies are amazing.
Excuse me.
I can pay for my own breakfast.
And you know what?
You two, work things out.
Your hurting me.
Kendal?
I think your having another off day.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm her future.
Really?
Incoming.
- God damn it, Kendal!
- What? Don't point at me. This is your fault.
Get out of here!
Will somebody please call the cops?
I'm so sorry.
Are you OK?
Let me help you.
Come on, lets get you
cleaned up.
Come on.
OK.
- I'm seeing some stars.
- Yeah?
I am Liz.
Chris.
You must have a death wish
getting involved in that.
- Here. Just...
- OK.
OK. Hold it there.
- Feel a bit.
- OK.
- It well.
- What well?
Your luck.
It's gonna change.
What are you?
A leprechaun?
Do leprachaun's get punched in the face
or have their car stolen?
- Your car was stolen?
- Yeah.
I'm hoping they find it today.
Supposed to be in Flagstaff.
Hey, is this tooth loose here?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
It hurts.
Listen, maybe I can give you a ride.
- I'm gonna go that way.
- That would really be helpful, Liz.
Thank you.
- I do have to make a stop though.
- It's OK.
And it may take a few hours,
so cool with that?
Hey, look.  If you're uncomfortable
with this all, I'll take a bus.
No, no, no. Its fine, its fine.
You're not a psycho.
Right?
Because the first psycho vibrate
you're out of the car.
- OK. Yes Ma'am.
- OK.
Deal.
It's amazing. Wasn't it?
I end up in a diner where you are
and both heading in the same direction.
I don't know if I can call
that amazing, but...
Destiny.
That's what it really is.
OK. I'm starting to get
that psycho voice.
Ah, no...
You don't believe in destiny?
Well, even if it does exist,
I don't think I want to know.
I mean if every move we make
is pre-ordained and...
...what is the point of that
life is supposed to be a surprise?
Isn't it?
It would be nice.
Yeah.
So he came in twice a day
for a week at exactly 9 past 8?
Yeah, he would stay a few minutes,
have a martini and then he'd go.
Until today
when he met that lady.
Did you find anything strange
about that?
Not strange enough
to call the police.
We got a regular who counts
the cornflakes in his bowel...
...it has to be an even number.
- Got any cameras?
- Inside? No.
Outside?
No.
Noticed what kind of car
he was driving...
...maybe overhear
where they were going?
I don't know what car but
they were heading up Flagstaff.
- Flagstaff?
- That's what they said.
Got another regular. She's always on a diet.
Brings in a scale to weigh the salad dressing.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Guy knows we are after him,
he still risks coming here.
8 or 9. Twice a day.
He didn't know if it's day or night,
just the time. He was waiting for her.
Allright. There is a traffic cam
over there, the bank,...
...7-11 across the street.
Run all the tapes. We will get lucky...
...and catch them at the wide.
Hey, remember Roybal,
the casino chief?
He had his throat cut last night
after getting a knee cap shot off.
You're telling me this now?
We just talked him about Johnson.
- Hey, I just found out.
- Allright.
- Local weapon?
- Dead end.
Forensic's came up emtpy.
Not a hair or a fibre.
Somebody wants information.
Now, next time anything happens...
...relevant to Johnson,
I want to know right away.
- I don't care if it's a paper cut.
- OK, boss.
The head of casino security.
What did you learn from him?
For a macho guy,
he screams like a girl.
He was questioned by federal agents,
looking for Chris Jonhson. Yes?
He said
they hadn't found him yet.
Do you believe this shit?
He can see things
before they happen?
It makes no difference
what I believe.
Look, we spent two years
setting this up.
And that man out there is worried
all this will be comprimised by Johnson.
We're wasting our time
looking for some magician.
We are being paid to secure
the operations, Jones...
...not to hunt down some
carnival barmy.
Really?
Then why are the same authorities that
are looking for us so interested in him?
Get rid of him.
Do it now.
Hi.
We have a super reservation.
I teach here once a week.
The conditions are pretty lousy.
But it's in the Canyon.
One of the eight wonders of the world.
- Hi, Sam.
- Hi, Liz.
A couple hundred years ago
this tribe was booming.
Plenty of food and thriving culture.
They should be better off
but I guess this is just their destiny.
I would like to meet there shaman.
I read once that in the many
North American tribes...
...their shamans purpose
wasn't only healing.
But they also claim
their power of the atmosphere.
To bring on or stop rain...
...even though future advance.
Do you think that's possible?
I believe any thing is possible.
Me too.
- Whose birthday?
- One of my students.
Hi.
How is it going?
Hello, how this everybody?
Good?
That's good.
That, that was a lot good.
But you messed up on the last part.
On the last part, yeah.
I thought you weren't coming back
til next monday.
Well I'm not, but it's Jake's birthday.
How could I miss that?
Who is that man you're with?
- Is he your boyfriend?
- No, no, he's not my boyfriend.
He's just my friend.
I think he likes you.
Why did you say that?
Because he looks at you like
my brother looks at his girlfriend.
Hey, Jake.
Do you want to see some magic?
I'll show you something.
Come here.
I found this rock out
in the Canyon.
And I want you to hold it
because it's a magic rock. That's right.
Hold it really tight,
keep squeezing.
It's magic.
It won't bite.
Happy birthday.
So you're a magician?
Well.
I have a small magic act
back in Vegas.
Frank Cadillac show.
- I thought your name was Chris.
- It is.
Frank Cadillac is my stage name.
How did you come up with that?
I picked two things I really like
and I put them together.
Frankenstein and Cadillacs.
Your odd.
Charming.
But odd.
Cease fire!
Get out of the range!
Nice.
A little closed, huh?
OK.
You were right about
the traffic cam.
We got a positive ID.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
It's OK.
- Did I drop?
- Drop?
- Yeah.
- Ah, no.
- God! It's coming down so hard.
- Yeah.
I like rain.
I like rain too.
Do you know once,
I think was in Denmark,...
...it rained fish.
Because the sun
dehydrated the water.
Took it out in the atmosphere.
Rehydrated the fish eggs,
and they hatched...
...and rained fish.
Is it truth?
Yes, in the clouds. True story.
Happened 50 years ago.
Just felt like sharing
that way to you.
The road washed out ahead.
You can't cross until morning.
Not even if it rains like this.
Spin around and go back about
two miles, take your second left...
...there will be a motel they called...
- Cliffhanger. Thanks.
Right.
Him right?
That's it.
There is no front plate,
where is the other side?
I don't have it.
What was that at the front window?
Go back. Back, back.
Back, there!
Zoom in.
It's a permit.
Track it and find her.
I'll light a fire.
Chris, one little problem.
Oh, no, no, no,
I'm gonna sleep in the car.
- Here.
- Oh, thanks.
Sure.
Hey, did you hear the joke about
the zen master who ordered a hot dog?
No.
He said he would have
one with everything.
Good night.
What we have?
They're in the Cliffhanger Motel
outside Flagstaff.
We found an Arizona foreman
who remembers the land cruiser.
How did they do that?
The road was floaded and he was
about to suggest a place to stay.
- But Johnson already knew, right?
- Exactly.
Callie, it just got worse.
All right people,
we got a nuclear alert. Code red.
In the southern California region.
L.A. to San Diego, 95% certainly.
Nuclear emergency search teams
are on the way, but until they get here...
...somebody please tell me what
my agency, the FBI are doing about it?
Well, sir, two main suspects
have been interrogated.
Cars and primacies
have been checked.
We have opened up surveillance on 2 or 3
suspects but nothing actionable yet.
All was that we are doing?
Waiting for something actionable?
There are 8 million lives
that are precaurious at best...
...so I say we widen this net
to slightly suspicious...
...and get some decent Intel before
this nuke blows up Los Angeles.
Allright, Callie.
What do you propose we do next?
I believe that
the urgency of the situation...
...compels the use of any and
all resources to obtain Chris Johnson.
We know where he is.
Let my team pick him up.
The FBI are mobilizing.
Continue watching.
- Did you have the image?
- Yes.
He said they're mobilising.
Standard procedure
when security is escalated.
Tell him to wrap it up.
They'll lead us straight to Johnson.
- Don't lose sight of them. Understand?
- OK, certainly.
You hungry? There is
a coffee shop down the road.
I'd rather eat here,
if that's OK.
Sure.
What?
There is an Italian painter
named Carlatti.
And...
...he...
...defined beauty.
He said it was
a summation of the parts...
...working together
in such a way that...
...that nothing needed
to be added.
Taken away or altered.
That's you.
You're beautiful.
That was incredible.
What was?
This.
Over here. This is a good stand,
our position had a good view of the motel.
We'll put our removable area surveillance,
this formation, over here and that turn off.
A team with a parabolic step
right here.
That's fine, but I also want
mobile surveillance,...
...get me 2 or 3 hummers.
If they run on us, I wanna be flexible.
Ferris.
Call the local police in Flagstaff.
Tell them patrol the outside perimeter.
I want that area locked down.
A body turned up at an apartment,
in line of sight of my office...
A slit throat, like Roybal.
Somebody trying
to follow us to Johnson.
Chris?
Yeah?
Maybe there is
such a thing as destiny.
Give her 40 seconds.
So after two minutes, he just
stop seeing what's gonna happen?
Not sure, I hope so.
- Elizabeth Cooper?
- Yeah.
Federal Agent Ferris.
- What is this about?
- I'm gonna need a few minutes of your time.
Yeah, OK.
They are putting her in the car.
- Silahýný býrak, geri çekil.
- It's his gun. He's gonna shoot you people.
This was 3 days ago?
He used you to get away
from Las Vegas.
You can be pretty sure,
everything he told you...
...is a lie. He's delusional.
A sociopath.
Oh, my God.
My God.
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Go back to the motel. Have a drink.
Put one of these in his glass.
It'll take 5 minutes to put him to sleep,
then we will come in and get him.
Nobody is being hurt.
But this is important, you need
to do it at least 2 minutes...
...after you get him out of the room.
Why do you need me?
Why can't you just get him?
Liz, as I understand that you work
for a federal founding program...
...teaching on a native reservation,
is that true?
Yes, that's true.
Well, I think you're here to help us.
We are on the same team.
Now they letting her go.
- Thanks for the note.
- Sure.
- Get a nice walk?
- I did. You know, it's really beautiful here.
Ah! I'm...
I have a present for you.
Ah, thanks.
I need that.
Yeah.
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, no. I'm fine.
Now, why don't you go wash up...
...I'm gonna make us breakfast.
- OK.
45 seconds.
1 minute 30.
And that's 2.
- Looks good.
- You think so?
Thank you.
Don't drink that!
It's drugged.
Oh, God, I don't know what I'm doing!
I don't know what I'm doing.
Some federal agent came up to me and
said that you are a delusional sociopath.
And they showed me this tape.
So maybe you are
but I don't want to believe that.
I don't think I can believe that.
They also said that if you run
they will shoot you.
So I should drug you instead.
Even if what they said is true,
I don't want you to die.
Chris, is it true?
Oh, shit!
Give me broadband noise reduction,
I don't like to hearing this.
Speak quietly and act normally.
How long they have said
this drugs will take?
About 5 minutes.
- What is he doing?
- He's drinking. Give it a minute.
Got a clean shot?
Not yet.
The man that in the casino
would have killed two people.
It happened,
it just hadn't happen yet.
Oh, my God,
you're delusional.
Fluffy cranberry or a stack of
chocolate pancakes for the kids.
Fluffy Cranberry or a stack of chocolate
cheap pancakes for the kids in a...
Safe?
Who knows what's safe?
I know a man dropped dead
from looking at his wife.
Safe?
Who knows what's safe?
I know a man dropped dead
from looking at his wife.
You can't get lost in the woods,
if you never go in to the woods.
Boy, you got
an answer for everything.
That's right sir. You'rr the only person
authorised to do so.
That's right sir. You're the only person
- How are you doing this?
- I have no idea how...
...but I can.
I was born with it.
- This is some kind of a trick?
- You know we don't have time for that.
You said anything is possible.
So, you see things
before they happen.
- You see the future?
- My future,...
...when it affect me
and only 2 minutes ahead.
Excepting you.
For some reason I saw you.
For some reason I saw you. Far beyond
anything I've ever seen before...
...and I don't know why.
What do you mean,
you saw me?
You have been...
You have been doing that to me?
You know what I'm gonna do
and what I'm gonna say...
...that your just setting me up?
- No, I haven't.
I wanted to find you because
I need to know why I was seeing you.
Because I...
It was not a setup.
What are they want from you?
They think I can help them
in matters of a national security.
I don't understand if
you can help them why don't you?
Because I can't.
I can only give them
2 minutes ahead start...
...and that's if my life
has personally involved.
- But with me you can see further.
- Yeah.
But they don't know that.
There is almost 10.000 dollars
in this envelope.
They know about you.
You need to get away from here.
What time do you have?
- 9 to 10.
- Set your wacth 9 to 17.
Read this when I left,
and wait exactly...
...45 seconds before
you do what it says.
I will take Ferris with me.
I might be away a week or month...
...but if you can wait,
I'll find you.
Something's wrong.
- Don't do it.
- I already have.
Go, get him!
Alive!
Lets go!
Son of a bitch!
Chris.
Oh, shit! Run!
Johnson!
You're not gonna shoot.
You gonna let me die?
Hey, I need some help!
Get him out of here.
Let's get him out of here.
I got you.
You allright? You OK?
Open your eyes. Look at me.
No good deed
goes unpunished, does it?
- She got him.
- Now what?
- Did you see her?
Smoke?
Thanks for today.
You didn't left me to die.
I appreciate.
That was a really showed character.
I know, I seem like a bad guy,...
...and all of this but in the interest
to preserving our freedom...
...there are larger issues at play.
- What about my freedom?
- With freedom comes responsibility.
- I have rights.
- This isn't about you.
This is about 8 million other people.
If I do what you want,
you will keep me in this chair forever.
There is a nuclear bomb
somewhere in Los Angeles.
And every television station
in the world will broadcast...
...precise details of it's detonation. So go on,
push that two minutes as far as you can...
...and find it.
...broadcast this afternoon for a
breaking news downtown in Los Angeles.
...the largest technology corporations
opposed this idea. And tech lobyying blame for...
...and members of the LAPD bombsquad
are staging in that area.
We gonna live now, our reporter
Lisa Joiner, at the scene with very latest.
- Lisa? - Jeff, this all began when police
received an anonymous phone call...
...saying that explosives would be
detonated at this parking garage...
...at Second and Broadway
at 6 o'clock tonight.
There is no, um...
They have no idea of the motive.
- The victim however...
- Oh, Liz, I'm sorry.
What?
What did you say?
We saw the LAPD surrounded the area.
They've secured a perimeter.
But now the bomb squad
is making there way onto...
...the deck of this building.
And there the men are walking up
with black suit on the sight.
Oh, my God!
There... There has been an explosion.
There has been an explosion.
Oh, my God.
The victim has been identified
as Elizabeth Cooper of Las Vegas.
And she was strapped
to a wheel chair.
Sorry.
...tax of %10 U.S. workers
receives that options.
Many technology companies will be...
- Tell me what just happened?
- I, I can't.
It won't work like this.
Just get me out of this room
and I will do what you want.
I'm begging you.
Please, get me out of this room.
Let him out.
- Cally! Cally, wait up.
- What?
The residue report of Betty Peterson.
The dead girl in the apartment.
Her throat was cut bleed out,..
...otherwise, nothing to the DNA,
the place immaculate again.
- How did it go with Johnson?
- Something happened...
...but he's not sharing.
There are traces of potassium iodine.
Some medication
Peterson was taking.
- They found an empty pill box.
- No. the only reason to take it is...
...to prevent radiation poisining.
Hey, wait, wait. Can I get a smoke
or something? I need to relax.
Thanks.
Hey, can I get a light?
Look.
Bay 01. Bay 01.
I got a visual.
Target is heading the south route
in the Seen street.
Subject is turning east
onto Broadway.
Stay here.
Let me deal with this.
Why are you here?
They killed her.
Two hours from now.
They killed Liz.
Tell me what you saw.
I saw them execute her.
Right there.
On the roof.
It hasn't happened yet
and I know who has her.
The same people we are after.
There is a reason that...
...they brought you here.
They are using Liz as bait.
10 to 1, you go out on that roof,
they are gonna put a bullet in your brain.
I know.
Right now, she is still alive.
She is, you are, we all are.
Lets try to keep it that way.
I help you,
you help me, alright?
I want a two mile radius.
Every telephone grid, short waves,...
...satellite tower, shut it down.
- What do you want me to do?
Let him shoot you.
You called an unpickable style.
Turn number and dial again.
FBI! Get on your knees!
You OK?
That looked pretty close.
Slide of hand.
- You didn't get him?
- Not alive. He fired on the chopper.
But doesn't matter,
he couldn't call in the hit.
As far as they are concerned,
you're not here yet.
Buys us time.
Everyway I tried,
she still ends up dead.
What if you do it earlier? I think, they'll
have to bring her here in a vehicle, right?
- Looking for a license plate.
- Right.
Can you see it?
It helps if you
don't speak right now.
California plate number:
50KF272.
California tag: 50KF272.
Please, where are you taking me?
- OK. Not a problem.
What do you want with me?
Be careful.
Who the hell are you people?
You set them up Cavanaugh?
Local SWAT has been deployed and
the regional team is here to show back us up.
Allright, listen up.
The van, carrying Elizabeth Cooper,...
...will exit the warehouse, crossed over here,
18 compounds, approximately 5 minutes.
4 minutes and 27 seconds.
Do you mind?
- Not anymore. Go ahead.
- They've got a wrap of explosives...
...wired to a cell phone.
- Remote trigger.
When the cell phone has setted off
they'll use one of speed dial.
They will take this road
to the entrance gate.
At that point, Alpha and Bravo
will swarm to the entrance...
If you can just be quiet
and do exactly what I say...
...I will save your life.
We needed to stop the vehicle here
before it gets into the gates.
Alpha and Bravo will hold
and contain here,...
...sniper teams will initiate on
Johnson's call. On his call. Are we clear?
Our elements
shoot to kill any hostiles.
- What about the intel?
- We don't need them. We have him.
Allright everybody!
Lets go.
Go! Lets go! Move!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
Go, go, go!
- Stop the van.
- Not yet. You'll kill her.
Now!
We gotta go! Now! Now!
Pull back! Pull back!
They've got a gun on the crane,
northeast corner.
Negative, no visual.
Give me that.
The opened door way,
eight inches above the guard rail.
Allright, lets go!
The girl escaped.
David, Charlie,
heading the entry point!
Turn right.
Clear.
Go! Go! Go!
Come on, lets go!
Round up!
They're coming to round up!
Stop.
No!
Go.
This is Charlie-1,
element clear, over.
Thanks.
There is explosives,
there, there and there.
Stay close.
- Sniper.
- Where?
- Behind us.
- Sniper at 6 o'clock. Got a visual?
Nobody move.
I'll find him.
Cat walk, second level.
Cat walk, 6 o'clock, second level.
I got him.
We have to clear this
deck by deck.
You check this one.
I'll do the rest.
Lets sweep and clear.
She is near the engine room.
Come on, man.
Release the hostage...
...if still wanna get out of this.
- Don't patronise me.
- How good are you with that gun?
- Very good.
- You gonna be OK, Liz.
- Back off!
I've seen
every possible ending here...
...none of them are good for you.
- I will take my chances.
One more step fortuneteller
and it definitely won't be good for you.
You have one way out of this.
That was not it.
Liz, look at me. It's OK.
Look at me. It's over.
It's over.
No, it's not.
The nucleur device was removed.
We need to find it's exact location.
Now, this registers any significant
detonation in the earth's crust.
Take a look.
Tell me what you see.
Something's wrong.
- I made a mistake.
- What?
I made a mistake.
- It's happening.
- When?
Now!
I've got 4 teams in the place,
we just waiting on road group.
Allright.
Ferris.
It's me.
I'll do it but I have conditions.
I want her left out of it.
I'm sure we can work
something out.
Liz.
Come back to bed.
I gotta go.
Go where?
Something that I have to do.
I can't put it off any longer.
- Are you coming back?
- Yeah.
Maybe a week or a month.
But if you can wait
I'll find you.
Here is the thing
about the future.
Every time you look at it,
it changes.
Because you looked at it.
And that, changes everything else.
You ready?
Yeah.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3yxs7
Help other users to choose the best subtitles