Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I would like my parents
to have their seats up front.
Dear, the whole town
has come to see you.
You're brilliant.
You don't wanna let them down.
Okay?
I'm not playing unless they do.
Interviewer: Miss Simone,
you really the first
ever to blend jazz,
classical, and blues, but
I believe
you call it black classical.
Who were your
musical influences?
Well, of course, I was trained
as a classical pianist
since I was three.
I started at Julliard
and that's where
I learned about Bach and Mozart
and Chopin, and
those are the artists
that I return to, you see?
Yes, and yet you
became a club singer.
After Julliard, I was
denied entrance
into the Curtis institute
because I was black.
I'd hope to continue studying,
playing classical music,
but I was not allowed to.
So I went to Atlanta
to try to make
to try to make some money,
so that I can apply again.
But they didn't
want a black woman
to play the piano, to
play classical music.
They wanted her to sing
because...
That's what we do, isn't it?
Lawyer: I know you've come
a long way to be here,
unfortunately,
whatever money miss Simone felt
was owed to her
simply isn't.
I wish it were different,
but we've reviewed as many of
your contracts as we could find
and it looks like
the royalties to your songs
were sold a long time ago.
He stole my money and I want it.
I sang those songs,
I lived that life,
that's my porgy money
and they're taking it from me.
Nina, this is a fight we've
been fighting for years.
It's over.
What are you
talking about, Henri?
Just what I said, darling.
Tell him to give
me my fucking money.
Excuse us, sir, let's go.
Give me my money.
Henry: Jesus Christ, Nina!
You tell them to
give me my money,
tell him to give me my money!
Sorry about this.
Whoa whoa whoa!
You're not going anywhere!
All the way back, let's go!
- Nina: Hey!
- Officer: Stop resisting!
Nina: Let me go!
No, no!
Doctor:
She's a diagnosed alcoholic,
diagnosed manic depressive,
diagnosed mild paranoia,
severe dysfunction
when off medication,
moderate to good
function when medicated.
When she was brought in,
she had a money belt
with $8,000 in it.
She had to be restrained.
The police are placing
her on a 24 hour hold.
After that, it's up to
her how long she stays.
Nurse 1: Who is she again?
Nurse 2: Nina Simone.
Oh, I know that name.
Who is that?
Never heard of her.
Clifton: Hello, miss Simone.
My name is Clifton.
Just gonna prep
you for your shot.
Wait wait wait, what is that?
Take your medication.
If you do, it'll take the flag
off your file,
you won't be restrained
for meal times, showers,
or recreation.
Where you from?
Chicago.
Well, welcome to California.
It's so nice here.
Miss Simone.
Nina: Go ahead,
I'm taking my meds,
I'm cooperating,
I'm a good patient.
Nurse: There.
Would I sell you anything,
the way I look?
Man on TV:
Honey, you're right,
you're absolutely right.
Clifton.
Where's my money?
The money they took
from me, where is it?
It's in the safe
with your other stuff.
Can you check on it for me?
Uh-huh.
Thanks.
You seem better.
Yeah?
Hey.
You know I'm famous.
What?
Do you know who I am?
Yeah.
Yeah?
I think my mother
used to listen to you.
Good.
I hope it's okay
for me to say this,
but nothing's really
keeping you here,
I mean you can leave.
You should leave.
Hi.
Took your advice.
I'm leaving.
- Wow.
- Mmhm.
Good for you.
I want you to come with me
to France as my assistant.
What?
I will pay you $2,000 a month,
plus room and board.
In return, you take
care of all my affairs.
You don't believe me, do you?
I can't take that.
I can't take this.
Nina: Plane leaves at 9 am.
Nina: It's France, baby!
France is better.
Better than this.
Will you get some champagne
and bring it upstairs?
This is all I could find.
Come on, let me see.
You want me to make the bed?
No, I'm too tired.
Clifton, I need a drink!
I was clean for 30 days
in that goddamn hospital.
I want a drink right now.
There you are,
and please do my bed.
You've been in it all day.
I know that, isn't
that what you do?
Okay.
Now, please get me
something to drink first.
There's nothing here.
Well, then go get something!
You need to eat something first.
Listen, motherfucker,
you work for me, okay?!
I pay you!
I'm not your patient, now please
go get me something to drink.
Then come upstairs
and do my bed!
Champagne!
Clifton: Hi.
Nina: Good morning.
I brought you some
food and your medication.
I didn't ask for any of that.
Well, you need it,
you can't take
your meds on an empty stomach.
You shouldn't drink
on an empty stomach.
Since when?
What are you waiting for?
Nothing.
Hey, hey, hey, take it with you.
I told you
I don't want it, baby.
Nina: Motherfucker!
Nina: Stop watering down
my champagne!
You don't think I could
tell the difference?!
Expensive bottle of champagne,
motherfucker putting water
in it.
Interviewer: How do you manage
to balance these
two different things,
you have beautiful,
tender love songs
and very intense,
angry political songs.
When I first
started singing which,
as you know, I
didn't want to do,
but I had to so that
I can make money,
back then I only sang about love
because I didn't
have it as a child.
Of course I'm black, so I had
to sing about that too.
And then I had to sing
about them both.
That's the only explanation
I have for that.
- Hi.
What is that?
Lunch.
You don't give up, do you?
I don't want lunch!
I want a drink, not that.
All right, well I'll
just leave it here.
No, take it with you.
Pills.
Don't want them.
Clifton: Make
sure you eat first!
I'll eat.
But I'm not gonna
take the drugs.
I don't like the way
they make me feel, baby.
They stabilize you.
I don't wanna be stabilized.
I wanna feel free, really free.
You can understand that.
Yeah I do, Nina.
I do.
All right.
Clifton: Nina.
What?
You have a daughter, right?
From your first marriage?
Yes I do.
Clifton: Where is she?
She's in New York.
She's grown now.
Nina: Test.
This song is inspired by
the most talented,
elegant playwright,
miss Lorraine "raisin
in the sun" Hansberry.
My muse, my
inspiration, my friend.
Baby, I wrote it for you.
No, you wrote it
because you had to.
Yes.
Come here.
Hello?
Henri: This is Henri Edwards,
I'm Nina's manager.
Oh, hey.
Henri: I got
an offer from a club
in Paris for next Friday.
It'll pay a lot of money,
so make sure she's ready.
She's not in any
condition yet to perform.
She's drinking, not
taking her medication.
Very volatile.
Henri: Know that,
that's what she is.
She's a fucked up
alcoholic drug addict,
but people will still
pay money to see her.
I'll fax you the details, huh?
Make sure you get her there.
This fucking manager
hands me a set list.
14 songs, I have to play
five, maybe six songs,
14 would take us
an hour and a half,
maybe even two, but it's
fucking Nina Simone, man.
I'm not gonna show this to her
because she will
actually kill me.
You know what, you
show it to her.
Just fucking do something, ,
I really do wish you good luck
'cause you're gonna
fucking need it.
Shit.
Man: This is for you?
Hi, Mr. Edwards, I'm Clifton,
Nina's assistant.
- Hi.
- Is Nina ready?
It's the playlist.
What?
It's too long for Nina.
She's acting up again?
The band isn't happy either.
Man: If they're not happy...
She'll be fine.
No, she won't.
Listen, if she cannot perform
an hour half, it's on you.
She's been performing
for 20 years.
She can do 10 songs.
It's 14, it's 14 songs.
Clifton, is that your name?
Clifton: Yeah.
Don't even pretend you have
the balls to stand up to me.
Or to her.
You take the playlist,
you put it on the piano,
you put her
in front of the piano,
you tell the band
to shut the fuck up.
What you don't understand
is she needs this gig.
Don't blow it for her.
Okay?
Nina!
- What are you doing?!
- Talk now, motherfucker!
My time here is over!
It's all fucking done!
Singing to corpses!
What are you looking at?!
Talk now, motherfuckers!
Clifton: You okay?
Thanks for taking your meds.
What happened, Nina?
Why are you here
and not in America?
Why do you keep your
money under your mattress
and not in a bank account?
Why are you playing
in front of 100 people
and not 20,000?
Too much loss.
I lost my family, my
people, my country,
my money, my dreams.
I lost it all.
Don't be afraid of me.
Interviewer: You've been
an ex-patriot since 1970.
Nina: Being an
outspoken black woman,
I feared for my life in America.
That was my feeling then,
but now I realize it's
only normal to want
acceptance for
one's own country,
for ones gifts that
god has given you.
And I'm tired of begging for it.
But you do get a lot of love
when you perform though,
I mean people,
of course they love you.
Yeah, I do, I get a lot of love.
But not enough.
Come on, wake up.
Wake up.
Let's go to nice.
You should see me in nice.
I'm a star in nice, come on.
Yes, yes, yes, let's go!
Come on, go!
This is my Clifton.
My dear friends,
let's make a toast.
To friends.
Guests: Cheers.
And to gatherings.
I only got water.
It's okay, you can toast
with whatever you want, baby.
You're with me.
Nina Simone.
Merci, Merci.
I'm shy.
All right.
Want me to take your shoes off?
Take it off.
Nina.
Baby, come on, stop
with the bullshit
and just fuck me
already, come on.
- Nina, stop.
- Come on.
Stop.
Go get me Stefan
from the bar downstairs.
Go, faggot.
Get me a real man.
There's this beautiful
black boy in the valley.
Ask him if he'd like to
have dinner with us tonight.
Whatever you say.
Cheers.
Where the hell have you been?
I've been calling you.
What, are you packed already?
I'm not going back with you.
I'm gonna go get the bellhop.
I'm going home to Chicago.
- You're not going to Chicago.
- Clifton: Yes, I am.
We have a contract,
you don't break the contract.
Doesn't include
me being your pimp.
Pimp?
Think I need a pimp?
- Hmm?
- No.
I don't think you need a pimp.
Don't go, Clifton.
Take care.
Don't go.
Clifton!
Clifton.
Nina: Hello?
Cousier: Nina,
it's doctor Cousier.
Uh huh.
Cousier: I've called you
several times
over the last few months and...
You need to know.
The results of the
biopsy are serious.
We need to do
something about it.
We need to do it soon.
Okay.
Cousier: You must
come in to see me, please.
Bye.
Are you still sleeping?
It's 11 o'clock.
What about that job interview?
Did you go on it?
Not yet.
Yeah?
Shut the front door.
This where Clifton grew up?
Well, it's where the Clifton
tried to grow up.
Clifton's a good boy.
He is.
I just can't believe
you are in our house.
You know, I have all your music.
I do.
Growing up,
Clifton must've heard
these records a million times.
Nina Simone at Carnegie hall
and Nina Simone...
Let me see that.
I haven't seen this
in a long time.
Mother: Nina Simone:
Silk and soul.
This one.
I never ever took this
one off my record player.
It's got the song "four women".
Mom.
Mom, stop.
Honey.
This has got the song on
it that kept us marching.
"Mississippi".
Made me believe that
we had a chance.
Until we didn't.
President on TV: America
is shocked and saddened
by the brutal slaying tonight
of doctor Martin Luther King.
I ask every citizen
to reject the blind violence
that has struck doctor king
who lived by nonviolence.
Nina: Those motherfuckers.
Nina, what are you doing?
- I'mma kill them all.
- What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
- The fuck you think I'm doing?!
- Nina, stop!
Stop, Nina!
Do what you do.
You do what you do.
You wanna have
dinner with me tonight?
- Mom: That sounds so nice.
- Mom.
Mom: Thank you.
Dad: Yeah, it
would be our pleasure,
and I know just the place.
I'm gonna sing a song for you.
All right, all right.
Clifton, go tell
them I want to sing.
Well, you're my manager.
I wanted to wait
until the entire family
was here to tell you.
Clifton is now my manager.
Shit, boy.
That's good, congratulations.
Why do you think
I came all this way?
You're now my manager.
Let's see if they recognize me.
Musician: Check that out, man.
Musician: Ladies and gentlemen,
it looks like we have
a legend in the house.
Nina Simone is here, and I think
she wants to do
something with us.
Musician: Nina Simone!
Nina Simone, people!
Mom: That gave me the chills!
Dad: That was really
something, miss Simone.
Mom: I love that song!
Dad: That was
really something, huh?
What you think?
Well, you played beautiful.
Is that what you think?
That you put a spell on me?
That's not enough.
He's already talking
like a manager.
A toast.
To Clifton Henderson,
the manager.
- Mom: To Clifton.
- Dad: To my son.
I'm happy he's got a job.
What's going on, Clifton?
What do you mean?
I mean what's going on?
Nothing's going on.
Nina Simone followed you
all the way here
from France, so come on baby,
you gonna tell me there
ain't nothing going on?
That's what I'm
telling you, nothing.
Mom: Well, from what
I see, she needs you.
Baby, no, no, no, please, I have
a headache all over my head.
Bring me some Nutella
and a spoon please.
What are you looking for?
Don't sneak up on me like that!
Where are my earrings?!
I have them.
You're lying!
You gave them to me
when we went through
the metal detector, remember?
Oh.
What am I supposed to manage?
What are you talking about?
Why am I back here, Nina?
I won't make it.
Yes you will.
You don't understand.
Then tell me.
It's so damn bright
in here, Clifton.
What is it with you and this
damn light all the time?!
I put the sheets up,
you take them down!
I don't like so much sunlight!
Nina.
I can make this happen,
but I need your help.
No.
I'll try.
Allison: Hello?
Hi, my name is
Clifton Henderson,
I represent Nina
Simone, I was calling...
Allison: Fuck Nina Simone!
The last time she was here
is the last time
she will ever be here!
Tell that fucking diva
she can suck my...
Craig: Hello?
Hi, this is Clifton Henderson,
I represent Nina Simone, i...
Nina: Clifton, I can't find
any cigarettes!
Mr. Edwards, thanks
for meeting me.
I appreciate it.
As you probably know,
I'm Nina's manager now.
I heard, congratulations.
You know how much money I made
in the last five years?
Fucking nothing.
You're not gonna be her
manager, you're her nurse.
She's in bad shape physically,
financially, and mentally.
I understand that.
But here's my problem.
Locally, I just can't
get anyone to book her.
Henri: That's no surprise.
Look, I love her,
and she knows it.
But she's just not
a good investment.
Look, there's no
question a lot of people
wanna see Nina
Simone perform, me included.
I had a thought.
I was thinking about her going
back home to the states
and doing a free concert
in central park.
Bring the people back to her.
What do you think?
Henri: Central park?
Who do you think she
is, Barbra Streisand?
Why not?
Are you sleeping with her?
No.
All right.
Look, I'm not gonna help you,
there's nothing in it for me.
She's mean, crazy, drinks,
smokes, out of shape.
I understand.
Henri: Even her
voice isn't what it was.
All I need from
you is some advice.
She has to deliver truth again.
If she does, she can
do whatever she wants.
She's Nina Simone.
That's my advice, clean her up.
Clifton: Hey.
Hey, did you bring my ice cream?
Rum raisin?
No. How you feeling?
Nina: I'm fine. No ice cream?
Wanna go to the gym?
No!
Come on.
Like this, it's good
for your diaphragm.
Where are we going?
Nowhere. We're just walking.
That's stupid.
It's good for your heart.
Like that's gonna fix it.
I need a cigarette.
It's too sunny, I'm leaving.
Clifton: Nina!
That's it, all the
way back, here we go.
You got it.
Clifton: Where are you going?!
I'm exercising.
On my own.
Miss Laroche?
Hello, Mr. Henderson.
Hi, Clifton.
Come in.
Laroche: Miss Simone,
it's great to meet you.
It truly is.
So how do we get started?
Laroche:
Well, Mr. Henderson said
you just want
to get your voice in shape
and increase its
endurance and...
Who's paying you?
You are.
No, I'm not.
Stop this crap.
I told you get me a stage,
I will do the rest.
Clifton: Bonjour, this
is Clifton Henderson,
I represent Nina Simone.
Man on the phone:
Is she sober?
Of course she's sober.
No I'm not.
Man: Because what I've heard is
she's still impossible
and sounds like shit.
Clifton: No, no,
she sounds great.
Yeah right, listen, I'm gonna
tell you something important.
Lose my fucking number
and never call here again!
Hi, I represent
Nina Simone, I'm...
Woman: Oh, we love her!
- Nina Simone!
- Yeah.
Woman: Will you please
hold a moment?
Yeah, I'll hold.
Woman: I will get our calendar.
Clifton: Nina!
Nina, we gotta go.
Get in the water with me.
Come swim with me.
Nope, gotta go.
I don't wanna go,
you're such an old man.
Come on!
This is helping my headache.
We gotta go.
I worked really
hard to get this, Nina,
come on, out of the pool.
Okay.
Clifton: We have to go.
Ladies and
gentlemen, Nina Simone.
When you sing,
I've never seen
anything like it.
Never felt anything
like it, I mean...
You're different.
You're just different.
I'm not different.
Yes you are.
Nina: I'm not different!
You think I'm different?
Do I look different to you?
I am me!
And the only time
anybody can ever deal with me
is when my power
is channeled through my music!
That's too motherfucking bad.
I know who I am,
I'm a black woman!
That's who I am.
I'm not different, motherfucker.
You're different.
You're pretty.
I'm sorry.
Many of your songs
are about freedom,
and I wonder, what
is freedom to you?
I'll tell you what
freedom means to me.
No fear.
I mean really,
no fear.
If I could have that half
of my life, no fear...
Interviewer: What are you
afraid of?
Hello?
How are you, lover?
Richard: Nina,
can you imagine?
First I've lit my shit
up with this crack pipe.
Now, this ms shit
is fucking me up.
Something's gotta get us, baby.
Richard: Yeah, but
this shit is crazy.
Man, I miss being on stage
even though I was so scared
all the time, remember?
Nina: Yeah, I remember.
Announcer:
Village gate is proud
to present a very
talented lineup tonight
of music and soul!
But first, our young comedian
out of Illinois,
Mr. Richard Pryor!
When you see a woman
standing across the hallway
and she's got a cigarette,
and you wanna light it,
but you forgot
where you put your matches,
and you're...
- Right?
I miss that shit,
I love it, man.
But enough about me.
What's new with you, baby?
I met a boy.
I have a boy with me.
You got the boys,
you got the girls.
He's different.
He doesn't drink.
He'll never hit me.
That means he's not fucking you.
You're right, he's not.
Nina: He takes care of me.
I keep pushing him away though.
Nina, you're
scared of something.
I am.
Clifton!
Clifton: Yeah!
Where are you?
Clifton: Right here.
Get me a studio.
I want to record some music.
Yeah.
Yup.
Hey guys.
Man: Hey.
Man: Hi, Nina.
- Yeah.
- At the chart, yeah?
- Okay.
- It's good to see you.
It's good to see you too.
- I hope it good to be seen.
- Thank you for coming.
Yes, yes, wanna start?
Man: Miss Simone.
Need anything?
- No, I'm good.
- All right.
Keep your eyes on me.
Just watch me when we start
and you're gonna be all right.
From the top.
So, we'll take it from the top.
Nothing too big.
...over here.
Okay boys, how's the
sound in the booth?
Sound technician:
Sounds great, Nina.
Oh.
Baby, it's okay.
You're used to me already?
Think that would be impossible.
You were great tonight.
It was fun.
So much fun.
Dance with me.
What?
You wouldn't swim
with me, dance with me.
...What, here?
Why not?
Okay.
There's no music.
We heard music all day.
Thank you for the dance.
Hello?
Cousier: Hello,
I'm looking for Nina Simone.
Who's this?
Cousier:
This is doctor Cousier.
Is she there?
She's here, but she's busy.
Can she call you back?
Cousier: Well, she was supposed
to call me back and did not.
It's important.
Well, I take care
of all of Nina's affairs.
You can talk to me.
Cousier: Okay, well then
there's certain things
you should know.
Nina: I felt so
good after recording.
Why didn't you tell me?
Tell you what?
That was your doctor
on the phone.
A doctor I didn't know you had.
You were supposed
to come back in
to start your fucking treatment?
It's my life, Clifton.
It always has been.
If 30 years of alcohol, drugs,
and mental illness
have not killed me, this won't.
What?
I don't get it.
I have seen you go ballistic
over your pasta
not being al dente.
Would it make you
feel better if I did?
I'm tired, Clifton.
My pasta means more to me
than this fucking bullshit.
But I do like your
central park idea.
- Cousier: How are you?
- Good.
So...
Can I travel?
Where, and for how long?
America for a week?
A month?
Nina, the situation is critical.
You waited a long time
to come in, too long.
You need surgery, Nina,
and you need it soon.
Do you understand?
Does it matter?
Really?
It matters to me.
And it matters to the people
who love you.
Cousier: Scalpel.
Around here is
a slight infection
started from the iv,
I just wanna watch it.
No, it's okay.
We'll watch it.
Yeah, but it is infected.
How do you know this?
I'm a nurse.
Clifton: We'll
get through this.
You're the strongest
woman I know.
Interviewer: You
are a strong voice
in the fight against
racial inequality.
In fact, Eldridge cleaver
once said
that you are the soundtrack
for the civil rights
movement in America.
Can you talk about
that a little?
Well, darling, I've had my heart
broken many times, and the death
of Martin Luther King
and of that movement
was one of them.
Why do you say that?
Do you feel the movement failed?
No, no I don't, I think
the United States failed.
My country failed my people,
my people failed me,
and that's why I'm here.
Interviewer: Well, it
is our gain, I must say.
Quiet.
- That's good.
- Ow.
Okay, I gotta go.
I'll see you in a few hours.
I'm going to the pharmacy.
Girl on the tape:
Hello, miss Simone.
My mother recently passed away.
I just wanted you to know how
important your music was to her.
I'm sending you a picture
you autographed for her
and a necklace
she used to wear back then.
This was my mother's
favorite song.
I made this for her
before she died.
Girl on the tape: Thank you
for all you meant to my mother.
I hope you'll play
in America again.
I'd like to see you.
Nina!
So, how are you feeling?
I'm broke.
I see, so you want
me to manage you again.
No.
Clifton's my manager.
So why are you here?
I wanna play in America again.
Clifton secured central park.
Aha, I see.
Nina: But he needs collateral.
Sure, I could help,
I could make a call,
but why should I?
All the promoters think you're
a five star asshole, Nina.
What does that have to do
with playing music, Henri?
Nothing, if you wanna play
in your living room,
you can be as big
an asshole you want there.
Hey, hey, hey,
I'm not saying no,
I'm saying show me
that you give a shit,
show me you're
not gonna knife someone,
that you can handle it.
Nina: I can handle it!
Okay, okay, when
do you wanna play?
Clifton: There are
thousands of people out there.
Just for you.
Nina: Thank you, Clifton.
Are you ready?
Are you, Nina?
You know I am.
Woman: Miss Simone, it's time.
Announcer: Returning to
the central park stage,
the high priestess of soul,
Nina Simone!
I wanna thank you so
much for being here.
Woman in the audience:
We love you, Nina!
Coming home to you
feels really good.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7hy3y
Help other users to choose the best subtitles