Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Who do we?
Well, Bobby Fricker.
Disgusting. He always digs nose.
I eat saliva.
So what. Slabiæ said.
Come on, we can do it.
Come on Chrissy, just hang.
Flip reverse, let
Slinojed go first!
(Slooooobodan translation)
Hello, I am Sam, and I'm not there.
Deliberately avoiding calls.
Leave a message after the signal.
Hello, I was not sure
Is this your number until I
heard the message,
but now I am sure.
I'm Chrissy,
and many expect.
I'm expecting a child, and me to
show up like you promised.
Maybe I am old,
but I'm older.
So, do we'll report if,
but when you gonna come.
After all,
promise is a promise...
NEKADISAD
Thomas Wolf once said:
"You can not go back home."
Now that's great for old Tom.
But he was not a girl who has entered into
a pact with her friends when he was
12 years, it will be back whenever
one of them needs help.
And here I am, right back to your home
childhood in Indiana.
Place for which I am sure that
I never wanted to see.
But the promise is a promise...
I seem to have chosen the wrong
week to quit smoking.
Hey doctor?
Can be a bit of basketball?
Not today. I am very busy.
It is for me.
Morning. Chrissy.
Is anyone there?
Come.
Hey, I saw corn
flakes, and she remembered you.
Do not go to shop,
and accident smršaš.
Very funny. But if this baby
does not trickle out soon, has to be of self.
- It would be convenient.
- Where are the others?
- He will come.
Do you see this slut?
What she has,
why should people crazy?
Long legs, narrow waist
and bomb boobs.
- Honey, you know how I feel about swearing.
- Chrissy, sucking is not blasphemy.
- I can not hear you. - Sis. - I can not hear.
- Sis. - I can not hear. - Sis!
SCENARIO
Hey, good to see you.
- You look great.
- How are you?
Image!
And you... see the...
Thank you for coming.
Hey bitches!
God have mercy.
- How is a star? It's nice to see you.
- Oh my God.
Image!
- See the stomach.
- Tina Tursall.
Images. Oh great look.
Nice to see you, Teeny.
Too much time has passed.
Enter. Enter.
Wow. Strong crate.
Just in the style of your mother.
You know what they say:
"What a mother, such Daughter."
Would you like you two
something to drink?
Can Jack Daniels.
We do not keep the violence at home.
Then whatever you have.
Anything is fine.
- We have a beer.
- Great.
Well.
'll Be right back.
I was just looking for this one.
I can not believe
you saved this.
- Morton wanted to tear down and burn.
- I hear my dear.
But I could not
to separate.
After all, is not mine to collapse.
Belongs to us all.
I really want you
thank you for coming.
Hey, do not worry about Chrissy. I think
you'd be a great mom.
Little prebrižna and rigid, but with
God's help, will bebac
izaæi relatively nepovreðen.
And if not, we can always
seek psychiatric help.
I can not believe that
are you going to give birth Chrissy.
It makes me very old.
Everything around me baby
thrown into a depression.
I mean, it born again, odgajiš,
recite him not to fuck,
and what you discard,
and blame yourself for rejection.
Iunatic.
Then it has a child, which
vicious circle just continues.
Thanks, sinister
kragujevaèki undertaker.
Well Sam, You're welcome
currently doing?
Drop this.
If you ask me to write
a book about doing something with as soon as
people can relate to.
I do not understand how you went with
those "aliens from the neighborhood."
To accept it as a compliment?
Why do not you write romance?
As it... Danielle Steel.
Well, this is a woman who knows how to
and making him okreæeš page...
This is true, Robert.
Making them no longer,
All the èudnije.
You know what, I would just like
you Vidam little more often.
How did it go?
Ten years since you went away.
We do not stop the passion.
Robert, for example, chose
to be an "alternative".
Living in sin with my boyfriend,
but it is still normal.
Yes, I am normal.
She had four wedding,
no endless series
monogamous relationship.
Do not wear black.
Not successful.
Technically, I was just married
three times, first was a duck.
See?
You always all funny.
If you ask me,
should grow up.
Maybe you're right.
Shelby, Indiana, there was not
the most exciting place to grow up.
In fact, most deaths
puberty, she died of boredom.
In those days before MTV and Nintendo,
we had to find a way for entertainment.
It began in the summer of 1970 and
every second summer.
The school is closed, and before us
There were three months of freedom.
But that year, freedom was not
enough. We wanted independence,
in a place called "home."
So we opted to buy
dog kennels in a tree.
Come up to steam,
Summer was our goal.
Four of us have lived in the Gaslight
Addition-in, the end of your dreams.
The all-new community built
on another, just shut down.
I already told you, I do not want
on how to talk.
Calm down Tom.
I can not anymore. How many times
We have had such conversations.
Everyone has problems.
Pokušaæemo to solve.
We tried, but no use.
Perhaps if more
his time home...
Come on.
My parents They argued
from when I remember.
It never bothered me.
On the contrary, actually.
It is that
comfort and safety.
Whatever I did,
they are all the greater.
Hurry up!
Breakfast getting cold!
Robert grew up with his father,
and three brothers.
Her mom died when
she was four years ago.
That's her picture on the mirror.
Robert, never left
house without the pictures.
Tina,
Tell us how you felt at the moment
when you realize that you won?
Well Ron, I can only say,
I thought about this day...
... I thought about this day...
... Dreamed about this day...
... From when I remember.
Win the "Oscar" in those years
outstanding success.
What do you plan next?
Teeny was the unit.
Her parents were èlanov
"Country Club". Never there.
Typical environment for future
actors and pathological liars.
Thanks director...
93, 94, 95 ..
Chrissy? Oh, sorry honey.
Can I get inside?
Of course.
Oh baby, holding it closed.
Collects the dust.
O-oh, can not gore.Mora down.
Is not that correct?
Chrissy You know what?
I was thinking...
about your question.
What about sex?
Yes, baby.
Are you saying it as "the way"
that the mother was afraid.
Like when somebody says "Boo!"
"Argh". That it is sex.
Sorry mom.
It does not matter. It's okay.
I think you're still too young
for this, but since these friends
bitches, you better know.
This may shock you...
This is a flower, right?
Well... all women have a garden...
a garden is a great need
hose to the Gulf.
Or you could do little as long as
effective.
As a direct
result of this conversation
Chrissy has spent a significant part of
life searching for the gardener.
These are Wormersi (worms).
The neighbors all had
sorry for their mothers.
Like us, they are
had a summer goal:
that we burnt life.
They were enemies.
Hey wormy Wormersi!
Now!
It is they want.
Down with Chrissy!
Run! Run! Run!
Just to reach you!
Robert, are you okay?
Shall we have worms!
And we always right back debts!
We are just
posrali girl from the crowd!
I need!
Foreplay:
A - Dinner with sveæe,
and walk along the beach,
B - 'vatanje medveðoj the skin,
at the local hill,
C - watching an erotic film
or D - all of this,
B.
E - none of the above.
Robert, this is not possibile answer.
Then B. .. I guess.
Definitely A.
What a surprise.
I chose D - all of these.
What iznenaðenjeA to niespodzianka.
We have 107 dollars and 24 cents.
- As far as we are missing?
- $ 23 and our dog kennels.
I suggest that when we buy,
Now make a party in pajamas.
I, see your mom.
- How short shorts.
- How mighty èizmice.
I do not know why, but earlier
This summer, my mom is begun
that dresses like Nancy Sinatra.
Your mom is so cool!
Hey, tonight is full moon.
Festival spirits.
They return to Earth
and walk among the living.
Four "of cows". It is
dollar and sixty, boys.
We are girls.
I know.
How horrible.
What you expect?
She's a witch.
I swear. There are voodoo dolls.
I saw it.
And you know, one of the dolls
looks the same as the director of Winters.
And it was a needle
stabbed through the heart.
I saw it in the morning
when it is strefio infarction.
Well, shall we try to
another session tonight?
Has not worked through,
and will not even this time.
Upaliæe.
It is the only night, when it breaks
barriers between the living and the dead.
I've read it in the encyclopedia
"Supernatural phenomena".
You're so screwed.
- I'm with you.
- Yes, me too.
Èitaj results.
Robert, you're a woman on the edge.
"Although your sensuality yet
to thrive, it's like
volcano ready to erupt. "
Wow, beware of the Robert.
It sucks.
Samantha: "You are walking a thin line
between romance and sex.
Do not be afraid to take initiative.
Maybe itself iznenadiš. "
Zapamtiæu it.
Chrissy:
"Bypass obstacles, rather than the
osušiš Šerifoviæ like Mary. "
What does that mean?
And now I am.
"Teeney, you're a sex magnet
attracted men from around the world.
Take care of it. "
I'll take the rest of my stuff
when a girl will not be there.
Do not leave me, please.
Becky, please do not ponižavaj
be. Just does not work.
I decided not to say
others for my father.
Tell me stupid, but I
really thought he would be back.
I wish that I did not
believed for years.
At that time, nobody in the neighborhood
are not divorced.
And I wanted to
different from mate.
It is so cold here.
Take my shirt. It's gonna be me
cold, but at least you'll æutati.
This looks fat.
- You are thick.
- I am not fat!
Am I fat?
Catch the person to hand himself.
Let us invoke
Marlin Monroe.
She did not want to cooperate
last time.
No one does not cooperate.
I think we need to bring up someone
buried in this cemetery.
How about
"Dear Johnnija?
To find out how he died.
Close your eyes.
Takes us on his way to another world.
Take care of our circle of safe,
and protects us from evil.
Dear Johnny, we know that
you were a child when you die.
I want to know how.
Ovdeee saaaam!
Concentrate.
Dear Johnny, can you hear me?
If you hear me, give us a sign.
Let us know.
OK, we just want
to talk to you.
Tell us how you died.
He is there.
Wants us to tell you a prièicu.
Mo ¿that it should stop.
He is afraid.
Tell him not to be afraid.
Say that all is well.
He is utterly alone.
Lonely.
He needs a friend.
My you.
It hurts.
You've earned it prdaro.
Never do not do that.
Sorry girls.
But you are too emotional
starting to all this.
I mean, all this is "like", right?
Where you goin, Chrissy?
Stop it, before
get a heart attack.
Chrissy, wait a minute!
Come on Sam!
I! I, we have here!
There is someone.
- What?
- There there.
I do not see anyone.
Probably just the wind.
Come on... Let's go!
Robert, what you can not
acting like a girl?
Look what you did to me!
You know what I hate
to be dirty.
This is nothing.
It's crazy Pit.
Run away from here.
Base called Chrissy,
database called Chrissy,
Chrissy, do you hear me.
What is it?
We have a secret meeting.
Sad?
I remember when I saw someone
at the cemetery after the session?
I think we came into the room.
Who?
- "Dear John".
- Come on...
This is a very bad idea.
This is definitely
not a good idea.
Shut up, Chrissy, that
and now not be offset.
Too.
Sam, are you okay?
Oh God!
We made it! We really did it.
Returned.
We summon him.
Nothing about "dear Johnni.
Until 1948 the
burned in the fire.
But Miss. Wendy says
copies of newspapers saved in
Greenfieldu library.
And that's it.
What is it?
We can not ride bikes
to Grienfielda.
Can we?
- True, or the challenge of Robert?
- True.
How big are you now sike?
Drop dead!
Has to say,
Do not I?
Not necessarily, if you do not want.
- And can we see them?
- No, you can not see them.
Freak.
I have not received them.
You'll get them... and mrzeæeš them.
No.
Robert're happy.
Men like you are great.
See what are my present.
Æoveèe, look like.
Filled with the pudding.
Pudding?
"Crviæi" gave me the idea.
They want the fever.
When the pudding is
relistiènija texture.
That it is the aroma?
Vanilla.
Chrissy, truth or challenge?
True.
Have you ever
tongue kissing?
Are you kidding? I do not want to get pregnant.
You can not get pregnant by kissing.
I know, mind.
But it is clear that if
kiss with a boy so
It automatically understand that you'll
and what to do with it.
I can not refrain. Such as.
It was their curse.
And what is the "what"
as you mentioned?
You know already...
leaving him to
I watered a flower.
Do not go for that.
Man took his pipe,
and sprayed you cvetiæ.
I think the
Time to pause.
But we moved away quite far.
- Come on Chrissy.
- Dobro.Samo go, and leave me.
I do not care, I can rest.
Listen... Shut it.
It's beautiful.
Where did she go?
Where to go?
What is it?
The hair you.
Remove it to me!
Remove m it, please.
I can not.
- Totally hit it soft.
- Come on...
Calm down, Chrissy.
Stop it!
Beware! Go bomb!
It's too
shallow for that!
Go bomb!
Where was gone?
Come on... take out the!
- Do not breathe.
- Someone has to mouth-to-mouth.
You work the mouth to mouth,
I'm going to masiram heart.
- We will reverse.
- Get out of the 'times.
Well,
nice to know who they are
your true friends.
You know, I wanted to do it.
- And I wanted to.
- Yeah, right...
Chrissy is the only
that is really...
Never again to me this
you did! Never!
It was a joke.
It was not the first time that
Robert isfolirala death.
Earlier that year we were scared
when he jumped from the roof and
rules to be broken neck.
None of us has not experienced a loss
as it is, so we did not understand her jokes.
But she is still trying
that death made the ridiculous.
Perhaps to facilitate it?
What was that?
Listen,
I'm sorry.
If you mean, I appreciate what you wanted
that we are doing mouth-to-mouth.
To death frightened me.
Sorry.
Robert, you are my
best friend.
You have fucked right.
Robert, do not curse.
Hey, come here!
- Oh my God.
- What is it?
- I saw his penis.
- Whose?
- And eggs.
Scot.
Oh my God...
Great. Now I am not only
see Scotovu stvarèicu.
I'll be subject to gossip
end of summer...
Guys are making me look.
Chrissy, no and no to what does not...
Well, pogledaæu.
But I want to be perfect
clear that gledm in protest.
Yes. Right.
Not something big.
What's so funny?
Large only...
when the dude lifted.
And when that happens,
be this big.
What does "raise"?
Did not Mother nothing story?
Starting to think that
wrongly informed.
Hey, girls...
Let's do it!
Do you wish to
Men wearing his underwear.
Yes, you better get started right away.
Back off, pervert!
Let's be serious. Let's go.
This is too easy.
Crviæi Hey!
Time for revenge!
Reach us now donkeys!
Better to us to return...
Yes, just a dream sroljo!
Quick!
Well, the game is over!
Come on, come on it.
Return our clothes, hell!
Moooolim vaaas!
Gosh, it's nice!
Come and get it!
All for one,
and one for all!
LIBRARIES IN GREENFIELD
Come on Chrissy.
Wait a minute.
I think I
alergièna dust.
Nothing happened in April.
Never arose not
happened in Shelby.
Me up so much.
Nothing.
KILLED TOWN teacher.
What is it?
This is my Mom.
"There was a crash... lanean
Truck driver was
asleep at the wheel.
It's been an hour and a half while
Rescuers did not reach her car.
She was fully conscious while the
trying to get out
the destroyed car.
She died the same night of bruising,
and massive internal bleeding. "
I do not understand this.
It is not fair.
What does that mean?
Much namuèila.
A lot of pain.
She was very pretty, is not it?
As a movie star.
Girls, I think
I found something.
Read.
"Saturday will be held on
funeral of 12-year-old Jonathan,
and his 36-year-old mother,
Beverly Simms.
Because tragiènog sequence of circumstances,
which include the death,
the family has requested that
funeral to be private. "
That is all. There is nothing else.
What do you mean "it's all"?
How they died?
Just a little.
Torn the pages.
Someone has just tried,
Johnnijeva to death a secret.
Hi.
Are you in the army?
Was.
Vietnam?
You killed someone there?
Not because I wanted.
Are you wounded?
It's a great song.
The foot and still in pain?
Yes. Pain as the devil.
But this wound is the best
what ever happened to me.
How so?
She packed me
the first plane home.
But we are the winner, right?
Nobody wins.
You want some?
Thanks.
Cigarette?
I want one.
Smoking slows growth.
Slight...
Well, have received a "purple heart"?
Yes.
Why do not you?
Yes. It is a great honor, right?
It is not.
On the news say that the U.S.
there almost settle things.
Forget it, okay?
Do you have what you heard,
what you see,
even you have people who lie about
what they saw there...
... Or did.
It seems that no one
no longer be trusted?
You believe in yourself.
If you are lucky.
Well, ostaæeš here for a while?
No.
I try to nowhere
linger too long, you know?
Yes. Definitely.
Is that earrings on you?
Yes.
You're a hippie, right?
On the track of me...
My Mom says that all
hippies sex fanatics.
I'll tell you something, I would like to
someone told me at that age?
What is it?
Parents are not always right.
Do not shit...
It's late. I think
you should go.
- Bye.
I guess he was right.
Thanks.
Bye...
See ya.
Hello.
Whatever you seek,
I hope you'll find.
Peace.
Where is my Dad?
I told you already, he had to go
for a while. But soon you will
be able to see it...
Ate? Every other weekend,
and holidays?
But I want to see it now.
I would love to you heart
but you can not.
Hey Ande, I saw yesterday
crazy pie.
Children, leave the poor
man alone.
Why are you so dressed up at all?
How?
So. Was humiliating.
Anybody home?
Do not answer!
It's just a grandmother.
What happens?
Baba you are upset because
Dad moved up.
So? Let yelling at him.
He is the one who is gone.
I know you're there!
I saw a car in the garage!
Open up the door!
Hide.
What?
Hide!
Open! I want to
I see a girl.
I can now see it.
Once you're gonna have to surrender!
- This is a nightmare.
- Why not let Baku.
Open the damn door!
It's here.
Suspicious lack of detail
Johnnijevu related death,
led us to the only person
that could help us.
Mistika - Divination
Yes?
We need your help.
I was not really in the mood
Today, guys.
Come on... give her money.
Mo ¿and that this cheer.
Enter.
I can not believe that we are
give up dog kennels, because of this...
What brings you here?
We have contacted the spirit.
- His name is Jonathan Simms.
- I know.
I feel a strong presence
ghosts here.
For ten dollars out of the kennel
wood, and I'd oseæala.
Silence.
Pentecost is here, and that
they want to with you a story.
Shuffle this twice, and sections
three times in front of me.
Relax mind and body,
and open up the spirits.
DEATH
We want to know
how he died.
Did you see her facial expression?
She was scared.
Girls, it's fake.
She was scared - and so have you.
Well, what do we do now?
Ghosts haunted live with razlogom.Dragi
Johnny wants to know how he died.
You saw the map. He was killed.
You may want to take revenge.
Come on, this izmièe control.
You should talk to some
who was living when he died.
Who, for example?
With my grandmother. It is
the oldest person you know.
Today he plays poker, but said that
Tomorrow morning we can turn aside.
Your grandmother playing poker?
He likes to gamble.
Oh, but I promised his dad that I
help to dye ogradu.Mislim,
Come on girls... it is 10 dollars.
- Kenny, where the fire?
- In softball, the Candles field.
- Oh, come on.
- But It'll only boys
And then I wait until what?
- Come on Berti, you can do it.
- I houmran is now inevitable...
Let's go to second base!
Let's go!
Show them how to play Robert!
Well, pride!
This is for that of yesterday.
- Come on Robert, you can do it.
Gaðaj over their heads!
- Shut up!
Come on Robert... Tae Down!
Hello dear.
Go away, you nerd!
Well, come on Robert,
Home Rule ran, ran the Home Rule...
Who you kidding?
Girls can not
to play softball.
What did you say?
I said, girls can not
play softball.
What's he doing?
Robert, remember that you are a lady.
Why do not you go home,
want to play with dolls.
She has a doll and GI Joe.
TUÈAAAAAAA !!!!!!!!
Robert, see my hair.
Crazy bitch...
- Fuck off!
- What is the feeling when the girl beats?
It's a shame that your mother is dead.
For someone so I have to learn to
acting like a girl.
TUÈAAAAAAA !!!!!!!!
Ah there you are. Samanha, I want to
meet my friend...
That's Mr.. Kent. A friend of mine.
Hey Samantha.
Your mother talked about you all
much. Tells you you're a good kid.
I'm glad.
It gives me great pleasure,
young lady.
And it looks good...
just like your mother.
And Samantha, Your Mama
I said that you are interested in science.
Nauen size.
Have you ever been
in "Smithsonian" museum?
E to be seen, I tell you...
This place is huge.
And bigger than huge.
I do not know Mama, you should
planning a trip to DC before school?
What do you think?
It would be great! Do not
Samantha would be cool?
I think we could all
to have fun.
Dad would take us there.
Well... hell...
Mr. Kent?
Please, call me Bad.
Gad?
No. Bud.
B - U - D.
So Bad, I have a piece of food,
that you stuck to your teeth.
Damn!
It's okay. Just wait.
'll Be right back.
What are we...?
I think there more...?
No, not disappeared.
Thanks.
Jitters of the first meeting.
This is a very pretty scarf.
Thanks Lydia.
Well I have isflekao tablecloth...
It's okay.
Samantha?
"Love is when you never...
you have to say sorry... "
What the movie?
Izvlaèi tears.
Where did you get so late?
I left a little to think.
In spavaæici?
Dog kennels to try the wood?
Of course.
You are not followed by the.
Who asked what?
're Pretty good.
Thanks.
I do not think you are good only
the girl, but also to boys.
Want soda, or something like that?
Super. Èekaæu.
- Robert?
- What is it?
Why the constant strife?
That anything done.
Because you know, I wondered...
because I think you're a great girl.
I've always
I thought that you hate me.
And I am.
- Robert?
- What?
- Mo... HGH... and p.. Love?
- What are mumlaš?
Would it be okay to...
Can I kiss you?
-... I guess...
- Super... ready?
Want it now?
Yes.
I mean, if you will.
Well.
Ah, it was great.
It's okay.
Scot, if equal mention this to someone,
and especially his brothers...
izbatinaæu the shit out of you.
Well.
Truth or challenge?
True.
Do you find yourself on a desert island
with me, Chrissy and Robert,
and that there is nothing to eat,
which would be killed and eaten?
This is silly pitanje.Šanse
for they are almost none.
Regardless, you have to answer.
So I guess Chrissy.
Why?
Feed more people.
Truth or challenge?
True.
Do you love your parents?
I do not know your parents.
But as I'm concerned,
They are assholes.
You know, I believe in what he
soldier said, they are not always right.
I mean, that as adults
does not mean absolutely nothing.
I never thought it means.
And I am...
Dad moved.
Divorce is.
But I thought that when you agree.
- I lied.
- Why?
I do not know.
I just wanted
normal family, you know?
As Brady Bunch.
Well, six kids in one
the bathroom, I do not sound like fun.
After all, Mike and Carol
the ožalošæeni.
Then Partridge Family.
Shirley Jones, the widow,
Buffy and Jody are siroèiæi.
Like the time Eddie's father - a widower.
"My three sons" - a widower.
"Bonanza" - a widower.
"Beverly Hillibillies" - widows.
You see Sam,
no perfect families.
It is normal that things
be shitty.
Maybe this is normal,
but it still hurts.
All of them have died Teeney.
But my Dad has decided to leave.
I really miss.
It's okay.
I'll always be there for you.
Thanks.
What are you doing? Adore it...
When I was 12 years old, and no
efforts live for the moment,
do not complain about the past,
and do not worry for the future,
but at that moment in the kennel
wood, we met Teeney
heart, sigurnošæu and comfort.
Best friends for life.
For life.
- Better get going.
- Yes.
You know, I heard that will in ten
age, gender rhizobia be divorced.
Well, in that we already
hard to believe.
Come on! Run away from here.
- Teeney?
- What is it?
She disappeared!
- What do you want?
- Rosary! Just came off!
We'll be back in the morning. Rain is...
We have to find now.
There she is!
- You see.
- I do not see it.
Inside is, you see.
Dohvatiæu is me.
Damn!
It's okay. Dohvatiæu said.
- Be careful.
- Well, I will. Hold this.
Oh, God.
Can you? Only carefully.
Here is svaèega...
See, jojo.
Hurry, please.
Really starts to treatment.
- I got it.
- Super. Come on now, hurry.
Teeny, give me your hand!
Hold!
Help me!
Let us some help!
I'm coming!
Are you okay?
Why do you fear me?
It's weird to hear that you
out only at night.
It's kinda... creepy, you know?
Yeah, well... I do not like
lucky a lot of people.
And I think that they do not want
much happiness to me.
Take her home.
We'll see the Pit.
And that was not there, Sam?
Teeney and I know what
whether it was not there.
And since that night, we had
hero in a crazy Pitta.
Robert, you missed a bit.
And do not the ass of odlepiš
asphalt, and help us.
You know that if you do not eat every
few hours, I get dizzy.
Grubby alert!
And I thought that something stinks.
Perhaps your
smart, skinny.
Oh, your wit me stunned.
- I do not want to brag...
- Come on, man, we go from here.
Ladies...
What's his problem?
It may be disturbed...
And maybe not such a jerk?
That day, Robert had stopped
to prelepljuje sike.
I did not know that oppose
my whole neighborhood.
Enter.
I have prepared many
fresh lemonade.
Sit down girls...
Samantha, how you hold?
I'm good grandma.
I'm glad, most
I care for you.
We'll be ok.
Well it was Mrs. Anderson.
We take care of it well.
I'm glad to hear that.
Let's see now... because
have extra company.
L'll still EASA, and to hear
this important issue that interests you.
Sam, What so many concerns
bake for you?
Who knows?
Well... refreshing.
At one gulp.
What is it?
Shiny.
So?
Grandma, did you know a boy
our years ago and his Mother,
who died in 1945?
Jonathan and Beverly M. Simms.
Only we are interested
how they died.
Is' them something
terrible had happened?
Yes.
But it is something that
do not want to hear.
- Please...
- We regret to learn.
Theirs nightmares for weeks.
Please Mrs. Albertson.
Tell us...
Yes, let's Grandma... what happened?
It took me a long time...
to forget that
terrible tragedy...
I do not want to
re-experiencing.
The same're your grandfather.
He had a fascination and...
He was interested in every
event in the city.
Oh, God.
Ed and Mod.
Ispijte all!
I would like to talk, but waiting
... me a big bingo tournament.
Move girls.
I want to take this time
some really good cars.
Hurry go, zakasniæemo!
Hi Grandma...
Bye.
Come by soon
me, Samantha.
Must love Bingo.
I really need to hurry.
We can to go down for this.
- Do not drop me.
- Okay, on three... pull.
One, Two, Three.
I know that Dedina
archive somewhere.
You found something?
Not yet.
I, I think
I found something.
These are my parents.
Are a great couple.
Yes.
MURDER CITY amazed.
Jack-pot!
Were killed.
"Beverly Simms and her 12-year-old
Jonnathan son was brutally murdered
petek late evening.
Body was discovered by Peter Simms.
After leaving the pub at midnight,
found their bodies riddled.
Sheriff believes that the robbers
escaped, and both victims
killed in his sleep.
There is no evidence, no suspects.
Sheriff believes that the robbers were
in passing, and left town. "
This is an introductory Article I
my grandfather's newspaper.
"Although nothing is as it seems,
something we understood from the killings,
and that is that if we thought that
Shelby being protected from violence from
outside world - we are deceived. "
Shelby is a safe city.
If something like this happened here,
imagine how is it there?
Robert, that's okay.
No, not right! Not OK!
Why did they have to die?
Why she had to die?
Dad lied.
He said that the beautiful angel
down to earth, and took it.
People should not feel cut pain.
Why did he have to die?
Why have I lied?
Only on my left,
and lying to me.
You're not the only one he left.
I only you and
can count.
I know how you feel.
What do you mean?
My Dad moved.
Divorce is.
Divorce...
I'm sorry.
Fuck them.
You have us.
Let's make a deal. Here and now.
We are always there for each other.
No matter what happens in life.
If Teeny goes to Hollywood
or I marry
rich doctor...
setiæemo this day,
and this agreement.
Whenever you need a friend,
to be there for each other.
And on that count. Always.
No matter what.
Then the deal.
All for one,
and one for all.
Now, more than ever we must
Johnni provide peace.
Ready?
We returned from the dead Johnnija,
and for us to send him home.
Close your eyes.
Takes us on his way to another world.
Take care of our circle of safe,
and protects us from evil.
Dear Johnny, we know that you and
your mother was brutally murdered.
Have you returned to tell us
Who did it?
We're here to help you
to poèivaš in peace Johnny.
We listen to you.
Here is...
Do not break them round.
Tell us who did it Johnny.
We're here to help you.
Holy God...
- It's a killer!
- Please do not hurt us!
Hey, this is not a polygon.
This is the cemetery.
And you kids should have
little respect for the dead.
Hey, we have a lot of
respect for the dead, okay?
Yes, this is why we are here.
We have risen from the grave Johnnija.
Really?
And to think that his
monument broke in half?
I've broken down tractor.
Really?
Yes.
It is not easy to ask all
and monuments.
No longer work
this stupid session.
It is a waste of time.
I can not believe that we
thought that we managed...
And what about the tarot cards, in. ..
Forget it.
I knew that day that our
days fantasizing over.
As they get older, it becomes
increasingly difficult to blindly believe.
It's not that we want, but it is too
it happened that we could.
Let's go.
You see, this is a Crazy Pete.
Leave him alone, okay?
What is it?
I forgot something in the cemetery.
Stiæiæu you.
You want to go with you?
No, I'll be good.
You are Peter Simms.
They were my closest.
It is terrible what happened to them...
I'm sorry.
I have long thought that I
To prevent it could.
I was at home,
and not in that damn pub.
You were there for me.
I Proæerdao many years,
afraid to face the people.
Usually afraid to
confront with them.
And then I'm afraid.
What's your name?
Samantha.
Well, in life you will happen
things that you can not spreèiti.
But that is no reason
discard the world.
There is a purpose and for good and for evil.
He gave me the only
gift that he could.
Lessons, which would be required
a lifetime to learn.
And no matter what I
realize the importance of his words,
only now when I look back,
understand their meaning.
Sleep in peace, dear Johnny.
We've tried grèevito
to fit in, look the same,
to do the same thing... practically,
to be the same person.
While we have not seen,
to be changed.
Dog kennels in the tree is supposed to
give us a bigger independence
but we were actually done this summer
independent from each other.
What is it?
Your car blocking my jeep.
- Oh shit!
- I come...
- I think I saw the head.
- Who has seen my head?
- I have not seen my head?
- You did not see his head...
- I'll get the keys.
- Ma forget kljuèeve.Idemo limo!
Go for bags, and call Morton.
No, do not leave me
here with her!
Well, we go to school before
ispljuneš something...
- How are you?
- Hello...
Comes out, I need your car.
Huh?
I've got a pregnant woman
must be in the maternity ward.
No problem. Just me
say where, and there are an instant.
Second is too long.
- Get the mamlaze!
- See?
Thanks.
Nice day.
Move!
- This is too much effort.
- Sorry.
Morton is in the midst of work,
we find in the hospital.
There is a lot of mail.
Dare you to do this?
Got a video recorder! I can not believe...
Robert! Here is a video recorder?
Right? And is there a remote?
Well, a lot of screaming.
Thanks.
Breathe... breathe... breathe...
Chrissy, your uncle.
And no, not him.
Oh, shit!
Do not curse in front of my baby.
Sraaanjeeee!
Chrissy, you'll have to push!
Come on, just push!
God, I changed my mind
I get the drugs!
Too late for that.
Give me the drug, or the unic!
Give her the drugs, give her...
And you'd better calm down, okay?
Chriss now push, push!
Come, see the head, see head.
I really see little head.
Is' it needs to look?
Yes. Chriss, You're doing great.
- Is a boy or a girl?
- I do not know.
For now only the head.
It is almost over. Once again
inflates... You can do it.
Here it is great. Once again
inflates Chriss.Hajde!
Extracted it from me!
Extracted it, takes out!
Extracted it from it! Extracted it, takes out!
The girl.
A beautiful girl.
This is my baby.
Am I late?
You have not, come see.
It's your baby.
Oh my God.
We have a girl.
Thanks.
Thank you...
See?
It's really beautiful.
You know, it looks like
Tomislav Nikolic.
No vreðaj, Robert.
Chrissy, truth or challenge?
True.
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
So much that I feel that I blows,
and spill luck everywhere.
- Roberta, truth or challenge?
- True.
How big are you now sike?
And what are yours?
36 D. And are worth every penny.
D? Who knew...?
I, the truth or challenge?
True.
Are you happy?
Not really.
AII, I guess it is normal to
zasrane matters.
Listen, I had the A +
"Building a career,"
but I guess I missed the hour
of "intimate relationships".
You may need to add
a little color to the outfit.
Men like
pastel on women.
It's not about pastelnoj,
or men.
It's about me.
What are you talking about, Sam?
I have had many relationships,
for many years.
And from all I ran away,
we do not at all easy
transition to the next level.
The level of intimacy...
Well, if you do not fall in love,
you can not get hurt.
But you probably like this alone.
Yes, I did.
I remember one summer
tame the wild?
Oh God... We loved the mystery.
Is not it be fun summer?
It was the best.
You know, I sent him Božiæne
Congratulations, and a little cash every year.
But returned last year.
Yes, he died.
You know, you just can not say this,
But, Pete was Johnnijev father.
- Really?
- How do you know?
I remember last
session at the cemetery?
I returned and saw him
placed flowers on the grave Johnnijev.
He told me something, which we then
has not meant much to me mean now.
He said that will happen in life
things that can not be stopped,
but that is no reason
I dismiss the world.
I realized that I was so
afraid of bad things,
I missed all the good.
I did not want to
I come back here.
AII is really
glad I did.
I forgot how
worthwhile to have you as friends.
We are really happy
we have this dog kennels...
... And each other.
Part of me would like to
forever remain here.
I would not go that far.
AII would be nice if more often
I come to visit.
I agree.
Let's make a deal.
All for one...
... And one for all.
Come on...
You can try to escape
and forget the disappointment,
but only when you accept your
past, you can move on.
Perhaps Thomas Wolf more
will never go home,
but I found my way to
there... and I'm glad I did.
Translation and processing (the "listening") freak
cudak31177@gmail.com
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6wx2
Help other users to choose the best subtitles