Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Man:
SO THE HOUSE HAS
A REALLY WONDERFUL FLOW.
IT'S PERFECT
FOR ENTERTAINING
OR ENJOYING AN
INDOOR-OUTDOOR LIFESTYLE.
YOU SEE HOW EACH OF
THE ROOMS IS CONNECTED?
IT'S GREAT, ISN'T IT?
THE KITCHEN HAS ALL
THE MODERN APPLIANCES.
AND RIGHT THROUGH HERE,
THERE'S A SMALLER BEDROOM.
IT'S PERFECT FOR CHILDREN.
IT'S PEACEFUL
OUT HERE, ISN'T IT?
Woman:
GARDEN LOOKS LIKE
IT'S A LOT OF WORK.
ACTUALLY, YOU'D BE
SURPRISED HOW WELL
IT MAINTAINS ITSELF.
Man:
THE ROOF LOOKS KINDA OLD.
Realtor:
HAVE YOU SEEN
THE KITCHEN YET?
THE MARBLE'S WONDERFUL.
(chain clicks)
- THANKS VERY MUCH.
- OH. THANKS FOR
STOPPING BY.
- DID I GIVE YOU MY CARD?
- YES.  WE'LL BE IN TOUCH.
- ALL RIGHT.
THANKS AGAIN.
- THANK YOU.
BYE NOW.
HELLO?
(panting)
- Woman: HELLO? CARL?
- HEY.  ALICE.
I'M DOWN HERE.
IS IT HOT OUT?
- HOW'D IT GO?
- UH, IT WENT OKAY.
- THAT BAD, HUH?
- IT'S A TOUGH MARKET.
WE COULD WAIT A FEW MONTHS,
SEE IF THINGS TURN AROUND.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU
HAD DIFFERENT PLANS
FOR THE HOUSE.
IT'S OKAY.
- Alice: I'M SORRY.
- (chuckles)
YOU KNOW, I'M ALWAYS
HERE FOR YOU, ALICE,
IF YOU EVER--
IF YOU EVER WANNA TALK.
THANKS, CARL.
- BYE.
- BYE. YEAH.
(shower running)
Alice on film:
Honey, what do you think
of this room
for a new nursery?
Man on film:
I think we could fit
a pool table in here.
Alice on film:
Josh, you're a dork.
- (both chuckling)
- Alice: Oh God.
(remote clicks)
(glasses clinking)
- SO THE CAR WAS TOTALED.
- YOU MEAN MY CAR
WAS TOTALED.
WELL, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU LET OSCAR
DRIVE YOUR CAR
IN THE SNOW.
Man:
UH-UH. I WAS NOT DRIVING.
SO WHO WAS DRIVING?
WALTER?
- OSCAR.  OSCAR.
- (all laugh)
- OSCAR, WHEN'S HE BACK
FROM BERLIN?
- TWO WEEKS.
HEY, IS THERE
ANY MORE OF THIS WINE?
YEAH.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
YOU TALKED
TO HIM RECENTLY?
NOT REALLY.
I MEAN, I TOLD HIM
I WAS SELLING THE HOUSE.
GOOD.
HE SAID I WAS
BEING IRRATIONAL.
ACTUALLY, WHAT HE SAID
WAS "OVERLY EMOTIONAL."
HIS FAVORITE.
WELL, THEN YOU CAN TELL HIM
HE CAN KEEP PAYING HIS
HALF OF THE MORTGAGE.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY?
SCREW HIM. IS HE REALLY
THAT OUT OF TOUCH?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S A GOOD THING.
YOU KNOW?
A GOOD CLEAN BREAK.
THAT WHAT YOUR
THERAPIST SAID?
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T AFFORD HER ANYMORE.
GOD, YOU ARE SUCH
A LIGHTWEIGHT.
I KNOW IT'S, LIKE,
ONLY A COUPLE DATES,
BUT I REALLY THINK
HE MIGHT BE THE ONE.
- ALICE, ARE YOU EVEN AWAKE?
- YEAH, I'M AWAKE.
(laughs)
WHAT DID I JUST SAY?
YOU HAVE A REALLY GOOD
FEELING ABOUT HIM.
(crickets chirping)
JENNIE?
JENN, YOU UP HERE?
JENN.
JENN?
(door opens, creaks)
(water running)
JENNIE, WHERE ARE YOU?
JENNIE?
JENNIE, ARE YOU THERE?
THIS BETTER NOT
BE A JOKE.
(creaks)
JENN?
JENNIE, ARE YOU THERE?
JENNIE?
(shrieking)
(thudding footsteps)
(murmurs)
(muffled panting)
(door opens, creaks)
(latches clicking)
(muffled whimpering,
protesting)
(muffled)
NO NO NO!
VERY NICE.
I LOVE THE MARBLE.
I LOVE IT.
IT'S HOME.
(ringing)
HI, ALICE, IT'S ME.
I'M GONNA SWING BY
AND PICK UP MY GOLF CLUBS.
I THOUGHT
I COULD HAVE A LOOK
AT THE HOT TUB FOR YOU.
ARE YOU THERE?
I'M IN HOLLYWOOD
SO I'M GONNA BE BY
PRETTY SOON.
(beeps)
ALICE?
ANYONE HOME?
HI THERE.
HELLO.
I'M JOSH.
I'M ALICE'S EX.
I'M LILA.
I'M JUST VISITING.
DO YOU KNOW
IF ALICE IS HOME?
ALICE? NO.
NO, SHE'S NOT IN.
SHE ASKED ME TO CHECK
THE TIMER ON THE HOT TUB.
BY ALL MEANS.
- HOW'S THE TEMPERATURE?
- IT'S PERFECT.
GREAT.
SO, UM, HOW LONG ARE YOU
GONNA BE IN TOWN FOR?
JUST A FEW DAYS.
I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE LONGER.
REALLY, IT ALL DEPENDS.
WOULD YOU BE A DARLING
AND FILL MY GLASS?
THE BOTTLE'S ON THE TABLE.
SURE.
- YOU WANT A GLASS?
- I SHOULD PROBABLY
GET GOING.
WHY? YOU GOT TO
RUSH OFF SOMEWHERE?
NOT REALLY.
JUST GOT SOME ERRANDS.
I SEE.
IF YOU SEE ALICE,
COULD YOU TELL HER
I STOPPED BY?
- OF COURSE.
- ALL RIGHT.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
JOSH, CAN I ASK YOU
A PERSONAL QUESTION?
- I'M SORRY?
- I'M TRYING TO DECIDE
IF I SHOULD TELL YOU
SOMETHING ABOUT ALICE.
BUT FIRST I NEED TO ASK YOU
A PERSONAL QUESTION.
OKAY.
WHAT ARE YOUR TRUE
FEELINGS FOR HER?
- MY TRUE FEELINGS?
- ARE YOU STILL IN
LOVE WITH HER?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY,
I STILL CARE FOR ALICE.
- OKAY.
- BUT I--
I DON'T THINK I'M
IN LOVE WITH HER ANYMORE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT FADED, I GUESS.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE APART.
UM, SO WHAT WAS
THIS INFORMATION?
COME ON.  HAVE SOME WINE.
ONE GLASS WON'T KILL YOU.
GO ON THEN.
SO WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO TELL ME?
YOU'RE ALL BUSINESS,
AREN'T YOU, JOSH?
NO. I JUST HAVE THE FEELING
THAT YOU'RE TOTALLY
MESSING WITH ME.
WHAT IF I AM?
- HAVE YOU MET ANYONE NEW?
- NO.
UM, NOT SERIOUS ANYWAY.
WHY? HAS ALICE?
IS THAT IT?
NO. MAYBE.
I CAN'T BE SURE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU WITH ANYONE?
THERE IS SOMEONE.
HOW DO YOU MAKE IT WORK?
WE HAVE AN
OPEN RELATIONSHIP.
REALLY?
- MM-HMM.
- AND YOU'RE
COOL WITH THAT?
I THINK SO.
(chuckles)
IT'S A LITTLE
FRIGHTENING AT FIRST
WHEN YOU REALIZE YOU HAVE
OTHER DESIRES, YOU KNOW?
HOW DO YOU ADMIT
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
TO THE PERSON
THAT MOST COMPLETES YOU?
BUT IF YOU CROSS
THE LINE TOGETHER
AND YOU'RE HONEST
WITH EACH OTHER,
IT CAN BRING YOU CLOSER.
YOU TELL HIM EVERYTHING?
THAT'S PART OF THE DEAL.
WHAT ABOUT HIM?
DO YOU BELIEVE HE
TELLS YOU EVERYTHING?
OF COURSE.
(inaudible conversation)
...NOT GUILTY.
- DO YOU FEEL GUILTY
ABOUT SOMETHING?
- NO.
NOR DO I.
YOU REALLY--
YOU ARE QUITE SOMETHING.
WHAT WAS THE--
WHAT DID YOU WANT
TO TELL ME?
OKAY, I'LL TELL YOU
ON ONE CONDITION--
YOU HAVE TO GET
IN THE WATER.
NO WAY.  NO.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
WHAT IF ALICE
GETS BACK AND SEES ME?
SHE'LL KILL ME.
SHE'S NOT GONNA
BE BACK ANYTIME SOON.
DIDN'T SHE TELL YOU?
I'M HOUSESITTING.
SO?
LOOK.
NOW YOU'RE ALL WET.
NOW YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO COME IN.
(thudding footsteps)
(inhales weakly)
- MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T.
- THEN STOP.
(panting, moaning)
(cries out)
(whimpers faintly)
Lila: DAVID?
(saw buzzing faintly)
IT'S SO QUIET HERE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO MEET
THE NEIGHBORS.
(fork clinks)
IT WAS FUN TODAY,
WASN'T IT?
AFTER DINNER, WILL YOU
SET UP THE VIDEO?
- (grunts softly)
- (chains jingle)
HMM.
SHE HAD GOOD TASTE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S ACTUALLY
BEEN A PRETTY LONG DAY.
DAVID.
YOU'RE HAPPY
I'M BACK, RIGHT?
GOOD NIGHT, DAVID.
GOOD NIGHT, LILA.
(clicks)
(Josh speaking
on film)
(loud rustling
Don't lock us in.
Obviously.
(kissing on film)
(mumbles)
It's pretty hard
to do.
(giggles)
You're very talented.
- Cheers to?
- To...
our new home.
(clicks)
- (footsteps)
- Lila: BYE.
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
(knife slides free)
(creaks)
(chains jangling)
(Alice whimpering)
(gasping)
(breathlessly)
I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
PLEASE.
I HAVE MONEY.
(screaming)
HELP ME, PLEASE!
(shrieks)
HELP! SOMEBODY HELP!
NO ONE CAN HEAR YOU.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
(chains jangling)
HERE.
DRINK.
IF SHE FINDS OUT
YOU'RE ALIVE,
YOU'LL DIE.
OKAY.
I HAVE TO WORK.
WOULD YOU LIKE
SOMETHING TO READ?
I HAVE TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
OKAY.
COME ON.
KEEP THE DOOR OPEN.
I WON'T LOOK.
(toilet flushes)
COME ON.
LET'S GO.
(screaming)
HELP! HELP!
HELP ME!
(screams)
(shrieks)
(chuckling)
Oh, mur-der.
Grandmas.
What a fairytale.
Little men.
Oh brother!
(laughing)
(clanging on TV)
- (TV clicks off)
- SHE'LL BE HOME SOON.
(coughs)
THIS IS OUR SECRET.
(sizzling)
HI.
DID YOU EAT ALREADY?
- WHAT THE FUCK IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- NOTHING.
Lila:
I MET A FRIEND
FOR A DRINK, OKAY?
I'M SORRY I YELLED.
I DON'T WANT TO YELL.
YOU JUST--
YOU SUFFOCATE ME.
I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T BE THE ONLY ONE
WHO HAS TO CHANGE, YOU KNOW.
I KNOW.
- LILA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- LAUNDRY.
- I CAN DO THAT.
- I WANT TO.
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
I DON'T MIND--
DAVID, PLEASE.
I'M TRYING.
I KNOW HOW TO
DO LAUNDRY, DAVID.
COME ON,
YOU STUPID MACHINE.
- (clicks)
- (washer hums)
HERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
YOU CUT THE CRUSTS OFF.
MY MOM USED TO DO THAT.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO DO.
IT'S OKAY.
I UNDERSTAND.
BUT IF THIS
IS GONNA WORK,
WE NEED TO BE HONEST
WITH EACH OTHER.
OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
WOULD YOU LIKE
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'LL GET YOU SOME WATER.
(knocks on door)
- (muffled gasp)
- SHH.
(keys jangle)
HELLO?
MISS ALICE?
(speaking Spanish)
- HOLA, JOSE.
- HEY, MISS ALICE.
¿COMO ESTA?
- NO WORK TODAY?
- TODAY'S NO GOOD.
OH.
TODAY WAS NO GOOD?
YEAH, BUT IT'S MY FAULT.
I'LL STILL PAY YOU.
IT'S NO GOOD.
YEAH, 'CAUSE IF YOU WANT,
WE COULD JUST COME BACK LATER.
NO NO,
I'LL JUST CALL YOU.
OKAY.
YOU SURE?
- WE COULD JUST DO
THE OUTSIDE IF YOU WANT.
- I'LL CALL YOU.
OH. OKAY.
OH, OKAY.
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
(both speak Spanish)
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD'VE CALLED,
BUT NO CLEAN TODAY.
NO. NO, IT'S NO PROBLEM,
MISS ALICE.
(speaks Spanish)
- NO!
- (women screaming)
AH! AH!
YOU LIED TO ME.
(gasps, whimpers)
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
LIED TO ME.
(Alice whimpering,
crying)
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
LIED TO ME!
LOOK WHAT
YOU MADE ME DO!
LOOK... AT WHAT...
YOU... MADE...
ME... DO!
(sobbing)
(whimpers)
(groans)
MMN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
EVERYTHING FITS.
SHE MUST'VE BEEN YOUR TYPE.
HOW DID SHE WEAR HER HAIR?
LIKE THIS?
I DON'T REMEMBER.
OR MORE LIKE THIS?
DID SHE HAVE A NICE ASS?
OR IS MINE NICER?
(giggles)
YOU'RE SUCH A PRUDE!
LET'S DO
SOMETHING FUN.
I HAVE TO WORK.
DIDN'T YOU WORK
ALL DAY?
COME ON.
COME AND PLAY WITH ME.
LET ME READ IT,
PLEASE?
PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE
PLEASE PLEASE?
IT'S NOT
FINISHED YET.
WELL, FINISH IT LATER.
I WANT TO HAVE SOME FUN.
YEAH!
- LISTEN.
- ('80s music playing)
REMEMBER THIS?
COME ON.
DANCE WITH ME, DAVID.
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON.
DON'T YOU
REMEMBER THIS?
- NO, I DON'T REMEMBER IT.
- YES YOU DO.
HOW COULD YOU FORGET?
¶ ...off on a friend ¶
¶ Well, I thought
I heard you say... ¶
DON'T STOP.
¶ But I can't give up looks
until it's away ¶
(music swells,
echoing)
- DAVID?
- I DON'T--
DAVID?
I DON'T--
I DON'T FEEL WELL.
(music stops)
(retching)
WHAT'S WRONG, DAVID?
ARE YOU OKAY?
NOTHING.
I'M FINE.
- ARE YOU CRYING?
- NO.
I DON'T FEEL WELL.
DAVID, TAKE MY HAND.
COME ON, YOU NEED
TO LAY DOWN.
COME ON.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
DO YOU WANT A WET TOWEL
FOR YOUR HEAD?
I'M OKAY.
I'LL GET YOU ONE.
(faucet running)
(shuts off)
(kisses)
I MISS YOU.
WILL YOU COME UPSTAIRS?
I DON'T THINK
YOU REALLY LOVE ME.
OF COURSE I DO.
IF YOU LOVED ME,
YOU'D MAKE ME STOP.
YOU'RE SO FUCKING WEAK.
I TRIED
TO MAKE YOU STOP.
YOU LEFT ME.
Reporter: And there was
another drive-by shooting
today downtown.
It appears to be
gang-related.
Reporter #2:
The victim was taken away
unconscious,
but is expected
to recover fully
and should be able
to help police with
information.
Well, the crime rate
in this country
for the first time
in 50--
Chef on TV:
And then I like
to put in three tablespoons,
one, two, three,
of olive oil.
This baby needs
a good pinch of salt.
First of all,
that's very very very good.
And what it wants
is the following:
a little more--
(David screaming)
(grunts weakly)
(cries out)
YOU'RE STIFF.
YOU NEED TO MOVE YOUR BODY.
COME ON.
(cries out)
GO AHEAD.
GET UP ON THERE.
YOU CAN DO IT.
GOOD.
MOVE YOUR FEAT.
FASTER.
COME ON, MOVE YOUR FEET.
(shower pattering)
(handle squeaks,
water stops)
(shower door clacks)
I'M SORRY
THAT I BEAT YOU.
(grunts softly)
IT DOESN'T HAVE
TO BE THIS WAY.
YOU COULD GET AWAY
AND I COULD HELP YOU.
WE COULD HELP EACH OTHER.
YOU'RE NOT LIKE HER.
YOU'RE DIFFERENT.
IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK?
REALLY?
LET'S JUST GO RIGHT NOW.
OKAY?
LET'S JUST GO.
(whispers)
LET'S GO.
(knocks on door)
ALICE?
HELLO?
AH.
I GUESS SHE'S NOT HOME.
- YOU SURE IT'S OKAY.
- IT'S TOTALLY FINE.
PLEASE COME IN.
SO THE HOUSE
HAS A WONDERFUL FLOW.
YOU SEE HOW ALL THE--
YOU SEE HOW ALL THE ROOMS
ARE CONNECTED?
WONDERFUL.
ORIGINAL HARDWOOD FLOORS.
I LOVE THE STUDS.
(both chuckle)
IT'S HER.
GET IN THIS CLOSET.
SO HERE IS THE KITCHEN.
I LOVE THE MARBLE.
IT'S NICE, RIGHT?
AND CHECK OUT THE GARDEN.
- PEACEFUL.
- IT'S VERY PEACEFUL.
WHERE ARE THE BEDROOMS?
UM, THERE'S
A SMALLER BEDROOM
RIGHT THROUGH HERE.
THERE'S TWO MORE
BEDROOMS UPSTAIRS,
INCLUDING THE MASTER.
- IT'S...
- PERFECT FOR CHILDREN.
RIGHT?
SO SHE'S GOT IT SET UP
PRETTY NICELY WITH THE
FLAT SCREEN RIGHT THERE.
MMN.
AH, AND THE BATHROOM
HAS A FULL SHOWER.
I'LL TAKE IT.
(chuckles)
EXCUSE ME?
I WANT THIS HOUSE.
WOW, GREAT.
UM, THAT'S--
THAT'S GREAT.
- I JUST HAVE ONE QUESTION.
- OKAY.
IT'S A BIT OF A PERSONAL
QUESTION, ACTUALLY.
FIRE AWAY.
I WAS WONDERING.
DO YOU EVER GET TEMPTED?
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T REALLY
KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
(chuckles)
OKAY.
YOU HAD ME THERE
FOR A SECOND.
(laughs)
SO ARE YOU INTERESTED?
ARE YOU?
(chuckles)
WOW, OKAY.
UM, OKAY.
YOU DON'T
FIND ME ATTRACTIVE?
NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
YOU'RE NOT MARRIED,
ARE YOU?
NO.
THE OWNER OF THE HOUSE--
- UM...
- HM?
- SHE'LL NEVER KNOW.
- YEAH.
I PROMISE.
OKAY.
UM...
- NO, I REALLY--
I REALLY CAN'T DO THIS.
- SHH.
- (soft thud)
- WAIT.
- I THINK THERE'S
SOMEONE HERE.
- DON'T BE SILLY.
NO, I'M SERIOUS.
NO.
HELLO?
IS ANYONE--
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
WHAT THE FUCK, DAVID?!
SERIOUSLY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
- (Carl gurgling)
- I'M SORRY.
WILL YOU MOVE HIM
TO THE BATH?
I DON'T WANT THE BLOOD
SOAKING THROUGH TO THE
CEILING DOWNSTAIRS.
DAVID, DID YOU HEAR ME?
YES.
(Alice shivering)
(coughs wetly)
HE'S NOT DEAD.
I CUT HIS ARTERY.
HE WILL BE.
- LILA.
- YES?
WHAT?
NOTHING.
I'M GONNA USE
THE OTHER SHOWER.
I THINK I'D LIKE TO THROW
A DINNER PARTY.
REALLY?
WHAT, YOU DON'T
THINK WE SHOULD?
I WAS JUST--
WE BARELY SPEND
ANY TIME HERE JUST US.
WE'LL HAVE TO BE
ON THE MOVE SOON ANYWAY.
- (phone rings)
- (answering machine beeps)
Hey, it's Oscar.
I'm just checking up on you.
We got the message
from your doctor.
Hope you got your voice back
and you're feeling better.
Anyway, in case you were
wondering, the office is
so boring without you.
Call me, okay?
I want to know you're okay.
Just call me.
Love you.  Bye.
WHAT ABOUT TOMORROW NIGHT?
TOMORROW?
WHAT, YOU HAVE OTHER PLANS?
I WONDER
WHAT I SHOULD WEAR.
(latch clicks)
ALICE.
(whispers)
HERE'S A BLANKET.
Alice:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S ASLEEP.
HERE.
THIS'LL KEEP YOU WARM.
I WANT TO STOP.
REALLY?
YEAH.
THEN YOU'LL HAVE
TO LEAVE HER.
I KNOW.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
WILL YOU COME
WITH ME?
YEAH.
I'LL COME WITH YOU.
- (door opens, creaks)
- Lila: DAVID?
(both gasp)
DAVID.
(door closes)
WHERE'D YOU GO?
I WAS IN THE GARAGE.
OH.
I THOUGHT I HEARD YOU
TALKING TO SOMEONE.
NO.
I HAD TO CHECK ON
SOMETHING.
WHAT?
- ONE OF THE BODIES.
- OH.
ARE THEY ROTTING?
YEAH.
THEY'RE STARTING TO.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
GOT LONELY UP THERE
ALL BY MYSELF.
I COULDN'T FIND YOU.
I'M SORRY.
GOOD NIGHT, DAVID.
GOOD NIGHT, LILA.
(zipper zips)
DAVID?
DAVID!
I THOUGHT YOU LEFT
WITHOUT ME.
THANK YOU.
DAVID, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PREPARING DINNER.
YOU COULD HELP
IF YOU'D LIKE.
DON'T DO THIS, OKAY?
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO THIS.
IT'S NOT TOO LATE
TO STOP.
YOU HAVE TO
GO BACK DOWNSTAIRS.
WHY?
I KNOW YOU THINK
I'M DIFFERENT.
BUT LILA'S PART OF ME.
(phone ringing)
Hey, Alice.
It's Oscar again.
- I still haven't heard
from you. Are you okay?
- (scraping)
I'm starting
to get really worried.
Call me.
(scraping continues)
- DAVID, WHAT TIME IS IT?
- IT'S ALMOST 8:00.
ARE THERE
ANY MORE CANDLES?
I THINK WE NEED MORE CANDLES.
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
DECANT THE RED WINE?
- WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO?
- MAYBE.
I WANT EVERYTHING
TO BE PERFECT.
- IT IS PERFECT.
- SO?
- YOU LOOK GREAT.
- (giggles)
WHAT ABOUT THE SHOES?
TOO MUCH?
- THEY LOOK GOOD.
- THEY DO, DON'T THEY?
HURRY UP AND CHANGE.
PEOPLE ARE GONNA BE
ARRIVING ANY MINUTE.
I'M ALMOST DONE.
- HI!
LILA, THIS IS
MY FIANCÉ SETH.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HI. HERE. WE BROUGHT
YOU SOME WINE.
OH, THANK YOU.
THAT'S SO SWEET OF YOU.
DAVID'S JUST UPSTAIRS.
HE'LL BE DOWN IN A SECOND.
- I LOVE THIS HOUSE.
- OH, THANK YOU.
WE'RE REALLY HAPPY HERE.
PLEASE, COME ON IN.
(footsteps)
(mock laugh)
THERE HE IS.
DAVID, THIS IS
LAUREN AND SETH.
- HI. HOW ARE YOU?
- HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
- HI.
- HI. WELCOME.
THANK YOU.
AND THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR INVITING US.
OF COURSE.
WE LOVE MEETING
NEW PEOPLE.
DAVID, SETH AND LAUREN
JUST MOVED HERE
FROM SEATTLE.
NO.
UH, SAN FRANCISCO.
OH, RIGHT!
SAN FRANCISCO.
I'M SORRY.
AND YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
IS THAT RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I JUST STARTED MY
RESIDENCY AT CEDARS-SINAI.
SO HOW DID
YOU AND LILA MEET?
WE MET AT THE NAIL SALON,
- CAN YOU BELIEVE?
- YEAH, I CAN.
LILA WAS SO NICE.
WELL, HERE WE ARE.
- (doorbell rings)
- OH, I SHOULD GET THAT.
- DAVID, CAN YOU POUR THEM
SOME WINE, PLEASE?
- OF COURSE.
- OH, HI!
- HEY, LILA.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- AND YOU MUST BE BETHANY.
- YES. HI.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
COME ON IN.
Lauren:
DAVID, THIS FOOD
IS INCREDIBLE.
YOU HAVE TO SHARE
THE RECIPE.
DAVID IS AN
AMAZING COOK, ISN'T HE?
- EXCELLENT.
- DAVE, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
OPEN A RESTAURANT.
(giggles)
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULDN'T LAUGH.
I JUST CAN'T SEE
YOU DOING THAT.
HE LIKES TO WORK
FROM HOME.
WHAT KIND OF WORK
DO YOU DO, DAVID?
HE'S A WRITER.
OH YEAH?
WHAT KIND OF STUFF
DO YOU WRITE?
Lila:
OH, COME ON.
DON'T BE SO SHY.
- IT'S REALLY JUST A HOBBY.
- HE'S WRITING A
CHILDREN'S BOOK.
REALLY?
THAT'S WONDERFUL.
WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
- IT'S ABOUT TWO LITTLE CHILDREN
LIVING IN THE WOODS.
- LILA.
ONE DAY A CREATURE COMES
AND TELLS THEM ABOUT
THIS MAGICAL PLACE JUST
OUTSIDE OF THE FOREST
THAT HAS EVERYTHING
THEY COULD EVER DESIRE.
HE TELLS THEM THAT
HE'LL TAKE THEM THERE
ON ONE CONDITION:
THAT THEY CAN NEVER
GO BACK TO THEIR HOME.
SO THE CHILDREN FOLLOW
THE CREATURE ALL THE WAY
DEEP INTO THE WOODS,
BUT HE'S RUNNING
SO FAST THAT THEY
CAN'T KEEP UP.
HE LEAVES THEM
LOST AND ALL ALONE.
I ASKED YOU
NOT TO TELL IT.
BUT IT'S SO GOOD.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE ASHAMED.
DAVID.  DAVID?
DAVID.
IS THAT HOW IT ENDS, DAVID?
IS IT?
THEY CAN'T EXACTLY
FALL IN LOVE BECAUSE
THEY'RE BROTHER AND SISTER.
THAT IS WHAT YOU WROTE, HM?
TWINS?
OH, NONE FOR ME, THANKS.
I'M DRIVING.
MAYBE ONCE I GET TO KNOW
THE CITY A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
EXCUSE ME.
I HAVE TO CHECK
ON MY FIANCÉE.
(women giggling)
HONEY, IT'S GETTING
A LITTLE BIT LATE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
HEAD HOME?
OH, HONEY,
I'M HAVIN' FUN.
(laughs)
SEE?  SHE DOESN'T
WANT TO LEAVE.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I'M A PARTY POOPER.
UNFORTUNATELY,
I'M ON CALL TOMORROW.
UH, IT WAS
A LOVELY EVENING.
- (door opens)
- THANKS FOR HAVING US.
GOOD NIGHT.
(door closes)
Lila:
DAVID, COULD YOU POUR
SOME MORE WINE, PLEASE?
THANK YOU, DAVID.
NOW CAN YOU GO PUT ON
SOME MUSIC, PLEASE?
AH, THANK YOU.
('80s music playing)
WHAT WAS HER PROBLEM?
WASN'T EVERYTHING PERFECT?
IT WAS.
EVERYTHING WAS PERFECT.
THANK YOU.
(giggles)
¶ Well, I thought
I heard you say ¶
¶ And I know
I feel the rain... ¶
(glass clinks)
¶ But I can't
give up looks ¶
¶ Until it's away ¶
¶ Now I just
can't take ¶
¶ The way to live
my life ¶
¶ Holding dear
my last breath in my lungs ¶
¶ I know
i'll see you again ¶
¶ See you again ¶
¶ Don't take my hand
'cause I take it away ¶
¶ And I take everything
just to take it away ¶
¶ Well, you can't
give me problems ¶
¶ You can't
give me signs ¶
¶ As easy as you give,
I can take it away ¶
¶ Now I know
the things I say ¶
¶ Don't hold up
in the rain ¶
¶ Every touch was a gift
straight from my heart... ¶
(music fades)
- (screaming)
- (slicing, thudding)
- (screaming stops)
- (body thuds)
(sighs)
ARE YOU ALMOST FINISHED?
ALMOST.
IT DOESN'T HAVE
TO BE PERFECT.
YES, IT DOES.
DAVID, WE HAVE
TO LEAVE TOMORROW.
I WAS THINKING
MAYBE WE DON'T HAVE
TO LEAVE RIGHT AWAY.
WHAT?
WE'VE BEEN CAREFUL.
MAYBE WE CAN
STAY LONGER.
(laughs)
YOU KNOW WE CAN'T DO THAT.
IF IT'S TOO RISKY,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO STAY.
DAVID, WHERE IS THIS
COMING FROM?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
REALLY?
JUST, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
YOU CAME
BACK TO ME TONIGHT.
I SAW IT.
YOU CAN COME UPSTAIRS
IF YOU WANT TO.
WE CAN WATCH THE VIDEO.
(water splashes)
(weeping)
(sighs)
(shivering)
WHAT TIME IS IT?
IT'S EARLY.
(sighs)
DAVID, WILL YOU
GO TO THE STORE?
WE'RE OUT OF MILK.
DAVID.
DID YOU HEAR ME?
WE RAN OUT OF MILK
AND I NEED SOME
FOR MY COFFEE.
OKAY.
I'LL GO TO THE STORE.
I'M GONNA PACK.
DO YOU WANT ME TO MAKE
SANDWICHES FOR THE ROAD?
THAT'D BE NICE.
- (scraping)
- (grunting)
(panting)
(knife clatters)
(humming)
(Josh's voice
on film)
Alice on film:
YOU'RE A DORK.
(conversation
on film continues)
(flies buzzing)
HELLO?
ALICE?
YOU BITCH!
(Lila grunting)
(Alice panting)
(spits)
(loud thud)
(breathing heavily)
(footsteps)
OH JESUS.
Oscar: ALICE?
OH MY GOD.
(stammering)
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
- WHO'S COMING?
- HE'S COMING BACK.
JUST GET ME OUT.
JUST GET ME OUT!
(stammering)
WHERE ARE THE KEYS?
I DON'T KNOW.
GO IN THE GARAGE
AND GET SOME TOOLS.
WAIT. THERE'S NO--
(stammering)
GET THE TOOLBOX!
HE'S COMING!
WHO'S COMING?!
(rummaging loudly)
JUST HOLD THE CHAIN.
ALICE, I'M GONNA
CALL THE POLICE, OKAY?
I'M GONNA GO UPSTAIRS
AND CALL THE POLICE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- COME BACK FOR ME.
- I WILL!  I'LL BE
RIGHT BACK.
(rapid footsteps)
(gasping)
(phone beeps)
9-1-1.
What is your emergency?
JUST NEED--
YOU NEED TO HURRY.
I CAN'T GET HER OUT!
(Oscar cries out,
gurgles)
Sir, are you there?
Sir? The police are
on their way.
(rapid footsteps)
ALICE!
STAY BACK, DAVID,
OR I SWEAR I'LL KILL HER.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I'LL CUT HER GODDAMN THROAT!
THROW ME THE KEYS, DAVID.
THROW ME
THE FUCKING KEYS, DAVID!
I'M GONNA KILL HER, DAVID.
I'M GONNA SLIT
HER FUCKIN' THROAT.
IF YOU KILL HER,
WE CAN GO.
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID?
I SAID I'LL KILL HER.
IT'S OKAY.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
WE'LL BE TOGETHER.
HERE.
JUST CUT.
I'LL SHOW YOU.
GOODBYE, LILA.
DAVID?
- (Alice cries out)
- ALICE!
- ALICE.
- (gasping)
(gasping, wheezing)
(coughing)
WHAT'D YOU THINK, DAVID?
THAT SHE REALLY LOVED YOU?
NO ONE'LL EVER
LOVE YOU EXCEPT ME.
WE HAVE TO GO NOW,
DAVID.
COME ON.
WE NEED TO GO.
(garage door whirring)
(police sirens
blaring)
(gasping)
IT WAS BUILT IN 1952--
SO MID-CENTURY MODERN.
THESE WINDOWS
ARE ALL ORIGINAL
AND THEY REALLY DO ALLOW
THE HOUSE JUST TO BE
FILLED WITH LIGHT.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I LOVE IT.
IT'S HOME.
('80s music playing)
¶ I JUST COULDN'T WAIT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ NO, I NEVER EVER
TURN OFF ON A FRIEND ¶
¶ WELL, I THOUGHT
I HEARD YOU SAY ¶
¶ AND I KNOW
I FEEL THE RAIN ¶
¶ BUT I CAN'T GIVE UP LOOKS
UNTIL IT'S AWAY ¶
¶ NOW I JUST CAN'T TAKE ¶
¶ THE WAY TO LIVE MY LIFE ¶
¶ HOLDING DEAR
THE LAST BREATH IN MY LUNGS ¶
¶ 'CAUSE I'LL
SEE YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ SEE YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ DON'T TAKE MY HAND
'CAUSE I TAKE IT AWAY ¶
¶ AND I TAKE EVERYTHING
JUST TO TAKE IT AWAY ¶
¶ WELL, YOU CAN'T
GIVE ME PROBLEMS ¶
¶ YOU CAN'T
GIVE ME SIGNS ¶
¶ AS EASY AS YOU GIVE,
I CAN TAKE IT AWAY ¶
¶ NOW I KNOW
THE THINGS I SAY ¶
¶ DON'T HOLD UP
IN THE RAIN ¶
¶ EVERY TOUCH WAS A GIFT
STRAIGHT FROM MY HEART ¶
¶ WELL,
THEN TAKE IT AWAY ¶
¶ TAKE IT AWAY ¶
¶ AWAY ¶
¶ I TAKE IT AWAY ¶
(music continues)
¶ I JUST COULDN'T WAIT
TO SEE YOU AGAIN ¶
¶ NO, I'LL NEVER EVER TURN
OFF ON A FRIEND ¶
¶ WELL, I THOUGHT
I HEARD YOU SAY ¶
¶ AND I KNOW
I FEEL THE RAIN ¶
¶ BUT I CAN'T GIVE UP LOOKS
UNTIL IT'S AWAY ¶
¶ DON'T TAKE MY HAND
'CAUSE I TAKE IT AWAY... ¶
(music fades out)
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3jf49
Help other users to choose the best subtitles