Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Go well past it.
Right.
Oh, I thought...
You need to go
one block this way...
This is LaSalle?
This is LaSalle Street.
All you have to do is go
two blocks this way, one block
that way, and you're there.
Thanks.
Sure.
Holy shit.
Tom, I just hit somebody.
Can you believe it?
Okay, Le Petit Auberge
at 8:00. Right.
Oh, damn!
Is he all right?
Somebody call an ambulance!
It wasn't my fault. He stepped
off the curb in front of me.
You saw it, didn't you?
I saw it.
Great. Great.
Is he okay?
You saw him jump
in front of my car, right?
Do you mind?
This man is hurt.
Someone call the police.
Please? Call the police.
No, no.
I'll call them.
No.
I'm late for work.
I'm gonna get fired
my first day on thejob.
I-I-I don't think
you should move.
You could have
internal bleeding
or soft tissue injury.
What?
Look, you're sitting up.
You're fine.
We should wait for the police.
They're gonna know
what to do with this.
Ow. Oh.
You might think about
calling your lawyer.
Hey, look. We do not
have to make a federal case
out of this thing, huh?
Why don't I give you,
say, uh, ooh, uh,
a hundred dollars
for your troubles?
What? Ow.
My cousin Al got nailed
one time like this.
I think he got paid
something like
a million-five.
Okay, okay, uh,
everything I got.
Uh, 266.
I'm late.
What time is it?
The guy can't afford
a watch, you give him
a lousy 266?
Here. Take mine.
Really? Thanks.
That's a nice ring.
Ow.
All right.
Come on.
Easy. Easy. Ow! Geez!
Okay. Take it easy.
Move out of the way!
Give the guy some room!
Ice is good for this.
Take care of the leg,
all right?
Okay. Yeah, he's...
Very good.
Ice and heat.
No, heat and ice! That's it.
Boy, you are
a lucky guy. Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, um, little word of advice,
if you don't mind.
Advice?
From now on,
hands on the wheel,
eyes on that road.
Okay? Wheel, road.
All right.
- No, no, no, no!
Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Oh, ladies. Hello.
What?
Please accept this gift
on behalf of the city
of Chicago.
Thank you very much,
and have a nice day. Bye!
Hey! Think fast.
Lou, Lou, Lou.
Eddie, Eddie, Eddie.
That new bit
about your cousin Al?
That was genius.
Thank you.
You see that guy's face
when you said a million-five?
Yeah!
You know, Lou,
that was your best hit ever!
Thank you.
Not only that,
now we can eat
something tonight, huh?
Well, now that depends
on who won the exacta
in the sixth.
Oh, no, not again.
Sammy swore to me
that that jockey
was paid off!
Lou, you don't bet horses.
You bet dogs.
I know.
Horses are a...
A gamble.
Dogs are a...
Investment.
Smart guys
are dog guys.
Dog guys. I know.
Hello, Lou!
No!
Hey, hey, easy, easy.
Pink, easy.
He don't call me,
bet a grand and stand me up
for three days.
I want it all,
and I want it now!
Did you hear that, Lou?
That's what I admire
about this man.
The directness,
the ability
to express urgency.
Very important
when running a business.
You think you're funny.
Sal Nichols
is gonna tear your head off.
Is that funny enough for you?
That's very funny.
Louis.
Can I have
your money, please?
Thank you.
That's 266.
So we owe Mr. Nichols what?
What do I look like,
a rocket scientist?
All right, uh, $734.
He's gonna have it
tomorrow.
- You'd better, 'cause I
don't like you guys.
- Really? Hmm.
'Cause we like you.
We should hang out.
I'm not just saying that.
And you know what?
Lately you look good.
Did you change your hair
or lose some weight?
Whatever it is, it works.
Tomorrow!
Louis.
Where are we gonna get
700 bucks, huh?
- Yeah?
- Bob Marley,
Lakeshore Utility.
We've got
a class-A level gas leak
in the neighborhood.
Get a reading,
Tommy!
Right!
- Uh, wait a second.
- Apologize for
the inconvenience, sir.
Excuse me...
It cannot be helped.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
How long is this gonna take?
No way
of telling that.
- Smell that? Whoo!
- Hmm.
I don't smell anything.
Because you've been here
the whole time.
Anyone else here?
Children, dogs, fish?
My wife took the kids
to their karate lesson.
What are you getting?
High readings.
Oh, hell.
Is that bad?
Where's that furnace?
It's in the basement.
This way.
Tommy, check every room,
and make sure that it is safe.
This way. Come on.
All right.
Just don't touch me.
Whoo!
What's that?
That's the dryer.
Clothes dryer?
Yes. It's electric.
You don't sound too sure.
No, it's electric.
- What's that?
- That's my...my lawn mower.
How long you had it?
I don't know.
A couple years. Why?
Could be nothing.
What is going on?
Maybe you should tell me.
Well, looks like 12-gauge,
7.1 hardened steel.
Less than six inches
off the ground.
- Does it always make
that sound?
- Is that dangerous?
- There it is.
- What?
Bob, get up here!
I've got a gas pocket!
I can't! I just pushed
the gas-flow igniter!
I need you right now!
This whole house could blow up!
Oh, Jesus!
Come here, come here,
come here.
Put your finger
on this button.
Come on.
Now, do not let go
of that button.
Do you understand me?
Whatever happens,
do not let go.
Right.
I-I-I understand.
I understand.
Come on.
All right.
All right, all right, okay.
Easy.
What's going on?
Uh, nothing
to worry about.
Just decompressing
the gas pocket.
Decompressing the gas?
Stan!
We're home, honey!
Oh.
Don't come in!
There's a gas pocket!
It's okay, though.
The men are here.
Why do they have
our television?
Ain't this one of them
new gas TVs?
I'm calling the police.
Hah!
Now, uh, just
take it easy, kids.
- We don't wanna hurt you.
- Hah!
Eddie, let's
get out of here!
Stan, get upstairs!
Boys, be careful!
Go, go, go! Go!
Kids, be careful!
Boys, come back!
Yah!
Let's not ever...
tell anyone
what just happened.
What are you doing?
What?
Check it out.
No lights on, newspapers,
no killer kids...
Bida-bing-bam-boom.
No, no.
We are not break-in men, Lou.
We are con artists.
All right?
Eddie, this is no time
for splitting hairs.
I got Pinkie all over me, man.
I'm in the mood for a good,
old-fashioned burglary.
No, no.
This is not
your field, okay?
I would rather be
a live burglar...
than a dead
con artist.
- Come on.
- No. No. No.
You're a surgeon, Lou.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Careful.
Ah! Go! Get out!
Shut it! Shh!
I just shut...
I'm sorry.
Okay. All right.
God!
Oh, Eddie, man,
look at this place.
Oh, my God.
Someone lives here.
Yes.
And I hate them for it.
God, this place
has everything. Oh.
Look at that.
Take what you have to take,
and let's get the hell out.
Okay. Decisions, decisions.
Eddie. Eddie,
give me a hand.
All right, all right.
Ow. Shine the light.
Okay. CD player.
An excellent choice.
Thanks.
Hi, you've reached David Malkin.
I'm off to India.
I'll be gone a few months,
but you can leave a message
forJonathan Albertson.
He'll be staying
at the house.
Thanks.
Go. Let's go. Go.
David, it's Jonathan.
You probably missed this call,
but they upped that offer
on thatjob in Seattle,
and I couldn't pass up
the big bucks.
Go.
The nub of it is,
I can't house-sit
for you.
What?
As Pericles said
to the Athenians,
"Let each man receive
according to his merits. "
That's me, pal.
C'est la vie.
Good thing
Eddie. Creamsicles.
This guy really does
have everything.
As Pericles
said to the Athenians,
I really need another beer.
Okay.
This is the life.
Really.
When I hit it big,
I'm gonna get this.
Big screen TV. Same deal.
Pool table, wife, kids.
Me too. Same deal.
TV, wife, kids.
I'm afraid.
Eddie, the guy's in India.
No, that's not it.
It's the idea of you
having children.
That's one of
the most frightening things
I've ever heard of in my life.
Ooh!
All right,
let's go see Max.
Breaking and entering.
What did you do,
take stupid pills?
You got the gift.
I knew you had it
when you brought home
your first bicycle.
What were you,
eight?
You can play people
like a Stradivarius.
But that guy back there
is a plumber.
Oh, no. No, not this again.
Now, come on.
He's my friend.
Loyalty I like.
He's my friend!
But that guy's a bozo.
You've been carrying him
since you were 11.
You need a new partner.
Well, you could always
come out of retirement. Huh?
Eddie... Don't tempt me.
Come on.
The good old days were great!
Let's move those legs!
I'm an old guy.
Come on. Cut it out.
I was good, wasn't I?
Yeah, you were.
You know, Eddie,
when you were little...
you know,
before your mother died...
I made her a promise
that I wouldn't raise a bum.
You did good, Max.
Well, maybe I did,
and maybe I didn't.
I just taught
you all I knew
like I would my own son.
I know that.
It's just that...
Sometimes I feel there's
got to be more out there...
than picking up
chump change
at car accidents.
Of course there is. The world
is full of opportunities
for a bright young man.
Bank scams, stock swindles.
Those are the big ones.
I mean, that's what life
is all about, kid.
Hey, Max.
Yeah?
Can I have my wallet?
I still got it,
don't I?
Velvet hands.
Nice touch.
Eddie.
How about my watch?
I got no damn shot.
You're bad luck, Farrel.
If I hadn't seen this today,
Sal would've had me bury you.
You can't even bury
an eight ball, Pinkie.
Put your money
where your mouth is,
chooch.
Well, sweet little Mary
was just 13
Can you spot me a 20?
Walkin'down the street
she'd make a good man mean
Take a truthin'man
and she could
make him a liar
She could take the coolest cat
and set his soul on fire
It's all yours.
Mercy, little baby
now I'm down on my knees
You got me workin'
every night, baby
tryin'to please
It's good work
if you can get it
It's good work...
Oh, man. Oh, man.
Uh, uh, oh, oh.
It's good work
if you can get it
Baby, just let it work
Let it work, let it work
let it work, let it work
It was lucky.
I don't pay luck.
And don't let me see
your ugly faces again!
Hey, hey.
Easy. Easy!
Come on.
Come on!
Big turd.
Jerk.
Heh. Huh?
Louis,
what are you doing?
Autographing Pinkie's car.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Th-That's not nice.
Let's do something nice
for the guy.
Let's give Pinkie
a convertible.
I said, hey, babe
take a walk on the wild side
And the colored girls say
Doo doo doo doo doo
Doo doo doo doo
doo doo doo doo
Eddie, don't.
Don't answer it.
Eddie, resist the temptation
just this once.
I can't. Why not?
You can.
Just this once.
Come on. I have to. Uh...
Hello.
Greetings.
My name is Tagra.
Am I talking to the jerk
who stole my car?
Listen, scumbag...
He's really pissed.
Great.
I do not appreciate
your profanity.
If you wish to continue
this conversation,
may I suggest a new attitude,
one more positive?
Listen to me,
jerk face...
I am talking!
You do not talk when I talk.
When I talk, you do not talk.
It is very simple.
Now, who am I talking to?
Hey, punk, this is
Sal Nichols,
and you'd better
shut your mouth and listen.
Ohhh.
Oh, I am speaking
with Sal Nichols,
and you want your car.
Sal Nichols?
Hang up. Hang up!
Ah! Oh! Ah!
Sal Nichols!
Oh, great!
Pull over.
Where?
Here!
Anywhere! Pull over!
Let's go.
Let's go! Eddie!
Let's go!
Run!
Come on, Eddie!
It's insured, Sal.
It's only 500 deductible.
Hey, I'll pay it myself.
Mr. Marino,
the automobile
is only part
of a greater problem.
There was $60,000
in the trunk.
- Now, how many times
have you been instructed...
not to leave my collections
in the trunk, scumbag?
Wait a minute, Sal.
I know who did this.
It was a couple of creeps
I been doing business with.
Eddie Farrel and Lou Pasquino.
They're the guys you want,
not me!
Your business practice
has become a source
of great irritation to me,
and I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to
relieve you...
of your financial
responsibilities.
Ah! Ooh! Oh! Ah!
Find Mr. Farrel
and Mr. Pasquino.
I want my money back.
Eddie,
where are we goin'?
We'll know when we get there.
Oh, shit.
Get the lights.
Open the door!
Let's go.
Oh... Uh...
What you want?
Sal Nichols wants his money!
Money? What?
Sorry. Got no money.
You two jerks
took $60,000
out of his trunk.
Sixty thou...
Sixty... Let's go!
I wonder
what he's talkin' about.
Oh.
Jerks not here.
No-Nobody here.
Eddie!
Uh, they let me stay
because I am leper.
I am leper.
Oh, very bad disease.
Got bump everywhere.
Don't look good.
Let's go!
Oh, yeah. You stay out.
I make it simple:
Come in, bump;
stay out, no bump.
Your decision!
It's not going down.
It'll go down.
Eddie, what's wrong
with this thing?
Come on.
Eddie!
We missed 'em, goddamn it!
We gotta get out of here.
Right.
What the hell you doin'?
What?
- Eddie!
- What?
Later!
Much later.
Hello?
Uncle Max, it's me.
You okay?
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I'm fine. Listen.
If Lou calls...
He did?
He just called.
Eddie, are you in trouble?
Then where is he?
I have no idea.
Okay, that doesn't
matter now. Listen.
If he calls again,
tell him that I am at
the stereo house.
"Stereo house"?
He'll know what I mean.
You're at the stereo house.
Okay.
Thanks, Max.
Oh, God.
Take a hike.
Hey, I was browsing.
Hi!
Ahh!
Come in
And pull yourself up a chair
Like Chairry!
Let the fun begin
It's time to let down
your hair
Pee-Wee's
sure excited
Uh-huh.
All his friends
have been invited
That's you!
It's so wacky
at Pee-Wee's Playhouse
Uhhh!
There's
a crazy rhythm
Comin' from Puppetland
What's that?
Oh, God, that sucks.
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
Every day you wake up
I hope it's under a blue sky
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
Wow.
I'll just be
a minute, honey.
Oh! Doh! Ooh. Oh.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
I must be in the wrong house.
Oh, no,
you're in the right house.
Oh. I'm so sorry,
but you scared me to death.
David said
you were coming tomorrow.
Oh, this is David's house.
Oh, what a relief. Oh.
- Well, then you must be, uh...
Now, don't tell me.
- Mona.
Mona!
Oh, I-I heard a scream.
It's all right, honey.
I'm fine.
Jonathan Albertson,
I'd like you to meet
my favorite husband Milton.
Jonathan Albertson?
Well, nice to meet you,
Milton. Milt.
Milt.
Well... Mona and Milt.
David's parents.
Oh, of course!
It's just that I always
think of you as Milt and Mona.
Well, we just came over
to leave you a welcome note.
But now that we've got you
in our clutches,
you absolutely must come
for lunch at the club.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I can't.
I mean, I would
love to, of course,
but, uh, I'm pretty lagged out
from the flight, and, uh,
the limo didn't meet me
at the airport, and they
scratched one of my good bags.
- Oh, poor baby.
- Oh, it gets worse.
They lost another one
of my bags,
with my wallet and all
my credit cards and... Oh!
The nub of it is,
it's like losing your identity.
It's been a complete nightmare.
C'est la vie.
I love it!
He's broke!
One of the rising young stars
in American business,
and he needs a loan.
What do you want? One?
What, you want two?
Oh, I-I couldn't.
You want three?
Here. You're good for it,
aren't you?
Oh, Milt.
Now, front door, back door,
and the car's in the garage.
All right.
Now you have no reason
not to have lunch with us.
Another sun was shining
and he knew he wasn't great
He didn't ever talk about
he knew he couldn't wait
Time is running out
the illusion fades away
another day is on its way
I can't wait
for you two to meet.
Mom, I'm sure I'm not his type.
Well, if his type is
a nice, intelligent girl,
you're his type.
Mom, David said that he
used to date Miss Texas.
If you think
that I'm gonna
twirl a baton...
and sing the national anthem
in a bikini for this guy,
you're crazy.
I used to do that
for your father.
Didn't I, Milt?
Leave her alone, Mona.
Jonathan!
Hi.
Oh. Jonathan.
Glad you made it.
Come.
Milt.
Welcome.
Hi, Jonathan.
Jonathan,
this is Annie.
Well, I always thought
David was exaggerating.
- He wasn't.
- And, uh,
we've heard aboutJonathan
since David's freshman year,
haven't we?
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Uh, it's nice
to finally put a face...
to the reputation.
Well, I, uh, hope
I can live up to
at least a little bit...
of what David
has told you all about me.
- He told us you were single.
That's a good first step.
Mr. Malkin,
your table is ready.
Oh.
Table's ready.
Great.
Thank you, Cyril.
Why don't we celebrate?
My good man,
as Pericles said
to the Athenians,
where do I drain
the lizard?
Thanks.
Hey, hey.
How many sinks
do you need?
Does this cost anything?
It's complimentary, sir.
Hmm.
Jonathan Albertson.
Pleasure to meet ya.
Jonathan, I've got to
ask you something.
Phillips made you
the youngest V.P. ever, right?
And you walk away
to take a shot
at something better.
Now, that takes guts.
Hey, hey.
So, tell me,
what are you after now?
Well, negotiating
a few oil leases up north.
You must be familiar with
the U.S. oil lease program,
huh, Milt?
- Could be the bonanza.
- Risky business.
Wouldn't put a dime in it.
Yeah, it has a downside.
I agree. I agree.
That's why I'm, uh,
really leaning...
toward a very interesting
situation in Mexican coins.
Come on, Jonathan.
What I'm interested in
are those interviews.
You turned down
Procter & Gamble, AT&T,
Colonial Insurance. Why?
Why? Why?
Yes, why?
Why? Milt.
I think we're boring the ladies.
Thank you, Jonathan.
- Mr. Malkin.
- Jonathan, I understand
you're the great sommelier.
So why don't you do the honors.
Well, it's, uh...
it's been a while
since I, uh,
"sommeliered."
Actually, most of my equipment
is still in storage.
"Equipment is
in storage."
Well, uh...
Yeah, I'll have
this one right here.
Excuse me,
but that is the address
of the wine distributor.
Yeah. How about this one?
That is
the surcharge, sir.
May I suggest something
a little higher up on the page?
Chateau Lafite.
Oh. Excellent.
Excellent.
Hope everybody's thirsty.
Annie, the beeper again?
Are you the only doctor
they have down there?
Dad, I'll be right back.
Wow, a doctor.
You two must be very proud
of that girl.
Yeah. Sometimes I think
she works too hard.
Mm.
Hey, you know, if you ask me,
hard work and dedication
is what it is all about.
- Look at Elvis.
- Who?
Elvis. Elvis Presley.
Thirty-five platinum albums.
Ha-Had his...
Had his own floor at Caesar's.
Really?
Mrs. Gonzalez
is having her baby.
Annie, you practically donate
your time. You have to do it
in the middle of lunch?
Dad, calm down.
Listen, I'll tell you what.
If it's a boy,
I'll suggest
Milt Gonzalez.
Bye, Dad. Bye, Mom.
- Good-bye, sweetheart.
- Bye, Jonathan.
Bye.
Chateau Lafite.
- Think he'll come back
and burp me after lunch, Milt?
What are you
saving it for there, slim?
Come on, come on.
Yeah.
Wow! That is incredible!
You guys
gotta try this. Mm!
Thirty-five years ago,
my father started
making hand dryers.
And today,
aside from making blowers,
we make over 18%
of all the bathroom stalls
in the U.S.,
thirteen percent
of all the fixtures
and accessories.
But still, our high profit item
is the classic Malkin Blower.
Mr. Malkin, Mr. Malkin.
Mr. Harris
finished his meeting
with Mr. Nimaku.
The interpreter left,
but Mr. Nimaku still seems
to have one other question.
Well, we've got the man
right here, Vi.
Great.
Two years
at the Nagasaki office
at Phillips.
Help us out,
will ya, Jon.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, th-that's easy.
He, uh...
He's saying that he is
happy to be here.
Oh.
He b... He's saying
that he admires the power
of the Malkin Blower...
and the way it strikes
the moisture off his hand!
Huh?
Oh, he says
that Malkin Blowers
are number one!
Somebody oughta tell him
what that means in America.
Jesus.
Yeah.
Well, this might seem
like a small operation
compared to Phillips,
but, uh,
we call it home.
It's got a nice view.
It's very nice.
Very nice.
Oh-ho. Milt.
Ernie Banks? Huh?
Color me impressed.
You, from Harvard,
and a Cubs fan?
Thought all you guys did was row
those skinny boats around.
Come on. What,
are you kidding me?
I have been
a loyal Cubs fan
all my life.
How about
that Ernie Banks, huh?
"The Cubs
will shine in '69!"
Ha! "Let's play two!"
Ha-ha-ha!
"Let's play two!"
I gotta show you somethin'.
Wait till you see this.
There we go.
Ernie Banks's...
four hundred and ninety-ninth
home run ball.
Number 500
is in the Baseball Hall of Fame.
Oh. "Milt... Nice catch.
Ernie Banks, 5/9/70."
Huh.
That's my
most prized possession.
It'd be mine too. Hmm.
Hey, uh,
you ever hear of a bank?
You must have
a hundred grand
sitting here.
It's 180.
Most of my suppliers
are from the old school.
This stuff
is the only thing they trust.
Trust...
is a wonderful thing.
Didn't go for oil.
He didn't go for coins.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do next.
There's a con
for everybody, Eddie.
You just gotta scratch a little.
Why don't you go to work
for the old man?
What am I gonna do,
walk in with a briefcase
and do card tricks?
I know nothing
about business.
Well, you're gonna say
I'm sentimental,
but my intuition tells me...
June's the time
for the love con.
Go for the daughter.
Mm-mm. No way.
She's too smart.
So read a couple of books.
No, this... this chick is cold.
- So warm her up.
- Your Aunt Connie's right.
The way to a man's money
is through his daughter.
That's one of your basics.
And we're not just talking
about the 180 grand.
That's just the tip of
the iceberg. You're building
your future, Eddie.
Gee, I remember
my first marriage.
I mean, I left him in a motel
in the Poconos.
He was wearing a top hat
and his socks.
I hocked our wedding silver,
took your Uncle Max to Bermuda.
It sure beats workin', Eddie.
You know, guys,
I think I'm fallin' in love.
Hi, Harold.
Hiya, Doc.
How you doing today?
I'm all right today.
How are you?
You feel okay?
All right.
Yes, I do, Doc.
Oh, I'm here
for my checkup. Yeah.
I been talking
like this all day.
Wait. Wait.
Oh, I'm fine. I guess I just had
to clear my throat. I'm okay.
- What are you doing here?
- Oh.
Actually, Milt tells me
you're doing some
great work down here.
Uh-huh.
Oh, my God. Oh!
You look incredible
in a stethoscope.
Does that look like
a barstool to you?
This is not
a pick-up joint. Okay?
It's a clinic.
Now, I really think
you should leave.
Wait, wait.
I didn't come down here
to pick you up.
I don't know where
you got that idea.
I came down here
to, um, uh,
help... help out.
You want to help?
Yeah.
That's wonderful.
Lie down.
Why?
Well,
because you're
gonna give blood.
No! Wrong. Sorry. Eh!
Time out. No, no, no.
No, no. Ha-ha.
I don't do this sort of thing.
I don't have extra blood.
Sure, you do. Lie down.
Push up your sleeve.
Does this kind of activity...
Is... Does it hurt?
You ever been bit
by one of them big bumblebees?
Harold, stop it.
Oh, uh, wait.
Okay, okay.
I got a much better idea.
Wh-Why don't I make some sort
of a financial contribution?
Maybe a portion
of my Alaskan oil profits.
A tax write-off?
Come on. You're a big boy.
Very funny, Harold.
I do my best.
What you in for, Harold?
For going too fast.
There are some fine ladies
over at the home still waiting
on old Harold Monroe.
Well, Harold, we'll try
not to disappoint them.
Oh.
H-Hold on. No, shouldn't
I drink some whiskey
or bite on a stick or...
Ow, ow, ow.
Ah... Ah...
Jonathan?
Well, welcome back.
You're okay.
You just passed out.
Good-bye, Mr. Albertson.
No, ah.
I'll get it.
Hello.
Hello, Mona? Is that you?
This is Jonathan.
Oh! Hello.
It is you.
Gosh, you sound so young.
Now, what is your secret?
Jonathan, you stop that.
I love it.
Listen, how would you and Milt
like to go, uh, waterskiing
this Saturday?
I've made all the arrangements.
Oh, Jonathan,
I'm so sorry.
We can't.
It's our nephew's
bar mitzvah
on Saturday.
Wait. Wait, wait.
Why don't you come?
No, no.
That is a family affair.
Jonathan!
Temple Beth Shalom
at 10:00.
You'll get to meet
Annie's favorite bubbie.
All right, all right,
enough twisting my arm.
You've got me, okay?
I'll be there.
See you then. Bye-bye.
Bye.
Temple.
Albertson.
Holy Christ. I'm Jewish.
Tradition
Traditions,
traditions.
Without our traditions,
our lives would be
as shaky as...as...
Oy vey.
as a fiddler
on the roof.
So, why don't...
I would like to dance
with the most ravishing woman
in the world.
I'm sorry...
Bubbie,
what do you say?
Ooh-hoo!
Oh, how he talks!
Let's go.
Milt, what's the matter?
Nothing.
Milt.
Look at him.
Jonathan.
Who? Ah.
I would give five V.P. s for one,
oneJonathan Albertson.
Milt, will you leave
the office already?
Jonathan is David's friend.
Now, don't be pestering him.
Come on.
Give me a smile.
Terrific.
We went to McDonald's.
She was still trying to order
the dim sum dumplings.
At McDonald's yet!
Crazy!
What is so funny,
you two?
Oh, we decided
you're too serious.
Go. Enjoy.
So, if at first
you don't succeed,
work on the bubbie, huh?
Guilty. What can I say?
Come on.
Please, let's just
have some fun.
This is as fun as I get.
Really? So then
you're gonna make me...
go out here all by myself?
You know, I'm very nervous
on a dance floor.
I don't really know how.
When I look
into your eyes
So much passion
burns inside
If you need some coaxing
I will do it
Step by step
there's nothing to it
One, two, three, four
Come on, baby
say you love me
Five, six, seven times
Eight, nine
ten, eleven
- I'm just gonna
keep on counting
Until you are mine
One, two, three, four
Come on, baby
say you love me
Five, six, seven times
Eight, nine, ten, eleven
I'm just gonna
keep on counting
until you are mine
Oh, hey, there.
There it was.
You definitely laughed.
That was a big laugh,
and, really,
this is a very
solemn occasion,
and I may have to report you
to the Solemn Occasion Police.
Uh, that wasn't a laugh.
I was yawning.
No, I have to disagree.
It was most definitely a laugh.
Okay, but it was more
a "Boy, what an idiot" laugh.
Really? Boy,
I could've swore it was a...
"My God, he's incredibly
charming,"and"How do I
get to know him better?" laugh.
There it is again. That's two.
I'm on a roll. I'm very happy.
David never mentioned
this side of you.
Well, uh, there's
a few things about me...
that might surprise
even David.
Eddie?
Eddie!
You couldn't say "Meet me
at the pinball machine house,"
or the pool table house.
Or "Meet me at
the Creamsicle house."
That I would've known.
Eddie. Oh.
Now, remember,
don't tell Mona.
She'll never know.
"Tilt"?
Great.
- Well, it's about time!
- Lou!
Uh... what the hell
are you doing here?
Sal Nichols
has a contract
out on us.
Oh, great.
That contract
came through.
That's terrific.
I'll have my lawyers
check on that in the morning.
Ah.
Uh, Milt.
I would like you
to meet Lou Pasquino.
Milt Malkin.
Milt.
How do you do?
Lou's my broker.
Hey, kill the music, and, uh,
why don't you get us
a couple of beers?
We have a lot
to talk about.
Beers.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
He had a complete
nervous breakdown.
Totally wiped out
on Black Monday.
You're kidding.
Well, this won't take long.
I just wanted to show you
some sales charts.
All right.
Now, these are the, uh,
the sales projections...
and inventory totals
of the past two quarters.
You've got that sideways.
There you go.
Well, you...
you said you wanted
a fresh perspective, right?
Mm-hmm.
Well, this is serious.
Turn it this way,
like I had it, it looks like
the Rocky Mountains. I mean...
My God, you put
your finger right on it.
These have been
the most erratic sales figures
that we've had in 35 years.
We don't have
a snowball's chance
in hell...
of getting a, uh,
a sales budget
under these conditions.
I don't want to make you
uncomfortable.
I know the big guys
are after you, but,
damn it, I need you.
You walk into my company,
you're vice president
in charge of marketing.
Me?
Yes.
Well...
Excuse me, Milt.
What are you movin'?
Nothing's moving.
That's the problem.
You're a broker?
I am a broker.
What's your specialty?
Oh, whatever you need.
Take a look at these babies.
Oh, Lou,
you're great.
Chicago, Tokyo, London.
This guy lives the market.
Oh, I don't believe it!
Look how late it's gotten.
Milt, do you mind
if we do this, uh,
in a day or two?
We sure can, as long as
it's in your new office.
I'm not leaving
until you say yes.
I'll give it a try.
Oh, Jon.
Jon.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Wonderful. We're gonna be
a hell of a team.
I know.
I know it too.
What great news.
Monday morning,
Mr. Vice President.
I'll be looking
forward to it.
Eddie, you got
a coaster on your head.
According to all the research
done for hand dryer
and bathroom accessories,
name-brand recognition
is still the key factor.
Look at the third survey,
page seven.
The company has
no alternative but to increase
advertising expenditures...
in the third quarter.
That's a $3-million price tag
we're talking about,
just to remain competitive.
Hold it, hold it.
Hold it a second.
I'm hearing the same old B.S.
I'm always hearing.
Jonathan,
I know you've had those figures
for only a few hours, but, uh,
we sure could use
a fresh perspective around here.
Yeah. Okay.
I don't really have
anything to say...
i-in here.
Look, I don't spend
a lot of time in boardrooms.
Why don't we all
adjourn this meeting...
to a place we're a little more
familiar with, hmm?
All right, come on.
Come on. Everybody in.
Ladies too.
Don't be shy.
Now, I want you all
to go in those stalls
and close the door.
Come on.
Double up if you have to.
Milt, I'd like you
in this one
right over here.
Jonathan,
this better be good.
Okay, that's right.
Go in. Take a seat.
Take a seat
and close the doors.
Excellent.
Now, at Harvard
we call this...
field research.
Milt, will you please tell us
what you see in front of you.
A door.
A Malkin door.
And what else?
- Who the hell wrote this?
- Come on.
What does it say?
"Milt Malkin...
is full of hot air."
Now, that...
is an advertising message.
Not necessarily the message
we're trying to get across,
but a message.
You see, the average person
spends seven and a half minutes
of every day...
staring at the back
of a bathroom door.
And we can write anything
we want on 18% of those doors
sold in America.
Why?
'Cause we make 'em.
That's seven and a half minutes
of every day,
three hundred
and sixty-five days a year,
for an average life span
of 72 years.
That's 3,280 hours
of a captive audience...
at a time when they're
most open to new ideas.
Because we all know...
that your major
life decisions...
aren't made in the boardroom!
No. They're made...
in the bathroom.
Yeah!
Jonathan!
Let me say since
Since we've been together
Ooh, lovin' you forever
Is all I need
Oh, let me be the one
You know what? This has
been an incredible date.
You come runnin'to
Wait a second.
This isn't a date.
Well, then what is it?
This is merely the sister
of your best friend
showing you a good time.
A good time.
Yeah.
What else
did you have in mind?
Let's stay together
Well, I'll tell you
what I'm going to do.
Lovin'you whether
Whether
Just sit back, relax...
and enjoy the show.
Times are good or bad
Excuse me.
Happy or sad
Thank you.
Oh, baby, let's
Let's stay together
Lovin'you whether
Oh, whether
Times are good or bad
Brad!
Happy or sad
Give me another one
of these, will ya.
All right, all right.
Come on. Hurry up.
Happy or sad, ooh
Michelle! Let's hear it
for Michelle! All right!
Ladies and gentlemen,
night after night...
we get some very,
very talented people
to come up from the audience...
and tear up the stage.
Tonight, ladies and gentlemen,
we have with us a star.
Oh, yeah!
The Wild Man
led one of the finest
rock bands in Boston...
and tore up the lvy League
for four big years,
and I think
if we give him
a big, kick-ass...
Quarry welcome, I think
we can get him up here
to do his thing.
What do you say?
Yeah! Yeah!
All right!
Come on, Wild Man!
Rock and roll! Whoo!
There he is,
ladies and gentlemen!
Wild Man Albertson!
I called them
this afternoon.
What did you tell them?
Just what David said.
I wanted to see
if you still had it
in you, Wild Man.
Come on up, Wild Man!
Come on up! Wild Man!
Wild Man! Wild Man!
Wild Man! Wild Man! Wild Man!
- I can't go up there.
- Wild Man! Wild Man! Wild Man!
Go on. Go on!
Wild Man!
Wild Man! Wild Man!
What do you
feel like doin', man?
I don't...
I got it.
Perfect for you,
Wild Man.
Rock and roll.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's star time!
Get your motor runnin'
Head out on the highway
Farrel?
Looking for adventure
And whatever comes
Our way
Farrel!
Yeah, darling
Gonna make it happen!
- Take the world
in a love embrace
- You owe me...
60,000 bucks, you punk!
Fire all your guns at once
- And
Louder! Louder!
- Yeah!
Give me that thing!
Like a true nature's child
We were born
born to be wild
I'm gonna kill you, you lowlife!
I'm gonna poke
your eyes out!
- I never wanna die
- I'll kill you!
Come here so I can
poke your eyes out!
Born to be wild
You're not even gonna
be able to...
Ow!
I'll poke your eyes out!
I like smoke and lightnin'
Heavy metal thunder
Racing with the wind
And the feeling
that I'm under
Yeah, darling
gonna make it happen
Take the world
in a love embrace
Fire all your guns
at once and
Explode into space
Like a true nature's child
We were born
born to be wild
We could climb so high
I never wanna die
Born to be wild
Yeah!
- Whoo! Yeah!
- Born to be
Wild
Born to be wild
Why are we running?
Those fans are crazy.
I can't believe this.
What?
I'm actually having
a good time with you.
Yeah? Well,
you should see me
on a really good night.
Whoo!
Should've never made
eye contact
Should've been
a heart of stone
When you stopped me
to say hello
Would've been twice as easy
Tojust say no
'Cause I don't wanna lose
at love again
Ooh, but as a couple
we were quite handsome
And the moon was out
that night
So we let our hearts
go dancin'
If the thing that's missin'
in my life
There's not enough romance
in this world
Oh, my. What was that?
Oh
There's not enough romance
in this world
Ooh
There's too many people
thinking only of themselves
You've gotta give love
Before it returns
Oh
Wanna sing about new lovers
Who stand up
against the odds
Mmm, nothing can change
a thing that strong
And myself I know
my emotions
I got my love to share
And when you're needin'
something so tender
What you're looking for
is so rare
There's not enough romance
in this world
No
There's not enough romance
in this world
John, did you get
those Cubs tickets
for this afternoon? Great.
1:30? Absolutely.
And listen, they better be
behind the first baseline.
Williamson is a fanatic.
I'm sorry, Milt.
Those facts and figures
might impress some executives,
but I gotta tell ya,
I'm a people person.
And my gut says people
really prefer paper towels.
That 1:30 meeting
all set, Paul?
We're in, Donald.
Well, Milt,
if you'll excuse me,
I got a big sales meeting.
I understand.
Fresh roasted
and salted shell! Yes, sir.
Yeah! Yeah!
Whoa!
Whoo!
What a catch!
Great catch.
That was close.
Yes. Too close.
Hell of an idea,
going to a ball game, Jon.
Hey, all work, no play,
huh, Milt?
Milt, look familiar?
Son of a bitch.
He told me he had
a sales meeting.
Oh, he does.
He just doesn't know it yet.
Over there.
Gentlemen, your attention.
Nobody move, please.
Secret Service.
I'm going to ask for
your cooperation in remaining
exactly where you are.
All right, Mr. President.
We're all clear.
Well, thank you, Tom.
You know, that's
quite an exciting ball game
we're seeing.
Oh, yes, sir.
It is.
Yes, sir.
All righty.
- Paper towel, Mr. President?
Not gonna do it.
Wouldn't be prudent
at this juncture.
You know, what do you say
we try that blower thing
over there?
It's right over here,
Mr. President.
You know, Bar and I
love these things.
Love... love doing
that blower thing.
Good for the hands.
Good for the economy.
You know, make a note, Tom.
We'll get one up there
in the White House.
Get one up in Kennebunkport.
Maybe a gift set for Gorby.
You know, seems to me,
blowers good,
paper towels bad.
Well, I'm ready
to move along now.
We're moving out.
Mr. President.
Uh, gentlemen, thank you
for your cooperation,
and, uh,
just go back
about your business.
Thank you.
I can't believe it!
I'm using the exact same dryer
the president just used!
Oh, yeah.
No paper towels.
Take a hit off that,
my friend.
Is that nice? Whoo!
Oh, yeah.
Take some of that,
my friend.
If it's good enough
for the president,
it's good enough for me.
That's right!
Blowers are where it's at.
Blowers are great. Towels suck.
That's right.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Hey, get some money.
Get your money,
money, money.
ToJonathan.
L'chayim.
L 'chayim.
- L 'chayim.
- Jonathan, I don't know
how you did it,
but Williamson
came back to the office
begging to make a deal.
I would like to
thank you personally.
And this...
is the best way
that I know how.
Milt.
Dad.
Oh.
I can't take this.
Huh? What do you mean
you can't take it?
What, I'm gonna
live forever? Besides,
I was hoping that we might
keep it in the family.
Dad.
Believe me, no one has ever
given me anything like this
before in my life.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Are you okay?
You're so quiet.
It's just I still can't believe
your dad gave me this.
It's just his way of
showing you how he feels
about you.
You know what 5/9/70 is.
Yeah. That's the day
Ernie took this one out.
It's also my dad's
license plate number,
his automatic teller code...
and the combination
to his safe.
That's the kind
of Ernie Banks nut
we're talking about here.
Whoa. This ball does
mean a lot to that guy.
Well, you mean a lot to him.
You mean a lot to me.
I can't believe
I am falling in love
with a Harvard man.
You're not.
Yes, I am.
She loves me.
She said that?
That's great.
We're in.
Well, I mean,
what if I get their money?
Hmm? Then what?
What do I do next?
Just go to another scam
and then another scam?
Yes.
God willing, yes!
Maybe I could stay.
I mean, I have a real job.
Oh, shit.
Huh?
I think I could become
the guy they think I am.
Oh, shit.
Hey, they see
something in me.
Eddie, you conned them.
That's all. You're a con man.
And now you're
conning yourself.
Then it's the best one
I've ever pulled,
because it's working on me too.
Love in a love con?
What is this, amateur night?
I've gotta tell
Annie the truth.
Great.
Do it fast.
Nice picture
of the Taj Mahal, huh?
Jonathan,
David's coming back.
Marlena,
have Murphy and Davis
gotten their vaccinations yet?
Annie.
No...
Jonathan, hi.
Hi, hi. Uh, I have to talk
to you. It's real important.
It's flu shot day.
I'm way behind. Can it wait?
No. No, it can't wait.
Okay.
I love you!
Ew!
I love you.
I'm happier than I've
ever been in my life.
Oh, me too, Jonathan.
There's more.
Okay. I'm all ears.
This... This is very scary
to say to someone.
Uh,
it's about us, I hope.
Y-Yeah. But...
Something about
our future maybe?
Well, yes, but it's...
Oh, Jonathan, you coward.
What?
The answer is yes.
- "Yes"?
- Yes, I will marry you.
Annie, you don't understand.
I am a phony.
Jonathan,
I know you're a phony.
Of course I do.
That's why I love you.
Because underneath all of
your degrees and all of
your money is a real person.
Oh, I've got kids
who need flu shots.
Bye.
Wait. Th-There's more.
Tell me later.
I love you.
Married.
Lou.
You're not gonna believe this.
I'm gettin' married.
Eddie!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Congratulations, Eddie.
We're all very happy for you.
Aren't we, guys?
Your partner here was fencing
some very lovely merchandise
in the neighborhood,
so I thought we'd all
drop by to say hi.
Sal, I don't mind you
dropping by.
I just wish you would
call first.
Where's my money?
We dumped the car, Sal.
We didn't take your money.
Then let's say
I didn't kill you either,
and we'll call it even.
I'll get you your money.
I'm no good to you dead.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I know a way to get
$180,000 by tomorrow.
I swear it.
I'm supposed to buy this
from a punk who never had...
two 20s to rub together
in his whole lousy life?
Look at this place, man. Huh?
Look around.
I'm in the middle of
a major situation here.
It costs you nothing to wait.
It costs you $180,000
to kill me right now.
Get the car.
I'll tell you what.
Mr. Pasquino here
will be the collateral
in our little agreement.
No, no. You... No.
Yeah. He'll be alive until,
let's say,
4:00 tomorrow afternoon.
Okay?
- Hey. Ow.
- Good.
Lay off me!
I hope this doesn't put a crimp
in your wedding plans.
Frankly, I'm impressed.
This is a great deal
of money for a street punk.
Lou, you feel okay?
Yeah.
I feel like Elvis
back from the dead.
Now, go on.
Get out of here.
Go throw yourself
in front of a car or somethin'.
Hey, Sal.
How'd you like to make
a lot more money?
What?
Four times that.
How could I possibly believe
some lowlife like you could
come up with that kind of cash?
I believe I just gave you
180,000 reasons.
You are gonna
get us killed.
We're not gonna get killed.
We're gonna get rich. I don't
know how we're gonna do it yet,
but we're gonna sting Sal,
then we're gonna retire
to Florida.
I thought you were
gonna marry that girl.
No, no, no.
What, are you kidding?
Lou, the whole thing was a con.
What was I thinking,
I could step into a new life
like a new pair of pants?
But, you know,
you and that broad...
made a real cute couple.
Get in.
I'm impressed.
Nearly a million of our
dryers hang in schools,
public libraries,
police precincts.
Yep. Even his mayor's
private bathroom.
So, what's your point?
Relax.
You look a little
stressed out.
My point is is that
we're both businessmen.
Hey. Come on.
Hey, I'm a businessman.
You're a fuckin' con man.
Of course I'm a con man.
I conned my way into this.
I'm just offering you
a piece of the action.
What action?
- Gerald Fox.
- The building commissioner?
You see, Gerry's looking for
the right wrecking company
for a city demolition job.
Pays 900 grand.
But you have to put up
a cash bond.
175,000.
Nonrefundable.
Kickback.
We don't use that kind of
terminology with Mr. Fox.
Why me? There's a lot of
wrecking companies.
Because not everyone's
comfortable with
this kind ofbusiness.
But you're comfortable.
Aren't you, Sal?
Yeah, I'm comfortable.
Excellent.
I'll call the commissioner.
Bullshit.
This whole setup is bullshit.
Okay. Let's go.
- What do mean, "Go"?
Go where?
- City hall.
Exterminator.
Exterminator?
We didn't call an exterminator.
You didn't ca...
This is the building
commissioner's office,
isn't it?
We didn't call for
the exterminator.
Oh, great.
Now, if you don't mind.
That's great.
Maybe he did.
Oh, my God!
Have a nice day.
Commissioner!
Yes. Now, you know
the commissioner's all tied up,
but maybe I can squeeze you in
next month, okay?
Oh. Please hold.
Why, Mr. Albertson,
what a pleasant surprise.
Look, I know we don't have
an appointment, but, uh,
do you think Gerry might be
able to slip us in?
Let's just see, shall we?
Well, what about
the end ofJuly? Yeah.
Jon! Jon Albertson,
get on in here.
Uh, yeah, Senator,
I say 20 million...
Let's not take
too much of his time.
He's a very busy man.
Well, I hope the governor
sees it our way.
Yeah. All right. Right. Bye.
Jon!
Gerry.
How are Betty
and those kids, huh?
Oh, fine. Just fine.
Great.
Gentlemen, why don't we have
our little conversation outside.
Yeah. Outside.
My office is not gonna pay
for this exterminator.
Well, I can't help it.
I'm never coming in here again.
Oh.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now, we need a cash bond
from you, Mr. Nichols,
for, uh, $250,000.
Two hundred and fifty grand?
That's 75 more
than I thought.
If you've got a problem
with the numbers,
there are contractors
in this city who'd swim
Lake Michigan...
for a $1.3 million job.
One point three?
Uh-huh.
No, no, no.
Those numbers are fine.
Fine.
You know what?
I had a feeling that
you two would hit it off.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
Oh, yes.
This'll fool anybody.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, boyo.
You gotta knock that off.
You still have to play
that city official tonight.
That's why I need another one.
I haven't done this in 20 years.
Uncle Max, Sal Nichols
may have a problem with
handing over...
a quarter million dollars
to a damn leprechaun.
Listen, don't worry about me.
I'll be sober
in a couple of hours.
- You'll still be stupid.
- Hey, I know what I'm
supposed to be doing.
Now, we meet 9:30
at the building site,
then bida-bing-bang-boom,
and 11:00 at the airport.
- Connie, have you got
the tickets?
- First class, kiddo.
All right.
We're out ofhere.
- Whoever that is,
get rid of'em.
- Okay. I'll take care of it.
Let's go, let's go
Oh, Milt, Mona, Annie,
what a wonderful surprise.
- Well, we've got
a big surprise for you.
- Hi.
Don't we, Milt?
We sure do.
Yes indeed.
Jonathan, you have company?
- Company?
- Yeah.
Oh. Uh, yeah,
I have company.
Uh, my... my parents.
Your parents?
Those are my parents.
They just got here.
Milt, Mona, Annie,
I would like you to meet
Thorton...
and Cornelia.
Oh.
They flew in when
they heard the good news.
That is just wonderful.
Thorton and Cornelia,
Jonathan has told me
so much about you.
I feel like
I know you so well.
Well, we feel as though
we've known you
all our lives.
Aw.
Don't we, Cornelia?
We certainly do,
Thorton. Yes.
Oh, how wonderful
to meet you.
How you doing?
David Malkin.
Okay, great.
Where are we at?
Spot the red queen and make her
yours. Where's the little lady?
Five will get you 10.
I can't believe it.
I cannot believe...
What?
that you don't
tease your hair.
No.
You mean that is
all in the cut?
Absolutely.
Oh, Mona. Listen, would you
let me feel that?
Oh, of course.
Oh, look at that.
Well, you know,
Alfred is just
a genius with...
Oh, Cornelia,
you are so kind.
Hey. I love your parents.
What?
Your parents.
I think they're great.
Yeah. Well, I hope this isn't
too rowdy for them.
They're a little
conservative actually.
Oh, Mona,
look how it's short
and then it gets long.
Oh. Beautiful.
Where's the little lady?
Five will get you 10.
Is she with the jack?
Is she with the king?
What do you say, Milt?
One ice-cold beer, Milt.
Thorton.
What?
Aren't you forgetting
something?
Ooh, yeah.
You know, Milt, I brought
the family album along.
It's back at the hotel.
Maybe I should pop back...
Ah!
You don't have to
go now, do you?
Nonsense. Nonsense.
You and the missus
will get a kick out of it.
And I'll drive you.
Jon, you want to
take a ride?
Uh, yeah.
Not a chance.
I am not letting him
out of my sight.
Jonathan, that might be
your surprise.
Hello.
David, where are you?
Well, he...
he's right here.
Come on. Go.
Oh. My surprise. Great.
Jonathan, it's David.
He wants to talk to you.
Go.
Why don't you talk to him?
Really.
Jonathan, take the phone.
Thanks.
David, how are you?
Jonathan? This doesn't
sound like you.
Uh, great to, uh, hear
your voice again too,
old man.
Really? Listen,
I beg to differ
on that point, my friend.
I think that Calcutta couldn't
have been as hot as it's been
around here, mon ami.
Is this some kind of joke?
Who is this?
Well, you're right about that.
l... I am a lucky guy.
Annie's one in a million.
You jerk. I am gonna
come out there and
kick the shit out of you.
Great. Great.
I'll be looking forward to it.
I bet you're very good at that.
Put my dad on the line.
What?
Can you believe it?
The car didn't meet him
at the airport.
Listen, can you stay put
for 45 minutes,
and I'll be right there?
Good idea, Jonathan.
Oh, yes.
What a sweet thing to do.
Okay. All right.
I'll see you.
Give me that.
Wait. Wait.
I think you've had enough.
Don't spill it!
Don't...
All right. Go.
Look at that baby!
You know, the governor
opposed this site.
Mayor was dead set
against it.
But when I get my mind set...
That's right.
Rammed this baby right through
city council. That's the kind
of building commissioner he is.
I'm sure we can do
more business together
in the future.
I think we might be
laying the foundation...
for a long and mutually
beneficial relationship,
Mr. Nichols.
Now, I need your signature
in triplicate.
City contracts.
1.3 million.
Your signature here,
here and here.
Completion guarantee.
Signature here.
Okay.
Hey, you got enough
hard hats to go around?
Oh, he's great.
Commissioner, uh,
shouldn't you explain
the time pressure?
Time pressure?
Didn't you want them
to start...
tomorrow before
the weekend is over?
Damn straight.
Yeah.
The medical center's due
to start construction here
next week.
I need the site cleared
before the weekend is over.
The weekend?
Nobody works on the weekend.
I've just wasted my time.
Forget it.
Wait a minute.
The weekend'll be
just fine.
Now, here's your copy.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, yeah.
There we are.
Oh, uh, Mr. Nichols,
one more thing.
Which way do you think
this baby's gonna fall?
Down.
I'm sure Mr. Nichols
knows what he's doing.
Good luck! Timber!
"Down."
We did it.
What's keeping everybody?
Where the heck is that hotel,
the other side of the moon?
It must be.
I don't know where
they're staying.
I'll ask Cornelia.
Cornelia.
Cornelia?
Whoo-oo.
Connie, you should
have seen us.
It was just like
old times.
Oh. Oh.
Keep your motor running.
We'll be right with you.
Eddie, are you okay?
Yeah, I guess so.
Well, you handled that
like a pro.
Now that you've got
the basics down,
I cannot wait
till you get to Miami.
Those clubs are crawling
with rich widows.
No, no.
I don't think I'm cut out
for the love con.
Oh, just give it
a little time, kid.
It'll work out fine.
I don't know. There's...
There's somethin' missing.
What's missing?
Look, you got the money.
You got Miami.
You got me.
I'm telling you,
the flight's already arrived.
Page him again, please.
Why don't you let me
talk to...
They're going to page him.
Jonathan!
Oh!
What's going on?
Where is everybody?
- Where's David?
- Wait. There's something
I have to say.
Where's David?
What is it?
You've been like
parents to me.
Aw.
You're like
our own son.
We love you.
This is your money.
I took it out of the safe.
How did you do that?
Why?
That's not all.
Jonathan,
whatever this is,
we can work it out.
I don't think we can ever
work this out.
Jonathan, what is it?
What's wrong?
I'm notJonathan Albertson.
NotJonathan?
You're not
Jonathan Albertson?
My name is Eddie Farrel,
and I'm a con man.
This whole thing
is a con.
Annie,
I used you to get to
your father's money.
Oh, my God.
But I fell in love with you.
Oh, Annie, honey.
Annie, I'm s...
I don't believe you.
Annie, I'm sorry.
I think you've done enough!
Milt, please?
Annie, I'm so sorry
I hurt you.
But I love you.
I really do love you.
Hey.
You must be David.
David,
Yeah.
you've got
a great family.
I'm sorry.
Police are investigating
the bizarre destruction...
of the I RS building
in downtown Chicago.
Mr. Nichols, who has had
previous problems
with the I RS,
now faces 247 years
in combined federal
and state charges.
All three are being held
without bail.
A spokesman for the IRS
in Washington said...
that taxpayer refunds
would not be affected.
We'll be bringing you updates...
Hmm.
Annie, this is Eddie.
Jonathan. Eddie. Whatever.
Will you pick up
the phone, please?
How many times do I have
to call? You're listening to me
right now, aren't you?
I was in
the neighborhood, and...
I've got
some extra blood.
Please leave.
I love you.
If you can turn around and
tell me that you don't love me,
I'll walk
right out of here.
I don't love you.
I'll bet you're glad
to be rid of that guy.
That's right.
He really was a nuisance.
Coming around,
bringing you flowers,
making us laugh,
dragging you
out on dates.
Yeah, he won't be
cutting into no more
of your busy schedule.
Damn you, Harold.
Eddie Farrel!
How dare you
do that to me!
Annie, I love you.
If you don't believe me,
there's nothing I can do.
No!
No! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Eddie. Eddie, are you okay?
Annie?
I'm right here.
I'm right here. Are you okay?
Ow.
Eddie, I love you.
I do. I love you.
That's all
I wanted to hear.
What?
Love in a love con.
I hate to see it.
It's like I said,
Max,
amateur night.
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
Every day you wake up
I hope it's under a blue sky
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
One day when you wake up
I will have to say good-bye
Say good-bye
It's your world
so live in it
You got to wash
with the crocodile
in the river
You got to swim
with the sharks in the sea
You got to live
with the crooked politician
Trust those things
that you can never see
You got to trust your lover
when you go away
Keep on believing tomorrow
brings a better day
Sometimes you smile while
you're crying inside
Just once you'll turn away
while the truth is
shining bright
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
Every day you wake up
I hope it's under a blue sky
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
One day when you wake up
I will have to say good-bye
Say good-bye
It's your world
so live in it
Good-bye
It's your world
so live in it
When I hold your small body
close to mine
I feel weak and strong
at the same time
So few years to give you
wings to fly
Show you stars
to guide your ship by
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
Every day you wake up
I hope it's a blue, blue sky
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
One day when you wake up
I will have to say good-bye
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
Every day you wake up
I hope it's a blue, blue sky
It's a cruel, crazy
beautiful world
One day when you wake up
I will have to say good-bye
Say good-bye
It's your world
so live in it
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4c5w3
Help other users to choose the best subtitles