Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
"You cannot walk away from love."
That was the advertisement
in a Baltimore newspaper.
And that is how he found her.
She was a young woman
in need of a husband.
And he was a man who wanted a wife.
Too late to talk sense to him now.
You can't marry her, Luis.
You've never met her.
I meet her today. The boat from America
comes at 6:00, we marry at 9:00...
...by 10:00, I'm back at work.
Ridiculous. This is ridiculous.
A man needs a wife, isn't that what
you've been telling me? Well... I sent for one.
From America.
What does she look like?
Comes a day in every man's life
when a band is playing...
...and he's the only one who can hear it.
Today is your day.
I love you, woman.
She is not beautiful.
She is not meant to be beautiful...
...just kind, true and young enough
to bear children.
Go on. The sun will be up any minute.
The boat will be coming in.
But what about love, Luis?
Doesn't love come into this at all?
Love is not for me, Alan.
Love is for those people who believe in it.
Let's go.
Why are you laughing at me?
You've been laughing at me all morning.
Never mind. You go! Go on!
No, this is not a love story.
Butitis a story aboutlove,
and the powerit has over ourlife.
The power to heal or destroy.
and this is where the story begins.
Mr. Vargas?
Luis Vargas?
You don't recognize me, do you?
Miss Russell?
Yes.
Julia Russell?
But this, this picture--
I've deceived you.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have.
I was unsure. You see...
...l didn't want you interested in me
just because I owned a pretty face.
So I sent another woman's photograph
and not my own.
I see.
I hope you forgive me.
I meant to write many times. I tried.
But my courage failed me. So l....
And....
Now I stand before you as I am,
and you know the worst.
No, no.
Not the worst at all.
Only, not what I was expecting.
If my deception has altered
your intentions...
...if you're not satisfied--
No, it isn't that.
...l am determined to make my way back
to my home in Delaware.
-If you say so, I will.
-Miss Russell....
Miss Russell...
...you have been honest with me.
I will be honest with you, too.
I will admit to a deception of my own.
You are exactly the image
of your photograph.
Yes, I am.
But I wrote to you that I am a clerk...
...in a coffee export house. I am not.
I own the house.
The business is my own.
You did not want me
to be interested in you...
...just because you owned
a pretty bank account.
Yes.
Then we have something in common.
We are both not to be trusted.
Of course, if my deception
has altered your intentions...
...if you are not interested
in marrying a wealthy man....
No, I think I could manage.
If you could manage
a somewhat prettier wife.
I'll make the effort.
Miss Russell.
Mr. Vargas.
Now we have all the time in the world
to get to know each other.
Well... No, not all the time.
No, we are going to be married at 9:00.
Well then, we'd better hurry.
"Take this ring...
"...as a sign of my love...
"...and fidelity...
"...to you."
Music!
Ladies and gentlemen, a toast!
To our groom and his beautiful...
...enchanting bride!
Will you dance with me?
Dance?
I don't dance.
I say you do.
May their life together be like this dance,
harmonious, smooth.
Dance for life never ending and--
Alan, enough is enough.
I'm almost through.
You're through now. Sit down.
-Good luck to you.
-Thank you.
Would you like to see the house?
Oh, no. I can see it tomorrow.
You must give me a few moments.
I'm shy of these things.
I will give you as many moments,
days, nights as you need.
When you want me to come to you...
...l will.
Not before.
You would do that for me?
If you say so, yes.
Then...
...l will say good night.
The room is there, to the right.
I think I'll find it.
Awake at last.
The day is half-gone.
I'm sorry. I'm not dressed.
I could wait outside,
but the coffee would get cold.
No, it's all right.
If someone brought me my coffee
every morning before I dressed...
...l would be very happy.
It would change the day.
But...
...you only drink tea.
I do? No.
When I wrote I worked in a coffee
company, you wrote back--
That was my sister.
She believed coffee to be a sinful
pleasure so I pretended to agree.
She read all my letters to you,
so I could not always be truthful.
All the more reason to forget them.
That's all behind you.
What do you think?
About what?
Do you believe as my sister does...
...that pleasure could ever be sinful?
Why did you choose an American wife?
Here, we are the past.
There, you are the future.
Why did you choose to leave it?
To escape the future.
To become someone else, I think.
I am someone else with you.
Someone more like...
...myself.
There, in his arms...
...she became someone else.
Someone more like herself.
I'm telling you, I've never been happier.
There's no such thing as happily married.
It's an oxymoron, like "happily dead".
I thought you'd be finding your way
back to the whores by now.
Seeing a little "Creole" time.
Not anymore.
You've had her for yourself long enough.
When do we get to see her again?
We're going to the theatre next week.
An American touring company
she wants to see.
Why don't you join us?
Soon comes the morning
when the knell is rung...
...to take my living breath.
Come, come, the night is almost done.
Satan is near!
The shrieking, grim and...
...hideous brim of hell to uncover.
Come, or you will share her wretched end.
Hellhound! Abominable monster!
Would that I had never been born!
Wonderful. Wonderful.
Disgusting.
Cheap melodrama.
Was it we who forced our way to you?
Who was it sent her to her ruin?
I...
...or you?
What evil thing has risen from the ground?
Father, let angels now have charge of me...
...encamped around heavenly company.
She is condemned to die.
She is redeemed on high!
Hither, to me!
Julia, my dear, you look flushed.
-Are you all right?
-Yes, it's the theatre.
I love it...
...even the cheap melodrama.
Will you excuse me?
Does she suffer from fevers?
She suffers from a little too much rouge.
Nonsense. A lady does not wear rouge.
No, a lady doesn't.
And a lady does not wander through
the theater alone, either.
Excuse me.
Perhaps you will find the second act
more appealing.
Excuse me, sir!
The public is not allowed backstage.
Don't touch me, sir.
That is my wife, damn it!
Luis, you've come to my rescue...
...just like a play....
What are you doing here?
Isn't it exciting?
Look at all these mysterious contraptions.
-Who was that man?
-What man? I was lost, that's all.
You made my heart stop.
Feel my heart. Feel how fast it's beating?
Christ.
You'll be the death of me.
I hope so.
Places, please.
Ladies and gentlemen, places for act two.
Take me home now.
My own dearest sister.
I can't understand why you treat me thus.
Itis many weeks now since you left.
In all that time, no word from you
to tell me of your safe arrival...
...whetheryou met Mr. Vargas,
whether the marriage has taken place.
What am I to think?
I have contacted the embassy in Havana...
...and the authorities there in Santiago.
I know how you feel about her, but...
...you have to write.
You have to,
before she has the police on us.
You're right. I've been unkind to her.
Although she has never been kind to me.
Just do it.
Do it, and then it's done.
No, no, no!
It's all right. It's me, Luis.
You were dreaming.
Are you all right?
That's it.
You were just dreaming.
It's all right.
It was just a dream.
A bad one, that's all.
You okay? You need something?
You.
I'm sorry.
You are here with me. Secure.
You're all right.
Will you stay?
Of course.
It's all right.
Luis, don't go.
How is the queen of the house
this morning?
Look. See? I've done it.
This is for the best. Thank you.
-I'll have Sara post it this morning.
-No need. I can do it myself.
I haven't addressed it.
I have the address at the office.
Then it's on its way.
What will you do today?
I'm going to an English dressmaker
at the Plaza Vieja.
You'll need money.
Sign here, Señora.
Is this for both your personal
and business account?
Yes, thank you.
I want my wife to have free use
of all my accounts.
There you are.
Should I sign using my Christian name?
No, your married name.
You must remember to repeat
the signature exactly...
...each time you draw a check.
I will try.
Oh, man!
So, Luis, is it love after all...
...or is it just lust?
Is there a difference?
Oh, yes.
To love someone is to give
and then want to give more.
And lust?
What is lust, Alan?
Lust is to take and then take more.
To devour, to consume.
No logic, no reason.
So...give, take.
Which is it?
Both.
I want to give her everything.
And I want to take everything from her.
Oh, Luis. You are a lost man.
No, no.
She is the one who seems to be lost.
How, why, I don't know.
But that will change.
I can change that.
Mr. Vargas?
Walter Downs.
I didn't mean to startle you.
-That's okay.
-I was told I could find you upstairs.
-How can I help?
-Small matter.
Hardly worth your trouble.
I've been engaged by Miss Russell.
You mean, Julia?
No, Emily. Julia's sister.
In Delaware.
I'm a private investigator.
Just recently arrived from Wilmington.
I understand.
I know Miss Russell was distressed.
But we've written to her several weeks ago.
I'm sure when she receives the letter,
she will be much relieved.
Then Miss Julia is all right?
More than all right.
And more than Miss Julia.
She's Señora Vargas, my wife.
So you are married?
-That's very good news.
-Happily married.
Yes, I can see that.
What a mystery a happy marriage is.
The bloom in the cheek,
the spark in the eye.
-It shows, I guess.
-Yes, indeed.
Miss Russell will be pleased to hear of it.
I'd appreciate if you'd tell her.
I will, indeed.
And I'll be even more convincing
when I've met your wife.
Yes, yes.
Why not?
We will be home Sunday afternoon.
You want to come by for a coffee?
Yes, I will.
And... please convey to your wife
how much I look forward to seeing her.
Outside, please. On the terrace.
Do as she says.
Oh! Just in time.
This is for Sunday paseo,
and this one for weekdays.
Fine, fine.
And the rest?
This one I like.
What do you mean?
There are seven days in a week.
What about your trunk? Is there nothing in there?
Nothing good. Anyway, I've lost the key.
We'll get a locksmith.
It's an easy job. Actually...
...l'll do it myself.
No, I want to show you something. Come here.
You must leave now.
I'm going to kiss my husband.
Then we're going to take a bath.
What do I smell?
My perfume.
No.
A cigar.
I tried one.
One of my cigars?
I wanted the taste of you in my mouth.
You have no shame at all.
Well, there is no shame in loving each other.
Do you love me? Julia?
Do you love me?
Or are you not the loving kind?
I forgot to tell you.
We have a visitor coming on Sunday.
We do?
Yes...
...a genuine private investigator...
...all the way from Delaware.
So, Emily sent him.
Yeah. Detective Downs.
Detective Downs, did you say?
Don't worry,
he only needs to see that you're well...
...and happy and truly my wife.
-Then this nonsense is over.
-When will that damn bird stop screaming?
Julia.
Careful, it's coming.
Oh, no.
Don Luis, look. He's dead.
He was just singing.
He's not singing now, is he?
Looks like he got his little neck broken.
Take him away.
I don't want Julia to see him.
How does a person die on this instrument?
I believe that...
...the turning of the wheel
breaks one's neck.
And if it doesn't?
Does one then strangle?
Are you afraid?
No.
Julia is not afraid.
But Bonny is.
I don't understand. Who is Bonny?
Who is Bonny?
I'm looking for Mr. Vargas.
That is a question
Luis would soon be asking.
Mr. Vargas?
My name is Russell.
Emily Russell.
I am Julia's sister.
So you understand how upset I was
to receive this letter.
Upset?
But... I... I thought you would be pleased
to receive it.
This letter, sir...
...which was written in answer to the one I last sent here...
...and which is signed in her name...
...is not from Julia.
Of course it is.
I mailed it myself.
This letter was not written by my sister.
Miss Russell.
I'm sorry.
Don't be upset. I swear to you--
Swear as much as you like.
That is not Julia's handwriting.
That is the handwriting of a stranger.
A person unknown.
At least to me.
-Where is she?
-I was going to send for you.
Where is she?
Go away, go away. Now get out!
Where did she go, Sara?
I don't know. She sent me to
the post office. When I come back--
She's not coming back, is she, Sara?
She never was here.
You've been married to a dream.
A dream that stole your soul.
Luis! What is it?
Your wife appeared at five minutes to
three for a last-minute withdrawal.
As you instructed,
I gave her full access to your accounts.
Your balance at closing was...
...51 American dollars and 40 cents
in one account...
...ten dollars in the other.
As I explained to your wife,
to help close both out completely...
...your signature
would have been necessary.
I'm sorry.
Don Luis?
God must have been angry with you
that day...
...he let you look in that woman's face.
I want her back. Sara...
...l want her back.
No, cariño. What for?
What for you want her back again?
No, this is not a love story.
But it is a story about love.
about those who give in to it,
and the price they pay.
and those who run away from it
because they are afraid...
...or because they do not believe
they are worthy of it.
She ran away.
He gave in.
Mr. Vargas?
Walter Downs.
What a happy coincidence.
Oh, yeah.
I remember you.
And the authorities here could do nothing?
After all...
...there was no crime.
She was my wife.
She just took what I had given her.
Your money.
And your love.
And you did not suspect?
It seems that I know a lot less
about women than I thought I did.
And I know too much.
Consequently, I've not much use for them...
...apart from the necessities.
For real intercourse,
I prefer the company of men.
Listen to me.
Could you find her?
Perhaps.
But I am, at the moment...
...engaged to find the real Julia,
the one you were meant to marry.
Have you found her?
Not yet.
If you do... if you do...
...she might lead you to the Julia I married.
Perhaps.
And vice versa.
As much as you want I will pay,
if you can find her for me.
That's all I want.
Then I assume you have made up
your losses.
As much as you want, I will pay, I said it.
I will pay.
Yes, I believe you would.
And if I did find your Julia?
If I brought her to you...
...or you to her...
...what good would it possibly do you?
Money's gone.
The love...
...ruined.
What could you possibly want with her?
What could you possibly want?
I want to kill her.
Yes, I do recall this lady.
Slim and dark and very....
I remember, coming along the deck
and the breeze catching her skirt.
She was coming towards me.
She quickly held it down with her hand
and as she passed, she smiled.
I believe she was traveling
with a troupe of American actors...
...touring the island.
Oh, yes, I remember.
Because she rolled up some lettuce in her napkin.
I thought it was strange.
She explained it was for her bird.
She was traveling with a bird.
Oh, yes. I remember her.
A lady with a birdcage...
...but this doesn't look like her.
She was young and very pretty.
Yes, that's her.
and the real Julia never appears, because...
...she is dead.
-You mean murder.
-Yes.
She could have had an accomplice.
These women often have an accomplice.
Someone she might use and then discard.
Someone who might even now be
in pursuit of her, just as you and I are.
This is where it happened.
Here in Havana.
This way, gentlemen. Welcome to Havana.
Mr. Downs will be in room 37...
...and Mr. Vargas will be just down the hall
in room 42.
I'll hook myself up
with the local authorities...
...and see if any dead bodies
have turned up recently.
You're welcome to join me.
No, thank you.
Havana is a very accommodating city,
especially during Carnival.
I suggest the Opera Restaurant.
It's just across the street.
It's very popular with American tourists.
Why don't you do something
pleasant tonight?
Treat yourself to a good dinner,
a good cigar and a good whore?
I prefer to be alone.
So I'll leave you on your own, then.
Here you are.
Privacy, and a view of the room.
If you see anything...
...or anyone who interests you, let me
know and I'll see what I can arrange.
If I could have my coffee every morning
before I dressed, I would be very happy.
It would change the day.
I would be very happy.
Then that is what you shall have.
When we are married,
you shall have everything you wish.
Married? Your wife might have
something to say about that.
This way, Colonel, s'il vous plaît.
S'il vous plaît indeed,
you silly mountebank.
-You're about as French as my asshole!
-Edwin, curb your tongue.
May I help you, sir?
I thought I saw an old friend of mine.
Colonel....
-Colonel Worth?
-Yes.
Oh, yes. This way.
No, no, no.
I wouldn't bother him now.
Is he staying at the hotel?
No, he's at home in Havana.
He lives at avenida Medios.
I believe his fiancée is at the hotel.
Fiancée?
Yes, Miss Castle.
Yes, yes.
I see. Thank you.
My dear, I don't have that kind of money.
But, my dear, you do.
Your annual expenditures
are $200,000, more or less.
How do you know that?
Because, under favorable conditions,
you could realize...
...at least 1.5 million pounds of sugar
in good seasons.
Five cents a pound--
No, don't.
Don't make me talk about business now.
I've been waiting for this all night.
Now, don't watch.
Be kind, my dove.
Be kind to an old man.
I am kind.
Kind as I have ever been.
Will you undo my dress, please?
Oh, yes.
Let me have thatpleasure.
That's enough. Thank you.
Thank you...
...for a wonderful evening. Good night.
-No.
-Yes.
I'll behave. I'll only sit and watch you.
You see...
...l sit...
...and I watch.
Is that what you want?
You are very tiresome and I am very tired.
-Good night.
-No.
-Good night. Yes.
No.
Mayn't I stay? Please, let me stay.
Darling dove, I'm weeping.
My heart is pudding.
I'll go.
But my pudding is all broken.
Good night...
...my little dove.
Good night.
"Parting is such sweet sorrow."
It's only me, Julia.
You haven't forgotten me, have you?
Who's Billy?
Just a fellow.
There must be quite a few
fellows in your life.
Billy...
...me...
...the Colonel.
Did you marry all of them?
-No, just you.
-Liar.
Liar.
Well, what is it, then?
What is it?
What are your plans for me?
My plans?
I just came here to kill you.
My God.
All right, do it.
There. There's my heart. Don't hesitate.
Your money's gone. Do it.
Gone.
Like the woman you murdered?
What? No.
You were with her on that boat!
You were seen together!
-I wasn't alone.
-She told you all about me, didn't she?
No!
I told him!
The next day, he told me she'd had
an accident and to take her place. So I did.
Another man?
Accomplice?
Friend? Lover?
An accomplice--
You saw us together,
backstage, at the play.
My friend, my accomplice and...
...yes, yes, my lover.
He was an actor, like myself.
Actors playing parts.
I told him that night I didn't want
to go through with it. I couldn't--
Why not?
Because!
Because I was....
Damn it.
I was falling in love with my own husband.
Again. Liar.
I could have bought him off!
I could have kept him away!
But you made me write her sister
and then it was all over!
Whore!
Thief!
It's how I live. It's all I know.
I took the money and I gave it to him.
Then I ran.
What does it matter?
It's over.
Whore!
Liar! Thief!
Yes!
Don't you see...
...that I cannot breathe without you?
I cannot live without you!
Don't you see that?
Don't you see how much I love you?
I'm sorry.
Where am l?
Who are you?
Really.
My name is Bonny.
Bonny Castle.
Is that your Christian name?
It would be...
...if I were Christian.
But I'm not.
I was never baptized.
I was a foundling.
So was Billy.
We were raised in an orphanage
outside of St. Louis.
He gave me my name.
He saw it on a picture postcard
from Scotland.
It had a drawing on it,
of a "bonny castle", it said.
When we were 14, we ran away together.
Like brother, sister, father, daughter,
husband, wife.
-He was my salvation.
-No.
I don't want to know.
Not now.
You are Julia Russell
from Wilmington, Delaware.
You were born...
...the day you stepped off that boat...
...and became my wife.
But then...
...l am not Julia Russell at all, am l?
I'm simply your wife.
-Who is it?
-I don't know.
It's Edwin, my dear.
Am I too early?
Don't hurry.
Nothing gives me more pleasure than
to wait for you outside your door.
Unless, of course, you were to let me in.
-Colonel Worth.
-Good God!
-May I help you, sir?
-You are not dressed, sir.
No, I am not.
I am engaged at the moment
in a private function.
A function for which clothes
are a hindrance, not a help.
A private function?
Yes, sir.
With Bonny? A private function?
Good God, man!
But I am being rude. Please come in.
No, sir. Are you mad?
Mad? No.
I am only curious to know
what your business is at my wife's door.
Your wife?
Did you say, "wife"?
Edwin, be careful.
He has a fearful temper.
I beg your pardon, sir. I do.
I beg your pardon.
I am an old fool.
I didn't know.
I'm sorry.
Good morning to you, sir.
Good morning.
You see?
You have no past.
It is gone. Finished.
Disappeared.
You have only me now.
There you are. You weren't in your room.
I have some very interesting news.
So do l.
"A woman's body found."
"Foul play suspected." How's my Spanish?
Julia Russell?
Stabbed in the neck with a small knife,
then thrown overboard.
Probably the work of a man,
but could've easily been a woman.
The blade of the knife
was still in her throat.
And so your wife...
...is now officially a fugitive.
Not only are we pursuing her,
but the police, too.
Cheer up. This is good news.
It won't be long until she's caught.
She...
...didn't do this.
I believe you still love her.
Of course.
How could you hate her so much if you
did not still love her?
Trust me, my friend.
There's no such thing as love.
Only misguided feelings and emotions.
It was my knife. He used my knife.
-It wasn't me, I promise you.
-I believe you.
No one else will believe I'm innocent.
Listen to me.
No one else matters. Not to me.
What are you thinking?
Of you.
Welcome to Cardenas.
Right this way. This is the entrance.
It's very elegant...
...in a very good part of town.
Mostly Americans and tourists
from the Continent.
I think you'll find all the furnishings
you need included.
a bedroom...
...a sitting room, a very good kitchen.
Here in Cardenas,
you are close to Havana...
...but very far away.
We are known for the waters
and for the healing powers of the sun.
Vargas.
What a happy accident.
Yes, indeed.
What brings you to Cardenas?
Not a rest cure, I assure you.
No, of course not.
There were reports of a woman
answering a certain description.
She was seen boarding an eastbound train.
You haven't seen or heard anything,
have you?
I've lost my taste for women
of that description.
Glad to hear of it.
Listen...
...can I offer you a piñales?
What's that?
A drink.
There's a cafe down the street.
The sun is warm.
Your face, for instance, is quite moist.
The body was positively identified
by her sister.
Very sad, but very accurate.
Two moles high on the inner thigh...
...and a gold crown on a back tooth.
And on her left hand, a small, round scar.
Very interesting.
Will you excuse me?
I have to use the convenience.
By all means.
Do as you must.
Julia?
Come upstairs. We....
Ah, Luis.
I am disappointed.
And yet full of admiration.
Where is she?
Who? No.
-She's not here.
-You called her name.
You have no business here.
Downs, please. Be smart and leave.
Get out while you can.
She's mine, Luis.
Give her up, before it's too late.
You are aiding a criminal!
And you are close
to becoming one yourself.
Come to your senses.
You saw it. She's not here. Now, please.
Don't lie to me, Mr. Vargas.
I can smell her on you.
Her perfume, stinking on your clothing.
You just left her, didn't you?
That's it. Get out.
Did she throw her arms around you?
Embrace you, like this?
Did she rub her cheek against yours,
like this?
Did she kiss you on the mouth?
If I kiss you now, will I taste her on you?
You would do this for her?
Wait!
Wait.
Speak of the devil, and she appears.
My God. What have you done?
What have you done?
It's him.
It's the detective.
He came here for you.
What are you doing? Don't touch him.
Don't touch him!
-Did he come here alone?
-Yes.
No one saw him come in?
I don't know.
Christ, Julia.
I've killed a man.
You need to go to the train station.
Buy two seats on the morning train east,
no matter where.
I will contact the estate agent
and tell him we've changed our minds...
...and there's been an emergency.
Julia.
Yes, what?
I've just killed a man.
And I just bought a hat.
But I don't dwell on it. I don't say
over and over, "I just bought a hat."
"I just bought a hat." It doesn't matter.
It's done. Help me.
God.
-That should do it.
-I'll bring him down.
No, go to the station
before the window closes.
Come here. Put these on.
Yes, I'll hurry.
No. Don't hurry.
Go slowly, enjoy the walk
and no one will notice you.
-Understand?
-Yes.
Billy.
You finally got what you deserved.
-Jesus!
-Aren't you glad to see me?
Aren't you glad
to see old Detective Downs again?
Should I be?
I got very good notices
playing this part in Chicago.
Or don't you remember?
Let go of me, Billy.
You thought I was...
...really dead...
...didn't you?
Did you think
there were real bullets in that gun?
You think they were real
the night he came to murder you?
I couldn't risk his putting out your lights,
not before I caught up with you.
-Let go of me, Billy.
-Never.
-Not till you come back to the game.
-What game?
The skin game, darling.
There is no game.
Yes. I see it so clearly.
No, no.
What do you see?
I see him running out of money.
I see you arranging that.
I see him doing the only thing he can do.
I see him going to Santiago,
selling his share of the company.
I see him coming back with money.
I see us...
...finishing what we started.
You and me together.
We're going to make you a rich widow.
He's worth a hell of a lot more
than we got out of him the first time.
And he's such an easy mark,
devoted as he is to you.
Bound together as you are
by mutual crimes and various...
...misdemeanors.
-Let go of me.
-Beg.
-Please, let go!
It tickles my dick when you beg.
He says he loves me.
No one loves you, Bonny.
No one could.
Except for me.
He does.
I think he does.
Not enough to live the life of a fugitive.
Back alleys, cheap hotels....
It won't be like that.
How then? Happily ever after?
A nice, respectable couple,
living on Main Street?
Sunday dinners,
walks in the park with children?
Christ, what's he done to you?
Who do you think you are?
Who does he think you are?
You're a whore, Bonny.
If a man puts his hands on you, you're wet.
True or not?
You were born one and you'll die one.
Sooner than later
if the police catch up with you.
You wouldn't do that to me.
I was your first man, Bonny.
Your very first.
And I will be...
...your last.
One way or another.
There's no future with him, darling.
Face the truth.
You can't live his life.
And he certainly...
...can't live yours.
Let him go.
No.
I was so hungry.
What about him?
We have to get rid of the body.
No, it's done.
It's done?
You mean you did it yourself?
I packed all our things, as well.
I left one suit out on the bed, for the train.
You get the tickets?
-The tickets? Yes.
-Good.
We go tomorrow in the morning.
Back to Havana. 7:00.
What an adventure.
Come to bed.
You must be exhausted.
I know I am.
Wait, wait, wait.
Have you no conscience at all?
I mean....
Yes, of course I do.
But you see,
I don't let it get the best of me.
It's just something that happened.
It had to be done.
And when something has to be done,
you do it, right?
So, here's to us.
A short life, but an exciting one.
Good night.
Listen to her talk.
Listen to the words
that came out of her mouth.
You mean Bonny?
Yes, Bonny.
Did you have no control over her?
No one had control over her.
No one did.
No one, except for Billy.
and he wanted the rest of the money.
They found a house
in the poorsection of town.
Bonny said they would go unnoticed there,
and she was right.
Many things would go unnoticed
in that house.
all she had to do
was get Luis to Santiago...
...and it would all be over.
No, you don't understand.
-We've run out?
-Yes, I'll go tomorrow to Santiago.
I'll take the first train in the morning.
What will you do there?
We need money, don't we?
Whatever you say.
I don't want you to go to Santiago.
I have to go.
I don't want you to go.
I have no choice.
You do. You have a choice.
Once again.
-When my hand strays to my breast....
-Hearts.
-My left eardrop.
-Diamonds.
-My right eardrop.
-Clubs.
-My throat.
-Spades.
-Little finger of my left hand.
-One.
-Little finger of my right hand.
-Ten.
When I do this,
it means they have nothing.
Right.
-King, queen, jack.
-Yes.
Yes.
You're a natural.
-Listen--
-This is the way.
This is the only way. This is our way.
This is you and me, together.
Please.
Now...
...tell me what I'm holding.
Would you like more whiskey?
Too rich for me.
Yes. Why not?
Why not, indeed? All right.
He wins again.
I'm sorry, gentlemen.
More champagne.
Does the lady mind if I remove my coat?
No, do and say as you please.
Try and forget that I am even here.
Easier said than done.
Can I get you another drink?
Will you ask the lady to retire, sir?
What do you mean?
Do you have to be told?
Take your hand from my wife. Please, sir.
Gladly.
If there's one thing lower
than a man who cheats at cards...
...is a man who will use a woman to do
this cheating for him.
Julia?
Well, my dear...
...let's see
what other tricks you might know.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Should l....
Should I call someone?
You are so kind.
You are so young and innocent and kind.
No.
No one is innocent.
You have a story as well.
Will you tell me...
...if there's time?
I have no story.
Not like yours.
Well, it was Bonny's story now.
and look what she had done.
He could not live in her world.
and she would never fit into his.
Dear Alan:
Congratulations.
You have just purchased my share
of Vargas-Jordan Coffee Export House.
The price I have settled on
is everything that was in the safe...
...which I believe is very much
in your favor. I'm sorry.
Luis! Wait!
I'm sorry I couldn't wait
to discuss this with you.
But as you may know,
I am now a fugitive from justice.
More than that, I cannotsay.
What are you talking about?
Murder.
I have done murder.
-No.
-Yes.
I did it for her.
And the truth is...
...that I would do it again.
Good luck to you.
Thank you for having once been my friend.
Go on.
God help you.
Will you light me a cigar?
I'll make us some coffee.
Damn!
-What happened?
-There's a rat.
-A rat?
-There's a rat. It ran right over my foot.
Do you see it?
No.
-I didn't see it.
-No?
What are you doing?
Going to the pharmacist.
-At this hour?
-Yes.
-It's 9.00. It's closed.
-I know one open till 10:00.
-What are you doing? Wait.
-I won't be long.
You can't save him, darling.
If that's what you're thinking.
Why not? Why can't we just go?
I have two tickets for us on the train.
Tonight, midnight. We have the money.
Leave him.
Bonny, it doesn't suit you,
this kind of compassion.
How could I trust you?
There'd always be someone between us.
Why hurt him?
He's a part of you that must die.
You need to kill it,
or I promise you, it will kill you.
What are you doing? Billy?
I'm going back with you,
to finish the job and have done with it.
-You'll have the police all over us.
-Then do as you're told.
Do it now.
-Say it.
-Billy--
Say you're mine. You're mine. Say it.
Yes, what?
Yes, I'm yours.
You startled me.
You took a long time.
What are you doing in the dark?
Thinking.
What are you thinking?
I was thinking that if I ever lost you,
my life would be over.
There would be nothing left for me.
Except to die.
Don't say such things.
Did you find what you were looking for?
Yes, I did.
I had to go all the way across town.
I'm going to go change.
Wash your hands and go to bed.
I'll bring the coffee.
There you are.
How do they die, you think?
From the poison?
I don't know.
Does it take a long time?
I suppose it depends on
how much you give them.
That's right.
Is it painful?
I really don't want to think about it.
No, of course not.
We don't want our conscience
to get the best of us, do we?
It's something that has to be done.
And when something has to be done...
...you do it.
Is your coffee too hot?
I saw him.
Who?
I followed you.
You saw who? Where?
Julia.
Shall we play the game...
...or just speak the truth?
The truth is best.
All right, then.
Is he here?
Yes.
Where?
Outside, waiting.
When I turn the lights off.
When I am dead?
Yes.
I led him to you in Havana, didn't l?
How'd he know I wouldn't kill you?
He put blank cartridges in your gun.
Like a play.
All of it.
Lies.
From the moment I met you.
Not all of it, no.
Do you laugh at me behind my back,
the two of you?
Do you laugh at me
for how stupid I have been?
How blind?
No.
Laugh now when I tell you this.
I loved you, Julia.
Julia is not here. Julia is dead.
Laugh when I tell you that I still love you.
No.
No, not me.
You don't love me.
Yes.
Yes, you.
Not Julia Russell. Not...
...Bonny Castle.
You.
I love you as I know you.
Because I know you.
As you are.
Good and bad.
Better and worse.
I told you this already,
but you didn't believe me.
Tonight you will.
To us.
A short life and an exciting life.
Don't do this.
No other one.
No other love but you.
From first to last.
Start to finish.
Don't change, Julia. Don't ever change.
Hold on.
Let's go.
You disappoint me, Bonny.
What do you think?
Do you think those are real bullets?
-Do you speak English?
-Yes!
He needs a doctor.
What about him?
He's dead. He needs a doctor.
All right. I'm calling the police.
Stay, stay.
I love you.
I love you. Do you hear me?
-Say it. Say it again.
-I love you. I love you.
I love you, Luis.
You hold on! Hold on!
Don't go! Stay!
Please hold on.
And this is where the story ends,
at least for me.
Even though he is alive now...
...how could I get to him?
Do you believe in forgiveness?
Yes.
And redemption for the human soul?
Even for someone like me?
Yes.
I believe so.
I will see him in heaven, won't l?
Yes.
Will you hand me my shawl, please?
Yes, of course.
Now pray with me.
Yes.
I wore this on my wedding day.
But my heart was not in it then.
I'm sorry, ma'am. It is time.
If I may?
What the hell!
-It's the priest.
-But he left an hour ago.
I saw him.
Guards!
I must say, it is a pleasure to be in such
lovely company for a change.
The pleasure is all mine.
Thank you, gentlemen,
for letting me attend.
And you, sir, may I say, it's a lucky man
who has found such a wife.
Yes, I am.
Perhaps, later on...
...l will tell you the story
of how we came to be here.
It is an interesting tale.
Some of it is even true.
But for now, all I can say...
...is that from the moment I saw her...
...l loved her.
And no matter the price...
...you cannot walk away from love.
Four.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org