Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
How about some red-hot peanuts?
Peanuts! Get your peanuts here!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Safe!
Now batting for the Cardinals,
number 14, Stanley Boyer!
Come on!
We missed four innings.
Well, like l said, l had to stop
and do some business. Here. Sit down.
Hey, you usher,
can l talk to you a second?
Yes, sir.
Gil, this is Stan.
He´s gonna watch you for a while.
l have some friends l´m meeting.
l´ll be back for the ninth inning.
- Have fun, kid.
- Get your programs!
- So, Gilly, big baseball fan?
- Kind of.
Dad bring you here a lot?
Once a year on my birthday.
Then he pays an usher to watch me.
Oh, l see.
You have to understand,
my father in his own childhood...
was without a positive
male influence.
Huh?
His own father kicked him out
when he was 15...
so my dad was taught to see
child raising as a burden--
a prison rather than a playground.
You understand what l´m saying?
- You don´t talk like a kid.
- Well, l´m not really a kid.
- You´re not a duck.
- l´m remembering when l was a kid.
l´m 35 now.
l have kids of my own.
You don´t really even exist.
- You´re an amalgam.
- A what?
A combination of several ushers
my dad left me with over the years.
- l combined them into one memory.
- Why?
This was a great
symbolic moment in my life.
My father dumping me with you.
lt´s why l swore things would be
different with my kids.
lt´s my dream--
strong, happy, confident kids.
That´s great.
You´ve got a lovely family,
and l´m a goddamn amalgam!
Who´s that?
- That´s my wife.
- Nice.
Yeah?
Game´s over, honey.
The St. Louis Cardinals thank you
for attending today´s game.
Please drive home safely
and soberly.
Let´s go.
Come on, Justin.
Do you want to walk? Let´s walk.
lt´s fun. Come on. Let´s walk.
Sure you don´t want to walk?
There we go.
l´ll get it.
There´s your pennant.
Watch it!
Watch the car.
Watch it.
There´s so many cars.
Want me to put you down?
Where is that kid?
Where is she?
- Daddy!
- Oh, there she is.
Get in the seat.
Buckle up.
- Honey? Taylor.
- Hey, hey, hey!
You´re a rat.
When you´re slidin´ into first
and you´re feelin´ something burst
Diarrhea, diarrhea
When you´re slidin´ into third
and you lay a juicy turd
Diarrhea, diarrhea
When you´re slidin´ into home
and your shorts are full of foam
When you´re sitting in your Chevy
and your shorts are feeling heavy
Kevin, honey,
where did you learn that song?
Last summer at camp, Mom.
Ah, that was money well spent.
When you´re slidin´ into first
and you´re feelin´ something burst
Diarrhea, diarrhea
That´s what you´re gonna sleep in?
You´ll get cold.
Perfect.
Gil, Taylor isn´t feeling well.
She wants you.
- lt´s those hot dogs.
- l´ll deal with Kevin and Justin.
Hey, what do you say? Later when
the kids are asleep, l wear this outfit?
She´s in our bed.
Hi, Daddy.
What´s the matter, honey?
You don´t feel so good?
- You feel like you want to throw up?
- Okay.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Taylor, baby, sweetie.
Gil, why are you
just standing there?
l´m waiting for her head
to spin around.
Oh, can you come with me to see
Kevin´s principal on Monday?
Oh, l love it when you talk to me
about school and meetings.
- Now talk to me about shopping.
- l know. l´m sorry.
l just remembered now.
l´ve been meaning to ask you.
Fine. l´ll be there.
What´s the matter?
Nothing. l was
a little tense before, but--
No, l mean with Kevin.
Why are we going to see his principal?
Oh, because his teacher said
he´s been making that face again.
Oh, what, this?
Yes, the tense face.
He makes that same face
at Little League.
- You know what his teacher asked me?
- What?
lf we´d ever taken him
for a psychiatric evaluation.
- What?
- She was just asking.
Why? Because he makes a face?
Has she ever looked in the mirror?
Well, you know, the face,
the crying, the nervousness.
- They mentioned the crying?
- Yeah.
You know, he doesn´t really
finish his work.
Hey, we´ll talk to them on Monday.
Don´t worry.
l´m sure he´ll be fine.
Come here.
Where was l?
- Was l here?
- Yeah.
- l was there already?
- Mm-hmm.
That really pisses me off.
The kid needs a little
more attention...
so the teacher´s gonna put
a label on him: ''problem kid.''
Let´s find out who Kevin´s teacher
is gonna be next year...
and make sure it´s not
one of these hysterics!
You´re right, Gil.
Kevin´s great.
He can´t be that much of a problem.
Right. Now, if it was
my sister´s kid--
Garry.
There´s a kid with problems.
Hi, Garry.
You´re up so early.
Yeah.
- Where are you going?
- Out.
- What´s in the bag?
- Nothing.
The whole family´s coming tonight.
There´s a big surprise.
Grandma and Grandpa
are gonna be here.
Uncle Gil and Aunt Karen
are bringing their kids.
Aunt Susie´s gonna be here
and Uncle Nathan and their kids.
lt was nice talking to ya.
Julie.
- Hey, Julie.
- Yeah?
- Can l come in for a minute?
- Yeah.
l really need your help.
The whole family´s coming tonight.
- Could you just give me a hand?
- Yeah, in just a few minutes.
Are you all right?
l heard you moaning last night.
l had a stomachache,
but it´s fine now.
- You hate me?
- What?
For making you study so much
and giving up all your dates.
No, you were right.
Honey, l´m telling you,
those SAT scores are your ticket.
And, sweetie,
once you get to school...
you´re gonna meet a lot of guys
you like just as well as that Tod.
Why do you always say ''that Tod''?
lt sounds so--
You´re right. l´m sorry.
lt´s been pleasant for a moment.
l´m just gonna give everybody
spaghetti and salad...
and l better cook a steak
for my dad.
See you later, honey.
You okay?
Man, your mother can talk!
Gosh, she hates my ass.
And it´s such a cute ass.
Last night she heard the moaning.
She thought it was me.
So you´re gonna have to try
and control yourself, Tod.
With you, it´s impossible.
Wait. l brought something.
Ooh, good.
We can record our love.
Susan? Hi, sis. lt´s Helen.
Did l loan you my big platter?
Great. Would you bring it tonight?
l just need it to serve.
Listen, Julie got 1291
on her SAT´s.
l know.
l feel so proud of her.
lt´s great. How´s Patty?
We´re a little disappointed
with the effort...
she´s been giving
lately towards her work.
Math, French,
everything´s gone downhill.
Nathan´s talking to her right now.
He´s trying to figure out
what´s wrong.
Look, Patty,
all l´m saying is...
if you want to have
just an ordinary academic career...
and attend an ordinary university,
that´s your prerogative.
But l must tell you, l think
you´re selling yourself way short.
- How´s it going?
- l don´t know.
Sometimes l feel as though
we want it more than she does.
Patty, you know we love you.
Could you just give your father
that extra effort he´s looking for?
Okay, Mama.
That´s all l ask.
Come on, Kevin. l got you.
l want that, Kevin.
- Time to come in now, children.
- Hi, Grandma.
Hey, you want to--
- Grandma.
- Gil, you have a good memory.
Was it yours or Helen´s
or Susan´s wedding l got drunk at?
lt was all three, Dad.
Congratulations.
At which one
did l punch the bandleader?
That was mine.
We have photos.
l´m having them blown up
for the commitment hearings.
You think he´s funny, huh?
He wasn´t this funny as a kid.
Stayed in his room all day.
You were a moody son of a bitch.
Gee, l wonder why.
Do you remember that little guy
who wouldn´t leave my side?
l know.
Now if l take a step toward him,
he takes a step away.
l don´t know
what´s happening to him.
He´s just so unhappy,
and he won´t talk to me...
and l don´t know how to help him.
Did you ever consider
having Ed talk to him?
Are you kidding? He won´t even
acknowledge he´s got these kids...
now that he´s got his new wife
and his new kids.
He won´t even fix
my kids´ teeth anymore.
He says it makes him uncomfortable.
l wish he´d drop his drill
down his pants.
Are you seeing anybody?
Well, Garry´s biology teacher
asked me out.
Biology? That´s promising.
Oh, no. He´s not the type
l usually go for.
''The Penal Colony'' by Franz Kafka.
Patty a doctor yet?
Mock if you will.
All right.
Our children are more capable of
absorbing information than we are...
yet we insist on treating them
like adorable little morons.
Are you saying Patty
can learn things l can´t learn?
Patty, which one of these...
is the square root of 8,649?
Ninety-three.
They´re like sponges, Gil,
just waiting to absorb.
l want this.
You see?
Take my advice.
Forget about Kevin and Taylor.
lt´s too late.
Work on Justin.
Actually, Justin is quite bright. ln his
preschool class, he was the only--
Slow down, Justin.
l´ll get you some dip.
You remember that guy you went out
with in college, Jeffrey Sanders?
He always chased me out of the room
when he came over.
- Oh, yeah.
- l saw him today.
- God, what a loser, huh?
- ln a Rolls.
l meant me.
What is that?
Oh, Nathan and Patty and l
are ''power eating.''
We bring our own food everywhere.
Nathan turned me on to it,
and l never felt better.
- Where do you get that stuff?
- This is it.
Everybody in the living room.
This is the big surprise.
Oh, Larry!
My baby!
- You look great. Dad!
- Oh, hi, son.
Great to see you!
- Shit.
- Well put.
Who´s that?
That´s my kid brother Larry,
your uncle.
- Don´t give him any money.
- l won´t.
Just a little something for being
the best dad in the world.
l found it a couple of months ago.
lt´s for your collection.
- A toy car!
- Oh, this is great!
A Stutz!
Yeah, if you´ve got it,
spend it on the people you love.
Right?
- ls this Grandma?
- Yeah, she´s still alive.
Jesus! Grandma, you got short.
l´m shrinking.
Bummer!
Gilbo!
- How long has it been? Three years?
- About that.
You stopped wearing your turban.
Yeah.
My God!
Susan, you look great.
lf you weren´t my sister--
l know it´s been hard.
Dad?
You were supposed to wait outside
so l could introduce you.
Well, why don´t you do it now,
Larry?
Everybody...
this is my son, Cool.
- Did he say ''Cool''?
- Cool.
- Your son?
- lt´s a long story.
Let´s eat.
Keep Patty away from my brother.
He´ll suck the intelligence out of her.
Cool is adorable. Why didn´t you
ever write us you had a son?
l didn´t know myself
until a couple of months ago.
See...
a few years ago l was living
in Vegas with this girl.
A showgirl. She was
in that show, ''Elvis On lce.''
Anyway, we drifted apart...
as people do
in these complicated times...
and then a couple of months ago,
she shows up with Cool, tells me...
''You watch him. l shot someone.
l have to leave the country.''
That´s a parent?
Anyway...
we´re back in town because l´ve got
something really huge cooking.
Enormous. Monster.
Dad, this is it.
From now on, l´m gonna be
taking care of all of you.
This isn´t another get-rich-quick
scheme, is it, Larry?
What´s wrong
with getting rich quick?
Quick is the best way to get rich.
Look who l´m talking to.
You ever see her family?
They find a nickel, they huddle together
and bury it like squirrels.
What´s the deal, son?
What do you have going?
Has anyone heard of hydroponics?
Well, that´s great!
Hydroponics is the growing
of plants without soil.
What are you using? Coarse sand
or suspension hydroponics?
l don´t--
There´s a guy with a lab coat that
makes that decision. l make the deal.
And l got to thinking,
Cool´s had no kind of life, no family.
So while l´m locking this down,
l thought we would stay with you.
- With us?
- A couple of weeks.
The thing is, we don´t have
the big house anymore, you know.
We just have the one bedroom for us
and one for Grandma.
Grandma´s welcome
to stay with us for a while.
lt´d be valuable for Patty to have
a multigenerational influence.
Fine with me.
Well, l´ll have to give you
a list of her medications--
and you´ll have to pick up
her shower chair.
There´s her hearing aid batteries,
magnifying glass for reading.
Oh, geez.
- What happened?
- Your mouth used up all the power.
Don´t worry, Dad.
We can still find the bar.
- l´ll get a flashlight.
- l´ll get it, sis.
- Where is it? ln the bedroom?
- lt´s in the nightstand.
Mom, Dad, what happened?
- You know l don´t like it in the dark.
- This is a blackout.
lt´s a temporary interruption
in the home´s electrical supply.
Something´s busted.
Where´s the switch?
- Bring it here.
- Oh, here it is.
What is this?
- Mommy, what was that?
- That was an electric ear cleaner.
- lt was kind of big.
- lt sure was!
l don´t think we really
have to worry about him.
The point is, once they see us
they´ll realize...
that we´re fine
and the kid is fine.
l think we have to be very careful
about Kevin´s educational environment.
Absolutely.
With that in mind, l don´t think
Kevin should come back here next fall.
l recommend that he
be transferred to a school...
that offers
special education classes.
You mean,
because he´s so smart?
Well, actually, l mean a class
for children with emotional problems.
Hi. l´m sorry l´m late.
You must be the Buckmans.
l´m Dr. Jeffrey Lucas.
Dr. Lucas is a child psychologist.
He´s been observing Kevin
for the last couple of months.
Why?
Mr. Buckman, this is a public school.
Thirty-eight kids to a class.
We estimate that Kevin´s teacher
spent at least...
20% of her time dealing with Kevin.
That class is going to finish
the year behind. lt isn´t fair.
Kevin is a very sweet, sensitive,
extremely tense little boy.
He needs some special attention.
- lt´s ´cause he was first.
- Hmm?
lt´s because he was our first.
l mean, l think we were very tense
when Kevin was little.
lf he got a scratch,
we were hysterical.
By the third kid, you know,
you let them juggle knives.
On the other hand, Kevin may
have been like this in the womb.
Recent studies indicate that
these things are all chemical.
She smoked grass.
- l never smoked when l was pregnant.
- ln college, you were like a chimney--
Fifteen years ago.
There could have been
some chromosome distortion.
Well, you let them do anything.
You let them watch TV
just like that.
So we´ll put the TV´s in the garbage,
and we´ll perform Shakespeare--
l´m sorry.
l´m just a little
thrown off by this.
You should not look upon Kevin´s
going to a special school...
as any kind of failure
on your part.
No, l´ll blame the dog.
ln an educational environment
that´s more sensitive to his needs.
First of all, Kevin is not going
to a special school.
Whether it´s right or not,
there´s a stigma.
Children are cruel.
l won´t subject Kevin
to that kind of cruelty.
lf we have to, we´ll send him
to a private school.
l don´t care what it costs.
l´ll get a second job.
Mr. and Mrs. Buckman,
this problem won´t just go away.
lf we need to, we´ll send Kevin
to a private therapist.
That´s right. Look, it´s a problem.
We´re aware of it.
But we´re his parents.
We can handle it.
Well, the next school year
is four months off...
so let´s see
what can be accomplished, hmm?
- l need to see.
- No, not in the street.
Please.
What is this?
lt´s the party celebrating
my mother´s promotion at the bank.
Excuse me. This is the wrong batch.
This is my mother´s.
There should be another envelope
for Buckman.
That was picked up already.
By who?
l, l, l think this one
is my favorite.
This is just--
lt was just for fun, Mom.
Well, l´m glad to know
it´s not a job.
lt´s that Tod, isn´t it?
There´s one where you can see his face.
Does it bother you that l did those
things or that l did them with Tod?
Gee whiz, Julie. There´s so many things
that bother me about this...
l don´t know how to separate them.
Whoo! Here´s something
for my wallet.
Tod is very important to me.
And we´ve got the pictures
to prove it.
- Mom.
- This is your room.
You did these things
right here in my house?
Well, l thought someone in
this house ought to be having sex.
l mean, with something
that doesn´t require batteries.
What did you say to me?
Goddamn it! You get back here!
Open this door!
Goddamn it to hell!
l would just like a little respect!
Not a lot, just a little!
Do you know why l´m having sex
with machinery?
Because your father left to have a party
and l stayed to raise two kids!
l have no life!
Goddamn it!
What are you doing?
l´m leaving before we say things
we´ll regret.
You´re gonna say something worse
than the battery remark?
Tod and l are in love.
lt´s not ''going steady'' love.
lt´s love.
l need him. He´s my life.
He touches me, and l quiver.
Oh, would you give me
just a small break?
See? You can´t handle it.
Tod´s working now. We´ll find
a place to live somewhere.
- Hi, Garry.
- Hi.
- l´m moving out, Garry.
- Bye.
You´ve upset your brother!
Julie, l´m telling you...
if you walk out of this house,
don´t ever think about coming back.
Fine.
Honey, l´m always here
if you need me. Sweetheart!
Honey, be careful.
lf you want anything, just call me!
Bye.
Oh, man!
lncredible!
Just incredible!
l knew you´d be the one
who´d appreciate this.
Three years, every night, every weekend,
l had dinner out here.
Yeah, it was a piece of junk
when l found it.
First time l got laid
was in a car like this.
- Frank?
- What?
Cool just finished lunch.
l´ll call the newspaper.
l thought you and Larry
could take him somewhere.
l am showing Larry my car.
Just plop him in front of the TV.
That´s what he always does.
Wasn´t that Super Bowl incredible
right down to the last minute?
Amazing.
They´re usually not that close.
And usually the winning team
covers the point spread.
Usually, you can count on it.
- Take a beating?
- No, thanks. l already took one.
Anyway, l had to pay off,
and it´s left me a little--
- What do you need?
- Huh?
Aw, come on. Don´t insult me.
l didn´t come here to be insulted.
Come on.
Puttin´ together a deal, you gotta look
like you can piss with the big boys.
You see? You know.
How much?
A couple thousand.
Three, tops.
- Three?
- Tops.
Good. See, Grandma,
Patty studies Eastern philosophy.
Our future leaders will have to be much
more in tune with the Oriental mind.
Okay, sweetie, one more time.
- Nathan, guess what?
- Oh, you´re home early.
- l have good news.
- What?
What´s up?
l´m going to teach summer school.
We´ll have vacation money.
Oh, that´s great.
Mexico.
Gil and Karen will watch Patty.
l just want to call them.
Gee, honey, l´m really not too pro
on Patty spending a week with Gil.
Why not?
l´m a little concerned
about his jocularity.
He´s a wonderful guy.
lt´s just he´s
a little lighthearted...
about things that l--
that we consider important.
She has fun over there.
You know, she scampers.
She cavorts.
Hey, try this.
We take Patty with us.
To Mexico?
lt´s a perfect opportunity
to start her on Spanish.
lt´ll be fun.
Nathan, l thought it would be nice
if you and l could be alone.
We will be.
We´ll get two rooms.
Which one will l be in?
That means ''come here'' in Spanish.
Please. l want you
to listen to something.
l´ve got a tape
of a mariachi band.
An authentic indigenous
native Mexican form of music.
- Gil, good morning.
- Hello, Cindy.
When were you gonna tell me?
Tell you what?
Lenny called this morning.
He wondered where we should take Phil
Richards to celebrate his partnership.
That Lenny is an asshole.
You believe that guy?
Nobody was supposed to have
that information until next month.
That partnership is mine.
You said when Ted got back,
you´d make it official.
Look, l never said you didn´t do
great work. You do terrific work.
Every firm does good work.
l know you´re smarter than Phil,
but the guy works like a Trojan.
He schmoozes clients.
He brings in business.
He´s here nights, weekends.
l own the guy. And that´s
what puts your name on the door.
This is really coming
out of left field.
l´ve been here eight years.
l´m the backbone of the operation.
l know that.
lf l don´t get this partnership,
l gotta think about going elsewhere.
- That´s not realistic.
- Why?
You go somewhere else,
you´re gonna have to get in line...
behind guys who are younger,
who have been there longer...
who are more committed
and are willing to work for less money.
Look, this thing with Phil
is not etched in stone.
l can jerk him along
for the next month.
Why don´t you use that time
to give us your best shot?
Put in the hours.
Dazzle me.
Dazzle you?
Listen, Dave.
l´m having a problem at home.
l really need to spend
a lot of extra time with my son.
Then l don´t know what we can do.
Get this guy. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, well. They´re bad dudes. That´s
why they call the game ''Bad Dudes.''
l should go stay with the girls.
Got enough quarters?
- Dad?
- Yeah?
How come l´m seeing
a psychiatrist?
We were gonna have
a big talk about that.
- What´s wrong with me?
- Nothing.
- You´re great.
- Then how come--
You´re a kid like l was.
You have a lot of worries. That´s all.
And these doctors are experts
at helping people with their worries.
lt´s nothing to feel bad about.
You´re a great kid,
and l love you very much, okay?
Hey, you know what l think?
This is gonna be a great summer for you.
And don´t forget
you got a birthday coming up.
Let´s have a great party.
Can we have Cowboy Dan?
- Who?
- Cowboy Dan.
The gun-fighting balloon man.
He was at Billy´s party. He´s cool.
Absolutely.
lt´s a done deal.
This is your dad talking.
Now you´ve got me excited.
Now, what do we say when we see
a cute eight-year-old girl?
Hubba-hubba.
Don´t tell your mom l taught you that.
lt could be bad. Let´s go.
Wow!
- You like it?
- Yeah.
- lt´s good. lt´s shiny.
And you know,
it was junk when l found it.
The first time l got laid
was in a car--
That´s a story for another time.
Hi, Dad.
Dinner ready?
What was that?
Huh? Oh, some friends
who were just dropping me off.
Friends? Friends slow down.
They even stop.
Sweetie, you´re gonna be okay.
Honey, why would you
be panhandling?
l needed money
for a place to stay.
You have a place to stay.
l´d have to tell you what happened.
- What did happen?
- l don´t want to tell you.
- Did you leave that Tod?
- Yes.
He promised me he was gonna start
a house-painting business.
Then he said he changed his mind.
He´s gonna race dragsters
with his brothers.
He can´t even drive a regular car.
So his brothers came over,
and we got in a fight.
He said, ''No bitch is gonna
tell me what to do for a living.''
He told me he loved me.
Sweetie.
They say that...
and then they come.
Honey, what can you expect
from a kid like that?
Mom, back off. The last guy
you dated stole our furniture.
- Men are scum.
- l know.
l know, sweetie.
Men are scum.
- Honey, Julie´s home.
- Great.
Come on. Let´s go eat
lots of ice cream.
You want an ice-cream soda?
How about a hot fudge sundae?
You want a banana split?
Do you want something
like french fries?
- Yes.
- You do?
l thought l´d find you here.
Does that make you Sherlock Holmes?
l live here.
You live with me.
l wouldn´t live with you...
if the world were flooded with piss
and you lived in a tree.
l´m going to the movies.
You´re not leaving here
till you hear what l have to say.
l´m not--
Let go of me!
- Let her go!
- Just listen to me.
Let her go!
Goddamn it! Let her go!
Please, Mrs. Buckman.
l love her.
You can´t run out on me.
You´re my wife.
lf you don´t let her go,
l´m gonna call the-- His what?
His wife. We got married
a couple of days ago.
Are you out of your mind?
Please, Mrs. Buckman.
Julie, l didn´t mean it.
l´m sorry.
My brothers were ragging on me,
and l couldn´t back down.
But last night, l told them.
They mean nothing.
You mean everything.
Christ!
Okay, look lively.
You´re doing great.
Shortstop, here it goes.
All right, pick it up.
Easy now, over to first.
That´s the way to play.
That´s right. You´re beautiful.
You´re a bunch of
wild, young Bohemians.
Let´s go again.
Second base, here we go.
Get down on it. Don´t be afraid.
lt can´t hurt you. Here we go.
Get down on it!
Wayne, get Ben some ice.
All right, we´re gonna need
a new second base man.
Which one of you outfielders
wants to try second base?
How about you, Kevin?
You want to try second base?
All right!
Oh, Matt, none of that.
Let´s be a team.
Get out there and hustle.
Remember, the word is ''fun.''
So just go on out there...
and what you catch you catch
and what you miss you miss.
Okay, Dad.
Way to go, Kevin!
And now it is my great pleasure
to introduce our valedictorian...
Kevin Buckman.
Thank you.
When l was nine years old,
l had kind of a rough time.
A lot of people thought
l was pretty mixed up.
But there was one person
who got me through it.
He did everything right.
And thanks to him, today...
l´m the happiest,
most confident...
and most well-adjusted person
in this world.
Dad, l love you.
You´re the greatest.
All right!
One more out, guys! Let´s go!
ls your arm tired, Shaun?
Hey, Gil, our boys
finally gonna win one game?
Way to be supportive, Lou.
That´s right, Kevin!
Way to go, Tommy!
All right!
We got bases loaded.
We´re only one run down.
You can do it.
Get up there.
Please, God,
let ´em win one game.
Got it!
You stink, Buckman!
- He had no business being out there!
- What´s the matter with you?
lt´s terrible!
Why´d you make me play
second base?
Someone´s climbed to the roof
of the bell tower with a rifle!
lt´s Kevin Buckman.
His father totally screwed him up.
What´s he yelling?
You made me play second base!
Kevin, l´m sorry.
l did the best l could.
Nice shot, son.
lt´s important to be supportive.
Come on. Let´s sing
one of the old tunes.
When you´re sliding into home
and your pants are full of foam
Diarrhea
Well?
Why are you pouring water
through my diaphragm?
To check.
To see if it´s okay.
You didn´t know l did that, huh?
Obviously not,
or you wouldn´t have tried this.
Are you accusing me
of making that hole?
No, a woodpecker came in here,
went into the bathroom...
opened the drawer with his wing
and pecked holes in your diaphragm.
l can´t believe you would jeopardize
our plan. Remember what we read?
A majority of exceptional people
are either only children...
or firstborns
with five years between sibs.
- We agreed--
- No, you agreed.
And they´re not sibs.
They´re babies, and l want another one.
So this is how you go about it?
By vandalizing your contraception?
- Because you won´t discuss it!
- We discussed this years ago!
l think we were wrong.
l think we were right,
and l´m not discussing it again.
- Tod?
- Yeah?
- Do you want me to make breakfast?
- No, thanks, Helen.
- Julie´s gonna do it.
- l´ll get the fire extinguisher.
l´ll see you guys at dinner.
Sweet Jesus!
What are you doing?
Are you joining the Marines?
l knew you´d make
a thing out of this, Mom.
Just clean up the hair.
You ready?
Want anything to eat?
How long are they
gonna be living here?
Not much longer, l think.
l was just thinking.
lt´s getting pretty crowded here.
lt´s not so crowded. There´s a lot
more room since they shaved their heads.
l was just thinking...
maybe l could stay with Dad
for a while.
What?
l´ve been here a long time. Maybe
l should live with him for a while.
You wanna live with your father?
Kind of.
Have you talked to your father
about that?
No. Not yet. l thought l´d call him.
Honey...
you don´t know
your father like l do.
l don´t know him at all.
What´s his number?
He´d be at work now.
So that´s...
2-0-6...
5-7-9-0.
ls Dr. Lampkin there?
His son.
No, Dad, it´s not Joey.
lt´s Garry, your other son.
l need to ask you something.
lt´ll just take a second.
Would it be okay
if l stay with you for a while?
A few months.
Shit.
He didn´t think
it was such a good idea.
- Sweetie--
- l´ve gotta go.
When´s Cowboy Dan, the gun-fighting
balloon man, gonna be here?
lsn´t that him?
That´s the schmuck
who brought the horse.
- l don´t think he´s coming.
- Of course, he is. He´s a professional.
You think he wants to put a blot on
the entire balloon-bending profession?
Go on and have fun. We´ll have
burgers and dogs in a second.
Let´s go watch the horse shit.
Why don´t you play with Justin?
l don´t understand what he´s doing.
He´s spinning.
What for?
No reason. Just for fun.
Doesn´t look like fun.
lt isn´t.
You tried it?
So does Julie have a nice place?
Yeah, she has a lovely place.
She has my place.
She and that Tod are both
living in my house.
Really?
Actually, it was my idea.
Otherwise, she was gonna quit school
and get a job.
Maybe this way
she´ll still go to college.
Here we go.
The thumb trick. Ready?
Here´s my thumb. Watch it.
- What are you doing?
- The thumb trick. Show her, Dad.
Okay, but this is the last time.
Here we go. Ready?
l mean, Justin is gonna
go full-time next year...
so everybody´s askin´ when l´m gonna
go back to work like l´m supposed to.
And l´m thinkin´ about it.
l mean, l used to work. lt was okay.
But l think l´m better at this.
l think l´m sort of good at it, so--
But then people make me feel embarrassed
like l don´t have goals or something.
Like l sit around here eating bonbons
all day, right? Oh, l don´t know.
What does Gil say?
He says l should do whatever l want.
l could have killed him for that.
What are you so upset about?
Nathan, she´s weird.
She´s a weird child.
l think a few days a week
of preschool could be very helpful.
This is not the right age for Patty
to be socially activated.
She´s not a bomb. She´s a little kid who
has no ability to relate to other kids.
You want her to relate to him?
Help, help, help!
When l met him, l was a little wild.
l was a little out of control.
He kind of took me in hand.
l liked that.
He´s very commanding.
He got me into teaching.
He got my shit together.
Boy, he really turned me on.
Really? l mean, of course, really.
Nathan and l used to be hot.
l know he doesn´t look it,
but we were like rabbits.
l used to give him, you know...
oral, you know, on the highway.
What?
He was always trying
to get a research grant.
And you thought that would help?
No, but, l mean,
he kept getting turned down.
He´d get real, real tense.
So if l saw him getting
really tense, l´d just...
lean over while
he was driving and l´d--
l just spoke to your mother. Grandmother
wants to stay at Helen´s for a while.
- Can you drive her there tomorrow?
- Sure.
He likes to butt things
with his head.
How proud you must be.
Here it is. Now it´s right there
in front of you. Be careful.
Here. Take this off.
Now really try and hit it.
Really give it a good shot.
Give it a good whack!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3djyy
Help other users to choose the best subtitles