Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
( birds squawking )
- ( alarm beeps )
- ( man groans )
( dogs barking )
Man:
Good morning, guys.
How's it going?
Bailey, what's up?
What's up?
Hey, Chewy.
Hey, Watson, how's it going?
Looking good.
Queenie, Rascal.
Okay.
Want some food,
want some food?
Wolf it down.
That's it,
that's all you get.
Water?
( water sprinkling )
- ( whines )
- How are you?
There she is,
there she is.
Okay, all right, Lexi,
all right.
Hey.
Back it up,
back it up.
Hey, Lexi.
Back it up.
Hey, hey.
Hey, big doggie.
Big doggie,
big doggie.
( muffled music playing )
( stop request chimes )
Holly, right?
Holly Garling.
Hi.
How are you?
Hi. I'm sorry,
do we know each other?
Oh, Seth.
West Brook High.
- Oh. Were you in my class?
- Oh, I was in the year
above you.
We didn't hang out
or anything,
but I knew
who you were.
You did?
Sure, everybody did.
I don't know about that.
So you're
a writer now, huh?
That's cool.
That's great.
Yeah. This whole
waitressing uniform,
it's just a disguise.
It's convincing.
I was gonna order
an ice cream sundae.
- Extra sprinkles.
- You wouldn't be
the first.
- This is my stop.
- Oh, this is you?
It was nice
to see you again.
Nice to see you too.
Hey, if you're not doing
anything...
...get a coffee.
( muffled music playing )
Hmm.
- Man on TV: We're looking
at your numbers...
- Seth: Hey.
There he is.
There's the man.
- Nate, let me ask you
a question.
- Hmm?
If there was this girl
and you wanted her
to notice you...
Are you serious
right now?
Yeah.
Shit, man,
I don't know you.
I don't know
what kind of game you got.
What are you asking me?
Sorry.
I thought maybe...
Listen, wait...
You like this girl?
- We are talking
about a girl here right?
- Yes, girl.
I do like her.
So just confident,
you know?
Guy who's confident.
Knows how to make
them laugh.
Tell 'em about your day.
Act like you give a shit.
I mean,
it ain't a mystery.
Confident, funny,
make 'em laugh.
Got it. Good.
Thanks.
Hey, and no more bringing
this shit to me, all right?
You and me,
we ain't like that.
Cool.
( taps )
Seth, Dr. Jessup needs
your help.
He's putting down
the German Shepherd in 34.
Lexi.
Look, you're a sweet guy.
But if you can't do your job,
I'll find someone who can.
- Is that clear?
- She's a really good dog.
Hey, Lexi. Hey.
Here's the thing,
we just--
hey, girl.
Hey, Lexi. Hey.
How's it going?
Wanna go for a walk?
Hey, hey, hey.
Good girl.
Yeah, it's exciting,
isn't it?
All right, Lexi.
Here we go.
All right,
that's a good dog.
Yeah, that's a good dog.
- Dr. Jessup: You all right?
- Yeah, she's just a good dog.
Shh, it's okay, Lexi.
It's all right.
You want her,
you can always keep her.
My building
doesn't allow pets.
Very strict.
Fucking find a new place.
$9.00 an hour?
I'm lucky I have
running water.
That's your whole problem.
You got no initiative.
It's how come you're still
working in a shit hole like
this at your age.
You want something
in this life,
you gotta take it.
( sighs )
So what's it gonna be?
I mean, you want her,
she's yours.
Do it,
do it already.
All right, Lexi.
Here we go.
You're a good dog.
Hold still.
( faint scraping )
( faint music playing )
Seth:
Hey, Holly, hey.
What time
do you get lunch?
What time do you
get lunch?
I get lunch at 1:00.
1:00.
Hey, hey, hi.
Hey...
Hey, remember me?
That's right.
Uh, well,
I guess table for one
while I'm here,
but really I was
just wondering
if you wanted to get
maybe dinner later.
I don't know about you,
but I love seafood.
Oh, you do?
Yeah, that's all I eat.
Seafood, seafood...
There's a, uh--
there's a place on--
there's a place on Wilshire
called the Crab Joint.
Oh, you know it?
Yeah, we could-- tonight?
It's--
hey, Holly, hey.
Hey, Holly.
How's it going?
Hey...
- Hi. Anywhere?
- Yeah, anywhere is fine.
Okay. Thanks.
Hey, how are you?
I'm Holly.
I'll be taking care
of you today.
You must be a writer.
- I'm sorry?
- Seth: A writer.
The disguise
from the bus.
We met a couple
of days ago on the bus.
- My name's Seth.
- I'm so sorry.
My memory, it like
totally sucks.
I know, just what you want
to hear from your waiter,
right?
No, that's fine.
Uh, can I get you
started with anything?
An appetizer?
Yeah, um...
Let's uh--
let's do water.
And then by the time
you come back, I'll know.
Water. Una agua.
You got it.
Hey, um,
I like your hair.
It looks different
from the bus.
- It's nice.
- Thank you.
Yeah. You shouldn't feel
insecure about it
or self conscious,
it's--
is a good haircut.
Uh. Why don't you
take a look at the menu
and I will go grab
your water.
Yeah. Pie.
Apple pie.
How's it going
over here?
- Seth.
- What's that?
Seth.
My name is Seth.
How's the food, Seth?
It's good.
It's quality.
Actually, I had
a question for you.
Do you like Ben Folds?
'Cause I have
a couple of tickets
to his concert this week
and the girl
I was gonna go with--
not a girlfriend
or anything--
she can't make it,
she has a thing.
I was wondering
if maybe you'd wanna...
- go?
- I'm sorry, I can't.
I don't like going
to shows by myself,
it feels kind of strange,
you know, so maybe...
Not a big deal, no pressure.
We could just go.
It wouldn't have to be
a date or anything.
The thing is, I already
sort of have a boyfriend, so...
No, you don't.
I'm just gonna
leave this here.
Thanks for coming in.
Hang on a second.
( branch snaps )
( people on TV chattering )
Man on TV:
But, like, when they do speak,
you know you're in trouble.
Hey.
- There's a guy out there.
- Ooh, is he hot?
I'm serious, Claire.
Don't get paranoid
on me, Hol.
You're no fun
when you're paranoid.
- Never mind.
- ( cell phone rings )
Ten bucks says it's him.
- Yes, Eric.
- Eric: Hey, babe.
- Holly: What do you want?
- Eric: Jesus, what's with
the attitude?
I just wanted to talk.
I've been thinking about you.
Is he drunk
and weepy again?
A little bit.
Eric:
Who are you talking to?
You with someone?
Don't get paranoid
on me, Eric.
You're no fun
when you're paranoid.
( snickers )
Claire:
So the other night
with Eric?
Really? Are we gonna
go there again?
He was two years,
you can't convince me
he never mattered.
I'm serious,
though, Hol.
Being alone
is just kinda shitty.
So, what, I'm just supposed
to forget everything he did?
Yes. Forget, forgive.
Move the fuck on already.
Just go back to the way
things were.
You know
I can't do that.
To us.
Hey, Sam.
- Someone's popular.
- What?
We put it
in the break room.
Okay...
Lucky, bitch.
Spill. Who's the guy?
- Hey.
Listen, I'm so sorry
for the drunk dial
the other night.
I mean,
you know how it is.
Yeah, I do.
Listen, can I get you
a beer or something?
Eric, you have to stop
doing stuff like this.
Stuff like...
what now?
Come on. Roses? You know
they're my favorite.
I didn't know that.
Okay. Well,
now I just feel stupid.
- Well-- just one beer.
- I should go.
It wasn't all bad, right?
We had some good times.
Yep.
So why don't we
give it another shot?
Are you really gonna
make me say her name?
Eric: This is
so fucking stupid.
I mean,
we had something.
Had.
Eric, past tense.
I'm gonna get some air.
Seth:
Nice night.
- Yeah.
- Yep.
- Not a smoker?
- Me? No.
( exhales )
That's good.
Don't ever start,
it's a terrible habit.
Okay, I won't.
Thanks.
- Have a nice night.
- You like the flowers?
You seemed like
a red and white roses
kind of girl.
It was just a guess.
Oh, my God.
You're that guy
from the restaurant.
Seth.
What are you, like,
following me or something?
What? No. Just...
Look, I'm not
some psycho, okay?
You know me.
We went to school
together.
What do you want?
I don't want anything.
I just want to talk to you.
When I saw you on the bus
the other day,
after all these years,
I felt something.
I know you did.
I can't just walk
away from that.
- I don't even know you.
- But you will.
- You can go, I just--
Can I just talk to you?
- No.
- Hey, hang on.
- Don't! Don't touch me.
Move!
Are you kidding me?
Seth:
Just let me talk to you.
Fuck you. Fuck you!
- Just let me explain.
- Eric: What the fuck?
- He tried to grab me.
- Seth: What? No.
Hey, that is not
true at all, man.
( grunts )
Fuck off.
( whimpers )
- Did he hurt you?
- I'm fine.
- ( chuckles )
- You think this is funny?
Eric, stop.
Stop it.
- Stop it.
- Laugh it up, dick head.
Let me handle this.
- Hey. ( strains )
- Come on.
Get the fuck away
from her.
Don't you
ever come back here.
( groans )
( coughs )
Maybe if you retrace
your steps.
No. It's gotta be
here somewhere.
Well, was your name in it?
Or like any
contact information?
What do you think?
( seagulls squawking )
( clatters )
( taps )
( clangs )
- ( screams )
- ( sprays )
( coughing )
You fucking bitch!
( coughs )
- ( homeless man yells )
- ( glass shatters )
( faint clattering )
Claire?
You here?
( muffled screaming )
Shh.
What I just put in you
is called pancuronium bromide.
It's a paralyzing agent.
It stings a little.
Don't worry, it's safe.
I tested it on myself.
( faint music playing )
( music continues )
( strains )
What you doing here?
Oh, boss lady calls
in the middle of the night,
gotta make a delivery.
Not so fast, man.
Sign in.
Right.
( dull thud )
( coughs )
- Excuse me.
- The hell's that?
I think it's
delousing powder.
All right,
see you later.
( Holly gasps )
- You hear that?
- What?
- Something wrong?
- Shh.
- You hear something?
- Quiet, man.
You heard that, right?
That "uh" sound.
I don't hear anything.
What is it?
( air conditioner humming )
Fucking, AC, man.
Shit's always going out.
Oh, I got it.
I got it.
- It's broken?
- It's always broken.
- This whole place sucks.
- All right.
( dogs barking )
( dripping )
( heavy breathing )
( whimpers )
( gasps )
( strains )
( screams )
( groans )
( screaming )
( faint screaming )
( dogs barking )
Shut up.
( alarm beeping )
( music playing faintly )
( electricity humming )
( zipper unzips )
So, I'm Seth.
In case you forgot.
Fuck you.
Your choice.
- Fuck you!
- I'm doing this
for your own good.
We'll try this
again tomorrow.
( Holly screams )
Fuck you!
( screaming )
( faint screaming
continues )
Fuck you!
( woman on TV chattering )
( dogs barking )
( barking continues )
( Holly wheezing )
( door opens )
( door closes )
( electricity humming )
( wheezing continues )
Seth: Hi.
I brought you
some water.
Here.
Drink this.
- ( chokes )
- There.
( gasping )
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
Sit up.
Sorry.
Take it easy.
It's okay.
I brought food as well.
In case you feel up for it.
Water, food.
Just take it easy,
all right.
That's all
you're getting today.
Wait!
Please don't leave me.
I know this is hard.
It's hard for me too.
But it's important to define
our relationship.
Establish some boundaries.
This.
This doesn't work.
That's right.
I'll come back tomorrow.
And we'll get started.
( door opens, closes )
He's gonna kill you.
But you know that.
Maybe he'll lose
his nerve, huh?
Chicken out.
Or maybe he'll
just get bored.
You're not helping.
He won't even need
a gun, Holly.
All he has to do
is walk away.
Shut up.
Claire:
Look at you.
You're letting him
beat you?
That pathetic
little shit?
If that's all it takes,
then maybe you deserve
to be in there.
Shut up!
- ( squeaks )
- ( gasps )
( stomping )
( panting )
Are you gonna rape me?
Seth: No.
Kill me?
I hope not.
You hope not?
Might not have
a choice.
And why's that?
I might not be able
to save you.
What is this,
some kind of fucking
religious thing?
Did God tell you
to punish all the whores,
something like that?
It's a different
kind of saving.
- And, no.
- So what, you're just
a sick fuck?
This is how you get
your kicks?
I'm not doing this
for me.
I'm doing this
for you.
Because you're special.
Special?
It's true.
Before I met you,
I was just floating
through life.
Like any minute,
I could just drift off.
No one would
even notice.
Then you came along.
And the thing--
the thing that made it
so hard is,
is I thought
you were different.
You're smart. Funny.
When you talked to me,
you saw me,
you really saw me.
That's just what you
wanted me to see, huh?
The version of Holly you are
when everyone's watching.
But we both know
that's a lie, don't we?
Go to hell.
That's the question.
Which one's
the real Holly?
The Holly on the outside
or the other Holly.
Because if there's
even a chance I can save you,
I have to take it.
But if that's it,
if there's nothing
left to save,
then you're never
leaving this room.
Nate:
What you doing here?
Man, if they catch you
fucking around them tunnels.
They won't catch me,
I'm not going in there.
Just grab a mop.
We got that place smellin'
like dog shit out there.
Shit.
( door rattles )
This fuckin' dude
is a joke.
Claire: So...
what are you
gonna do now?
I'm gonna wait.
Claire:
Good girl.
Seth:
It's a real page-turner.
You're a hell of a writer,
you know that?
You're a thief.
And now what?
Suddenly, you got me
all figured out.
I wish. No.
Mostly I just felt
sorry for you.
You? Felt sorry for me?
Yeah, it's the part
where you talk about love.
"Love is just a label
for our biological
imperatives."
I don't know.
Felt ignorant to me.
Are you really gonna
lecture me on love, Seth?
You're keeping a girl
in a cage.
I think I finally
figured it out.
All these people
who talk about love
like it's this
lightning bolt from the sky.
This irresistible force.
So you think, well,
I've never felt that.
But those people
are wrong.
Love is not
a lightning bolt.
Love is, real love,
takes work.
Sacrifice.
Real love is giving
everything you have
to someone else.
- That's love.
- Fucking kidding me?
You don't think?
"Love is sacrifice"?
You know who believes that?
People who hate themselves.
Who are alone, depressed.
Just like you.
- You think I have myself?
- I know you do.
You hate yourself so much,
you can't even imagine
how fucked up someone
would have to be
to love you back.
So you convince yourself
that love is this thing
that you can buy.
That all you have
to do is keep giving.
Well, like I said,
I just feel sorry for you.
Spare me
the fucking pity,
I'm not the one
who's alone here.
Oh, I guess not.
And how is Claire
these days?
What are you talking about?
You know, sometimes
before I open that door,
I can heard you
talking in here
to Claire.
The way you do
two voices
scared the hell
out of me at first.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I know more
than you think.
Is she here, right now?
No.
She's not real.
You don't think
I know that?
I think you're
starting to forget
Don't get paranoid
on me, Eric.
You're no fun
when you're paranoid.
Seth:
You're sick, Holly.
Feeding that sickness
until all it does is eat.
You just have it all
figured out, don't you?
Almost.
One thing
I still don't understand.
The journal.
( car engine roars )
First, I get it.
You and Eric getting
engaged.
Blah, blah, blah.
But here comes
your best friend, Claire.
The real Claire.
( imitates dramatic music )
Holly can't eat.
Holly can't sleep.
Holly wants to confront them
but Holly's too scared.
Fuck you.
Then here.
Here's where it gets
really interesting.
Claire:
I get home
and there's like
20 messages
from Dwayne, right?
He's like,
"Where are you?
Why haven't you
picked me up yet?"
Even though,
he's the one who said
that he was coming
to get me on Saturday.
You know,
somehow of course
it's just magically
my fault.
Were you going
to tell me?
Tell you what?
Come on, Claire.
You know.
Um, not really.
Eric.
( tires squeal )
How'd you find out?
His email.
He doesn't know
I have the password.
- Shit
- Yeah.
Holly, what do you
want me to say?
You know, I'm sorry.
We were so drunk.
And it didn't mean
anything.
Oh, well, as long
as it didn't mean anything.
Okay, Holly,
please slow the car down.
You're unbelievable.
( tire screeching )
- Do you know that?
- I'm sorry.
You have no idea
how shitty I feel
about this whole thing.
And if it-- damn it, please
slow the car down, okay?
You're supposed to be
my best fucking friend.
Holly, come on.
Jesus.
- ( car horn blaring )
- ( tires screeching )
Holly! God damn it,
you're gonna kill us.
- ( car horn blaring )
- ( tires screeching )
( crashing )
Boom.
( groans )
Oh, my God.
Oh, my fucking God.
We're okay.
I'm all right.
- We're gonna
be okay, Holly.
- ( gasps )
We're okay, Holly.
We're gonna be fine.
We're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna be fine.
And you think
that's what?
A confession?
I'm a writer, Seth.
Fiction's
kind of what I do.
( laughing )
Seth:
That's why I didn't go
straight to the police.
I had to be sure.
I thought I'd follow you
around for a few days,
but you didn't make me
wait long.
( gasping )
- ( glass shattering )
- Seth: It was a risky move.
- Homeless man: No!
- Seth: Even for you.
- ( Homeless man screams )
- ( fire erupts )
( screaming )
Seth:
There were so many.
You want to know
what I think?
I think you wanted
to get caught.
That's why you kept
the journal.
You wanted
to get punished.
Lucky you came along .
You don't get it,
do you?
This isn't punishment.
I'm trying
to save you.
Then do it.
Save me.
I will.
I meant what I said.
I'm gonna stop you
hurting other people.
One way or the other.
And the Oscar
goes to...
He wants to save me.
I have to let him
think there's a chance.
So that was all an act?
You were just
humoring him?
- Playing along...
- If you've got
something to say...
I'm just making sure
your head's still in the game.
I don't need another
useless pep talk, Claire.
And I don't need you.
Yes?
What?
No. Nothing.
Just was curious.
Why you did it.
I guess, when I saw
Eric's email,
all those messages
from Claire--
No, not Claire.
I understand that.
It's a crime of passion
or whatever.
I wanna know why
you didn't stop there.
Why you killed the others.
'Cause you feel guilty
for what you did to Claire,
for getting away with it.
You wanted to get caught,
didn't you?
No, because I could.
Yeah, I don't believe that.
Well, I don't care
what you believe.
'Cause see,
here's the thing, Seth.
When someone dies
in front of you,
the way Claire died,
it's like you're whole world
just snaps into focus.
Cry for help?
It was a way
to pass the time.
Don't pretend
you know what I am.
You're wrong,
I do know you.
I know you from this.
And the girl
who wrote this,
you had dreams.
She cared about people.
Who's scared to be alone.
This is the real you.
Not...
Seth's got a little crush.
This isn't about us.
If you love something,
set it free.
Isn't that
how that goes?
You know
I can't do that.
Do you know what happens
to a great white shark
when you put him
inside an aquarium?
It bashes its brains
against the glass.
Every time.
Come on.
- ( smacks )
- Stop, Holly, stop!
Stop, Holly!
What are you gonna do
when you come down
here tomorrow
and I'm belly up
in the tank, huh?
'Cause you can't
just walk away.
Not with your finger prints
all over the place.
I kill myself,
your life ends too.
So how's that
for the boundaries
of our fucking
relationship?
( door opens, closes )
( dogs barking )
( humming )
- Seth?
- Hmm?
Finish this up
and come see me
in my office.
Something wrong?
"Is something wrong?"
That's the question,
isn't it?
I'm not following you.
The kennels are filthy.
We've got bugs up
in the stock room.
And where's Seth?
He's not here,
that's for sure.
Nate says you haven't
been here in two days.
Mrs. Gundy,
Nate is hardly--
Nate does his job.
You should've done yours.
You're firing me?
Disciplinary notice.
This goes in your
permanent record.
One more strike
and you're gone.
Understand?
Understood.
Thank you.
You don't know how much
this means to me.
This, this is what's
gonna happen to you
when you think
you're in control.
You think you're
in control, Holly.
Well, this is what'll happen
when you think you're in--
- I control the situation.
- ( whispers echoing )
There's the man.
Just doing some maintenance.
Didn't ask.
Hey, Seth.
I got your paycheck.
Still here, huh?
Where's the rest?
There is no rest.
This is what happens
when you start acting
like you're in control.
That's not enough.
You don't get
to decide that.
Fuck you.
Fuck me?
I go through hell
for you
and what do you do,
threaten me?
You ever pull
that shit again,
I'll show you what
a real hunger strike feels like.
Fuck you.
I had a dream last night
and you were in it.
It was just
the two of us.
And we were in this house
down by the water.
And I think we'd been
living there a long time
'cause there were these
pictures on the walls.
Pictures of us.
It was weird
looking at them,
because something
about it felt right.
Like this,
this whole world
is a dream
and that house on the beach,
that's reality.
That's how things
are supposed to be.
Seth:
Maybe I can get you
some snacks
from the vending machine.
Thanks, Seth.
( door closes )
Holy shit.
There's a light
on the wall.
Hey, what's your name?
Um, I'm Nate.
Listen to me, Nate.
You have to find something
to break open this lock.
Can you do that?
What kind of fucked up...
- Did Seth do this?
- Nate, there's no time
for that right now.
Okay, go at it hard,
at an angle.
We gotta call somebody,
the cops or whatever.
You have to get me
out of here right now.
( Nate and Holly
faintly murmuring )
Holly:
Keep going, try now.
Nate:
That's what I'm doing.
- Holly: No, just...
- ( banging )
Harder.
Nate:
This is all fucked up.
Okay, that's great.
Nate:
Okay, on three.
All right?
One, two, three.
( straining )
( panting )
Hold on.
Do you know
what real love is, Nate?
- What?
- Holly: You know,
real love.
Say you loved somebody.
But she got sick.
And then someone
came along one day
to pull the plug on her
to take her away
from you forever.
What would you do?
Nate:
I don't know, I just wanna
get you outta here.
Holly:
You would do anything
to stop that
from happening.
Anything at all, no matter
what the cost
because that's
what love is.
Love is sacrifice.
- ( smacks )
- What the fuck?
You die.
Oh.
Are you stabbing me?
( screams )
Motherfucker!
The block, Seth.
Use the cinder block.
He's moving.
Come on, use it.
- I can't.
- You have to.
Seth, I can't lose you.
- Please?
- Nate: Oh, fuck.
( Nate screams )
I can feel my leg.
( screams )
What the fuck?
Somebody help me.
( groans )
- Oh, my--
- ( crashes )
Come on, do it again.
One more time.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Seth. You have
to listen to me, okay?
You have to do
exactly what I say.
Are you listening?
Okay, step one
is disposing of the body.
The sooner, the better.
Okay, burn it, bury it,
sink it, whatever.
Just get it out of here.
But you can't do that
before you get rid
of the identifiers.
Teeth, tattoos,
fingerprints.
The fingerprints are easy,
you can use a carob for that.
After the teeth,
you need to scatter them.
Dumpsters,
in water, whatever.
Just not all
in the same place.
And then there's
just the body to worry about.
Seth:
He's not gonna fit
in the incinerator.
Holly:
Well, not like that.
( fire erupts )
Holly:
Do you want to practice
with me what to say?
Seth:
Hey, Mrs. Gundy,
it's Seth.
Sorry to call you so late.
Um, yeah, Nate asked me
to watch the front
while he ran some errands
and he's still not back yet.
I don't know
where he went.
Oh...
Okay, good night.
Sorry.
How do you feel?
I don't know.
Disconnected.
Like it happened
to someone else, you know?
The first time's
always the worst.
There is no first time.
It was an accident.
- I told you.
- You know what always
got to me?
It was the questions.
I remember
in the beginning
all I could think about
was what if she had a pet?
It's poor little doggie
just sitting by the door
waiting for her
to come home.
But all that goes away.
The more you think
about it
the more you remember
the parts that you liked.
How it made you feel.
Like you were in control
of your life
for the very first time,
like nothing could hurt you.
That's not how it was.
But the only problem is
that sooner or later
it all goes back to normal.
All of a sudden
you're nothing special,
you're just you.
Stop, okay?
Holly:
And that's when you
start to wonder.
How far you'd have to go
to get that feeling back.
It's not the same.
There is no shame in accepting
what you are, Seth.
I did it,
to keep us safe.
I had no choice.
Didn't you ever wonder why
all the girls in the world
but you get a hard on for me?
And you think that's, what,
a coincidence?
You and me,
we were born to do this.
Don't act like you know
a goddamn thing about me.
I know that a normal person
finds a murder confession
and goes to the police.
not to PetSmart.
Oh, yeah,
"Excuse me, Officer.
You see that girl
over there, the waitress?
She's Hannibal Lecter.
You know how I know?
I broke into her apartment
and stole her shit."
Think that'll work?
Oh, and so plan B
is kidnapping?
'Cause the fucking
alternative
was sitting around
watching you hurt
someone else.
Mm.
Good thing
no one got hurt.
I told you...
I told you.
It's an accident.
Face it, Seth.
This was never
about saving lives,
you like this.
You like having
that kind of power.
Deciding who lives,
who dies.
Holly, it's not too late.
I can save you, please.
Please.
I can save you.
Maybe you're not
supposed to save me.
Maybe I'm suppose
to save you.
Don't, don't.
Seth, please help me,
I'm so cold.
Please make me warm.
Can you help me,
can you please make me warm?
( moans )
I thought you love me.
I do.
I do love you.
Holly. Holly.
Holly.
I'll come back
as soon as I can.
- Oh.
- Seth.
This is Detective Mira.
Something wrong?
Detective:
Is there somewhere
we can talk?
So, you work
with Nathan, yeah?
Yes.
When's the last time
you saw him?
Wednesday, I think?
Wednesday evening.
Yeah, he asked me
to cover the front
while he ran
some errands.
- What kind of errands?
- Um, he didn't say.
Uh-huh. And this
would be about...
what time?
9:00, 10:00.
Something like that.
He leave out
through the front?
Yeah.
The front door,
you sure?
Yeah, why?
Well, here's the thing.
The front door operates
on a keyless entry system.
As you know, it records
each instance in or out.
Now you wanna guess
the last time someone
opened that door?
4:00.
That's 4:00 AM.
- Huh.
- And you said it was what,
9:00 or 10:00PM?
It's kind of weird,
don't you think?
No, maybe
I'm remembering
it wrong.
He could have left
out the side door,
or loading docks.
Loading docks?
Oh, sure. Yeah.
I should check that out.
You and Nathan friends?
Well, we worked together.
He was a nice guy and all.
Until he tried
to get you fired.
What? Oh.
That is not what happened.
Nate and I
were friends.
Oh, now
you're friends again.
Or you were friends,
past tense.
That's the second time
you said that.
Well, you know
what they say.
First time 's confusion,
second time's confession.
What's this about?
Standard procedure.
So now, he asked you
to cover for him,
this is what Wednesday night,
nine or ten?
Did he say
where he was going?
I think he had
to meet someone.
He got a phone call,
something.
It's funny, because
the first thing we did
was check
the phone records.
And the last person he
talked to was his girlfriend.
5:32 that afternoon.
Hi.
Gotta eat something.
Holly, come on.
Come on.
Come on, don't do this.
Seth:
Now I know what
you're doing.
It's not gonna work.
Just talk to me, please.
Holly:
It's over, Seth.
I don't understand.
Because if you
can't help me
if you can't give me
what I need, then no one can.
Tell me,
tell me what you need.
You know the answer.
You put me in a box.
That's not love,
that's ownership.
You didn't
give me anything.
All you did was take.
I can't let you out.
- You know that.
- I didn't ask you to.
Then what?
What do you want?
Proof.
Proof?
- A finger.
- A what?
A finger?
My finger?
No.
No. No. No. No.
This is fucked.
Can't you see that?
This is totally fucked.
No. I'm trying
to save you here.
And I'm trying
to let you.
Well, you can't
ask me for that, Holly.
And I'm not gonna do it.
I used to think
I was the only one.
Even when I was a kid,
I still knew.
That if they
ever found out,
my family,
my friends...
If they knew what I really was,
they'd run the other way.
And so you learn to...
blend in, to fake it.
After a while,
you don't even notice
how lonely you really are.
But then...
someone comes along,
someone like you.
Even if he just
doesn't know it yet.
And all of a sudden,
you start thinking,
maybe it doesn't
have to be this way.
Maybe I don't
have to be alone.
And so let go
of the rope.
Because this person,
he's not gonna let you fall.
He's gonna catch you.
You know it.
At least that's what you
keep telling yourself.
The whole way down.
Don't come back.
If that's all
I am to you,
if I'm just a pet.
Then don't
come back for me.
Don't come back for me.
( dogs whining )
If I do this
for you,
then you'll believe?
Yes.
This is wrong.
Seth, you love me.
There is nothing
more right than that.
( groans )
( whimpers )
You're almost there.
( screams )
( crunches )
( screaming continues )
Open the door.
- What are you doing?
- Open the fucking door.
You're already down
a finger, Seth.
How much more
are you ready to lose?
( groans )
Get back.
Holly.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Shh.
I believe you.
You do?
Do you...
You saved me, Seth.
Of course
I love you.
But you know
what that means.
( choking, gargling )
( Seth gasps )
Holly.
Don't leave me.
( panting )
Oh, God.
( moans )
Eric:
You've been working
on these pieces for years.
Holly:
I know, I'm not saying
I'm not excited.
It's like great
to get that call.
- I just--
- I figured you'd be more
psyched about this.
It's a big deal,
getting published.
It's just a vanity press,
it's not exactly "The New
Yorker."
Screw that,
it's still awesome.
I'm proud of you.
I thought you didn't
even like my story.
I like you.
( phone buzzes )
- Hey, babe,
can you grab my phone?
- Yeah.
( man chattering
on TV )
Here you go.
Thank you, babe.
Hi.
( sighs )
I had another
bad day with Eric.
He's still fooling around
with other girls.
This morning
I almost hurt him.
But then I thought of you.
And how much
you love me.
And what you're doing
for me.
Then I felt better.
( music playing )
( music changes )
( music ends )
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org