Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
My name is Allison MacKenzie.
Where I was born, time was told
not by the clock orthe calendar...
but by the seasons.
Summer was carefree contentment.
Autumn was that
bitter-sweet time of regret...
for moments that had ended
and things that were yet undone.
And then winter fell...
with a cold mantle
of caution and chill.
It nipped our noses
and our arrogance...
and made us move closerto the
warm stoves of memory and desire.
Springwas promise.
But there was
a fifth season of love.
And only the wise orthe lucky
ones knew where to find it.
Hey, mister!
Which way to Peyton Place?
Go right up this road about 2 miles,
you'll come right inside the town.
Thanks!
Lucas stole my money and he'll do it
again. He drinks everything in sight.
l spent a year and a half saving
for a correspondence course.
Don't go, Paul.
You were my first born.
Hitting everybody who doesn't
agree with him. Even you!
-Only when he's drinking.
-Lately, that's been every night.
What did you marry him for?
When your pa died, you, Selena and
Joey had to have some kind of father.
Lucas tries hard to be a good man.
-Good-bye, mom.
-Paul!
Selena, don't you ask me to stay.
My baby-sitting money.
l wish there was more.
Paul!
Paul, I'll do extra work.
I'll find a job and...
get the money back.
Only don't leave.
I'm sorry we got into a fight.
It won't happen again.
l give you my word.
Paul!
He'll come back. You wait
and see. He'll come back.
Nellie, I'm... I'm going to try hard
not to drink anymore.
Selena...
I'm going to try harder
than I ever tried anything.
-Morning!
-Good morning.
May I have a couple of fried eggs
and a cup of coffee, please?
-All right.
-Do you have a washing room...
where I can clean up and shave?
-First door.
-Oh, yeah. Thank you.
-What are you selling?
-Nothing.
Sorry. Thought you might
be a traveling man.
No. I came here to get a job.
l should've known.
l hear that Harrington Woolen Mills
got some big government contracts...
for military uniforms cloth.
-Lot of people'll be moving in here.
-Which way is it to Harrington Mills?
Follow Elm Street to the river,
then look up to your right.
You'll hate it!
-Morning, Mrs. MacKenzie.
-Morning, Nellie.
-Paul left this morning.
-Left for where?
Don't know. He wants to get out of
here and make something of himseIf...
instead of working
all the time at the mill.
-He wants to see the world.
-Who's going to see the world?
-Paul.
-He left town this morning.
Allison, must you play records at
a quarter to eight in the morning?
Good breakfast music.
Digest your orange juice with cuIture.
I'm glad about Paul, Nellie.
How did Selena take it?
She's glad too, but she ain't
a mother. Neither are you.
I'd like to see the world,
have a romance in Venice...
meet a tall dark stranger
in Hong Kong.
-Allison, don't eat so fast.
-Have to.
Senior class is giving
a gift to Miss Thornton.
And I wrote a speech that
Rodney Harrington is going to read.
-Badly, I'm sure.
-What's going on?
School board's meeting to appoint
a new principal. Mr. Firth died.
How do you know they'll give it
to Miss Thornton?
They have to. There's nobody else
who deserves it.
I'll drop by the store
after school.
Good-bye, dad.
l wish you'd stop that ridiculous
performance every day.
What? Saying good-bye
and hello to my father?
Saying it to a photograph.
l suppose it's silly, but it makes
me feel that he's here with us.
-But you scarcely knew your father.
-Not my fault he died when I was 2.
l can't even remember him,
l admit, but I miss him.
You mean you miss a father?
Yes, mother. Wouldn't it be nice
if you had some man friends...
or some dates,
or even married again?
Will you stop talking about fathers,
and husbands, and marriage?
You miss him more
than I ever realized.
I'm sorry, mother.
I'll be late.
Forgot the speech.
-Good-bye, mom.
-Good-bye.
-Good morning, Miss Lindsay.
-Morning, Allison.
Hi, David.
-Good morning, Mr. Herman.
-Good Morning, Mrs. Allison.
Go home, Duff!
-Hi, Doc Swain.
-Good morning, Allison.
-Good morning, girls.
-Good morning, doctor.
-Good morning, Mr. Cross.
-Good morning.
Thank you, Norman. Everything's
gone wrong this morning.
If you didn't run all the time...
Ted's bringing the gift!
Rod! Excuse me.
Here's the speech.
-I'll never memorize this.
-Well, just read it.
She's coming!
Miss Thornton's coming!
"...the job of principal
of Peyton Place High School."
Quiet!
Miss Thornton...
the members of the senior class
have asked me to say a few words...
and, on behalf of them,
to present this gift to you.
The names of all of us are inscribed
inside the cover of that dictionary.
Because there are so many different
words that might express...
what we feel
in our hearts for you...
and your long services
to Peyton Place High School...
we decided to give you
all the words in the language.
We're going to lose you, but to
something bigger and more important:
the job of principal
of Peyton Place High School.
So that you know
we'll never forget...
you can turn to the words "love",
"friendship" and "remembrance"...
and know that we're always
thinking of them.
This is the loveliest thing
that ever happened to me.
l...
There's another word in this book:
"gratitude".
Now, let's talk about graduation.
I'd like to have a report from the
president of the class, Ted Carter.
Okay. Miss Thornton, l've arranged
for all the necessary committees...
and if they all do their jobs, I'm
sure we'll have a fine graduation.
Vice-president, Selena Cross?
The programs will be printed
in a couple of weeks...
and l've rented caps and
gowns at US$ 2.5O a piece.
We're going to have a tea and
reception on the lawn afterwards.
Editor of the yearbook,
Allison MacKenzie.
The copies are all done...
but the engraver's going mad waiting
for all the pictures to come in.
Who doesn't have a picture by
Wednesday won't be in the yearbook.
Senior dance, Betty Anderson.
Everybody has to help
with the decorations.
The tickets are printed and
will go on sale a week before.
I'm supposed to announce there's
to be no necking in the parking lot.
Nor anywhere else,
for that matter.
Harrington, Elsie Thornton has
earned the right to be principal.
She's given her life to this town!
The least we can do is recognize it!
Doc, as head of the school board,
is my opinion she should be retired.
I'm afraid I can't quite
concur with you, Leslie.
-I agree with Doc Swain.
-You would.
Miss Thornton is practically senile.
She's hypochondriac,
uses sleeping pills all the time.
You want a drug addict
for a principal?
It seems to me that I write a lot of
prescriptions for you every year!
And as far as Miss Thornton being
senile, she's of your generation.
-She's not. I'm 36.
-You're 45!
My father delivered you the year
they buiIt the Courthouse: 1896.
We need someone young.
This fellow who's coming...
is the resuIt of correspondence
with five teaching agencies, and...
...l can get him at the right price.
-Mr. Harrington, he's outside.
He can't do us much good
out there, Miss CoIton. Send him in.
-Would you come in, Mr. Rossi?
-Yes. Thank you.
Good morning.
-I'm Leslie Harrington.
-How do you do?
This is the school board.
Mr. and Mrs. Partridge.
-How do you do?
-He's a lawyer.
-Dr. Swain.
-Doctor.
Seth Bushwell, editor of the "Peyton
Place Times". Please, sit down.
Now, Mr. Rossi,
here's our situation.
We're prepared to offer the job
as principal to a qualified man...
with a minimum guaranteed
five-year contract.
Mr. Rossi is a graduate from
Penn State, "suma cum laudi".
He holds a master's degree
in English and Literature.
He was an outstanding athlete.
He's single.
Personally, now that
l've seen him, I like what I see.
Did I miss anything?
Only that l've been working
for a construction company.
If you're a teacher, why were you
working for a construction company?
l couldn't live on the salary
l was being paid as a teacher.
This job starts
at US$ 3,OOO a year.
Then we're all wasting our time.
That's US$ 5 a week more than I was
making as a teacher, Mr. Harrington.
But this offers you security,
a long-term contract.
Guaranteed poverty
is not security!
l want US$ 5,OOO a year, and a raise
of US$ 5OO on the second year.
-We can't do it.
-You own this mill.
How much do you pay a foreman?
About US$ 2OO a week?
This is business. These men
manufacture products that make money.
You must be practical
and face realities.
To people like you, education
is just a necessary evil.
You can't see it,
so it's worth nothing.
Well, let me tell you this,
Mr. Harrington:
the things we can't see are the
most important things on this Earth.
They're called ideas. Thank you
very much for the interview.
If we offered you US$ 5,OOO
would you coach...
...the basketball and football teams?
-No, I would not!
ln a town like this, if you can't afford
to pay the principal of your school...
a decent salary you have
no right to run the school...
...much less send your children to it.
-Mr. Rossi!
Leslie, I'm afraid you're
fighting a losing battle.
Now, Mr. Rossi, frankly...
"...the life history of the race...
repeats itseIf in the individual."
-A notice from the school board.
-Thank you.
"Effective immediately:
The school board of Peyton Place
is happy to announce...
the appointment
of a new school principal...
Mr. Michael Rossi."
Who?
"We trust that you will show him
the same loyaIty and devotion...
you displayed
to the late Mr. Firth."
Class dismissed.
I'm sorry, Miss Thornton.
l don't know how
they could do such a thing.
You should be principal,
you deserved it.
Allison, a person doesn't always get
what she deserves. Remember it.
If there's anything in life
you want, go and get it.
Don't wait for anybody
to give it to you.
Now, I have some work to do.
See you later, Al.
-Well, here we are.
-Good-looking school, Doc.
That must be
the new principal, you know?
They really gave it to you,
didn't they?
Everybody else in this town,
they really gave it to you!
Have you been drinking?
You work yourseIf to death for them,
they bring in an outsider...
...to pick the plum off the tree.
-You have been drinking.
l've known for a long time
you kept a bottle in the basement...
but I won't have you bring it
to the classroom ever!
-Now don't forget that.
-Might do your kids more good...
to learn how to handle a bottle of
liquor instead of algebra problem.
-You're talking like a fool!
-Oh, be l?
l sat in this classroom 4 years!
l sat right here!
Everything that was important to me
was learned somewhere else.
You never applied yourseIf. You
might have learned something here.
Tell that to my wife,
the cleaning woman...
tell that to me, a janitor,
cleaning toilets for a living!
-Stop it!
-Tell that to every mill worker...
...behind in his bills.
-I said stop it!
If you had applied yourseIf you might
have learned how to live intelligently.
There isn't nobody in this here
town living intelligently. Nobody!
-I don't believe that.
-All right!
Name me one important person
graduated from this school. One!
You can't.
l want to tell you something,
Miss Thornton...
something you can teach
your class someday.
The minute they walk out that door,
they walk into a doggie-dog world.
It's crawl in front of the big dogs
if you want to eat, get a job!
l won't do it.
l won't do it!
That's why I'm washing windows,
scrubbing walls, emptying ashes.
l never had nothing I ever wanted.
Shakespeare didn't do me
more good than did...
...Washington crossing the Delaware!
-You didn't help yourseIf!
Elsie, I'd like to have you
meet Mike Rossi. Miss Thornton.
-Hello, Miss Thornton.
-Mr. Rossi, welcome to Peyton Place.
-Thank you.
-Our utility man, Lucas Cross.
-Hello, Lucas.
-My hand is too dirty.
I'll start in another room.
-ls he always drinking?
-He's disappointed for me.
Loyalty is always
more passion than reason.
l guess that's why
l came to see you first.
There's strong sentiment
for making you principal.
Please, don't feel uncomfortable,
Mr. Rossi. My time came too late.
-I hope we can work together.
-Of course we can.
l suppose you have a lot
of new progressive ideas.
No, not really. I'm rather
old-fashioned, as a matter of fact.
l have just two rules.
First, I want this school to teach
the truth, as far as we know it.
l don't want any teacher
making a fairy tale out of life.
It's hard enough as it is without
being unequipped to meet it.
That's a good rule.
Shall we sit down?
And rule two:
teach a minimum of facts
and a maximum of ideas.
Our job is teaching to think, not
memorizing for a couple of weeks.
If war comes first...
these kids shouldn't fight
just for historical dates, but...
for the ideals behind them.
l like your rules, Mr. Rossi.
Peyton Place is very fortunate.
Thank you, Miss Thornton.
Allison, I don't know what Betty
is buying, but tell her to hurry up.
Okay.
Mother... Miss Thornton
didn't get the job.
l know. Betty Anderson and
Margie told me. They're in the back.
After giving her the gift
and the speech...
It must have been terribly
embarrassing and tragic for her.
-Well, she'll get over it.
-I'm glad I'm graduating.
l don't want to have anything
to do with the new principal.
Mrs. MacKenzie,
about the graduation...
-What about it, Selena?
-My mother needs a new dress.
ls there some arrangement I could
make with you to buy her a new one?
After graduation, I'll get a full
time job, and I can pay you back.
Well, you'll be needing
a new dress yourseIf.
l can get by.
Look, with Easter and the graduation
coming on, I'll need some help.
How would you like to work here
afternoons and Saturdays?
-Oh, I'd love to!
-Fine.
-Then, I can buy two dresses!
-Wholesale.
Oh, gee! No girl ever had two
better friends than you and Allison.
When you see how hard mother
makes you work, you won't say that.
-Rodney is outside.
-Good, let him wait.
Aren't you afraid you'll be
arrested wearing that thing?
No, just picked up.
Mother says women
should be mysterious.
-You think this dress is too old?
-No, you're just too young.
Aren't you afraid people
will think you're a little fast?
According to my philosophy, what
people think will not pay the rent.
So, if you're accused of being fast,
you might as well run.
That way, you get to
all the good things first.
Just remember men can see
much better than they can think.
Believe me: a low cut neck-line
does more for a girl's future...
than the entire
Britannica Encyclopedia.
-Allison, could you help me a moment?
-Sure.
-Be right back.
-Do you think Rod will like it?
When you have your 18th birthday
party, I don't want you to invite...
...Betty Anderson.
-Then I might as well not have a party.
If I can't invite Betty,
Rodney Harrington won't come.
-I wouldn't mind that at all.
-Then his friends won't come...
...and, pretty soon, nobody will accept.
-I can't understand why you want...
...to be friends with a girl like Betty.
-Mother...
l don't like the way
she talks about men!
-Mother...
-And sex!
The only perfect individual
in Peyton Place is you!
And we've had 17 dull
birthday parties alone.
Could you let me have
one for myseIf, please?
Hey, Allison!
What about Betty?
-Hi, Norman.
-Oh, hi, Allison.
What's the matter?
Same old thing.
Grown-ups who act like children.
Could I walk home with you?
No, it's out of your way.
Besides, you'd get home late.
You mean your mother
wouldn't like it.
-Well...
-Come on, Norman. Come on!
Did you spend the afternoon
in the library again?
Yeah.
Isn't it awfully dull going
there every day?
Yeah.
Oh? Then why do you do it?
l like books.
Good place to do my homework.
Besides, where else
could I go, but home?
Go down to the water,
sit in the square...
take a walk in the woods.
l can't.
You know, that was a nice piece
that you wrote for Miss Thornton.
I'm sorry I did it now.
Why didn't you read it yourseIf
instead of letting Harrington do it?
Because I was afraid I'd cry.
l still might cry when I think of
Miss Thornton not getting that job.
You know, you might just
turn out to be a great writer.
Norman, I hope so.
You know,
every time I touch a book...
l read a story...
or even when I just
open the dictionary...
something inside
of me goes "thump".
And my heart starts pounding...
and my stomach...
It's how people are supposed
to feel when they fall in love.
Of course, I never have.
l wish I could be sure
of what I wanted to do.
You must have some idea.
No.
No, I thought of everything,
but nothing seems to fit me.
Maybe I'll be unique
and retire at the age of 18.
Norman, it's about time
you got home!
Hello, Mrs. Paige!
-Bye, Norman.
-Wait just a minute, will you?
-But...
-I don't want to go in just yet.
Oh, Norman, what an awful thing
hating to go home.
Come on in here.
Well, thanks for walking with me.
l enjoyed it really.
Good-bye.
-May I walk on it, Nellie?
-Sure. It's dry by now.
-Your mother wants you to call her.
-I really don't feel like it.
-You two had a fight again?
-Same fight, different round.
-Nellie?
-Yeah?
You've been both a daughter
and a mother. Which one is worse?
-Being a mother.
-Why?
You find yourseIf doing the same
things you hated your parents doing.
That's very interesting.
Somewhere along the line,
doesn't someone get intelligent...
and realize that your children
have to grow up their own way?
The mind's got nothing to
do with it. It's the feelings.
Kids get born...
and you just worry about it
and you hope for them.
Well, I got to get going.
-Good night, Nellie.
-Good night, Allison.
Hello?
Hello, mother.
l just wanted to tell you
l've been thinking it over...
and you can invite anyone you
want for your birthday party.
Oh, mother, thank you!
Thank you very much.
I'll be home in a little while.
Bye.
2676J, please.
Hey, watch where you're
going there, buddy, will you?
-Thanks much.
-Thank you.
Right now, I want it.
l want some!
-Would you like a sandwich, Norman?
-No, thank you.
Excuse me.
-Happy birthday, Allison. Hi!
-Hi, how are you?
-Betty and Rodney!
-Where's Ted Carter?
Right here.
Let's take that corny music off and
get down to some serious dancing.
-That's a good record.
-Yeah, that's a new one.
-How about a sandwich?
-I brought some mistletoe.
-Mistletoe?!
-Matt, hang it high, will you, boy.
-Only if I can kiss Betty Anderson!
-Nobody's safe with me here.
Mistletoe?
Christmas is 8 months away.
Yeah, and I believe in doing
my Christmas kissing early!
-Where's the punch?
-Over there, Rodney.
-Good, I'm really thirsty.
-The old family formula.
-Now you're talking, Rod.
-Rodney, we can't do that.
-My mother wouldn't want...
-Don't tell she's here!
-No, she's at the movies.
-Great!
-Put the booze in the bowl!
-Come on, she made me promise.
Come on, Allison, you want
to have a party or not?
-You can't fight city hall.
-Don't! Put the liquor in the bowl!
Allison, forget it. I know 1O other
ways to make a party successful.
Now, first...
we got to make the atmosphere
a little more intimate.
Oh, Rodney, aren't you the one?
-Evening.
-Good evening. Hello, Doc.
Hi, Connie.
-Just coffee, please.
-Right.
Who's that, Doc?
She's Mrs. MacKenzie.
She runs a dress shop.
She has a daughter in the
senior class, Allison MacKenzie.
-Beautiful woman.
-Yeah.
She's a widow. She was born here,
but she had ambitions and left...
married a New Yorker,
some advertising genius.
When he died, she came back here.
-I'd like to meet her.
-Wouldn't do you no good.
Bring your coffee.
Connie, you haven't met Mr. Rossi,
the new school principal.
-Mrs. MacKenzie.
-How do you do?
Hello. I hear about you
every day from my daughter.
You've been working kind of late?
No, l've been to the movies.
Allison's giving a birthday party.
What does your daughter
plan to do after graduation?
She'd like to be a writer.
I'd like her to go to college.
It's too bad she didn't have
some brothers and sisters.
-Why do you say that?
-I'm against only child families.
Only children are on the receiving
end of the attention and energy...
of the parents, good and bad.
l don't think Allison's
turned out badly.
She hasn't turned out yet.
Her life is just beginning.
Anyway, it's a late to give her
any brothers and sisters, isn't it?
ln your case, I'd say it wasn't.
If I didn't like you so much, Matt,
and know you so well...
Ah, now, Connie, don't
you go proposing to me.
-For you, Doc.
-Excuse me.
Try a cigarette.
-Swain speaking.
-Thank you.
l will be right over.
Speak of babies and they appear.
Mrs. Runkle's in labor. See you.
-Thanks, Doc.
-Bye.
Doc Swain's always
talking about babies.
-They're his stock in trade.
-Not a bad subject though.
We teach school children
English, Math, History and yet...
we neglect the one subject that
gives them the most trouble in life.
You don't recommend classes
in baby-making, do you?
Only in theory. I intend to start a
Sex Education course in the school.
-Isn't that a function of the home?
-I think it would be.
And yet, not one
parent in ten does it.
-No. Sex is taboo in the home.
-And it should be in the schools.
Where would they learn?
ln the alleys, in parked cars?
They'll learn it when they marry.
Good night, Mr. Rossi.
Doc Swain offers
a special price for frostbites.
-Come on, Allison.
-Rodney!
Allison!
This was supposed
to be a birthday party.
-Mother.
-We were just playing Photography.
You turn out the lights
and see what develops.
Don't be fresh.
Just leave immediately.
-All of you!
-I'm sorry, Mrs. MacKenzie...
...but I caught her under the mistletoe.
-Will you please leave?
Happy birthday, Allison.
Come on, Betty.
Thanks, Allison.
Come out here.
Allison, I said "Come out here"!
l knew this would happen
if you invited Betty Anderson.
-It wasn't my fault.
-You and Rodney making love!
We were kissing, one kiss.
Not making love.
Our house in darkness, and couples
necking all over the place!
l know, mother, but everyone
wanted to dance in the dark.
And I couldn't very well...
Well, mother, at every party in
this town, they turn out the lights.
l don't want you to be
like everybody in this town.
l want you to rise
above Peyton Place.
It's my home and my town!
Why should I want to rise above it?
Because its standards are low.
These people spend time trying to
drag each other down to their level.
l don't want to be
perfect like you, mother.
l don't want to live in a test tube.
l just want to be me, and have
some fun, and have some friends.
I'd rather be liked
than be perfect.
By liked you mean being
poured over in the dark by...
by some young animal
with one thing in his mind!
Oh, mother, don't make
it sound like that!
Everything has to be
learned, even kissing.
And sex! ls that what you're going
to practice at your next party?
You keep trying to accuse me of
things I'm not even thinking about!
Allison...
l don't want you to get a reputation
for a half-hour carelessness.
l already have one,
the wrong kind.
l want you to fall in love...
and, at the proper time,
to marry a man who respects you.
l want you to have a good name.
-I want...
-You want, you want, you want!
ls that all you can say?
Well, if any man would ask me, I'd
run away and become his mistress!
Don't you ever let me hear
you say a thing like that again!
l don't know why I said it.
Allison!
Good morning, Ellen.
Hello, Rudy.
-Hello, Allison.
-Hello, Joey.
Selena will be out
in a couple of minutes.
-Thank you.
-Come out in the back.
-I got a new baby lamb.
-Oh, I'd love to see it.
Oh, it's darling.
l didn't show you my lizard.
l keep him in a box, right there.
l got some holes punched in it,
just so he can breathe.
His name is Pocahontas.
Used to be a man didn't
have to cook his own meals...
-Look at it all you want.
-Times have changed.
Mom's working
and I'm late for church.
The way you parade up and down.
Taking off and putting on clothes.
-I don't parade up and down.
-You do!
You just like showing
yourseIf off, don't you?
l don't like to show myseIf off!
Just because we don't live in
a palace we have to act like pigs.
-We've got a trash can, remember?
-Well, well, well.
If you don't pick it up,
somebody else has to.
It wouldn't hurt you to take
the garbage out and bury it either!
Or do you like living like a pig?
What do you think you are?
A general? Always giving orders!
Take your hands off me!
Don't you touch her!
Don't you touch her anymore!
Hey. It was just
a little family fracas.
l guess my little girl
is getting to big to spank.
It was my fault, Allison.
l made him mad.
Every family has fights.
They're forgotten in an hour.
Hey, Norman, you know what?
There's a place I know
that I'd like to show you.
That no one knows about.
Not even you.
It's my secret place.
l know every spot
within 3 miles of Peyton Place.
Not this one. Come on!
You were right.
l never knew this place was here.
l don't think anybody does, but me.
And maybe God.
And now you.
It's beautiful!
l've just decided. This is the last
time I'm ever going to come here.
Why?
Oh, I'm going to leave it
for somebody else to find.
Maybe your children
will discover it.
I'm never going to get married,
I'm just going to have lovers.
-Oh, Allison...
-What's wrong with that?
No children to grow up unhappy.
Nobody gets hurt, except maybe me.
Yeah, but that's the worst kind
of emotional maladjustment.
Who said so?
-A book I read.
-What book?
Well, see,
l've sent out for a book...
It was US$ 1.98
in a plain wrapper.
-A plane wrapper?
-Yeah, a plain wrap...
And... Well, it was about
marriage and sex.
l had it sent to me at the
post office, general delivery.
It took me about 2 weeks to get up
the courage to go pick it up.
Golly...
Golly, I know it sounds funny...
but that was the only way
l could find out anything.
Norman, you know what?
l sent for a book just like that.
ln the same plain wrapper.
General delivery.
Really? The same one?
And I read every word of it.
And I think most of it is just
mid-Victorian nonsense!
Maybe yours was better.
Hey, you want to trade books?
Oh, no.
I'd be too embarrassed.
That's your whole trouble, Norman.
Everything embarrasses you.
-Everything frightens you.
-I know.
And I'm sorry. I'm sorry we
started talking about all this.
Hey, Norman, look...
it's about time you learn that girls
want to do the same things as boys.
And you have the right to know how.
l think we should help each other.
-Are you suggesting that...
-Oh, Norman, don't get me wrong.
All I want is some normal,
intelligent discussion.
And maybe some normal affection
between a boy and a girl.
Nothing more.
Everybody in this town hides
behind plain wrappers.
You're so afraid.
You've even been afraid to
ask me to the graduation dance.
Oh, Allison...
l want...
I'm just not asking anybody.
I'll be there, but I can't ask you.
-Why not?
-Well, my mother.
Your mother...
Well, she wouldn't
actually forbid it.
It's just that she gets jealous of
anybody that I spend my time with.
Oh, you don't know her.
You don't have to live with her.
But she's my mother.
There's nothing I can do about that.
You don't have
to tell me anymore, Norman.
Please, Allison,
l have to tell somebody.
She won't let me have friends.
She...
She makes me tell her 1O times
a day how much I love her.
She's afraid she'll die alone
in a poorhouse. Oh, and marriage.
Marriage, she says, is misery, and
a woman can only cause me trouble.
Oh, Norman...
-I can't believe it.
-Nobody would.
Now maybe you know
why I hate to go home...
why I live in the library...
why I can't dance or kiss girls,
or look anybody in the eye.
You see, I'm a sissy and a coward.
No, you're not, Norman.
No one around town stopped
to think and give you a chance.
You shouldn't be afraid of girls.
l know, but I am, and I don't
know what I can do about it.
-I know what you can do.
-What?
You can start with me.
I'll prove everything
your mother ever said was wrong.
Would you kiss me, Norman?
-I don't think I can.
-Yes, you could.
Kiss me!
l don't know why
l should act so experienced.
It was only
my second kiss this year.
It wasn't as good
as Rodney's, was it?
No...
Hello.
l guess I should've phoned.
-But I was in the neighborhood...
-No, that's all right.
l have a message for Allison.
ls she home?
No, she and Selena have just gone
over to Kathy Ellsworth's house.
It gives me a good
excuse to talk to you.
-May I come in?
-Oh, of course.
-You have a lovely house.
-Thank you.
Please, come in.
It's a very comfortable room.
Good books, pictures...
My own hotel room is a bit basic.
l have a mirror for shaving,
a basin for washing...
and a closet where I hang
my coat, and that's about it.
-You ought to find a house.
-I'm trying to.
ln the meantime, I have my room,
which I clear out of after dinner.
You said you had something
you wanted to tell me.
l was telling you something,
but you weren't listening.
Your husband?
He died when Allison was 2.
And Allison?
-Well, a few years ago.
-She's grown a bit since then.
l came to tell you that Allison
has been named valedictorian.
Oh, that's wonderful.
She'll be terribly pleased, and so am l.
She's a fine girl.
Bright and sensitive.
-You should be very proud of her.
-Yes, I am.
Well, that's what I came about.
-Good night, Mrs. MacKenzie.
-You are lonely here, aren't you?
It's not the worst thing
that can happen to you.
Isn't it?
You can learn to live by yourseIf.
You can get used to it.
Maybe, but that doesn't make it
the best way to live.
The best way?
What would that be?
People meeting, talking...
Well, in Peyton Place,
two people talking is a conspiracy.
A meeting is an assignation...
and getting to know one
another is a scandal.
l think you're hard on
the town and on yourseIf.
No, l... I'm quite
all right the way I am.
What were you going to do tonight?
Wash your hair, read a book,
go to the movies alone?
-Well, that makes time pass.
-Time shouldn't just pass...
Mrs. MacKenzie, it should be used!
-I wouldn't know where to begin.
-Begin at the beginning.
Begin by getting out.
We need another chaperone for the
dance. Why don't you help us out?
Will you come?
-I think I'd like that.
-Fine.
Good night, and thanks.
-Good night.
Betty Anderson's father
stopped me in the shop today.
What did he want?
Ask me when you're going to marry
Betty, before or during college.
l hadn't exactly thought
of marrying her.
l wouldn't hear of it
even if you wanted to!
Anderson is a good foreman,
but his daughter's something else.
-I agree.
-Then stop seeing her.
l can't stop seeing her right away.
l invited her to the dance.
Uninvited her.
-Oh, dad, I can't do that!
-You're going to!
Do you realize what would mean if
you were to marry the local tramp?
When you marry, you're going
to marry someone your own level.
-Call her and tell her it's off.
-Are you trying to kill me?
Call her!
-Oh, please, dad...
-Go on, call her!
1O42W, please.
l can understand you wanting
to see this girl, but not in public.
-You know what I mean.
-Okay, nobody is fighting you.
I'll be as big a
Harrington as you are.
I'll marry a cold fish from Boston,
have one child, and cheat for life.
An apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
Yeah, but, dad,
the graduation dance is important.
You want a new car, don't you?
Betty? Hello, Betty.
This is Rodney.
Look, Betty, this is so terrible
l don't know where to begin.
-Tell her!
-The graduation dance is off.
She hung up.
What a fine graduation!
-I know someone you can take.
-Who?
Allison MacKenzie.
Her mother kicked me out
for kissing her on her birthday.
I'll talk to her mother.
Allison is a girl of quality.
Quality is a good thing on woolen
cloth, but very dull on a big date.
l didn't know you were
such a good dancer, Allison.
-Thank you.
-Yeah, sure.
-Hi, Rod.
-Hi there, Allison.
Hi.
Hey, Rodney, looking for someone?
After the dance,
shall we go to Rockland? Okay.
Oh, really?
-Some more, Mrs. Mackenzie?
-No, thanks, Miss Thornton.
May I have this dance,
Mrs. MacKenzie?
l haven't danced for such a long
time I'm afraid I'd be terrible.
Dancing isn't something you forget.
Listen, Allison,
l promised a dance to Betty...
the second one after intermission.
Do you mind?
-Not if you promised it to her.
-I'll see you around, okay?
Allison. Did you see your mother
dancing with Mr. Rossi?
No. l've never seen
my mother dance.
Standing right over there.
They make a good-looking couple.
They do?
-Hi, Norman.
-Hi.
Dance with me, Norman.
-I don't know how.
-Just try.
-Where are we going?
-You'll see.
Hey, Rodney, you got a new car!
Come on, get in.
Rodney, it's beautiful!
Here we are snug as peas in a pod.
-Where are we going?
-Nowhere.
I'm mad at you.
Come on, Betty.
You really want to kiss me,
don't you?
-Oh, I do.
-Tell me how much.
-Betty, l...
-Tell me.
l want to kiss you
more than anyone in the world.
l want to kiss you a thousand times,
and never want to stop kissing you.
That's pretty good.
I'll give you one kiss.
What would Allison say?
Why bring her name up
at a time like this?
Only one kiss to a customer.
Betty, I couldn't help it.
My father made me call you.
-Would you rather be with me?
-Yes. Yes.
Tell me how much.
ln the whole wide world there's
nobody I'd rather be with than you.
Give me another kiss.
Oh, honey, honey...
-You want to make love to me?
-Oh, yes, of course I want.
Now, go make love
to Allison MacKenzie!
Go get the girl you brought
to the dance and try with her!
And the next time I go out it will
be with a man not a papa's boy!
Ladies and gentlemen...
pupils and faculty of
Peyton Place High School and...
especially the seniors...
they tell me it is a tradition here
to end each graduation dance with...
"Auld Lang Syne".
Since I'm new here and not yet
part of your traditions...
l think the song should be led by a
woman who has been with you long.
Miss Elsie Thornton!
Thank you, Mr. Rossi.
We're a small spot, in a small town
on a great big map.
And maybe Peyton Place High School
isn't a name that shakes the world.
But it's a part
of each of you forever.
Make it great by honoring it...
and come back to see us
whenever you can.
Now, let's form a big circle.
Everyone holding hands.
Should acquaintance
Be forgot
And never brought to mind
Should acquaintance
Be forgot
And days of
Auld Lang Syne
For Auld Lang Syne
My dear
We'll take a cup
Of kindness yet
For Auld Lang Syne
It's an odd feeling being
in the school when it's so quiet.
l always think of it
as being sleeping...
resting up from the pounding
it takes during the day.
-Do you work here at night?
-Oh, yes, quite often.
You don't realize the work and
preparation it takes to be a teacher.
It's like...
Well, it's like all these kids
were my own.
l love them.
l want so much for them.
It's more than a job to you,
isn't it?
l didn't want to sound
like the dedicated idealist.
Well, there's nothing wrong in that.
Connie...
l did want to thank you
for coming tonight.
Well, you don't have to.
l enjoyed everything.
lncluding the dancing?
lncluding.
You're wasting your time, Mike.
l had my love.
A long time ago.
And, when my husband died,
l came back here...
and l've had no time for anything
but Allison and the dress shop.
-You've got time now.
-It's too late.
-Look, Connie, if l...
-I said it's too late.
l made my choice.
Long ago.
Please, take me home.
Sure.
Selena, let's get married.
-You mean now?
-Sure, I can get a full-time job.
What about college and Law School
that you've always talked about?
It's just a dream. I can't do it.
My old man doesn't make...
But whose father does?
Not everyone in college
is a millionaire's son.
Don't get so steamed up.
Ted Carter, you've always wanted
to be a lawyer. Now, go be it!
Don't crumple up
at the first obstacle.
The first obstacle
is the biggest: the money.
Well, then, get over that,
and the rest should be easy.
Selena, you know how long
it takes to become a lawyer?
What difference does it make?
It's what you want to do in life.
One of the things I want
to do in life is marry you.
If I don't do it now,
maybe I never will.
Ted, the only family
I'll ever have will be half yours.
I'll wait,
no matter how long it takes.
-Good night.
-Good night, Selena.
Ted...
thank you.
Mom?
Joey?
l thought you were
something out of a dream.
Where are mom and Joey?
Let's... Let's have a drink,
celebrate your growing up.
-Where are mom and Joey?
-Working at a party at Harrington's.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Rather stay in the dark,
getting kissed by Ted Carter.
I'm going to bed.
About time I started
teaching you something.
Lucas, let me go!
Lucas!
Never had nothing I wanted!
Never had a beautiful woman!
Let me up!
Let me offer to the class of 1941
this fun farewell.
The world outside waits for you.
It is a world full of love
and rich in opportunity.
That may be dangerous...
but if you hold firm to your
purpose and your ideals...
you'll storm the ramparts
of success and capture them.
Tomorrow, you grow up,
and your true happiness begins.
-Thank you.
-My best wishes to you.
Selena Cross.
Norman.
At first, the diploma seemed
like a reward forthe past.
But once in your hand it became
an obligation to the future.
lndependence was a distant word
that we suddenly owned...
and we exploded with it.
Some of us splashed away
the summer.
Or swooped and stretched
with joyfulness...
and emptied ourchildish piggy
banks of their play money.
Yet,others of us eager
to feel aduIt...
or,out of necessity,
begin ourwork early.
-Put the bottle on one step.
-Here?
And gradually,as the happy
confusion of summer faded...
one by one we knew the morning
of responsibility was at hand.
-Hi, Mr. Rossi.
-Hello, Allison.
Did you read those stories
l gave you?
Yes, I read them.
Well?
-When did you write them?
-All summer, ever since graduation.
Has anybody else seen them?
Only Selena.
She thinks I'm a genius.
What do you think? Are they good
enough to send to a magazine?
Yes, if you want
to end up in prison.
Those stories were full
of enough liable, slander...
and double-entendre
to hang us all.
Allison, is that how Peyton Place
really looks to you?
They were only fiction.
l didn't use any real names.
You didn't have to.
l recognized everybody in town.
But let's get down
to the important part.
You have a talent.
Those stories were a good start.
-Now, where do you go from here?
-It's what I hope to find out from you.
Then I suggest college.
-With your talent and ideas...
-Thank you.
But I don't want to go to college.
l never have.
Why not?
Because I don't want to study
about writing. I want to write.
Nobody has to tell me Shakespeare
was a wonderful writer...
or that a million wonderful books
have already been written.
Allison, those books
tell you how and why.
I'd rather find that out myseIf
at a typewriter.
l need some place to get me going,
some place to start.
All right. If that's how you feel
about it, then let's do it.
Let's start at the
"Peyton Place Times".
Who said I was a cynical
hard-hearted newspaperman?
Aren't all newspapermen
supposed to be?
Allison that's a myth. We're the
most sentimental slobs in the world.
-The softest touches there are.
-Prove it.
-All right.
-When do I start?
All I want is a chance
to show what I can do.
Write something up this week
and I'll run it on Friday.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Bushwell.
I'll start right away.
I'll dig up a story you'll never forget.
-I don't doubt it.
-Thank you.
Just remember there's no
such thing as a cheap lawsuit.
Hold on!
We haven't discussed pay.
You don't have to pay me.
I'll do it for experience.
The first thing that experience
teaches us is to get paid.
Five dollars a column to start,
more later.
Gee.
That's more...
Well, I wouldn't want these stories
to fall in the wrong hands.
Thanks, Seth.
There's no question about it.
The tests confirm you're pregnant...
I'd say about 3 months.
-Who's the father?
-I won't tell you.
What kind of rot is that? You're not
the 1st who ever had to get married.
Not in this town, for that matter.
Who's the father?
-Ted Carter?
-No!
-Don't you lie to me! Don't lie.
-I'm not lying to you.
Doc, help me.
l need your help.
What do you mean by help?
l don't want to have the baby.
Give me something.
There's nothing I can give you
to take that could help.
Just tell me who's responsible.
Maybe I can help you that way.
-You can get married.
-He's already married.
Well, then he'll have to take care
of you and provide for the baby.
-Just tell who it is.
-Please, just give me something.
l've done a lot of things in my time
but l've never broken the law.
What you're asking me to do is
break the law of men and God.
Now, tell me, who is the man?
Selena, tell me who he is. Who is he?
It's my stepfather!
It's my stepfather! It's Lucas!
Hi, Doc.
Come on in, have a drink.
-l've got Selena in my office.
-Selena? What for?
She's pregnant.
l told her she'd get
in a mess of trouble.
Always rassling around with that
Carter boy. She wouldn't listen.
You low, miserable crazy slime!
-Don't you go shoving around...
-It's your child Selena's carrying.
-It ain't!
-I can prove it, Lucas!
l've got proof on you to put you
in jail for the rest of your life!
-I never touched her!
-Here, sign that.
It's a statement of the facts.
Are you out of your mind?
l never touched her!
Maybe you'd like the State Police
to sweat it out of you.
l never touched her and I don't have
to sign nothing that says I did.
All right. You don't want to sign
this paper, that's up to you.
Doc, Doc...
You know I could never do something
as awful as that, don't you?
I'm going back to my office...
and start telephoning
every father in Peyton Place.
You wouldn't.
Don't know what they'll take it into
their heads to do but I know this:
you're the janitor in a school
full of young girls.
And an hour from now,
l don't want to be in your shoes.
Doc, doc, don't do it.
l wouldn't think of fooling
around with any other girls.
It was just Selena, Doc.
Well, there was something about her.
It was just Selena.
Please, Doc, don't.
There's just one thing
that will stop me.
You sign that.
If I sign it, what are you
going to do with it?
I'll lock it up in my safe.
Give your pen.
Now get out of here
and leave a man to work.
No, Lucas, you get out
of Peyton Place before dark.
-Doc! I signed it for you.
-If you do...
I'll keep this paper in my safe.
If you don't, I'll use it against you.
-I signed it!
-Don't you ever come back here.
Not next week,
not next year, not ever!
If you do, I'll kill you myseIf.
Well, you little...
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org