Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Damn, damn, damn!
Damn!
Surely the facts are
not in dispute?
This man...
a harmless enough old
creature by all accounts
was running away
from an army patrol.
He was sick, terrified.
You're hurt...
Please!
And you killed him,
did you not?
He was mortally wounded
when I found him.
And you Kevin Woodford took it upon
yourself to put him out of his pain.
He said he was dying,
he begged me to finish him off.
A sick old man...
frightened...
doubted himself out of his wits.
No doctor present?
No medical orderlies?
We hope not many such
fall into your hand.
It wasn't just his bullet
wounds from the patrol.
Really?
His illness...
he had...
he was...
turning into an animal.
Are you being metaphorical Woodford?
Or are you suggesting some
kind of actual metamorphosis?
A werewolf.
A werewolf perhaps?
Well, well, well.
Changing...
It seemed to me
into some kind of animal.
How extraordinary!
Well...
That obviously justified you
finishing him off, didn't it?
I'm not saying that.
We shall not try to penetrate the odd
recesses of your imagination Woodford.
We shall ask you exactly what you
are trying to saying about his death.
Did you feel you personally
have the right
to arbitrate on a matter
of life and death?
Please!
I was confused.
As indeed I'm sure we all
are in this court today.
- But it wasn't murder.
- But you did shoot him?
Yes.
And you seriously plea that
this was an act of mercy?
Yes.
Well as in the eyes of the law
it was plain homicide.
I was confused.
As indeed I'm sure we all
are in this court today.
- But it wasn't murder.
- But you did shoot him?
Yes.
And you seriously plea that
this was an act of mercy?
Yes.
Well as in the eyes of the law
it was plain homicide.
I think maybe...
people should be allowed
to die the way they choose.
Ah, I see.
An expose of some higher moral law
to which you have privileged access.
I wouldn't say that exactly.
No, but some moral argument
which exonerates you
from the charge of murder.
- I'd say that. Yes, I would.
- Hmm, I see.
So you feel that your
action lies outside
the inadequate and pathetic
assumption of this court...
that wilful slaughter
is murder?
Why are you so
contemptuous?
The idiosyncratic notions of moral law
which exist within the accused's head
are not our concern.
However innocent he is
within his own eyes,
he is guilty before the
laws of the state.
We are here to decide not whether
his action was justifiable,
nor even comprehensible,
only if it is criminal.
We have the medical evidence
here of Dr. Mark Eddington.
We have the accused's own word.
And we have the unequivocal
nature of the law of the state.
I'm assure the ladies and
gentlemen of the jury...
I'm sure that your
conclusions
must be...
inevitable.
Oh, Sonia!
Why did you marry that petrified
lawyer, the son of mine.
I tried to warn you...
It'll have to be rewritten
in so little time.
And...
Oh shit!
It's Mark Eddington.
Damn it, I'll make you
a friend of Claude's.
I haven't seen you for ages.
What did you make
of that, then?
Well, you've seen Claude
prosecuting before.
He was hateful today,
I'm furious!
I wouldn't say that...
Fury in Claude isn't
like most people,
comes out ice-cold,
logical.
The jury was obviously
sympathetic to that boy.
And it's not Claude's way to
let that confuse the issue.
What a strange young man.
Funny sort of crank
to find in the army.
Crank? I thought what
he did was brave.
- Well I...
- Mark.
You're going to have lunch
with Claude and me.
Come on, join us at Luigi's
in about half an hour.
- Yes, fine, I'd love to.
- Ya, alright.
But dear I'd...
Oh.
Sonia!
Wait a minute!
But what are you in my
scheme of things Eddington?
The Jolly old, bloody old
doctor character?
God forbid...
Here he is again!
Never liked you Eddington,
never understood what
Claude saw in you.
I'm getting rid of you at once.
Sonia!
Here now...
What she...
Of course, she's intrigued.
She wants to meet that
Kevin Woodford.
I get it. He wants to cut me up.
Shall we let him try?
Wait a minute though...
right hospital,
wrong pathologist.
Wasn't Eddington going to
lunch with Sonia and Claude?
Oh, get out of my mind!
I regret nothing! Damn and blast you!
My love and respect
for the human body...
the hard muscle,
fine skin.
At Cap Ferrat, those days
salty and strong out of the sea.
Not a vain man, well...
"Ugly", Molly used to say.
Green,
but handsome in your
own fashion Clive Langham.
I loved the sun, loved
the cold wine...
Christ, I can taste it now!
God, what a tailor's dummy he is.
Your mother...
Ah, Molly where are you?
She always had the wine chilled
to exactly the right temperature.
And prawns
red in their shells.
Yes, I see her laughing there
on the terrace in the sun.
We...
Can't you take a hint?
Didn't I say bugger off!
You think this horrifies me?
All the pain before I care about.
Well, there's the
morphine I suppose...
Verdict: "Not guilty"
There wasn't a jury in there.
There was a twelve man
law reform commission.
I wonder why Sonia
asked me to lunch.
Well, why shouldn't she?
She's always seeking
allies these days.
What's the matter with you?
We've know each
other for thirty years
and trusted each
other for nearly ten.
It was a command really.
Are you and she in
some sort of crisis?
Oh, for Christ's sake Mark, really!
She always thinks I'm prosecuting her
when she sees me in court.
Do you resent the
boy getting off free?
Well, I have no things
about him whatsoever.
What about losing the case?
Oh, I think my reputation
will stand up.
Where the hell is she?
Look, I'm going to have a pee
and then I'm going to order.
Oh, I got another of those telegrams
this morning from my father.
He's still dying,
of course.
I've never known anyone take
quite so long about it.
And do it in such good health.
Claude.
I thought you might like to
meet Kevin Woodford.
I have met him.
To apologize for your aggressiveness
in court, I thought.
I was just going for a pee.
- Why did you whether bring you here?
- I don't mind where I go.
I never mind where I am.
Oh dear!
I think he's fey.
It's always tiresome.
You are fey aren't you?
Oh, I know that you
have inner peace.
That usually implies no powers
of rational thinking.
Whatsoever...
I don't feel like lunch today...
suddenly.
Oh Hell!
These places are almost becoming
de rigueur as fear symbols.
Jolly well, bloody old
de rigueur, eh.
Well, if one's had
a fatuous life
one might as well have
fatuous nightmares.
But I am frightened.
You will not get me,
you fucking bastards!
That's right children,
go in, go in.
Why not in Claude's house?
Let battle commence!
Yes.
In here.
Bang on Clive Langham!
Get it down!
No.
No, stop...
it could seem vulgar.
And must not!
Now, that's fascinating.
Yes, I approve of that.
Do get on with it children.
My god, he doesn't look
as if it's urgent though...
Not angry when rejected...
but wistful.
Good, good.
But what about the
tyrannical lawyer himself?
Where would he be?
OK, so in his office then.
And furthermore father since there is
no point in telephoning you,
far less in visiting you, which
would only be exposing ourselves
to our now familiar
mutual recriminations.
Damn it all father,
you're a rich man!
If you must do your
dying with such a...
disgusting lack of dignity.
Why don't you do it in
a nursing home?
Or some such place...
Where they can
stand in...
amazed, well paid tolerance,
while you shout and drink and
protest your way to death's dark door.
The silence when you reach
the other side will be our
only reassurance that
you're actually gone.
And I could add...
I could add...
When you find yourself
potentially alone.
You sod!
You odious, sanctimonious,
stiff-necked little crumb.
I'm not having this, by god!
Watch it Langham.
The blood pressure...
I mean to say...
If I don't know how to die,
at least I knew how to live.
But what about that mistress
of yours, my son?
What did I do with her?
Don't tell me I mislaid her.
I-diddle-i-de a drunken life for me.
Damned it I'm giving you
to the dreaded Claude.
I could do with you myself...
if I could just get off this bed,
out of this coffin of a room.
Yes, you'll do for the moment.
You can be Claude's mistress.
Quick, quick, quick,
first name into the mind...
Helen...
Wiener
Ya.
Intellectual journalist.
Goes to conferences on every bloody
thing, that's you Helen Wiener.
Just another wee drinkie whilst
they get you onto terra firma.
Did you know...
Did you know,
those astronauts who've
been to the moon
It's had a peculiar effect
on some of them.
Lurching about on a lump of
frozen rock hanging in space.
Claude's due back.
I think of God's eyes
watching them.
A pair of huge brilliant eyes somewhere
out there beyond the sun,
brighter then the sun.
Kevin, I'm not overawed
by the universe.
It's a very peaceful place
you have here,
you and Claude should like it
quite a lot I should imagine.
And you also imagine that we
should get out before he arrives?
I've never done this before.
I always thought if I did it would be
somewhere else and in the sweat of guilt.
On his account...
I'm quite easy in
most situations.
You see there's every indication
that some of the astronauts
have been profoundly disturbed
by going out there.
- Kevin.
- Yes?
Why are you so bloody obsessed
by the fucking astronauts?
Why do you go on
about the astronauts?
Well I think it all
has its poetic side.
Clomping about under
the stars and so on.
Sod the moon.
No poetry there anymore.
Another of those stabbing
pains right up the arse!
Then another stinger
coming right down the spine.
Meet the one from
the backside.
Out there...
in the icy universe...
there's nothing.
Physiological disaster...
there'll be some reddish brown stains
on the underpants yesterday.
No more doctors!
I suppose he'd meet his
mistress in a motel.
No...
Here, Claude, here.
You can't, not now.
Mustn't go home.
It's inconvenient.
Or is it...
Now...
Am I springing Claude on them?
It will give me no end of fun.
With me it was almost
the other way round,
husbands catching me
with their wifes.
Bang, thump, wallop.
Down you go Langham.
Always the bungler...
Never caught anyone with my wife.
I don't actually smell sex.
Hasn't there been any?
You should meet my brother.
He'd take it just like you,
he's a famous footballer.
The telephone...
Why not?
What would you say was
interesting about him?
I mean, what exactly is the
point about him, his attraction?
Any clues about yourself, Woodford?
Any ideas...
If your wife's attracted to me,
I think that's your problem not mine.
I don't I've ever been
a problem have I, Claude?
Problems have a way of acquiring
status in a relationship you see.
Hello.
Helen.
Where?
No, I'm having a drink in the
bedroom with my wife,
and the young man
she seems keen on.
Now?
Yes.
Right away.
Who's Helen?
I despise you Woodford.
I'm sorry about that.
He's frightfully unattractive.
I mean, it doesn't matter whether
you're good enough for my wife...
but are you good enough for me?
I really don't think so.
Who is Helen?
I don't remember.
I don't remember...
I think he'd better get off
and meet old Helen.
Oh, there goes
another thing.
Slip the suppository
into position.
No such luck for me,
a sudden coronary.
No, it has to be...
slow, squalid and messy things.
Live by the guts and
die by the guts.
Now let science soothe
the troubled rectum.
And back to business...
I-diddle-i-de-ti-tum-ti-tum-ti-tum.
Who does not know the mixture of fear and
excitement of going to meet an old flame.
Carrying one's thundering prick...
Already composing
the get out clauses,
just in case she's cooked up
an actual demand,
or the erstwhile reliable
member should fail
in it's exquisite duties.
And what's more
if the new encounter
should turn out disastrous
from the word "Go".
Will one be able to get rid of her
with a dash of style?
A little panache?
Not you Woodford,
damn and bugger you!
Christ he's intractable this one.
I'll never get the hang of him.
Out! Out!
She looks like his mother.
Clearly the boy must have
an unconscious mind,
just like everybody else.
Oh, Molly...
You look well.
I'm dying.
Have you ever heard
of an allegedly...
famous footballer...
called Woodford?
How's your wife?
I'm thinking of killing
this footballer's brother.
It's one of those rare, slow, deadly
diseases you can have without knowing.
Then it suddenly accelerates and
nothing can stop it, or reverse it.
Suddenly you are
not just ageing,
you are irrevocably dying.
How's your father?
He's still dying.
Well, he's an old man.
There is no necessary connection
between one's age
and the length of time
taken to die.
I am told I have about six months.
Maybe a year...
We must make the most of it.
What a bastard!
Great! Smashing!
Of course it's been said about
my work that the search for style
has often resulted
in a want of feeling.
My goodness, does he
find this erotic?
However but I'd put it another
way I'd say that,
style is feeling,
Its most elegant and
economic expression.
Ten out of ten, Clive Langham.
Christ, it's the bloody footballer,
the dreaded younger Woodford!
He can't just, just trundle in here
and take a shower.
Can he?
So what to do?
I suppose we could start up
again in another hotel.
We could live together.
And leave Sonia?
To watch me die?
Shouldn't everyone live as
if they're about to die,
not next week, nor
next month but now?
Anyway...
it's impossible.
So how do you and Sonia live?
In a state of unacknowledged mutual
exhaustion behind which we scream
silently.
Sounds binding.
I learnt self control as a reaction
against my father, it started as a habit
then became a trap.
We squirmed...
How did you get out?
Maybe you really scream...
No, I never have...
No, you have to have a big passion,
a compelling reason.
I've had neither of those...
neither, I think, has she.
How glad I am
I chose to live alone,
right from the beginning.
Are you?
I feel nothing at all.
He can say that again.
Damn!
He'll be bloody well
blind anyway.
Poor Claude!
What a thin owlish little sod
you were at school.
Prig from the
word "Go."
Ought we not always to live
as if one's going to die.
Eyes like marbles.
"Why haven't you got the
Nobel Prize daddy?"
"Our English master says you aren't
nearly as good as Graham Greene."
Beset the bugger, say I.
Some of us, fuckface, wonder why Graham
Greene hasn't got the Nobel Prize either.
He once offered to teach me
how to masturbate.
Your father?
I was deeply shocked.
He'll have to go into a
nursing home, of course.
Eight housekeepers
in five months.
Nobody tries still...
he tries to screw them.
You are not going to put that extraordinary
old man in a nursing home.
That purely incontinent,
ageing infant!
You just resent his independence,
just as you'd resent mine,
if I had any.
You're not a husband or a son,
you're a goddamn jailer.
How's Kevin?
And being a goddamn jailer is the
nearest thing you've got to an instinct.
You must want him very much.
Well I don't want you very much.
Not anymore...
You must be forcefully
attracted to him.
I want...
I suppose you fancy he's got the
poetic spirit, or something like that.
I want...
I would like...
I...
I!
First person singular!
Do I have to oppose you to
reassure myself that I exist?
Let's just say there's something
in Kevin that intrigues me.
In him?
You mean inside him?
A kind of visionary?
Funny pictures, in his head?
Chubby little people with wings?
Get out.
Get out!
Now look I do insist...
We must do something about father.
When will you pull
yourself together?
You're always sniveling.
Shall we never be free of you?
Well, yes father I...
I admire your books very much.
I think you're a very fine writer indeed.
And I hope that you die with every
nerve end in your body shrieking.
When will you pull yourself together?
You're always sniveling.
Shall we never be free of you?
Yes, father I...
well, yes I do...
He's improving, improving.
So now...
How about a half of
cold champagne.
Petite truffles.
Damn footballer, must've got
lost in that hotel somewhere.
Molly...
If you're out there in the
cosmic dark somewhere,
don't wait for me.
I'm not coming.
There we go...
the tremors, the warnings.
Once death seemed like a gentlest
earthquake of the system,
but now...
gathering force,
after the years.
What I really mean to
say Molly is, of course,
I'd prefer not to come.
I think we'll try this one again.
How's Helen?
He killed her.
Father killed her really.
Those holidays of
ours at Cap Ferrat.
He tortured her.
He was always randy
when he had a hangover.
There's a chap in football gear...
jogging along the street.
I haven't been...
no, I wouldn't say
bored with you.
Self eliminating, yes.
Clever of you to catch
me at seventeen.
Well I've been dreaming
you'd wake up.
You became my authority.
There's a deep sadness...
You remain my only authority...
As if dreaming is my only
real level of existence.
And so I passed from childhood,
more or less...
to wifehood?
Without the tiresome
intervention of a....
developing personality in between.
I'm not a person...
I'm a fucking construction.
Yours...
Was...
After certain dreams nothing in waking
life can have such intensity.
Even if it's a common fiction,
it's still poignant.
One thinks...
ho-hum.
You might as well drink my drink too.
Not Molly!
You can't have my wife!
Do I resemble your mother?
There's something...
Mugged!
Yes, mugged!
This city is definitely falling to pieces.
All hell out there sometimes.
My last conscious words were...
On the question of subatomic
particles, gentlemen...
One gets confused by
what is infinitely small,
and what is infinitely large.
The mind buckles...
the head aches...
Much more violently than
the impact of your fists.
gentlemen.
So this is how it was?
This is how it was.
Nothing can compare with the
memories of childhood.
And yours and mine of each others...
I think I began to love you because
I knew straight away you wouldn't...
invade me,
colonize me.
Not some kind of moral achievement
on your part, it's just that I...
suppose you simply exhausted
your prejudices on your wife.
How penetrating.
Truly, I wouldn't have lived
as I have if I'd met you first.
I now look back on all those years
with bitter scepticism.
I'm ready to defect.
It's a little late.
Aren't you rather letting yourself
down by saying that?
I thought you were bored and
disgusted by the idea of living
with someone continuously.
How you and father
would have fought.
There's a terrific fire across the city,
the sky's red for miles.
Are you still here?
What are your opinions on adultery?
Do you care about
the nature of things?
Have you got a philosophical bent?
Do you worry?
What do you think of
my wife's body?
It isn't the point.
I beg your pardon?
Let me put it this way...
It isn't the point.
Did you hear that old boy?
She has a concise way
of putting things.
Well what do you make of it?
What do you make of love?
How'd you like to run
away with her?
There's no need to run anywhere.
I've already left you,
so why run?
We can manage perfectly
well just as we are.
See if you can cope,
I'd be fascinated.
You will continue to exert
self-control I'm sure.
The chap's an enigma,
he really is.
She is an enterprising fuck
though, isn't she?
I'm always content where I am.
My husband you see Kevin, Claude,
is committed to self control.
He exaggerates of course,
it's a performance.
If you knew him you'd realize
he has no emotions to control.
My wife has turned your head.
Oh yes she has...
I can tell the signs.
Woodford! Don't go to sleep!
I know you have inner peace...
And you have inner stagnation.
Childhood is shattering.
I can see that you must
have got off to a bad start.
But you've got more than your fair
share of inner peace, old boy.
You'll have to be put down.
"Like a mad dog" as they say.
Sonia!
Put him down at once.
- Where's the lady?
- Going for a swim.
- Haven't I seen you somewhere before?
- I get around.
Aren't you the famous footballer?
Or is it cricket?
Steady.
I believe I'm the affronted party.
After all it is your brother who's
screwing my wife, isn't it.
He's not screwing anybody,
isn't Kevin.
Do you spend very much time jogging
about town dressed like that?
Oh, training are we?
Big match coming on.
I'm very famous indeed, see.
And an equally serious occupation
of mine is taking care of our Kevin.
He needs it, he needs it...
Our childhood Mr. Langham...
we was brought up like pigs.
My goodness!
You do seem to be a very
serious sort of chap.
It's a fine game, football,
beautiful to watch.
Well, you know...
I mean as a general activity
it seems meaningless,
but the form, pattern,
is elegant.
If it is football...
Choreographically there's
plenty of poetry there.
Plenty, plenty...
Oh, when one gets hold
of the ball, and...
tickles it along...
Can I do anything for you
famous footballer?
Ah, this'll never do.
Won't do at all!
Can't have people thumping
our poor old bloody Claude.
Can we...
Oh, for Christ's sake.
The pains are banging in my neck
like sodding tom-toms.
Oh, is it the arteries?
Or the jugular...
Going to burst?
Then spew out,
living, red juice.
Helen?
Molly?
The pains are catching up with me.
In the end I shall call for morphine.
No hero, not heroic, never was...
Do you see Molly, they're taking
some of them away.
But not you my love.
No...
What a punctual fellow you are.
Come on.
Miss Boon.
Ah Miss Boon, how erotic
you look this morning.
This is my friend Woodford.
He used to be in the army.
But now he's nothing more,
nor less, than a failed astronaut.
That's his, his brother Dave.
The famous footballer.
What can I do for you
Mr. Langham and...
or Mr. Woodford?
Well you see...
frankly...
my wife is thinking of taking
him away with her.
He has to be taken otherwise
he'd never go.
He's never had the urge for...
Bangkok
Venice
Tokyo
any of those places
you and I would
side for.
Woodford, sit down and
explain your problem!
Well...
It all started after his wife had
asked me out to lunch.
I'd just been acquitted of murder.
What's more...
I think that he and Sonia should
have a quiet, beautiful place
where they can fuck,
night and day.
A sort of backdrop
of a place...
I don't even know
his wife, not really.
Nonetheless, bundle him
out of the country we must
before I shoot him.
Do you approve of
violence Miss Boon?
Certainly not!
Neither do I.
It reeks of spontaneity.
Come, come, young Buddha.
Right...
now...
Yes...
Where was I?
In the travel agent...
In case there's a myocardial
infarction, but patient...
No...
Jesus! That was a spear of fire.
So...
Dress the creature will you.
What was that Mr. Langham?
Dress the creature!
Don't bugger about.
He can't walk with my wife
dressed like that.
Yes, Mr. Langham.
Dress not the humble exterior clay
Mr. Jennings, but the man within.
Oh come, come, come.
I have to leave for my
gunmaker by noon.
Your father rang yesterday,
ordered a dozen shirts.
Shirts?
He should be ordering shrouds.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org