Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
We're going tomorrow,
me and vijaylaxmi.
You're taking her along?
She's a very sweet girl.
She seems a bit of
a hippie but she isn't.
Where's your friend?
I'm just saying hello.
It's in our culture.
Yeah. Where's she?
I'd like to do this
culture thing too.
Your adult film ended
before it could begin.
Such a terrible thing to happen.
Dolly. Look who's here. Rani.
Rani who?
Our Rani. Mr. Mehra's daughter.
Ah yes, My poor baby, my poor lamb.
This is my friend, vijaylaxmi.
She is from Paris.
Bon jour, bon jour.
Never mind, my little one,
never mind. Sit down, sit down.
You're again on your massage chair?
Okay, what will you have?
Nothing, thank you. Just water?
Just water? Mom, Rani's here.
Rani who?
Our Rani. Mr. Mehra's daughter.
My child, my poor child.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4xejp
Help other users to choose the best subtitles