Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Okay, guy, you're in the important play, allright
l need you to be in 1 00 %%%
Unfortunately l can't be there....
l'll be there in half
and you better not loose
Why did you call ?
why did you call ?
We're almost there
Hey, coach
kiss my nap, kiss my nap
Hey, clown, you keep running your mouth
l'll come over there
and rearrange your beak
Shut up
Why don't we play Jazz
if we not playing basketball ?
Oh, l was wait over here
That's true, get out of here
Just because....
Did l do that ?
did l do that ?
That's why you give me a check
You need to shower
No, you need the shower, dude
you need to shower
Yeah, keep your mouth, keep your mouth
Victor ?
Coach Roy killed Victor !
Feel bad, feel real bad
You had present everything
wrong to college boy today
You didn't care about the player
you didn't care about the games
Look, if you gonna fire me
fire me,
l can lie down all day
was it ?
lt was such pleasure that
l say that you McCormick
Are officially ban from coaching NCBA
For the remain of your year alive
You abandon me, huh ?
yeah, okay, l'll be ahead that long yard
lf you got the 3 championship
Then you missed the vice president
And then you want abandon me ?
l want abandon you
l abandon you for life
Can he ban us ?
-Of course not
Excuse me, gentleman....
ln short, you gonna give Roy one last
chance to prove himself
Yes, but it doesn't say l've to leaf
Coach Don the year in my league
Was that is, Roy ?
good luck to find another team
Lets go
Good, because if you don't
l will
Dad call
you coming again ?
Keep practise, okay ?
Come on, leave
Okay, look, l would love
to take you there
Everybody need this lied
it will gonna be great
And you can't always
count those people
That be a lie
Your dad is not upon lie anymore
allright ?
But l got you back
and l'm keep helping you back
So, before you go
giving up this road
You need to wait through
Until about 1 8, might get ready
allright ?
Mom, if you so smart
how do you pretend this personal?
You know what, you're
too smart for your own good
Oh, because if l hate
l wouldn't have you
Keith, l wouldn't head you
What ?
...First stop, we have Keith Ellis
Now everyone know, Keith Ellis are the
best player on the team
Okay, this only thing Ellis love more
in playing basketball
ls his shoes, his hair
and his image
Last year, he having the record
for the most ball shoot the face
Look, this year
he had the shoot
Now, we have higher proctetion
for the kids
Oh, yeah, how ?
He gone through forjob
-Okay
Your deal
l guess you guy want a women
What for ?
You want cookies ?
Team 9, and the pressure is on
But you couldn't tell by look up the
confident face
Easily the best year in the team
and the week
86/0
l'm here, Tim
l'm here
Man, if we have Coach Don
we never loose
Ouch
Allright, guy, look back at the
games he lost this time
He promise he is not
to loose anymore
Please, welcome the
Coahes of Polytechnic
Roy McCormick
Roy, remember your word ?
You only said you come on to the show
when you available
And brother,
you're very available now
Well, you know, l have option
l'm a free agent, baby
l heard the street said
You couldn't get the job right now
real or cheat ?
Man, look, l want to go somewhere where
where there desire to win
This is great, you know
Because we're normal, and l...
l kind want to go back to my rules
That's what l wanted
Come on, l got a plan
come on
Fax to get ?
l will get it
stay
l want 3 NCBA championship for me
What ?
what l gonna to do ?
Roy, don't you see ?
is perfect
ls your own school
Okay, look, we accept they all
You work quickly for a week
they get used to realise of it
You look like a saint and we get
ger free PR
We desperately need
ln the mean time, it will be your chance
to get a job offer
What offer to me now ?
Emm ?
Dorrin, this is the supplementary budget
Could you get me
the full budget , please ?
That is the full budget
Tim Fink, Principal partner
Fink agency
Yeah, Marry Walsh
Principal...
Wow, whoo
okay, is Coach Roy
Coach Roy in the house
Allright, well done
Boh, community service
Did you get a receipt or something ?
We get more great sport guy
aren't you
We're here to accept your offer
l have not idea what you talking about
Your offer
So you're telling me
that Roy McCormick want to coach here ?
Roy is gonna work for your team
They're gonna coach
the best of the best
For absolutely, work for
no charges
Yeah, l want to get back
to the community
You know, here is where l
found my first true love
Which is basketball
Well, teamwork
l guess that's true love
True love
That was very inspire
coaches
Well, l guess
follow me
Apparently some of you had tried
certify the school policy
And hired a new head coach on your own
Further deal,
please welcome your new coach
Oh, they're really short
Yeah, they're 1 3
Allright, well, good luck kids
and you have yourself
We will
l was talking to him
Coach Roy, l'm your big fans
l know your commercial
Couple thing l should warn you about
...when you get nervous
eat pills
You're my assistant coach ?
Yeah, l appreciate
Maybe they're own for the kids
having fun
Yeah, sure
thanks
Excuse Mr
for talking rude
We don't have any skill
We just want to make some nothing
Marry, is that really a great idea ?
l don't know, Jinny
you may find this hard to believe
l don't have money and
l don't have resources
l got nothing
Excuse me, that's what l like it
Stick it to the sun
do not shine
So, when coaches in basketball
want to coach my kids for free
...l not going say no
Besides, Coach Roy is never
hit appear
Okay, great, great,
so that is the criteria
He is never hit the kids, then he could
work in no one find it
Yeah, l know
but check it up
lf he step his line in anyway,
all we have to do is call the NCBA
And he is been out of here
So l think he is gonna be responsible
Okay, how you gonna to run the school
and monitor a mad man ?
Well, Jinny
l'm not
No, no...
l'm not either
You go all the games, anyway
you gonna be my eye and ear
Yeah, the minute you said he is
out of line
He is gone
Come on, coach
trust me
Coach Roy have some issues
Out
Stop...
You were really great watch
high blood pressure
Too much press
What's that ?
Look, l don't care how many
times he wants
l don't care anything about that
under his reputation
Come on, give him a chance
-Of what ?
He got some problem
Oh, he didn't hit anybody
-Yeah
We hit him and
brought off of him
But he doesn't know that yet
Look, l'm sorry
My name is Jeanie and....
ltjust something might a lot to me
Excuse me
Miss Jeanie, look, l don't mind
reputation proceed me
But this just rap
you know, it is not true
Roy Mccormick
is really nice to meet you
l know who you are
My son either like of you
Well, your son, he...
he is good kids
l think he gonna do big
thing in this games
He gonna be allright
That's good to know, because
that is not my son
That is my son
He gonna be good too
Quite frankly, l don't have to
view you treat your player
My son doesn't need some hot shot
or telling me he is good
Because he is good
Ma'am, Miss Jeanie, look
l swear the only reason l'm here
ls to help this kids
l won't do anything wrong
Well, it is nice to meet you
-it's very nice to meet you
lf you don't mind
l'll call you sometimes out ?
l don't think so
Dudes, Roy checking on you mom
Coach Roy, what's like coming back to
ColdJas your old school ?
That's right
l could open a main street
in some there
l have one dream
that was to get out
l'll not end up here like
this rules
l guess, l would love to give back to
Such a great coach
He really doesn't do once
doesn't he ?
No
ls this games really ?
That's what l want you for
...And l l remember you there
l appoint to your assistant coach
7 times
He said not
l was too reached
Turn out l wasn't so reached
l couldn't meet the 5 games
in tonight state championship
Whoo, l don't know middle school have
state championship
Yeah, we do
and l want it do 9 times
9 times ?
Big close
The only team member l count for
is my son, Richard
Good luck. man
You are in my house
This is my world
1 ,2,3...
Catch up
Oh, wake up now
Excuse
Aren't you can suppose
to be doing something ?
Yeah, l'm thinking about what
l'm gonna eat for lunch, yuo interest
Your kids ever learn the pass
Judge
Are you kidding me ?
There was 1 0 minute ago
Come out
Listen, l don't mind you
embarrass yourself
Because you used to it, okay ?
But now, you stop embarrass me
What's your name ?
-My name is Keith
Keith, you think you can try not to
turn the ball over ?
Guy, l need you get out and
go to work, okay ?
And try to keep this single dishes
lets go, guy, lets go !
Oh, speaking of animal
in the follow you read the story
Over NCBA, Coach McCormick
lost his first games today
1 00 and 9 could nothing
he is the real
Well, he have to teach the kids the
fundamental thing like
Which basket is our ?
Like jumper, it mean your team
is gonna drop through
Look, Roy gonna do betterjob
if he wanna be coach again
ln the NCBA
is that simple
Yeah
Roy, Fink
what the hell did you doing ?
Hey, man, that wasn't big deal
okay, is middle school
Who cares ?
Who cares, you see
that's what l say
But you know, Roy
you made out a national news
...Nobody want to hire a loser
Look, coach. you gonna win in one games
which this kids is be able work again
Hi, are you Mr Cormick ?
l'm your big fans
Please leave a autograph
Oh, sure, thanks, young lady
-Thank you
Wait
That is my car, -here you go
that wasn't your car
Have a great day
l want my whole life back
l must be honest with you
l can't afford to loose
about this again
So l decide to teach you
how to play the games of basketball
Yeah, concept of passing and score
Okay ?
so play time is over
lf you don't like it,
the door is right there
Get back here
l gonna need some help
Unbelievable
Give me back
What ?
Shut up !
Look, you come with me
Look
She is in trouble again
Hey, look, this wasn't
allow in school, okay
You're natural
What's your name ?
Big Mac
Big Mac, you come
with me, allright ?
No, l'm not, l'm not
going to teacher
Small light work, really
spoke one
Allright ?
trust me
Suit up, come on, Big Mac
suit up
Trust me
Whoo, yeah, man
why not ?
Excuse me, can l help you ?
l just want to talk to
one of your player
Player ?
This is my student
l'll come back later
okay ?
Look
Walsh is really shy
he is not in the sport
And he really doesn't need
to be in first round
Like your type
My type ?
What is my type ? as you know
what is my type ?
Unbelieve, stubborn boy
always give it away
You're good, thank you
l'll come back after class
Look, son, you like basketball ?
l'm not really working in this
That's perfect...
So join us, please, perfect
You, out
You know what, just give me a second
30 second, allright ?
Son, do you know everybody
wonder how she like ?
No
Then you wanna be love
l love you
Because you're 6 feet with
extremely long arm, you know
l confirm you, if you join the team
You know, you like the girl
l can help you
But you gotta promise
you gonna be a good player
What l can't guarantee is that
You won't be bub
nobody jokes
How tall are you son ?
-6'2 -6'2 ?
l deeply deeply love
Whoo, 6'2 ?
Will you join us ?
l...
...Because you practise hard
l'll be there
Careful, l'm watching him
-Okay, thank you
This here are our new crew
This is Wes
This is Big Mac
This girl is running the drill ?
Yeah
That's girl stole my wife's car
Well, you aren't in forces
allright ?
The only you got to fight...
Don't be afraid to be useless
l don't want fight
l'm sure
lf you have a good hand,then
you have a good foot work
Use it
ls not what l'm talking about
Wes
Look, do yourself a favour
l don't want trouble there, allright ?
But l...
l know, you never ever play basketball
But for the next 1 5 minute
is our new secret, okay
Whoo, secret weapon
No weapon form against
How're you doing, McCormick ?
You always come through for
brother
Hey, god bless you
oh, brother
Thank you
You're shine
you're shine of my light
Smelters, come
God bless you, basketball baby
How're you doing ?
-Good
Coach Roy ask me come down
here and speak with you
So if l may, l would like to say a pray
with you good
Look down your head, please
God is good
God is great
Thank you for this games we about
to receive
Because we about to give in really
Thank you for the full
for we about to...
No, that's the wrong phrase
God, we ask you give us the strength
let everything to go all way
l'll be on the god...
We ask you to inject some key player
on our team
...So that the Smelters
will win this games
Amen
Because we know you god
Love always
Amen
Oh, no problem
Cricket
89, 2 years before it works
Technical false
What's wrong with you ?
ls a technical false
delay games
Look, you can't have a parade
everytime you score
Get your ass to the games
lets go
Big Mac, you really try my patient
l need you to go out here
be cool
Try not to chunk
can you do that ?
Give me some shake
shake your base, you know
Double it up, you understand ?
allright ?
Stay still first
stay still
Take him out of here...
Wes
Out
Hey, you did good, son, allright
Have a seat
Ralph
Thanks
Come on. go
...That's why you do 45 shoot aside
lets go
What ?what were you doing here ?
what ?
Coach, what happen if we win ?
Fuzzy, if you win
if you win
l will do shoot aside for
every point you win by, okay ?
Now, take it out
get back to work
See they way you run
that's why you're loser
Remember what l embarrass you ?
That's not gonna embarrass me
l pulled down every trick
in the book today
And you're 1 3, right ?
Allright, take down
Ladies
3 pizza here
Guess it is like
All you want
all you want
Cheese, here, l gonna take
excuse me
Yeah, Pizza
ls there always gonna be pizza here ?
There will be from now on
You won't mind, right ?
-Yeah
How is your pizza ?
Okay, good
there is your new job
You straight ?
-Yeah
Hey, green team out
green team out
What would we grant ?
-Me
There not art in team
ls about you
what do you think ?
Shake it
Whoo, did l angry you ?
Give me the ball
So, when l get black,
l start looking for my team
You know, l mean
they can help me out
You know
But if l get the ball
through their leg
What would happen soon ?
l don't want to do it
How were you passed the ball ?
You, go on
just pass it
l will give you right back
come on
Oh, coming next
Allright
Allright, you pass the ball, man
How was that feel ?
When the ball go from your
hand to another hand ?
Again
Allright
Teamwork, besides
l tell you another day
...You might do some win
Go guy
Right there
allright
Go...Mac
Allright
Who can tell me again that how did
complex way and beating the pick in low ?
Somebody ?
Talking
Talking, exactly
Talking, guy
You got to communicate out there
you're team
Allright, communicate as a kids
Like the healthy relationship at home
You ever tell your lady like
''come on, come on
and your lady like
No, no, lets make there
l remember...
You know, run to you play again
and run to eat the rice
Run it, come on, guy
Come on, communicate out there, you
guy knew each other like the back
Come on, communicate
l didn't said stop playing
communicate out there
Okay, now you have to talk
Ellas, lets go, guy
move the ball
Allright, remember, Ellas
you invited me here
This is all your fault
You got a problem, son ?
You always piss on me
l'm the best player on the team
And all you ever do is right!
Okay, you got me
fair square
l do something wrong
you yelled
And l wonder why it is ?
Even if l do it right, you yelled at
me to do better
Hey, kids, you gotto give, okay
You can actually beat someone
You got what it takes...
And guess what, you win
Maybe you know what
your mom will laugh at myself
Here, the hold basketball and skill
You're your mom asshole
that's what you got
And we didn't live in
the best neighbourhood
We saw it like
the neighbourhood you got
That's why l want to see you do good
That's all
Coach
l got a problem
lf you don't say anything, they
can make me just fire it
And l got a lawyer
No, l got to learn, this is the
hand play ball
...Acting in eligible
That's what l said
l'm eligible
Well, l'm your coach
l'm not to get, okay ?
l'll serve our kids fair
Why not, you scare over ?
Of course
Come on, man
you gotto to be brave
You, l don't think
you scare everything
You gotto be brave, man
You gotto straight your chest
get need
Give me the face
work the face
Give me some groan act
l look bad
-l look bad
-You, -you
we gonna win
Do you want to be scare in the rest
of your life, son ?
Big Mac, l would love to
take you out
See, she is a sweet young lady
Not really
You serious ?
Yeah, l'm serious
Guy, now we have to
forfeit another game
Okay, we're not going lost
Why you always mad all the time ?
l want to go for other games
l can't get it there
l'm gonna help
Why me ?
What the hell we does ?
l don't like take the tyre
Hey, coach
want to give some help ?
Come on, lets get out of here
Okay, everybody there ?
-Allright, lets get on the bus
You got to share the sport light
you know ?
l'm not said like that's good
Get out there work hard, man
And get the rebound
and you will feel good about that
You'll feel good about the games
So what you said is that ?
l'm not really good ?
Oh, man, l'm not saying that
l'm saying the opposite there
l'm saying you so good
l want every games l won it
Just don't tell about them
l promise
Wait, is there a girl on your team ?
Girl can't play basketball
What did you ?
Look, l know you don't like the
back there from afraid
But real power is about there
respectic
No just cracking it
think about it
Hey
l heard what you said to the kids
l was wrong about you
And l'm sorry
Sorry ?
Sorry, unless go out on daytime ?
Time could change
l can make a description
He pretty smart
l'll be at home by 8
can l call you ?
Smelter apparently abandon
the useful strategy...
Hand up
go
Time out
You know what, guy
keep your hand up
Everybody hands up
Come on, now guy
Right there
good job
Time up
time up
What we do now ?
You're playing basketball now
baby
Listen
1 ,2, 3
Smealters
You're playing basketball now
yeah
What ?what in god
name just happened ?
Allright, guy
you're leaving 2 minute
Oh, coach, you forget something
Yeah, coach, we won
Oh, you guy don't mess about it
So lets kept go on, okay ?
Go, Roy....
You like it ?
-l love it
Come on, guy
come on
Don't make me down the eye
...the only have to do is just
kick up and play
25 left in first games
He score
Are you insane ?
l bet how you be a
coach in middle school ?
Roy, 55597
is my phone number
Write it down
Go ahead
go
-55597
-41 , okay
This from magic Johnson
Hi
He is shy
l'm Gog
l'm the sixth man
She is your friend ?
Hey, Wes
Hey, Coach
l met you came out from ladies
what happened ?
Oh, no
is not that
ls just, l can't have a girlfriend
Hey, please don't mean that
-This is to coach
Trust me, he has a girlfriend
And how would you know ?
Because l seen her
And if you talk to that girl again...
Ok
Just one more
And thank you for dressing up
Very nice for you
you look really nice
Thank you
This been along a week
Why don't you come in
Keith,
Keith, stay something low
come on
And you gotto clean yourself
Don't put on my flower
Thank you baby
Thank you
You know when you first come here
l had real bad for stand
But you do that wrong, right ?
No, l was do right
l mean, you're spoil, play boy
handle everything you ever want it
Didn't give a damm about
coaching basketball
All l'm saying is
look at you now
Look, this is personal attack
on my personality
lt's not lead to a kiss or slap
cause l can't tell you yet
Coach
Hey, what you doing ?
you go to the games ?
Hey, you know Fuzzy been our 5
man
Oh, good for Fuzzy
what's the Fuzzy ?
Look, do you check your messager ?
The NCBA's review
today
They want to reinstate you
l know that
l work it out, look
The NCBA review l schedule till 4
games at 5
You can make both
we gotto move now
Seriously ?
-Seriously
Let me get for you
Lets go, l want you to pull
come on, l'm talking to you
What happening ?
Good, don't worry about it, okay
We go in there and
l will come there
Excuse me
Coach Roy Firm
-Roy ?
l'm sorry
This is representative
Tim Fink, how can l help you ?
Roy is in the meeting
Meeting ?
But he have a
championship games today
Right, with the small group
Yeah, he is in the NCBA review
Well, can you get him out
of the meeting with NCBA
Okay, just hang on a second
l'm not going do that
He is got career to think about
Can you tell him he have
huge appointment to me
To my son, to the Fuzzy, to the everybody
actually care about something
Huge appointment with you and son
got it
And your name is, sweetheart
You want my name ?
Sit down, sit down, Roy
sorry keep you waiting
l just want to be the first to say
Those kids is get more president
polytech themself
You know, just feel nice
get back to community
Yeah, allright
You know you got yourjob here
you can drop your PR with anyone
You can just sign here, coach
and you get your old name back
You know this kids, man
They really took me a luck
And it may be better to coach
better than l ever was
l swear to you, Roy
We'll give you everything you want
No
Thanks for the offer
but...
l really got a team
l'm a coach, man
You out of your mind ?
-no
l'm not out of my mind
l found a group who care
and love to basketball
The way l love to basketball
l just want have fun
and teach this kids, man
So thank you very much
l got a team get coach
went to final
You making me late
You got to get back, Fuzzy
-What ?
You're doing what you do ?
you're not, l coach
Working Fail, Smelters
ls Coach Roy !
l thought you gonna throw team
This is my team
Oh, he come back
Guy, where you come
lets go
Time out
Allright, guy, listen up
this is important
Ralph, how many quaters did you play ?
Big Mac, l'm proud of you
congratulation
You, big Wes, yes
the ladies Mac
Keep doing the thing
Hello, guy
No matter what this score was set
l know you to know
you're all winner
Have fun, allright
l love this games !
l know you do
So go ahead
and have fun doing it
1 23
Smelters
Hey, first across
first across
l just gonna say you
do a real good job
Yeah, l'm doing a good job
l just read a book you should get
yourself pass on the back...
Would you just relax, man
it's just a games
How do you know is just a games ?
This is a state championship...
l got a tactical
Smelters should 2
Allright, listen
communicated, okay ?
Work together as a team
...next year, l'll be back
1 23, Smelters
Be captain
l want you to trust it
trust yourself
Do you think ?
Not to shoot 2
You can't told them to stop
when the games is over
Hey, listen, there is a message
l want to talk about
What is that ?
Well, basically
in my own words
Oh, whoo
You know what you just said about me?
You were right
...l said
l gonna teach you
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4hre2
Help other users to choose the best subtitles