Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Let's go.
- Taylor. Bob and Marianne Taylor.
- Just bear with me one second.
- There are other hotels in Miami.
- I'm sorry.
What is the problem here? We made
these reservations over six months ago.
- I know, I'm just not seeing it.
- Where's Lisa?
- Lisa always takes care of us.
- She's out of town.
- Her grandmother passed away.
- Cynthia?
- Yes?
- Would you get in more trouble
if you bothered her
or if I called corporate?
OK.
Damn! Dallas drivers!
Who taught you how to drive?
Stevie Wonder?
- You'll catch your plane. You got...
- Ten minutes.
- Lisa Reisert.
- Lisa? Hi.
I'm so sorry to call, but I didn't
know what to do. I have a situation.
- Slow down. What's the problem?
- Bob and Marianne Taylor.
Yep. They're regulars.
Yeah, well, I think I sort of
erased their reservation.
I was never checked out
on this system.
Did I mention I had a confirmed
reservation? This is my receipt.
I downloaded it off the Internet myself.
- I know, Mrs. Taylor, calm down.
- Don't say that. No...
- Calm down?
- She told me to calm down.
Don't tell us to calm down.
We've been very calm right up until now.
- I'm so sorry. Lisa?
- Cynthia, tell them one more minute,
- they'll be happy, you promise.
- One more minute. You'll be happy.
- I promise.
- We better be.
Now, enter my PIN.
It's 7-8-8... Hang on.
- Dad? Hold on.
- Lisa?
- Can you hold on?
- Sure.
OK, it's 7-8-8-4-underscore-L-Reisert.
- Lisa, I'm so sorry for calling.
- No, no, no, it's fine, it's fine.
- Are you logged in yet?
- What do I do?
Click on the Crisis folder,
you'll see a list of empty rooms,
give 'em fourth-floor,
comp 'em for tonight and tomorrow.
OK, just a sec. OK, you are all set.
The first two nights
are gonna be on us.
And if you need anything else,
just let me know.
We won't.
This is not my fault.
God, they totally threw me.
They were such assholes.
There are no assholes.
Only guests with special needs.
- Here we are.
- Keep it. Anything else?
The Simpsons didn't get
the California King they requested.
What else?
- Oh, my God.
- Tell me.
Security left a message
saying the Charles Keefe party
will be arriving
at 5:30am instead of pm.
That's not that unusual.
It's a security thing.
Make sure our guys have the entrance
set, his security takes it from there.
Is Mr. Keefe Platinum Club
or something or?
Political. Homeland Security.
Make sure there's a box
of Montecristo Cubans in the room
and a bottle of Cristal on ice.
It's 3825.
- OK. Got it covered. Safe flight.
- Thanks.
Attention passengers
leaving on flight 1387.
- Lisa Reisert.
- I'm still here.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
- It's fine, sweetie.
- What's up?
Gearin' up for another sleepless night
with a comedy marathon.
Before I forget,
that book I gave you,
you finish it yet?
Almost.
You know, he's from Texas.
I didn't think shrinks came from there.
Yeah, they do. They just move
to California and start TV shows.
- How's the remodeling?
- Good. Good.
They made headway
in the last few days.
I lost my wallet, but that's par
for the course. It's lookin' good.
That's good.
I can't wait to see it.
You should. The upstairs hallway
is totally unrecognizable.
- Your room hasn't been touched.
- No, Dad.
Please, go nuts, make it
into a gym or a putting green.
You know I can't do that.
You never know when you might just
wanna spend a few nights back here.
You know? Make an escape
from the day-to-day.
Day-to-day, it's where I thrive.
You know that.
Right.
So,
- how's your mom holdin' up?
- As good as can be expected.
You? What about you?
You all right?
- Yep, I'm fine.
- You sure?
Everything's fine, Dad. You're gonna
have to start takin' my word for it.
Look, I gotta go. I gotta check in.
You sure you don't need a pickup?
- I thought you lost your wallet.
- Leese, it's just five minutes.
I'm taking the red-eye.
It's the last flight.
It's gonna be late.
I love you. I'll call you.
- I love you too, sweetie.
- OK, bye.
Attention. We have a cancellation
update. Flight 1192 has been canceled.
Anybody who was on the flight
to Atlanta that was canceled,
come to the front of the line
so we can reroute you.
Flight 1019 to Miami...
- I'm sorry.
- Don't sweat it.
I'm wearing my combat boots.
- Excuse me?
- Travel is war these days.
Yeah.
I just love him.
How is that? Are you learning a lot?
I'm not really sure.
He's so handsome.
I work during the day
so I always miss his shows.
Flight 247 to Cleveland
has been delayed.
- Here. That'll catch you up.
- Oh, no. No, no, I... I couldn't.
I'm finished. My Dad's given me so
many, I could start a library. Please.
- That's very nice of you.
- Once again anyone who is scheduled
on the flight to Atlanta, if you
wanna get out of Dallas tonight,
come to the front
of the line at this time.
Excuse me.
You're letting them go,
but we've been standing
for an hour? How does that happen?
If we don't re-book,
they miss their flight.
It doesn't matter that you
canceled my flight then rerouted?
- I understand.
- Get your boss. This is ridiculous!
Don't make her do that.
She's doing the best she can.
I don't think I was talking to you
- I realize that...
- I'm trying...
Please, sir.
She is the one standing
between us getting out and anarchy.
- Yeah, but she's not the one in...
- She's exhausted, worked 18 hours,
and she suspects we all hate her
just as much as you do.
What do you say we give her a break?
Let her get back to a job
I'm guessing is a lot
more thankless than yours.
This airline sucks.
Next in line, please.
That's me.
Here.
Thank you very much.
And thank you.
You're welcome.
Yeah. Thank you.
Not at all.
That was just backup.
- You got the ball rolling.
- Yeah.
- Reflex, I guess.
- Why is that?
I work in a hotel. I deal
with people like that all the time.
The Marriott? The Hilton?
- The Lux Atlantic It's in...
- Miami.
- Right. I know it well.
- Yeah.
- So you're on this...
- Very delayed flight to Miami. Yeah.
- You?
- Yeah. Sadly, yeah.
But you know what? That's
why God created the Tex-Mex.
The best nachos in the airport
and right across from our gate.
Good tip. Thanks.
Save you a seat.
Yeah, that was... I thought
since we're on the same flight...
I didn't mean to invade
your personal space or...
- No.
- I can take you over here.
- I just... I have a few calls to make.
- Sure. I understand. You go ahead.
- Have a good flight.
- OK. You too.
We will be updating you
with the departure time
of flight 1019
with service to Miami...
- Hi.
- Hi. You must be Rebecca.
- Yes.
- Well, my name's Mary,
and I hear this is the first time
you're flying by yourself.
Well, you must be very brave.
- Are you gonna be OK?
- Yes, Mom.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- I'm just asking.
- I'm 11, not nine.
Come with me, you two.
There you go, sir.
Your nachos. Careful, hot plate.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, my God! I am so sorry.
- It's iced. Don't worry.
- OK.
- Let me find you napkins.
- No, no, no. It's fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
OK. Larry,
could you run back to Starbucks?
I need another mocha.
- Finish that one already?
- Someone's wearin' it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention.
Flight number 17 leaving Dallas
National Airport from gate two
will be delayed for 20 minutes.
Paging a skycap with
electric cart to gate four.
- Hi.
- Is this taken?
- No, it's all yours.
Thanks.
So did you get your calls made?
Yep. No more calls.
Good. What will you have?
- No, it's... I'm OK.
- If I can guess...
OK.
I'm feeling vodka.
Definitely sweetened.
Cosmo. Way too common.
Screwdriver.
No. No. No. Way too boring.
So that leaves me with the
simplicity of the grapefruit
or the complexity of the pineapple.
Grapefruit sea breeze.
- Could I have a bay breeze?
- You got it.
Thanks.
It's an impressive talent, though.
Very close.
- You know, breaks the ice.
- Yeah.
- So are you headed home?
- Yeah. Trying.
Yeah. Flying's so
much fun these days.
Fun for me is just getting off
that plane in one piece.
- Fear of flying?
- Yeah. Just a little.
Were you in Texas
on hotel business?
No. My grandmother died.
It's OK. She was 91.
- Ninety-one.
- Yeah.
That's respectable.
What was her secret?
Grape-Nuts. And a guy named Duke.
Excuse me?
Yeah, she said the Grape-Nuts
kept her arteries clean
and Duke helped with the rest.
Wow. A dynamic woman.
Nothing fazed her, you know?
She was so optimistic.
"Always look forward."
That's what she'd say
- There ya go.
- Thanks.
...heightened security
measures are now in place.
- That taste OK?
- It's fine.
You sure? 'Cause we can
always get you that sea breeze.
You sound like my dad.
I say I'm fine,
he says, "Are you sure?" I'm sure.
- OK, I believe you.
- Good.
- The name's Jackson, by the way.
- Lisa.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Is it Jack for short?
No, I haven't gone by Jack
since I was ten years old.
Last name's Rippner.
Jack Rippner.
Jack... the...
- There you go.
- OK.
- That wasn't very nice of your parents.
- No.
That's what I told 'em
before I killed 'em.
What?
Well, if it's any comfort,
my middle name's Henrietta.
Henrietta.
But that's my
grandma's name, though.
Was.
Well, here's to Henrietta,
whose spirit is very much alive.
What?
I'm tellin' you, man,
she was tasty.
And now let's go
to Washington for an update.
As the war on terrorism escalates,
Deputy Secretary of Homeland Security
Charles Keefe embarks on a seven-day
tour of Southern port cities,
starting tomorrow. You may
recall that four months ago,
Keefe sent shockwaves through
the department after he made remarks
during his first press conference.
I don't discriminate, I communicate.
Just not always with a kind word.
Now, don't get me wrong,
I believe in diplomacy.
It can work. But first
you have to have their attention.
Do I have your attention?
Thank you. Thank you very much.
We're cleared for the boarding of
flight 1019, service to Miami, Florida.
- I guess that's us.
- Wonders never cease.
Yeah.
- Let me get this.
- Oh, no. No. Please.
I got it. I got it.
- Yeah. Keep the change.
- Thanks.
- Welcome.
Well...
Report unattended baggage
- to airport security. Thank you.
- Can you hang on? I'm sorry.
Hello? Yeah.
Can you just hold on?
I gotta take this.
- I'm sorry.
- That's OK.
- Nice to meet you.
- Have a good flight. Bye-bye.
- You too.
Bye.
Hey. Yeah, looks like
we're gettin' outta here.
The storm's moved on.
No, there's time.
- Thank you for your patience, sir.
- Yeah, right.
Come on, we gotta move it, bro.
Come on.
- You made it, boys.
- Yeah. Just barely.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Here we go.
- Thank you. Enjoy.
- Thanks.
There you go.
Thanks for your patience.
5-A is to your right.
Enjoy your flight. Hello.
- Hi.
- 18-G. Down the aisle to your left.
- Thank you.
- Thanks for your patience.
- How are you?
- Better now.
- Sorry for the delay.
- 21-F.
- 21-F is right down...
- Yeah. Thank you.
Hi, how are you?
We're going to dim the lighting
for tonight's flight. Lights can be
activated by the button on your armrest.
Once we've reached cruising altitude
and the captain turns off
the fasten seat belt sign,
we will be offering our beverage service
with complimentary soft drinks,
juice and coffee.
- I'll help.
- Cocktails available for a charge.
Thank you
Hi.
Again.
- I figured you'd be in first class.
- No, not me.
- I'm all coach, all the time.
- Me too.
Yeah. I think that's my seat.
- What, you're not sitting here.
- Well, I don't know.
- That says 18-G?
- You're kidding.
You're not kidding.
You need a bellhop?
- No, no, no. That's OK.
- Let me help. I insist.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
- You sure? OK.
I'm not normally such a lightweight.
Those were strong bay breezes.
Well, I'm cutting you off anyways,
all right?
So... What are the odds?
Yeah, I know.
Wait a minute.
You're not stalking me, are you?
No.
- You got me.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, jeez.
- You all right?
If I say yes,
are you gonna ask me if I'm sure?
No. No. That's your dad's department.
Yeah, I'm fine. I...
Earlier today I had
some cheap wine at the funeral,
and combined with the cheap vodka...
- I see.
- I blame you for that part.
- Well, I feel terrible now.
- You should.
Oh, I do.
We know it's been a long night, so stow
your belongings and take your seats
as quickly as possible,
we'll be under way. Thank you.
- I think somebody needs a bellhop.
- Excuse me.
OK.
Let me.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Just when I thought there
weren't any gentlemen left.
You have a pleasant flight.
Oh, my.
I'm already in chapter two.
Great.
I gave her this book earlier.
She's a huge Dr. Phil fan.
I saw that. Very nice of you.
Well, that's me.
People-pleaser, 24-7.
- Well, you are popular.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's OK. No.
- It isn't usually like this.
Go ahead.
Hey. What's up?
Yeah. No, it's OK.
So it's definitely happening?
5:30. OK, done deal.
Work. For the last time.
- Goodbye, Joe.
- Good flight.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
At this time we'd like
to ask that you discontinue
the use of any electronic devices,
pagers, cell phones, laptops,
anything with a switch
should now be in the off position.
The use of cell phones is not
allowed during the flight.
A list of devices suitable for use
can be found on the cover
- of your Fresh Air magazine.
- Flight attendants, please be seated.
From the deck, looks
like we're the red-eye to Miami.
Welcome.
The weather conditions may cause
a bumpy takeoff, but don't worry,
we'll soon climb above it.
We'll see if we can't
make up lost time.
We're number one for departure.
Flight attendants, secure the cabin.
Ladies and gentlemen, we've been cleared
for takeoff. Please enjoy your flight.
- We're not gonna make it.
- Shut up.
We're not gonna make it.
Shut up. I will punch
you in your face. Shut up.
Just kidding. Come on.
Are we there yet?
So was Henrietta your
mom's mom or your dad's mom?
My mom's. My dad's...
My dad's died a long time ago.
Are your folks still together?
They divorced three years ago,
married for 32.
That's a shame.
So your mom...
Mom moved back to Texas
and Dad stayed in Miami.
I see. And does Dad still work?
Yeah. No! He's recently retired.
He's got a lot of time on his hands
so he makes phone calls.
OK. He's filling
all his work time with...
Worry time.
Does he have reason
to worry about you?
Well, even if he does, I mean,
he's just gotta get used
to the fact that life changes
and sometimes things happen.
I know what you mean.
Usually when things are going perfectly,
you're back on track,
everything's going to plan,
and then one day, outta nowhere,
somebody forgets to bolt
the engine to the wing.
Yeah.
This is your captain. We're through
the worst of it, so you can relax.
Keep your seat belt
fastened while seated,
as we may hit more turbulence.
Thank you.
- Thanks for distracting me.
- Well, it's not really what I'm doing.
What are you doing?
Just keeping the focus
on you and your father.
Why?
Part of my job.
Are you a shrink?
No. Manager.
- Better not say of a hotel.
- No.
- That would...
- Cause you to buy a self-help book.
So, what do you do?
Government overthrows, flashy
high-profile assassinations. The usual.
- You're a spy. I should've known.
- No, I'm not a spy.
- A hit man.
- I'm a lousy shot.
Right. You work for the CIA.
Well, if I did,
I couldn't say, could I?
- But, no.
- The Mafia?
The money's shit.
OK, well, that's kinda weird.
- Why don't you tell me what you do?
- I did.
OK. OK, I'm sorry, I...
It's... Whatever you do,
that's your own business.
Just as long as you're not...
What?
Hijacking the plane.
No. No, I'm not suicidal.
That's good.
You're right.
Most days it is my own business.
But right now, as fate would have it,
my business is all about you.
- I'm sorry, about me?
- That's right.
OK, I'm not sure
where you're going with this.
Charles Keefe. One of your
regular VIPs. Ring a bell?
- No, should it?
- Yes, it should.
He's on his way to your hotel
and that's why you need to listen.
No. No, I don't think...
- I don't have to do that.
- Yes, you do,
if you want your dad to live.
- What did you say?
- You heard me.
Yeah.
Suit yourself. You might
wanna take a look at this.
JR. Joe Reisert.
Your father? Yes?
- Where did you get that?
- I didn't get it.
My associate grabbed it
off your dad's desk.
Apparently next to
your graduation picture.
JR. Definitely Dad's wallet.
His initials. But gee, mine too.
Jack Rippner. Credit card, license.
"For some reason,
Miss Stewardess, this unstable,
inebriated girl,
whom I've never met before tonight,
suddenly went crazy
when I took it out of my pocket."
You tell the flight attendant
and your dad dies.
Sit down.
You might wanna buckle up.
- Any luck?
- Our pensions go, then our coffeepots.
18-G's flashing.
Do you want me to?
I'll take care of it. She
probably just wants another drink.
Maybe I'll join her.
- Hi.
- What can I do for ya?
- Leese,
did you need another
pillow or anything?
No, I don't need anything.
She's just had a really rough day.
A death in the family.
- I'm so sorry.
- Yeah.
- I'll get you water and some tissues.
- Thanks.
- Be right back.
- Thank you.
That was great, Leese.
Keep doing the right thing.
Just bottle the emotions
a little more, OK?
Have you done something to my father?
No. And it'll stay that way
as long as you keep playing along.
What do you want from me?
Now, I wanna wait
for your Kleenex and water.
And once we have our privacy,
we can get back to business.
- Here you go.
- Thank you so much.
- Sure. Feel better, hon.
- Thank you.
I need you to call your hotel.
It's very simple.
Just use your managerial pull
to move Keefe
from 3825 to suite 4080.
I'll leave the details to you.
You just sell it.
You've got the wrong person.
I don't have the authority to do that.
Well, I happen to know that you do.
You're the only voice
that can get this done
by the time I need it done.
- You need me to write it down?
- No.
Well, then what's the delay?
So by changing Keefe's room,
does that make it easier?
Lisa, whatever female-driven,
emotion-based dilemma
you're dealing with right now,
you have my sympathy.
But for the sake
of time and sanity,
let's break this down into a little
male-driven, fact-based logic.
One simple phone call
saves your dad's life.
And it has to be made soon.
You're gonna kill Keefe,
aren't you?
You really need to start worrying
more about your dad, Leese.
How am I supposed to know if he's OK?
How do I know you haven't hurt him?
- He's fine.
- Why am I supposed to believe?
The last call I got said he was sitting
in the TV room eating leftover lasagna
and watching the comedy marathon.
Relax, Leese. By now my guy is
probably back in his silver Beemer,
parked outside
9321 Blossom Palms Lane.
He's sitting in the dark,
listening to a little smooth jazz,
while he sharpens
his 12-inch KA-BAR.
That's a knife, Leese.
- I wanna talk to my dad.
- Sure. After you make the call.
No. I wanna know he's OK right now
or I don't call anybody.
Your dime.
Credit card?
Ladies and gentlemen, the captain has
turned off the fasten seat belt sign.
You're free to move about the cabin.
Stay tuned for more of the comedy
marathon following these messages.
I'm comin', I'm comin'!
God.
- Hello?
- Dad?
Leese? Are you already home?
No, I'm on the air phone on the plane.
We were late taking off and...
Honey, I know you don't like it
when I ask, but are you all right?
You sound upset.
Leese?
Leese? Are you still there?
Did he sound healthy to you?
I hope that's a yes,
because that's the best I can do.
Now let's get this over with.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Can you help me again?
Last time, I promise.
Sure.
Don't get cute.
- You're so sweet.
- Hello, again.
You know, I didn't think that
this book would be so much work.
There's all these surveys about yourself
before you can go on to the rest...
Could you wait one second?
- Sure.
- My nails.
Know what? Don't worry
about the surveys. I'll just...
- I'll just highlight my favorite part.
- Wonderful.
- Got it.
- Great.
- You are a lifesaver.
- Yep.
Would you gimme your address too?
I wanna return the favor.
I'm always breaking
my nails on these things.
I'm gonna need you
to help me put it back up.
- Clear the aisle.
- We're on a collision course.
- I'll come back for that later.
- No. Here you go.
- Last time?
- Thank you.
OK.
- Sorry I'm... I'm blocking your seat.
- Not at all.
- Excuse us, ma'am.
- I'm going.
Thank you.
They're much pushier these days.
I didn't want this
to get complicated.
I have to assume
she's gonna read that.
Read what?
- How's she doin'?
- Much better. Thank you.
- Good.
- Thanks.
Pillow?
Would you like a blanket?
Pillow? Pillow?
Please return to your seats. Thank you.
"I want you to get
excited about your life.
But you gotta get real.
I'm challenging you, starting now,
to stop dealing
in opinions and assumptions
and start dealing in facts.
Fact: Fearing to act is human.
Failing to act
is just plain dumb.
Fact: Thinking when
you should be acting
will only make your head hurt."
I'm not makin' this up, Leese.
It's right here.
Fact:
You've been out
for a half an hour
and Keefe's room still
hasn't been changed.
So I got you some aspirin.
I need you coherent, Leese.
Well, we were hoping
things would calm down,
but that's not happening. So control's
just cleared us up to 35,000 feet.
Let's see if we can't get above
this weather, smooth things out.
Now, let's do this.
If I do it, if I make that call,
do you promise you'll tell who's
outside my dad's house to go away?
You call, I call,
Dad wakes up, puts on coffee,
never suspects a thing,
you go back to work, life goes on.
I am now calling your hotel.
I don't have to tell you
to sound convincing.
- You've said enough.
- Good.
Good morning,
Lux Atlantic Resort, this is Cynthia.
Hello? Hello?
Cynthia, it's Lisa.
Lisa? You sound terrible.
Are you OK?
There's just... There's
a lot of turbulence on the plane.
- You're still on the plane?
- Yeah.
I heard flights are delayed.
You'd be so proud of me.
We're all set for Keefe.
Cristal on ice, the cigars,
not easy to find this time of night.
You know, about that. I'm gonna
need you to do me a favor, OK?
You sure you're OK?
Please do not
ask me again if I'm OK.
I hope you're...
Look, something's come up.
We gotta change Keefe's room.
Can you pull up the file?
We're gonna move him
to room 4080. Right.
The PIN is 4882.
- I'm gonna need you to take...
- Gimme that.
Hello? Cynthia?
Pretty clear thinking,
given the circumstances.
Let me guess,
stress management courses?
They're really paying off. We get
outta this, I may have to steal you.
- Excuse me, miss.
- Yes?
- Are the phones not working?
- They cut out during storms.
They'll come back
when we find clear air.
- Great. Thank you.
- You don't have a backup plan?
- Why are you doing this here?
- Blame your grandmother.
She keeled over,
you hopped on the next flight,
- Keefe changed plans, here we are.
- Excuse me. Peanuts or pretzels?
- Peanuts, thank you.
- Ma'am?
No.
So, what happens
if they don't start working?
You bury your dad
in a closed casket.
Well, gang, brace yourselves,
'cause I have news. I'm engaged!
I know him.
- Know who?
- Keefe.
He's a really decent man.
Well, sometimes bad things
happen to good people.
Like you.
You know, I've known you
for a while now, Lisa.
Before tonight, I mean.
And far as I can tell,
your life revolves around your job.
The occasional cocktail
at the corner cafe,
the classic late-night movies.
And scrambled eggs at 3am.
What turned you into such a loner?
Was it your parents' divorce?
Wait, did someone break your heart?
The captain has turned off
the fasten seat belt sign.
- I have to go to the restroom.
- You're free to move about the cabin.
Best I can do.
OK, you know what? You got me.
I'm gonna make that call
when I can make the call.
But right now you gotta let me go.
I need to go.
OK. I trust you.
And I need my purse.
But not that much.
I was really nervous
there for a minute.
We just kept goin' in and out.
Excuse me.
You in line?
Yeah. Do you wanna?
You were here first.
Excuse me.
Oh, God.
OK. Get up.
I was wondering...
Don't fight me.
You're all worked up
from being so creative. Breathe.
Hey, Rebecca.
You can’t just run off like that.
A man went in there.
Everyone shares. I'll take you
to the one close to your seat.
But a lady's in there too.
OK, one of those flights.
Here, come on.
Please, just stop whoever's
at my dad's house.
I already have, by twice
intercepting these little communiqués.
If they'd have fallen into
the hands of a stewardess,
she'd have gone to the cockpit
and we'd land somewhere else.
If that happens, Leese,
our guy in the BMW's
gonna know about it.
So do Dad a favor
and stop gambling with his life.
You don't have to do this.
Any of this.
Someone do that to you?
No.
Is that what it is?
You know what I think?
I think you're not
such an honest person.
Because I've followed you
for eight weeks now
and I never once
saw you order anything
but a fucking sea breeze.
I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
I never lied to you, Leese.
Know why?
'Cause it doesn't serve me.
We're both professional.
We have the will and the means
to follow through.
'Cause when we don't,
our customers aren't happy.
And when they're not,
we suffer and our lives go to shit.
And that's not going to happen.
Is it?
- No.
- Good.
Because I'm gonna tell you
the phones are working again.
Are you sure we
got a deal this time?
Yes.
Peachy.
Well, thanks for the quickie.
Good.
Come on.
Excuse me.
This isn't a motel.
Sure.
- Lose something?
- Yes, my book.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org