SUJAIDR
They told me you are the man.
They said that this guy
can move anything.
(FUNK MUSIC PLAYING)
They said that?
Yeah.
I am the man.
USA passport.
The most valuable piece of paper
in the world and we
make it our own.
That shit's artisanal.
I'll be the judge of that.
Not bad.
What about Omar?
The friendly ghost?
He ain't gonna cut your
head off for this?
I know he owns the city.
Omar signed off personally.
(LAUGHING)
I don't know who you think you're
bullshitting, but it ain't me.
(GUNS COCKING)
Calling me a liar?
With guns on your face?
You crazy you don't trust me.
Let me explain something to you.
There's not a lot in
this world that I love,
but the shit that I love,
I don't trust with nobody.
I'll buy 50 now
and 500 after Omar
looks me in my eye
and lets me know he's not going
to kill me over this deal.
Is that something you can arrange?
Or is it more bullshit?
You're crazy, bro.
Yeah, I am crazy,
but in a good way.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(SPEAKING SERBIAN)
Shit!
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
Everybody down! Atlanta PD!
There!
Shit!
(GRUNTING)
Freeze!
Freeze! I said freeze!
Atlanta PD!
Get down!
See you, bitches!
JAMES: Freeze!
(GROANS)
Atlanta PD! Get me another car!
A Prius? Get this
bullshit out of here!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Damn!
Valet. Get out.
Get out! Yeah!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Asshole!
Move, trick!
(HORN HONKING)
Get out the way!
Here we go.
Hey!
(LAUGHING)
Whoo!
Oh, shit!
How you like me now?
Stop! Stop!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Oh, shit!
Yeah, baby!
I got you.
Yeah!
(LAUGHING)
I tried to be nice.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
You thought I was crazy?
No, baby, I'm nuts.
MALE GAMER: Does anybody have
a twenty on Black Hammer?
All right, let's get these bitches!
BEN: The target's on the
second floor. Let's switch it up.
Assface, me and you,
we'll go around back.
ASSFACE23: Copy that.
Watch your friendly fire.
Hey! Guys, remember,
if they throw a grenade,
you got five seconds to pick
it up and throw it back.
MALE GAMER: Frag out.
This is not a game,
gentlemen, this is real.
- Be on your toes at all times.
- ASSFACE23: Copy that.
How's my king this morning?
Good. I'm fine, babe.
Wasting his royal talents
in the kingdom, I see.
ASSFACE23: Bogies at nine. Bogies at nine.
I don't know if you're being
sarcastic, but I'm not.
Right now I'm on a black bag op.
Kick move!
- Can we talk?
- Babe, in a second.
- ASSFACE23: Did you call me "babe"?
- I didn't call you "babe."
Shut up, Assface.
I'm talking to my lady.
Do what you're supposed to do.
Get eyes on that sniper.
Does anybody have
eyes on the sniper?
Ben, let's go.
This is not the time.
Stop. Ang, don't start.
Oh, I'm sorry, guys, the
real world needs Ben. Bye.
Stop playing.
Give me the joystick.
Give me it back. Look at
what you're doing right now.
Stop. Seriously. Move
me out of the thing.
Put me in a bunker.
You going to get me...
Wow. Stop! Hey. Oh!
MALE GAMER: Not again, Ben.
No! No!
- ASSFACE23: That really hurts.
- Oh! Oh!
MALE GAMER: Hi, Angela.
Even soldiers have to
get to work on time.
You're pro-Taliban. You are.
Stop.
I'm sorry, guys. I had a black
bird in the living room.
I didn't hear it chirp.
It's not fair. Here's the thing,
you have to understand
how easy it is for me
to get caught up into that world.
I feel like I had been fighting in
Pakistan for the last eight hours.
Okay, first of all,
"Black Hammer"?
Speaking.
What is that about?
That's about when I pull my penis
out and it hits the ground.
Kaboom. Boom!
(LAUGHING)
What are you laughing for?
You do know that you're going
to be Mrs. Black Hammer.
The words every
girl wants to hear.
It better be.
Mmm. And when exactly is
this Black Hammer wedding?
- Soon. Very, very soon.
- Mmm-hmm.
Things are getting close to where
I want them to be.
I'm figuring it out.
- Can you make me one? (SNIFFS) Mmm.
- Sure.
So, is this about
you becoming a cop?
Yes, it is.
I got it all figured out.
Here's what's going to happen.
I'm going to get into
the police academy.
After that I'm going
to be on patrol.
to be a detective.
After being a detective, I'm
going to be a lieutenant.
That's how it happens.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
You know that I love you with
or without the academy, right?
I understand that,
but this is different.
I got such a good feeling, babe.
I did everything right.
Did you tell my brother
that you signed up?
I'm going to be honest,
and don't get mad at me,
but I'm going to say
what I want to say.
Here's how I feel when it
comes to your brother.
First of all, I've reached out,
but I know that your brother is
ignoring me because of that incident.
The barbeque incident was a first-degree
burn, not a third-degree burn.
I've gotten past it, okay.
He doesn't have to know.
I don't see why it's important.
Seriously, Ben, if I'm ever
going to be Mrs. Hammer...
Black Hammer. Black Hammer.
Hammer. Got it.
I need him to be on board.
You two are the most
important men in my life.
What you just said
has been received.
I will check in.
Give me a kiss.
Done. You know what we're
doing tonight, right?
- Mmm... Yes.
- What?
- Dinner. Yeah.
- Dinner at Dominick's.
A romantic dinner followed by
some sweet, sweet lovemaking,
dirty style.
That's right. Dirty style.
Dirty style? What is that move?
It's the move that Rihanna
does in that video.
(LAUGHS)
I don't think that's it.
This is it. It's very sexy.
- Is it?
- Yes.
I actually saw it in
a Kama Sutra book.
They call it the "Lathered Lotus."
After I'm done doing that, I'm
going to give you the Kawasaki.
(IMITATES MOTORCYCLE REVVING)
I don't understand what that is.
That's starting that bike up.
After that, what do
you think comes last?
- Ah, let me guess.
- What?
Black Hammer.
That's right. Kaboom. Boom!
ASSFACE23: Uh, dude, turn
your mic off. This is awkward.
MALE GAMER: Is that why you
call yourself Black Hammer?
I thought it had something to
do with Thor from Avengers.
No. Ben.
Why didn't you turn the game off?
You didn't turn the game off.
Congratulations.
They know we have a nasty household.
Is that what you want?
- Because of you.
- Whatever.
BROOKS: A car chase? Come on.
I authorized this operation
with very clear guidelines.
Instead, you shoot up a mall full of
civilians like it's a damn video game.
And for what? Fake passports?
Thinking those would
lead us to Omar.
Of course you were.
Do you know how many man
hours we spent on this case?
And in two and a half
years you've had
no breaks, so enough of this shit.
Your obsession aside,
there's no criminal,
nobody you get to use as an excuse
for ignoring the
rules of engagement.
- Lieutenant, this was a special...
- Nobody!
And especially not
for some lowlife
nobody's ever even seen before!
We know what he looked
like when he was nine.
BROOKS: Shut up, Miggs.
Look, these Serbs are dealing
more than just passports.
The fact that they're still alive lets
me know they got something Omar wants.
Which was going to
lead us right to him.
Well, this Marko guy's already
lawyered up and he's refusing to talk
except to claim entrapment.
Entrapment? How about
attempted murder?
Asshole tried to kill me.
Oh, you little pussy.
Someday somebody's going
to shoot you in the face
and that vest isn't
gonna do you any good.
The lawyer's already
claiming self-defense.
Says you guys fired
the first shots.
(LAUGHS) Self-defense? With all
due respect, that's bullshit.
I'm shortening your leash, James.
We all want Omar, but these
guys are a waste of time.
That's all. Get out, all of you.
SANTIAGO: Hey, James, how about
next time that you don't
tell me that this is about Omar,
you tell me, huh?
I don't want you to start
worrying, Santiago.
Worry? What are you, my mother?
Come on, James.
You go into a back
room, out of contact,
you come out with three armed
guys and a motorcycle.
You don't want me to worry?
That is need-to-know information.
We're going in there with no
backup, I want to be scared, man.
I want to be so terrified, I'm letting
out little involuntary shits. Okay?
Who put this together?
Me. All right? Follow my lead.
I'm the brains, you the brawns.
The "bronze"?
Yeah, it's the plural of brawn.
I know.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
BEN: Since when do you need
the brother's permission?
He is her only living
relative, I get that.
Her dad was a cop.
He got killed on the job.
Oh, that's terrible.
I'm not taking anything
away from that.
But why do I have to
suck up to the brother
just because she wants
us to get along?
It would be easier, but he's still
upset because I set him on fire.
- What?
- Here's the thing.
Doggone propane knob. What I did...
(STUDENTS SHOUTING)
Hold on. Hold on.
What did I tell you?
Get down! Get down, boy!
Hey! Hey! You're white!
You're white!
You don't fight.
What's wrong with you?
BOY: Come on, bro, let's roll.
BEN: Hey, Ramon!
You're not going to do
this today. Watch out.
Kick move.
Hey, Ramon! Hey, hey, hey!
- Ramon!
- Man, it's the rent-a-cop.
I know you hear me.
What are you doing
with these guys?
BOY: Catch you later, Ramon.
Don't you got an
English test today?
You think they're going to let you
play basketball if
you fail that test?
I already speak English.
Okay. Well, go ahead.
You got it figured out.
Hey. Before you go, let's
play this out. Okay?
You go with them, you get drunk.
Now that you're drunk,
you can't play basketball.
How long before you drop out?
I give it a week.
So now you're a 17-year-old wino.
When you're a wino, you
do what winos do best.
You're going to jail. Once, twice.
Third time you get a hard judge.
Judge gives you two choices.
You got jail, you got the army.
Which one you going to take?
Army ain't so bad.
You're right, it's not.
Except you forgot about
one thing. War!
So now you're in Afghanistan.
You know what they got in
Afghanistan? Landmines!
Boom! You got no legs.
So now what happens?
You're right back here.
You're in the streets, but let's
remember, you got no diploma,
you got no feet, you got no job.
That means you're back
at the liquor store
getting drunk all damn day.
Now that you're drunk all day, you try
to steal because you don't have a job,
but your stealing ain't going
too good because you can't run.
You know why you can't run?
Because you got no feet!
Now you're stuck living
in a refrigerator box.
Here's the bad thing.
You're lonely,
you're in a gutter,
and you're legless.
Is that what you want, huh?
BOY: Come on, let's go!
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
I think I'm going to
go back inside now.
- You going to walk.
- Run.
- (LAUGHS) Okay. All right.
- Sprint.
Because if you didn't have
legs, you got to crawl.
All right, man, go ahead.
You're something else.
About the dumbest damn
kid in this school.
I can't do it. I ain't gonna
be everybody's mentor.
I don't get paid for that.
I've been waiting all
day to look at this.
I got in!
(LAUGHING EXCITEDLY)
I'm in the academy!
Freeze. Get down.
Freeze, you best put it down
because I'm about to make change.
I have to call James!
(ALARM BLARING ON CELL PHONE)
Jesus Christ!
Are you blowing up there, James?
I have to ditch this phone.
You can't stop Santiago's mom, man.
You can only hope to contain.
Hey, I know you're trying to insult
me, but it's just too true, bro.
No, it's that little clown
that's dating my sister.
About a chromosome away
from being a midget.
(LAUGHING)
I should have put a stop
to that a long time ago.
So why didn't you, bro?
I tried.
She loves his little ass. I don't
know what she sees in him.
MIGGS: Maybe he's just a super lover.
He's short but maybe when he takes
his pants off it's just like...
(GASPS)
"What is that?"
SANTIAGO: Just right for her. She loves it.
(MOANING IN SPANISH)
(WHINNYING)
(MOANING LOUDLY)
- What?
- That's disgusting.
Look, man, does she know
you think this guy is a jerk?
Have you told her that?
I have to come at a
different angle because
she's not gonna want
me in her business.
I have to ditch this dude.
Look, man, maybe this
guy is all right.
Maybe he just wants
into the family.
(SCOFFS)
I know exactly what he wants.
(BOTH MOANING)
I love you.
Baby, congratulations.
ANGELA: You know what I want to do to you?
- What do you want to do?
- Let's go upstairs.
- No. No.
- Yeah, yeah.
No, because if we go up there you
know what's going to happen.
- You'll want to brush your teeth.
- Mmm-hmm.
After that you're going
to wash your face.
Then you got to put cream
and stuff on your face.
Let's be spontaneous.
Let's do it right here.
- I want to be wild like a savage.
- Okay.
Give you that Kawasaki.
(IMITATES MOTORCYCLE REVVING)
I'm about to give it
to you right now.
- You know what I want?
- What you want?
I want that kaboom.
Girl, you're trying
to crawl down...
The Black Hammer.
- You want the hammer?
- I want the hammer.
Then go get the hammer.
Okay. Enough of that nastiness.
Oh, my God!
(SCREAMS)
Babe, call 911! Now!
Get out of my house,
you son of a bitch!
(GROANS)
JAMES: I can't believe this shit.
Angela, what if I was
a real intruder?
Instead of my brother
creeping around my house?
Wasn't nobody creeping.
You were sitting in the dark
with a coke and a hot dog.
If you'd lock the door
or close the window
or bar that patio like I told you.
This is exactly why I didn't let
you install the alarm system.
It's about who's going to
protect you. This weenie?
One, he is not a weenie!
(JAMES SCOFFS)
He can be weenie-ish,
weenie-like, but I love
him, so it doesn't matter.
I picture you with somebody
with a little more prestige.
Somebody who plays for the Falcons
or the Braves, or even the Hawks.
Braves. Yeah.
Not with the mascot.
James, listen to me,
you do not screw this up for me.
BEN: Hey, guys.
I can hear what you're saying.
So if you want to stop.
Damn, it's Sir Scream-a-Lot.
James...
I was responding to a
hostile situation, James.
I have no shame in that.
You call for backup when
there's a hostile situation.
That wasn't calling for backup.
That was a high-pitched scream,
and you pushed my
sister in the way.
I pushed your sister
out of harm's way.
You shined the light at us.
It's different strokes
for different folks.
Put the ice pack in his
mouth. No, on his head.
Don't put the ice pack
on my head, babe.
I'm sensitive to extreme measures
of cold and you know that.
Put it on your head,
because you just got
knocked out by yourself.
James, you know what? You...
Um...
Guys, maybe we should...
What?
Is he still staring?
Make him stop.
Look. We were in the middle of
something, so you have to go.
Y'all wasn't in the
middle of nothing.
We were, James.
- Let's go. Get out.
- I got my sandwich over here.
Listen. Listen, I'm going.
Bar that patio door.
ANGELA: I will. Thank you.
Promise. Love you.
Hey, James, wait up.
Hey, can you wait up, please?
Hey.
Look, man...
I know that you don't
really like me,
but I feel like you don't like
me because you don't know me.
Nope, you're wrong. I don't
like you because I do know you.
Well, I bet you'll like this.
I got accepted into the
police academy today.
I'm going to be a cop. I've been
trying to call you all day.
I'm finally going to have a career
that I can be proud of, man,
and Angela can be
proud of, and you.
Who knows, maybe we can
be partners or something.
(SPITS)
Okay.
Now that I got things
straight, I feel like
I can finally make your
sister an honest woman.
There's just one thing
standing in the way.
I was wondering if I could get your
blessing to ask Angela to marry me.
BEN: James?
Did you hear what I said?
I have to go.
Yeah, okay.
I figured that you
probably just got to
let everything sink in,
which is fine.
Maybe we could take a ride
later and talk about all this?
Oh, shit.
So, just because you
joined the academy,
that suddenly makes
you ready to propose?
Yes. I mean, no!
I've been ready.
Look, I figured that if
I made it through the academy
that you would be
forced to accept me.
Is that right?
I just want to show
you the real me.
I don't want to be known as
the guy who set you on fire.
In my defense, that was a mistake.
I tried to put you out.
I got water, but you panicked.
I don't even want
to dig into that.
That's getting off subject.
I want to talk to you...
Show and prove.
Show and what? What are you...
You want to marry my sister?
Show me you're worthy of her.
And prove to me you
got what it takes.
How do you want me to
do that? I don't get it.
Tomorrow, I'm going to
take you on a ride-along.
You can show me what kind
of man you're made of.
And prove to me
that you deserve somebody
as special as Angela.
- Hell, yeah.
- Mmm-hmm.
Thank you, man.
I cannot wait to show you that I'm
twice the man that you think I am.
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
All right. I'll see you then.
It's time to let go.
Hey, this is going to be great.
You will not regret this.
Mmm...
(SNIFFS)
Morning.
(GASPS)
James!
Didn't I tell you to
bar that patio door?
What are you doing, man?
It's 6:00 in the morning.
Good cops wake-up
before the crooks.
Get your ass up. Let's go.
Okay.
James, that's not cool!
All right.
I'm ready, man.
Boom.
You forgetting something?
Uh-uh. Forgetting what?
This could be the last time Angela
sees your little ass alive.
Don't you want to say goodbye?
No.
You can get shot today.
You know that, right?
Dead. You.
Ang?
Hey, babe?
Listen, James just
told me I could die.
ANGELA: No, you're not going to die.
If I do die, I want you
to know that I love you.
Yes, baby, I know.
If this was a latte,
it would be a love latte.
And you make me think of rainbows,
because we both love colors.
Aw.
And I love the way your hands open
up and close, like monkey paws.
Remember when we ate
that peanut butter?
You was like, "Put it on your
nose," and I was like, "No."
That's the day I fell
in love with you.
Give me a kiss.
- I want five of 'em in a row.
- Five?
BOTH: Mwah! Mwah! Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
BEN: Deal. Done.
ANGELA: Go, go, go.
Hey. I hope I don't die, because
I still got a lot more to say,
and I know we got to go, so...
All right, let's go. Kick move.
You didn't tell me you
had a car like this!
What's under the hood?
A 5.7 liter Hemi?
Look at these tires! Those
are 22-inch Z Pirellis.
That's a racing tire!
Are you driving it with the traction
control or the posi... Okay. Okay.
I need a minute with you.
Where's your team?
I got them sitting on a location.
Who's this?
Benjamin Barber. Prospective.
Prospective what?
I'm a pre-cadet at the academy.
I didn't realize
that was a category.
No, I got him from that
Boys & Girls Club.
I'm starting to do some
mentoring and shit.
I'm just surprised you let
anybody in the car with you.
I'm starting to take your advice.
Letting people into my life.
I may actually become the new
smiley face of the department.
- Have a seat.
- Cool. (CLEARS THROAT)
Not there. Right there.
Where you want me to sit at?
You didn't say anything first.
You're not doing no mentoring.
BROOKS: The other perp from the underground
is in the hospital.
He just came to.
Anybody question him?
Because I'm pretty sure he
knows what's going down.
Kind of hard for the guy to
talk with his jaw wired shut.
He'll live. Hey, Lieutenant...
I think you're wrong about
this Serbian connection.
You mean about leading to Omar?
The guy that no one's
ever seen before?
Lay off, James.
Lieutenant, you're going
to see me a lot...
You got a piece of
lint on your jacket.
I'm sorry. That was... I'm sorry.
What's up his ass?
(SCOFFS)
Here you go.
- What's this?
- It's a waiver.
Sign it.
You don't just sign stuff.
What does it say?
That states if you get
your face burnt off,
or you take rebar
through your chest,
or accidentally get poked
by a hep C needle,
or so stressed out that
you want to eat a bullet,
that states that you won't
bitch out and sue the city.
City don't need that. City broke.
Is this necessary?
- Are you going out with him?
- Yes.
Oh, it's necessary.
Stay there.
DISPATCH: Unit 220-C, start out
on Piedmont and Peachtree.
Unit 260 is out on a signal twelve.
Hey, Gina.
Give me all the 126s you
got today. Everything.
The crazier, the better.
Send it straight to me.
You want 126s?
Yep. The more annoying,
the better. Do it.
Hey, what are you doing
with my glasses?
I wanted to see what
it looked like.
- Put this on.
- What is this?
James!
You did not tell me I was
getting a jacket in the car.
Oh!
Whoa, whoa. What's
with the tightness?
It's a Dri-FIT compression shirt.
Keeps my body dry.
It wicks the moisture.
Put that jacket on,
don't take it off.
Okay.
I'm not. I'm not going
to sweat in it either.
This is going to keep
my body dry. Wicks it.
- Let's go.
- Wait. Let me put my gloves on.
- I knew I was going to need gloves.
You don't need those. Let's go.
Okay.
Wait. I got a jacket.
James! Guess what just happened.
BEN: This is it.
The real deal.
The hard, gritty streets.
I am so ready for this.
I'm serious, man. Bring it on.
- Be quiet.
- I'm sorry?
You talk too much.
Shut up.
Today is your Training Day.
BEN: Let me tell you
something about that movie.
That's motivation right there.
I'm about to show you what
these streets is all about.
What it takes to
be a cop out here.
Right.
But you have to follow my lead.
I need you to do everything I say
when I say, how I say,
and as fast as I say.
I don't want no lip,
no back-talk, no "Why?"
I just need you to jump
to it. You hear me?
Do you want me to
say something, or...
There's rules out here,
you know what I mean?
Don't touch no perps
unless you bringing them in.
There's no reason to
escalate any situation.
You stay cool, and if
you're outnumbered,
you always call for backup.
Always.
Not some ways.
All ways. Locked in.
You got one day, and one day
only, to show me what you got.
If you impress me,
I have a few good words to say to the
guy over at the academy about you.
Hey, James...
James, don't play with
me like that, man.
Hey, give me one.
You're not a fiver?
All right. Dude, yes.
All right.
So what are we working
on today? Omar?
How do you know about Omar?
I overheard you guys talking
about it at the station.
What's this Omar guy look like?
Does he have a scar
and everything?
Nobody knows what he looks like.
Not even his own crew.
That's his power. He killed
anybody who ever seen him.
DISPATCH: Unit 19, 126 in
progress, Delacey and Leeward.
Pub owner complaining about
bikes parked illegally.
Unit 19, copy.
This is it?
This is it.
Oh!
(INHALES)
It's about to happen.
Let me push the siren.
JAMES: No siren.
- This is the siren.
- It's not a siren.
What is that? What?
That was the trunk.
That's pretty stupid for us to go
chase bad guys with our trunk open.
It makes it look like we
don't know what we're doing.
Okay, here's the deal.
The owner of that pub
keeps complaining about
people parking in his handicapped
spaces, and loitering.
No, we don't play that.
So here's what I need you to do.
Go over there and simply
get them to move.
Okay. Uh...
Anything I need to know, though?
Like, are they into human
trafficking, dealing?
What's these guys' resume?
They're loitering. That's it.
No. Loitering today.
It's Gotham City tomorrow.
Scum like this need to be taken
down here and now, you know?
Okay, Mr. Here-and-Now.
Go make an example.
BEN: All right.
How do you want to do this?
You go around the front,
I go around the back?
Little good cop, bad cop action?
- Just you.
- I don't understand...
This is your chance to show me
what you're made of, all right?
You got to represent now.
This is not the high school quad.
Yes.
Don't go over there
talking to those lions
meowing like a pussycat.
What did that just mean?
You'll figure it out.
I don't think you can.
That was definitely weird.
It's like the same thing.
Okay, I'm just going to go.
I'm going to go.
(CLEARS THROAT)
BEN: Command and respect.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Some nice bikes you got here.
Harleys. I'm a Harley man myself.
You mind if I take a
look at this one?
(BEN WHOOPING)
That's nice.
Uh-oh.
Houston, we have a problem.
I can't help but notice that you don't
have an authorized handicap sticker
on your DMV-issued license plate.
Now, with that in mind,
sorry, but I'm gonna have to ask
you guys to get on your bikes
and leave this sector.
What is not being understood?
(BIKERS LAUGHING)
You done did it now.
You guys think you're tough
because you're in a little gang?
You want to know what
tough looks like, hmm?
I'm the definition of tough.
My mother was a stripper.
Her dance name was Asphalt.
Anybody else here been raised by a
woman who clapped her ass for money?
Dollars. You haven't?
Which means that you wouldn't
last a day in my world.
Let me tell you what's
going to happen.
I'm going to tell you what's going to
happen quick, fast and in a hurry.
You, you're gonna get some
Purell and some baby wipes,
you're going to
clean this shit up.
Do I make myself clear, mister?
Huh?
That's not a "mister,"
that's my wife.
I don't know what the
hell you've been
looking at, but I'm
looking at a damn man.
I'm looking at a...
That might be a woman.
There's a chance of that...
I don't care what it is!
I'm not going to argue with you
over the sex of this thing.
You guys are going to jail,
because I'm sick of doing this.
(MOTORCYCLE REVVING)
What's that? Who
turned on their bike?
Is that your bike?
Because I hear...
Who called them? Did you call them?
One of y'all paged them?
Okay.
We all good for later?
SANTIAGO: Yeah, it's all set.
James!
- What about that other thing?
- Oh, yeah.
A kid named Runflat might
have some intel on the Serbs.
- Runflat?
- Yeah.
That piece of shit.
I'm putting cases
on all you bitches.
You think you're going
to do this shit to me?
You'll be playing
basketball in Pelican Bay!
SHU program!
I'll go check it out.
Right. Catch you later, baby.
King Kong ain't got shit on me!
- Really?
- Oh, shit!
(GRUNTING)
I'm a lion. Get your hands off me.
Get your hands off me.
I said I'm a lion!
You like that back, huh?
JAMES: Hey, hey, hey.
Y'all don't want to do that.
Get off of me.
(EXCLAIMING IN RELIEF)
Jesus, thank you. Come on.
You didn't follow one rule.
I did follow rules.
I told you don't touch nobody.
BEN: It looked bad at the end,
but you have to admit that for a
second I had it under control.
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
- No, you didn't!
- James, that's...
You were so happy to see me
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
you damn near jumped in my lap.
Can you stop? It's Angela. Please.
I know who that is.
Hey, bouncy butt.
So, how's it going?
- Great.
- Horrible.
- Horrible!
Greatable.
Yeah, babe, let me
tell you something.
I'm cleaning up these
streets so good,
you'll be able to eat off of them.
Stop lying.
Babe, let me let you go, because
there's a lot of stuff around here
and you're breaking up.
I love you, though. Okay? Bye.
JAMES: Did you call my
sister "bouncy butt"?
BEN: You don't want to know.
All right, stay in the car.
Wait, what? I ain't staying in
no car. I'm going with you.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
- No, you ain't. (SCOFFS)
- I want to help.
I'm not staying in this car, man.
Cool. All right. I'll let you help.
Thank you.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm looking for a kid
by the name of Runflat
I need to talk to.
Runflat. Like a tire?
- Long story.
- Okay.
See that youngster over
there playing basketball?
Black shirt, striped pants?
BEN: Right there?
Yeah. That's his little brother.
All I need you to do
is go over there,
find out where Runflat is.
That's all I gotta do?
Think you can handle it?
Yes. And after this we're
taking off the training wheels.
I'm sick of this putt-putt shit.
All right, over.
I need y'all to get out of here.
Let's move.
Am I speaking French? Go!
Uh-uh. You stay.
What's up, little man?
"What's up, little man."
What are you talking about?
I'm not the little man. You are.
Hey, don't start this if you
don't want to finish it.
Start what? What, you
about 3'10 ", 3'11"?
Yeah, but you know what
I'm gonna do. Grow.
What you gonna do?
Stretch? You hope!
Understand something,
boy. I'm a man.
Whatever you say.
I'm an officer of the law.
She need to stop flirting, too.
Ronald. Talk to you.
Ball up.
(YELPS)
What happened, man?
- Where are you going, Ronald?
- Come on, man.
Ronald, why are you
walking away, Ronald?
Hey, that's my car!
Get your ass back. I'm using it.
Take your time. You got it.
- It's okay.
- Come on.
Why you walking off
from me, Ronald?
Don't call me that around here.
Call me Runflat, okay?
Don't call me by my
government name.
What you know about
that Serbian crew?
Screw them, man.
Coming over here
thinking they own shit.
How they tied into Omar?
Who?
Nigga, don't play with me.
You still got them pins in your...
(SCREAMS)
Come on. God!
Mamasay, mamasa, mamakusa! Oh!
Man, you're not a cop.
I've been empowered by a cop
to come over here and ask you about
the whereabouts of your brother.
Now give it up.
You think I'm gonna give up my
brother again? He just got out.
You're gonna give him up.
You came to the wrong place.
I ain't telling you nothing.
What you just did
was spit on my lip.
Yeah, I did.
That just got you a
little time in prison.
You're gonna tell me
what I need to know,
or it's gonna get real
ugly for you, Ronald.
I'm going to lock you up.
This is bullshit.
Bullshit is my middle name.
I got a real shaky
relationship with the truth.
What the hell you shaking for?
Did you take a swing at me?
You reached for my...
Going for my gun?
(SHOUTING IN PROTEST)
Now I got to defend myself.
No! Hold on, man.
I'll tell you what's up. Damn!
All right. All I know is this.
Serbs ran on Omar's
territory. He got mad, okay?
They trying to push something.
They got a shipment coming in.
That's all I know.
I'm about to make
a citizen's arrest.
I'll make a citizen's arrest, too.
For what?
Impersonating an officer.
What?
You said you were a cop.
That's illegal.
That is it, boy. This is what
I'm going to do time for.
You better give up your brother.
Give me your brother!
Stranger danger!
What?
Stranger danger! Stranger danger!
Man, let me fix you up.
I don't want to touch you there.
You want to see my what?
- I don't want to see yours.
- He's playing.
My mama says that's private.
That's my nephew.
He's trying to touch
all the little boys.
Get him!
Who got next? Who playing?
MAN: Let's see your badge!
You got next? What's up?
I'll be leaving here
in a few minutes.
Once this little midget
gets back in the car.
Start the car!
BOY: Run, shorty, run!
Open the door!
It's me! Open the door!
BOY: Go cry home to your mama.
- What took you so long?
- BEN: We should go.
Do the thing. Make the tires skirt!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
JAMES: How did that work
out for you back there?
BEN: Uh...
I think it would have worked out
a lot better if I had a gun.
So, you need a gun to
interrogate children?
It's about having confidence.
Me having a gun just gives me a
certain level of confidence.
Knowing that it's below my belt.
That's all I'm saying, man.
Have you ever even
held a gun before?
The PX-48R controller is
extremely realistic. Okay?
(LAUGHING)
What are you laughing at?
Are you talking
about a video game?
Yes.
Don't mention those stupid
video games to me, okay?
Don't say stupid. Don't
call my games stupid.
It is stupid.
In my world, do you know what
you would be considered?
- A newbie.
- A newbie?
A newbie. You have any idea
what level player I am?
No.
You have no idea.
My gamer tag is spoken in
hushed terms of awe and envy.
When I log on, people go crazy.
"Oh, my God! Black Hammer's in!
(WHISPERS) Black Hammer."
Shit's not real.
You would be lost in my world.
Black Hammer would not help you.
Let me show you my world,
all right? The real deal.
BEN: Why don't we just go
to the department range?
Because that's for cops only.
Which you are not.
Yet. Which I'm not yet.
- Hey, James.
- Hey, Val, how you doing?
Good. How's it going?
Pretty fair for a square.
Got to train a new booty today.
I'm new booty?
- I'm Val.
- How you doing? I'm Ben. New booty.
- Good to see you, Ben.
- You, too.
- They got everything you need here.
- Right. Right.
- But this the real deal.
- Mmm-hmm.
It's not a Xbox. No
video game controllers.
- Just real deal.
- Right.
Here's the handguns.
Val can hook you up.
Beretta, Glock, whatever.
I wish Assface was here.
Because he's more of a suppression
fire disciple, you know?
I'm glad Assface is not here.
Why would you say that? He should
be here. This is his world, too.
Uh...
I could choose whatever I want?
Knock yourself out.
All right. You said it.
No take-back-sies.
What do I want? What do I want...
Hurry up. You act like you're
looking for doughnuts.
- Why are you so impatient?
- I got shit to do.
- Give me a second.
- Let's go!
Fine, fine.
I want to get...
I don't want that one.
I want this one.
- I want to go with this one.
- Pick it.
Smith and Wesson 500.
Let me get that.
- All right.
- It's a good choice, ain't it?
500 Smith and Wesson.
You like that choice.
- You like it.
- Here you go.
Oh, ho, ho!
Bang, bang... Shit!
- Problem?
- Did you feel that? No, no problem...
Got it?
Can I do that thing?
Like how they do that...
You know what?
Can you do it?
Let's just go with the Glock.
All right.
That's a good choice, boy.
Don't touch me.
That's a tap. I didn't touch you.
There's a difference.
This is touching.
I didn't touch you.
There we go.
- Hey, what's this? Shit!
- Oh!
It's all right, I got it.
- You got it?
- Got it.
- You want me to help you set it up?
- No, Ben I got it.
Should we get a book?
(GUNS FIRING)
Let's see what you got.
Do we need goggles or earplugs
or anything like that?
No, usually the bad guys don't give
us time to put on that kind of stuff.
Okay, right. That's
actually a good point.
It makes a lot of sense, and
it's better to keep it real.
I would rather this be real.
You know what I mean?
- Keep it real.
- Yeah. Okay. (GRUNTS)
Here we go.
Freeze! How do you say freeze?
- Freeze.
Okay. You know what it is? You
don't move your top lip that much.
I move my top lip so it
doesn't come out stern.
You get what I'm saying?
(IN DEEP VOICE) Freeze.
Freeze.
- Just shoot.
- Shoot.
You pronounce everything.
I got you. You ready? Here we go.
Freeze! Atlanta PD!
Get on the ground!
Hands behind your head!
Fingers laced!
You better lace them! Lace them!
- Shoot the gun.
- Okay. All right.
Ready? Here we go.
Damn it!
I pinched it. I pinched
the inside of my hand.
I don't think the sight on
the gun is quite calibrated.
The way I was shooting,
it looks a little...
Yeah, it's off by a
centimeter or two.
You right-handed or left-handed?
You were doing both.
You're ambidextrous.
That's why I like shotguns. I'm
more of a shotgun specialist,
because I need both of my
hands, because my upper body...
Let me use your 12-gauge, man.
Be careful, it's got a
magnum loaded in it.
Oh, yeah. (LAUGHING)
Now we're talking. The street
sweeper. Just like Fallujah.
Just like Fallujah.
My nigga.
Denzel, Training Day.
You might want to step
back a little bit.
This thing got a little
kick to it. Okay?
Freeze! You better stop before
I put a hole in your back!
Oh, you think it's a game?
Oh, it's on now!
Oh, shit!
Got a little bit of kick to it.
My stomach in my ass.
Oh, yeah, you're ready
for the streets.
This gun should be banned.
I really appreciate everything.
No problem, man.
Well! How did it go?
BEN: (IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE)
It was good. It was real good.
(CLEARS THROAT) I'm just a
little rusty, that's all, Val.
A little more used to a
higher-grade military weapon
like an RPG or a flame thrower.
VAL: Yeah, we don't really
get the exotic stuff.
Though we did have a couple of
Zastavas in here the other day.
Let's go.
Wait a minute, you
had some Zastavas?
- Mmm-hmm.
- M92 or the M93?
I had the M92.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
I was going to ask you
about the Black Arrow.
That's what I thought
you was going to say.
We're talking about the
Serbian submachine guns.
The M92 is a good gun,
but that Black Arrow,
let me tell you something,
take your back off.
- Serbian?
- Serbian, yes.
How the hell you know
they were Serbian?
Uh, because I'm the Black Hammer.
Platinum level. I told you that.
X-Y-C-Y. You press at the same
time and it gives you a...
Who had these guns?
Two guys. One white, one black.
Serbian?
Um, I don't know.
One had an accent.
Let's go.
Serbians?
- One had an accent?
- Yeah.
If you could do it, what would it be?
(SPEAKS ACCENTED GIBBERISH)
What if you had the...
(SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
- Let's go.
- I'm trying to figure this...
BOTH: Let's go.
What was that about?
Wait for me in the car.
- I just got a clue, didn't I?
- In the car.
I just figured something out.
I'm gonna get in the car.
Can you at least turn the car on?
Radio or nothing.
What's up, boss?
JAMES: Listen, them Serbians,
they got something big going down.
I think they're selling
something to Omar.
I believe it's
military-grade weapons.
Damn, if Omar gets that kind
of firepower, holy shit!
It'll never happen.
Matter of fact, I want you to
find your boy at the Airport PD,
tell him to keep his
eyes open for anything
strange coming out
of Eastern Europe.
Did you listen to Brooks?
He doesn't
want us anywhere near
this Omar thing.
We just have to fall back, please.
Santiago, you sound like a rookie.
Let me do the thinking
for both of us, okay?
You hook that other thing up?
Yeah, it's all set.
You're going to be hearing
from dispatch any minute now.
Good. I need to get
rid of this clown.
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
Sorry.
- What are you doing?
- I'm sorry.
My fault. I didn't know.
I didn't expect that to happen.
Hey, I got a clue, didn't I?
No.
Yeah, I did. I got instincts.
You say what you want.
You know I do.
You think just because you
play a little punk video game,
that you're ready to be a cop
out here in these streets?
Yes, I do.
You're ready to go toe-to-toe with
the biggest kingpin in Atlanta?
Yes.
You understand this guy has
killed cops, innocent people,
even his own crew.
And still he's got everybody
thinking he's a ghost.
What's your little ass gonna
do when we run up on Omar?
What a cop is supposed to do.
Why am I telling you
what I would do?
How about we back up?
How about you tell me "thank
you." That could go a long way.
"Thank you, Ben."
"You helped me with a clue.
Good instincts."
DISPATCH ON RADIO:
Unit 19, 126 in progress...
Shut up. Shut up.
Corner of State and Bellevue.
Let me say "Copy." Let me say it.
Please. Come on. Let me say "Copy."
Some cop stuff.
Copy.
19, repeat that, please.
19, come again?
Hold up. Wait a minute. Copy...
- Give me that.
- Stop it, she can't hear me!
Give me a second, dude.
Get off, man!
Get off of it!
That's my wrist. Now
that's unnecessary.
Copy that.
Copy that for real this time.
The first one wasn't real.
19, please repeat.
BEN: You don't communicate,
because if you tell me say
"that," I will say "that."
JAMES: Man, shut up.
You bent my wrist.
CRAZY CODY: No! She took everything!
She took my boat!
CASHIER: He's down there and
he won't stop throwing stuff.
Poor bastard's at it again.
CRAZY CODY: She took my car!
JAMES: This dude, again.
I just want my life back.
Cody Tillman, AKA Crazy Cody.
- You know him?
- No.
Take that!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
JAMES: Hey, hey!
You better sit your ass down.
You stay right there,
I'm going in.
No, let me go in.
- You done. This one's mine.
- No.
- You stay there.
- No. I want to talk to you.
- No.
- Here I come.
- Stay! Stay!
- No! No!
I'm coming in hot.
Grab me, James, grab me!
Okay. Okay.
- What you doing over here?
- I want to talk to you.
- I want to go.
- You can't handle Crazy Cody.
Can I please have some
of Crazy Cody? Please!
I'm breaking every
rule possible for you.
- Please.
- Okay.
You get this right or I'm
taking your ass home.
- That's a deal.
- Go in there. This is a layup.
- Show and goddamn prove.
- Hey!
CUSTOMERS: Oh!
I didn't see that coming, James.
Stop it!
You're here throwing all
this produce and shit. Stop!
Listen to me, what you going to do
is get on the ground and put
your hands behind your head.
I ain't doing shit.
Handle this! Don't embarrass me.
- What am I doing?
- Do your job!
I'm not trying to do my job?
Do your job! Go!
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't you take...
Keep your clothes on!
They took everything else.
Might as well take my clothes.
Hey! Uh-uh. Uh-uh!
Get this situation under control.
Make him respect you.
- You better not pull it out.
- It's getting pulled out.
He's going to pull it out!
JAMES: Control the situation!
What am I supposed to do?
- Arrest that man.
- You want me to arrest that?
He got his penis out!
He is packing, though.
I got nothing.
What are you doing? Stop. Stop!
Ben, what are you waiting on?
He has some freak honey shit!
- What do you want me to do?
- Quit playing.
That's it. You're going to jail.
- Honey Boo Boo!
- Stop it. You're going to jail.
Come on. Do your job.
Ow!
That's police brutality!
Let the dude go.
His heart is broken.
Hold on. Hold on.
Ain't nobody hurting him.
(SCREAMING)
Finish this, man.
(YELPING)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Quit playing. What are you doing?
Eat this chip! Eat it, bitch!
(BOTH YELLING)
You failing.
I'm gonna make you my bitch.
You ain't gonna make me no bitch!
Come on, Ben.
You ain't going nowhere.
No! Get off me!
Ugh.
BEN: Yo, stop!
Get off. Get off of me!
- Oh, shit.
- BEN: Stop, man!
I can't breathe!
James, he's choking me.
It's not funny no more.
Drop the bottle!
Please don't do this.
Now you calm down!
Ben. You okay?
Stupid.
You Okay?
Book him on drunk and disorderly,
resisting and assault.
I'll meet you up there.
I thought it'd be different.
I thought I'd be better.
I'm gonna go in here and
fill out this paperwork,
then I'll be back
to take you home.
Don't worry about it,
man, you'll be all right.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hey, babe.
ANGELA: Hey, babe, how's it going?
Fine. It's going fine.
Okay.
So, it's the weekend and
I was going to make plans.
I was thinking maybe we can go
to that new restaurant or...
Babe, I don't want to do nothing.
I just want to stay in the
house and play my game.
I don't feel like being bothered.
What's wrong?
Come on, babe, talk.
You want to know what's wrong?
Everything is wrong.
I don't know if I can do this.
What happened?
It's not what happened,
it's what didn't happen.
I met the damn devil today
in the form of a child.
Little boy was disrespectful.
He didn't respect me as a
man, he had a foul mouth.
We could start off
there, or if you want,
we could talk about
the fact that I got
confronted by a
man-lady biker thing.
I didn't know what it was. All
I know is she had a beard and breasts,
but the fact I thought it was a
man and spoke on it, I'm wrong.
"You got the beard, not me!"
And to top it off, I go
to the farmers' market,
I get into a dispute with
a guy named Crazy Cody,
he started pouring
honey on his body,
I'm wrestling a man with honey!
No, wait a minute, Ben.
Did you say Crazy Cody?
Yeah. What does that
have to do with anything?
Baby, James plays poker with
a guy named Crazy Cody.
What? What?
He's a blonde-haired white guy.
He's known him a long time.
Hey.
Question, babe, you
ever heard of a 126?
Yeah. It's a cop code for an
annoying situation nobody wants.
They do it to rookies. It's a joke.
Why?
Nothing. Babe, let me let you go.
I have to go. I'll call you
later, okay? I love you.
I love you, too.
I got your damn 126.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(OFFICERS LAUGHING)
CRAZY CODY: So, I'm standing there, right?
The guy's coming at me, he's like,
"I'm nervous, I'm nervous."
He's like, "Put your hands up."
And the closer he gets,
the shorter he gets.
And he's coming at me, then it
was like a Cabbage Patch doll.
I've never seen anything like it.
Then he gets on me,
tries to put the
cuffs on me, barn.
I got honey on me, I'm
yelling, "Oh, Honey Boo Boo!"
So, can we stop with these 126s
or is this guy coming back?
Oh, no. He's done. You hear me?
Done. Anybody got a fork?
(ALL LAUGHING)
JAMES: I'm serious, you know.
Matter of fact,
I don't even think he going
to join the academy. Yeah.
All in all, I got to say,
today was a good day.
All right, let's get you
home. Tucked in.
DISPATCH ON RADIO: Unit 19, 126 in progress.
Suspicious person,
55 North Peachtree.
Hey, baby, cancel that 126.
As a matter of fact, I'm going
to be offline for about a hour.
No, you know what? On
second thought, copy that.
Unit 19 en route to 551 Peachtree.
- Copy that.
The hell you doing?
I told you I want to be
a cop. I want to be a cop.
And that 126 might be serious.
I feel like I got my second wind.
Like I'm Action Jackson
or somebody right now.
Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We discussed this.
- You not cut out for this work.
- That's not true.
I'm taking you home.
I'm not going home like this.
It's not going to happen.
Now, if this doesn't go well,
I will be out of your hair, James.
All this cop talk
will be finished.
Matter of fact, I'll go one up.
If this doesn't work,
I will call Angela right
now and tell her myself.
Your funeral.
Indeed it is.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
JAMES: What's the problem this time?
I don't like these guys.
Something's wrong.
You're gonna have
to get a bouncer.
The department is getting
tired of doing this for free.
I'm serious this time.
The one by the bar.
Other dude, blue jacket.
They've been casing
this place all week.
JAMES: I think you're right this time.
I need you to go to
the car, call in 211,
tell them we need a backup.
Okay. Will do.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Ben!
What are you doing?
I want to go talk to him.
Gonna do it now.
Everybody on the floor!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Get on the ground.
On the ground! Now!
Atlanta Vice! Everybody be cool.
No, no, no. Don't nobody be cool.
We're about to heat this up.
- Ben!
- Yes?
Back to the car. Call for backup.
No!
Look, the situation's
already in progress.
- I got this.
- Ben!
- Get down!
- Yeah.
Get up, baby, stop.
It's not real, it's fake.
Man, you got to be kidding me!
You gonna pull out a gun
when you looking at this?
Get down, baby.
I didn't know it was
this much of a height difference.
Thank you. I'm gonna tip you.
Get 100 ones.
I got you in a second.
You better chill, man.
Put the gun down.
- We got hostages.
- BEN: Oh, no!
James, they got hostages.
You ain't gonna shoot me.
(PEOPLE GASPING)
I'm gonna do it!
You do it, you next.
- Ben!
- Yes?
Stand down!
I ain't gonna stand down.
I never stand down...
from a 126.
This ain't no joke, man.
This is the real deal.
You right, James, this ain't no
joke. This is dead serious.
We serious up in here.
Shut up! You're about
to get us killed, cop.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold on, cowboy.
Oh, God!
I got a way for you to
get out of here. Okay?
Put the gun down.
I'll forget you had hostages, and
y'all won't get that much time.
No! Overruled. No.
Overruled?
Overruled! I don't like it.
I don't want to do that.
Why...
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Why would I do that, man?
Why do that when we can handle
this right here, right now.
One winner, one loser.
Let's get to shooting!
- Ben!
- Let's shoot! Let's start shooting!
Man, you crazy!
Yeah, I am crazy.
Only thing that can kill crazy is a
bullet. You got that bullet, huh?
Can you kill crazy? Kill crazy!
JAMES: Ben, get out of there!
Come on, Tim, what's the move?
Yeah, what's the move, Tim?
He got to ask you because you
can't make no decisions.
The black man is following
the white man once again.
Make a decision by yourself.
Tim, I'm back over here to you.
What you going to do?
It's a chessboard.
I'm a rook. I'm about
to take your bishop,
but I can't because
I got your queen.
Where I go? Where am I?
I'm gonna stop so you can see me.
You see me, huh?
You see me? Shoot!
- Ben!
- I'm going to do this fool!
Do me! Do me!
(SCREAMING)
He tried to do me!
Freeze!
Bitch, you better
get down and shoot!
(GROANS)
James, this is real!
This shit is real!
Don't you move, boy.
Oh, Jesus! This is real!
Take it easy, man.
I didn't even do anything.
Hey, don't say anything.
Keep me away from this psycho.
Ow! Come on, man.
Where do I start?
Could say "good job."
You think because you're better
than the average riff-raff
that gives you the right
to do things your own way?
To tote that little civilian bastard
into an active crime scene?
L-T, I did not know it was going
down like this, all right.
This owner right here
is always crying wolf.
We come by to check it
out, it's going down.
Perp gets shot, no other
fatalities. What's the big deal?
You want a medal for that?
Now I hear you took
him to a gun range?
And something about
military weapons and Omar?
That dry, snitching-ass Santiago.
It's not Santiago! I got ears
out here just like you do.
I told you to leave it alone.
But you're out here on your own.
I don't know half the
shit you're working.
And all you say is "trust me"?
You should.
Haven't I earned that?
Let me be clear.
I can only cover your ass so much.
So clean your shit up.
Or I'll clean it up for you.
You, get in the car, you done.
Why?
We got more important 126s?
You almost got me killed!
Almost don't count.
So, you done. Let's go.
No, I'm not done.
I want to talk some more, I got
something else I want to say.
I may not be a cop right now,
but I will be.
You hear me? I will be.
And there is nothing that
you can do about that.
- I tried to help you.
- Hey! Hey, man!
You came to me and said, give me
a day to show me what you got.
I gave you a day.
It's not good enough.
So the answer to
your question is no!
I do not give you my blessing.
I don't need your blessing.
This isn't Afghanistan. I'm not
about to buy her with a goat.
That girl loves me, man.
That girl loves all of this.
Breathe it in, because
it's in your face.
I'm taking care of her, not you.
- You?
- Me.
You can't even take
care of yourself.
You wouldn't last
one day out here.
You think I'm gonna become a
cop and get myself killed?
Leave her by herself?
This conversation is over.
Get in the car.
This is your problem, man.
It's why you don't
have no damn partner.
You walk around here by yourself
because you don't trust nobody.
Eventually you're gonna have
to trust somebody, James.
I'd never trust you.
I'd never trust you with my life.
And my family's life?
Can you comprehend that?
You don't even know
why you don't like me.
Tell me why! You don't know why.
Because you don't know me, James.
I know who you are.
You that clown
that's always trying
to talk yourself out
of every situation.
No matter how deep you in it.
That's a bad character
trait for a cop.
So get your ass in the
car so we can go.
- I ain't getting in no car.
- You getting in the car.
I'm not getting in no car.
Walk.
You think I've never
walked before? I'll walk.
You think I'm gonna beg you?
Don't beg me. I'll walk.
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
Let me jump in because
I don't know where I'm at.
Back seat.
- I'm not getting in no back seat.
- Back seat.
No.
James?
Hey, James?
Can you at least let me ride
in the front seat, please?
Shut up.
Before I tase you in the mouth.
That's illegal.
That's very illegal.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
What?
Did you hear about Runflat?
Turned himself in to
County this morning.
Confessed to vandalism.
Weird. Weird.
That ain't weird. He just scared.
Trying to get off
the streets. It's Omar.
If he's onto Runflat, then
he's definitely onto us.
We might want to pull our skirts
over our faces and
just back off, huh?
It will never happen, all right?
So just keep your eyes open.
All right, copy that.
That's a damn shame.
Boy just got out of jail and
now he got to go back already.
See, that's where you don't
know what you're talking about.
Runflat ain't been on the
inside for about two years now.
That's not what his brother said.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
- Ow, man!
- What did he say?
I'm not telling you
nothing after that.
What did he say?
He said, "You think I'm gonna give
him up when he just got back?"
That's exactly what he said?
I got perfect conversation
recall. It's a gift.
I just got another clue.
This is a two-clue
kind of day for me,
and being that that's the case,
I need to be in the
front seat right now.
- No, it ain't.
- Yes, it is.
The kid's got another brother
that drove for Omar, all right?
He escaped custody, left town.
Now, no way he'd risk coming
back unless he had to be.
So, what's our move?
My move is to find the brother.
Oh, come on. Come on, James,
after all I just did?
What'd you do?
I'm giving you clues
left and right!
- No.
- I can help!
I'll keep my distance. I'm serious.
Veto. You're done.
Fine. Take me home.
I don't need this.
- I'm going home.
- I'll take you home.
I'm going to go home
and use the phone,
call Lieutenant
Brooks and tell him
you out here freelancing
this Omar case.
See what he thinks about that.
- You better not.
- Oh, I am.
You'd call the
lieutenant and tell...
You damn right I'll
call the lieutenant.
You little snitch bitch.
Call me whatever you want.
Snitch Bitch Ben.
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
Hey, man, you know where
I can get these things?
Oh, hell no! I got the right
to refuse service... (GROANS)
You better be lucky it wasn't me.
James, you broke the glass!
Oh, shit!
What's up? Come here.
Get your ass over here, boy.
Get your hands off me, pig!
What you doing? Hey!
How stupid are you to hide out in the
same place we found you before, Jay?
Plain sight. Classic tactic, man.
You better tell me where that
Serbian buy is going down, boy,
or I'm gonna give you
a classic tactic.
I ain't telling you nothing!
Why'd you even come
back, Jay, huh?
This is becoming
a family tradition.
Tell me where that buy is, or you
going to jail with a bullet wound.
You think he playing with you?
You think he got time for games?
This man is crazy. If he pull the
gun out, that means he serious.
Tell him where the
buy is going down.
Where's it going down at?
Bullshit.
BOTH: Bullshit?
Oh, no, this is real shit.
You better tell me where
that buy going down!
Tell us where the buy is. You hear
me? Tell us where the buy is!
Forget both of y'all!
Really? That's how you feel?
- You want to feel this?
- That's right!
You want to see crazy?
I'll show you crazy!
Tell me where the buy is!
Tell me where...
(SCREAMS IN PAIN)
Oh, shit.
He shot me!
I'm sorry.
Yeah, he shot your ass.
You damn right I shot your ass.
- He going to shoot you again.
- No. No.
Because he crazy.
I can't handle this one.
I'm crazy.
It's out of my hands.
You want to see crazy?
I'll show you crazy!
You think it's a game?
Tell us where the buy is!
You better tell me
where the buy is!
- Okay.
It's at the old factory. The
abandoned one off of Huber.
- Okay.
- Old abandoned factory.
- What time?
- 9:00.
If you lying, Jay, I'm gonna
shoot you in the other shoulder.
Just keep him away from me!
Boy, you want it hot?
You want to get some
hot slugs up in you?
Slugfest, homie.
Chitty-chitty-bang-bang!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Hey, man, it's going down now.
Over at that old factory on Huber.
SANTIAGO: Shit.
Okay, I'm on my way.
I'm calling in for some
heavy backup, all right?
All right.
Where'd you get that gun?
I kept it from the club.
You know the guy you
shot in the ass?
- Come on, man!
- Now!
- Here!
- Hey, mother...
I thought the safety was on. I got
him to talk though, didn't I?
Yeah, you got a very interesting
interrogation voice.
Nice and screechy.
Okay. It's all this intensity.
That's what it is.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
Wait for me here.
Are you serious?
Of course I'm serious.
If I had time to drop you
off, I would, but I don't.
It's my clue that got us here.
I've been helping you all day!
- Oh, you have?
- Yes.
Is that why you just shot
somebody? On accident?
That's not fair.
And before that, you asked a
suspect to actually execute you.
That's because I thought it was
another 126. You know that.
This is not another 126, Ben.
This is the real deal.
So the time for jokes is over.
So the kind of help you got, it's
not the kind of help I need.
I'm just trying to go...
Do I have to cuff
you to the wheel?
You ain't gotta do that.
Where's your ride-along?
He flamed out. I had
to take him back.
Where's backup?
Probably running late.
Listen, I got a look inside.
They're all in there, it's
going down right now.
We not waiting.
Just FYI, when I get in there I'm
gonna start shooting people.
I haven't shot anybody all day.
We know, Santiago. Let's hit it.
Okay. Here's what
we should do. I...
Man, what the... Oh!
Oh, hell no.
That's right. Stay still.
Yeah, surprise.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
I don't want to hear that.
(R&B MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROANS LOUDLY)
A-B-C-D-E-F-G-H-I-J-K-L-
M-N-O-P... I can't do it.
(SIGHS IN FRUSTRATION)
I can't believe you two punks been
protecting Omar this whole time.
Pays well.
No benefits, but we get
those from the day job.
I should have known.
Greedy bastards.
James, we're not
giving anything away.
We're selling it because
we're businessmen.
And we're enterprising it so that
Omar won't have to hide no more.
And all you had to do was
just let it go for one day.
If you had let it go for one day,
you wouldn't be here right now.
MIGGS: Now things are not
gonna end well for you.
JAMES: Yeah, don't be too sure.
You didn't want to play
ball, so here we are.
It's not easy on us
either, believe me.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Oh, my God! Shit!
Thank you.
Omar appreciates the
delivery of his weapons.
What is this?
That's just a loose end that we're
gonna take care of very soon.
Added bonus for Omar.
- SERBIAN BOSS: So, can we do business now?
- Yeah.
Can I see the merchandise?
Victor.
- Didn't have to be like this, James.
- Nice.
You could've had a
little taste of that.
I for one, though, I feel hurt,
because we never hung out.
We never watched sports or
shared some chicks together.
It must be tough being
an island though, huh?
Nobody to have your back.
You know what? You should
see a therapist about this,
because you don't want to
spend the rest of your life...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I forgot. You're about to die.
BEN: I want that one for myself.
(GUNS COCKING)
Who the hell are you?
Who am I?
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, shit.
Yeah, that makes me laugh.
Especially considering the
fact that this is my deal.
That these are my men.
SANTIAGO: Wait a minute.
You're Omar?
That's right.
Omar is here.
I know what you're thinking.
Nobody's ever expecting
to see Omar,
but he's here. And why is that?
Nobody can tell me why
because it's a surprise.
This is a surprise inspection.
So I suggest you all put
a smile on your face,
because today is the day that
I finally decided to let you see mine.
Welcome to me.
Where's Jay?
Oh, Jay?
I left Jay ass at the pawn
shop because he wasn't prompt.
Everybody knows that
I like my shit prompt.
It's more professional that way.
Ain't that right, my Serbs?
I've been keeping tabs on all
of you for some time now.
You.
Oh...
Let me take the time
out to give you this.
Yeah.
You have been crushing all
week, you hear me? Yeah.
I need more men like you.
You're a good man, you know that?
I want you to keep
keeping on, young butt.
Matter of fact, do me a
favor and give Omar a gun.
A gun?
Did I stutter, hmm?
You're gonna embarrass
me in front of
my crew after I just
gave you a compliment?
I said, give Omar a gun.
Hold up. Now hold up.
I thought Omar was 6'4".
(GUN COCKS)
(CRIMINALS MURMURING)
(ALL EXCLAIM)
(GROANING)
How tall is Omar now?
Anybody else want to weigh in
on how tall he thinks Omar is?
No? Does anybody else
want to test me?
We weren't expecting to see you.
But it's better that we deal
with this business personally.
Of course it is. I'm sorry
you had to see that shit.
Hey, and I want to apologize for
this because that's not me, okay?
I don't want y'all thinking it
is, and this is stupid, too.
So I'm sorry for that.
Now, I gotta take the time
to give a special shout-out
to Miggs and Santiago.
Hell, yeah.
Yeah!
I'm clapping, ain't I?
Am I mapping?
Yeah!
My double agents.
You guys brought me the
best prize of them all.
James Payton.
What you think you doing...
Shut your ass up, man!
You don't have the right to talk.
I'm gonna kill you.
See, James, for those
who don't know,
James has been chasing my ass day
and night for some time now.
But he can never catch me.
You know why?
Because he's one of those people
who thinks he always knows best.
Doesn't think that people are
good enough for certain people,
without even really knowing
those other people.
You with me?
Guess what today is, big man?
Today is the day that you die.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm going to have to put
some tarps down and shit.
Now I might finish
you off with my gun,
I might.
But I'm going to start you off with
the cold steel of my katana blade.
I'm talking death
by a thousand cuts.
Oh, I'd like to see that.
(KNIFE UNSHEATHING)
Give us a little taste of that.
MIGGS: (LAUGHING)
Yeah, I'd be entertained by that.
A little preview. Come on.
Hell yeah.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Okay.
You ready? Here it come.
Don't you.
- I gotta cut you.
- Don't you cut me.
What you think I gotta do?
I gotta do it!
(INDISTINCT)
(GRUNTS)
Yeah!
That's what you get, po-po!
Maybe stab him a little
more, cut him more.
Shut your ass up.
I ain't no show pony.
This shit is over.
Now what I'm going to do is
I'm gonna cut you loose.
Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
I'm going to let you
all handle this shit,
while I take this piece of shit
somewhere. Get your ass up.
Let's go. Walk!
SERBIAN BOSS: Good, because
this was getting ridiculous.
Thank you.
The hell are you looking at?
Nothing, Omar.
BEN: You can call me Omar now?
Can we just keep it moving?
I will not run a crew
without respect.
What?
I won't do it.
Get in here.
Let me tell you something.
Let me tell everybody in
here something right now.
It's about respect in this game!
I will not tolerate a crew
that does not respect me.
Respect is best served cold!
MAN: It's revenge!
BEN: Who said that?
Was that you?
Hmm?
Revenge is a dish
best served cold.
(LAUGHS)
Oh!
Who in the hell are you?
I'm Omar.
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing
in my warehouse?
What the hell's going on
here? Kill them both.
Fellas, please.
We don't want to
make Omar nervous.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(BOTH SIGH)
Let me explain something to you.
Omar is very comfortable.
You know why?
Because Omar doesn't have a
bunch of guns pointed at him,
new guy.
I really don't mind that
you're pretending to be me,
whoever you are,
but what I do mind is
that any of these idiots
actually believe this clown!
Ask this guy right here
who he thinks Omar is.
I don't know, it just hurts.
You shot Roberto?
You damn right I shot him.
I'm impressed.
Problem is, if Omar
shoots Roberto...
(ALL GASP)
Oh, shit!
Omar shoots Roberto.
I like you, little man.
You got balls.
So, you Omar!
Wait right there.
Damn, man!
You ain't what I pictured.
You ain't nothing
but a black dude.
Probably from Decatur.
(OMAR LAUGHING)
That's what you get for thinking, James.
That really ain't your thing.
See, if you was thinking,
you'd get the big picture.
You'd see where you are.
Look around you, James.
You see where you are?
You're in the middle of one
of the biggest arms deals
to ever go down in this town.
You could be in on it.
But you playing cops and robbers.
You think you been looking for
me, but I've been watching you.
I've been following you.
I've spent a lot of time, lot
of money thinking about you.
I spent so much money in fact,
your boys are now working for me.
Everything all right with
your packages, fellas?
- Yes, sir.
- SANTIAGO: Come to the other side, man.
Let go of this self-respect shit.
Last I heard, it ain't buying
you a house in Florida.
See, everybody wants to be
on the winning side, James.
That's what I want for you.
You out front, me in the shadows.
We could run this town.
Yeah, that's right,
I see you're curious.
I'm gonna make you this offer
one time, one last time.
What do you say?
I'm Omar!
Shut up! Would you please stop!
Nobody believes you.
Get over there.
I'm gonna get with you later.
(WHIMPERS)
Come on now.
What's it gonna be?
Get your goddamn hands off me.
(SIGHS)
Well, I tried to put the
man in the penthouse.
He wants to spend his
life in the poorhouse.
Guess we'll have to reinstate
the death penalty.
You know what, Omar?
It really don't matter.
You could smoke me right here,
because we all gonna
die up in here anyway.
- Oh, are we?
- SERBIAN BOSS: What are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
Your boy Marko told me everything.
It's a big setup.
Them boxes right there,
ain't nothing in
there but replicas.
Not true.
You ain't gonna like
how this movie end.
You just walked into
your own assassination.
We'll open the boxes and
find out, won't we?
(SCREAMING)
- Which way do I go?
- Right here.
Yo, this is crazy, man!
This shit is crazy!
- Calm down!
- I can't calm down!
Holy shit! Oh, shit!
James, I see a gun!
Get it!
(YELLS)
Shit! I got it! I got it!
Selective fire. Visual confirm
target. Short bursts.
Just shoot! Come on, here we go.
One, two, three, go!
Shit!
I thought it was the extended mags!
It's not the extended mags!
What you talking about?
Shit, I'm out.
What the hell are you doing?
In a game, you can pick
up ammo off the ground!
This ain't no damn video game!
Hold on! I got one!
- Oh, God!
- Let's go!
Same thing on the count of three.
Watch out!
I just saved your life!
- Shit!
- I just saved your life!
Shit.
Save my life and get me
the hell out of here!
(SCREAMING)
Yo, we can't go that way.
Why?
Because they got
AK-47s down there.
Two shotguns. They're
probably Benellis.
From the sound of it,
it might be AR-15 as well.
You can hear all that?
It's from the game.
I got a perfect recall.
I'm a Platinum level player.
Here you go! Huh?
See how you like that!
- Call me the perfect storm.
- Grenade!
Hey, what you doing?
You got five seconds to pick
it up and throw it back.
Oh!
(MEN SCREAMING)
Stop throwing the
goddamn grenades!
I already pulled the pin.
Another one!
James, the money.
JAMES: Ben! Get your ass back here!
It's gonna blow!
Let's get out of here!
Oh!
- You all right?
- I'm good.
Okay.
That's it?
That's not so bad. I thought it
was going to be bigger than that.
Damn!
My Car!
It's probably still
drivable though,
because it happened in the back.
You can't drive it now.
Yeah, it's definitely not
drivable. At first it was,
but after this, there's
no way you can drive it.
We have to get out
of here. Come on.
You wanna get a cab, or what?
- Let's go.
- Okay. All right.
BEN: So, what was Omar going to
do with all those guns anyway?
JAMES: Probably start an
army and take over the city.
He's got half the
cops on his side.
So, we stopped him?
For now.
- Hey.
- What?
Slow down, man.
You see I got the money, right?
Yeah, that was good.
Hold this. My sock is wet.
Must have stepped in
a puddle or something.
Hate it when that happen.
(GASPS)
What is that?
JAMES: Damn. You shot.
I think I would be able
to feel if I got shot.
You got so much adrenaline going
through you, you don't feel it.
But I'm serious.
- JAMES: Wow.
- BEN: What?
It went straight through.
Oh, my God!
There's a hole in my leg!
I got shot!
Yeah I was pretty clear on that.
Oh, shit! It hurts now!
All right. Sit yourself
down. Sit down.
I ain't gonna sit down!
I just got shot!
I can't feel my toes!
Shh! Give me your belt.
You gonna whip me
because I got shot?
- Tourniquet!
- Okay.
You have to get a cold piece
of meat like a steak.
You have to put a
steak on it, man.
- Listen!
- I'm listening.
- I got shot!
- You're gonna be okay.
You lost a little blood. Just
have to get you to a hospital.
- Anybody down here?
- Calm down!
All right, calm. I'm calm.
(PHONE RINGING)
(CHATTER ON POLICE RADIO)
(TURNS OFF)
Yeah.
Hey, Lieutenant, we
got a problem here.
I'm aware. Make this easy
on us, James. Come on in.
Wait, what are you talking about?
Listen, Santiago and
Miggs, they dirty.
(CHUCKLES) Funny, they're saying
the same thing about you.
They got Marko and his
buddy backing them up.
What?
Hey! Tell him I got shot.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
Lieutenant, you gotta believe me,
it didn't go down like that.
You know I'm on your side.
Come in, James.
Just don't make it any worse.
Where are you?
BEN: My foot, I think the
tourniquet too tight.
We already at worse.
Is the ambulance coming?
- Is it coming?
- No.
And we can't call one either.
They'll be all over the scanners.
What does that mean?
It means I'm on my own.
You're not on your own.
You got me, man.
Let's get you to a hospital.
Okay. Oh, shit.
Stop the car. Stop!
Sorry to inform you, sir, but
I have to confiscate your vehicle.
That's not even a real badge.
I'm a police officer,
I need you to get out.
How you gonna carjack
me without a gun?
You right. Get your ass out.
Watch the sweater, man!
Hold on to your weed!
Firefighters are still
battling a nasty blaze
here at an abandoned warehouse in the
Old Fourth Ward district of Atlanta.
Who cares?
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
DOCTOR: Let's start two bags of O neg.
Let me know when the
next OR's available.
- James, take my hand.
- Ain't happening.
James, please.
Here, call Angela.
Tell her I love her.
Tell her I love her so much.
She sent you a text.
- What she say? Read it to me.
- It says...
"Come home soon."
"Come home soon"?
Oh, my God!
It's okay. Keep going.
James, what if
I never see her again?
Where's the doctor at?
I'm right here.
- Doc, am I dying?
- You're not dying.
No, seriously.
- DOCTOR: What's going on, James?
- BEN: What's going on?
It's complicated. I know you
supposed to call this in,
but I need you to hold off on that.
(BEN WHEEZING)
Doc, I'm losing breath,
I think I need some CCs.
I want you to buy me some time,
so we can make sure that
the one that did this
don't come back and
finish the job.
- You feel me?
- Okay.
Your buddy lost some blood, so I'll
give him something for the pain.
We'll get him in the
next OR that opens up.
I appreciate it, Doc.
Nurse, start him on some
morphine, dress that wound,
and let me know when
the next OR opens up.
James, should we give him
some of the money we took?
I don't know what
he's talking about.
You know what I'm talking
about. The money.
- We good here, Doc.
- WWJD?
Shut the fuck up!
SUDS31: Lathered Lotus, what's your twenty?
I found the entrance to the prison
door, I'm taking heavy fire.
Assface23, take out
that machine gunner.
ASSFACE23: Negative. Too hot.
If you actually want to win,
you have to listen to me.
- All right.
- This is not a game.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
It is actually.
Shit! Someone lay down suppressing
fire. I have to answer my door.
You are go for door.
ANGELA: Who is it?
Angela, it's Santiago and Miggs.
Can you do me a favor,
can you open up?
I need to talk to
you for a second.
What happened? Is everything okay?
- How are you doing?
- Good.
Can we come in for a second?
Sure. Sure.
We're just looking for James
and your boyfriend.
They're not here by
any chance, are they?
No, I haven't heard from
James or Ben in a while.
Is everything okay?
For you, no.
Wait, did you guys just hear that?
Yeah, what the hell was that?
What should we do?
We should finish
the game, assholes.
No. Listen closely.
ANGELA: Miggs and Santiago, get out!
You can't hear that?
(ARGUING ON SPEAKER)
Yeah, something's wrong.
Can I ask you a question?
How many rainbows are
you made out of?
Because right now, I can see
one, two, three trainbows.
(LAUGHING)
I just said "trainbows."
- You know what, Ben?
- Hmm?
I read you all wrong.
What are you talking
about, you "read" me?
Me and Angela had it rough.
Moving from foster
home to foster home.
It was right after
our parents died.
It was hard, man.
I didn't trust nobody with Angela.
Can't nobody protect her like me.
It was how I used to think.
It's hard to change, you know.
Mmm.
It's okay. It's fine.
Nah.
I need to trust her a
little more, you know.
She a big girl.
She know how to
pick the right guy.
Wow.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh!
That is it right there.
That's why I made it my ring
tone, because I like it.
How do you answer this thing?
You have to slide it.
Those things are crazy.
It's your buddy, Assface.
Assface? You have to answer that.
I can't wait for you to meet
Assface. You gonna love him.
Hello?
I need to speak to
the Black Hammer.
No, he can't talk right now.
He's a little incapacitated.
Ain't nobody constipated.
What's this pertaining to?
I think there's
trouble at his house.
- What?
- I heard shouting.
When?
Just now, from Angela.
How many voices did you hear?
Two. Miggs and Santiago.
Are you sure those were the names?
Yes.
Thank you, Assface.
Oh, my God, what happened?
You look like a monster right now.
Miggs and Santiago, they got
Angela at your house.
What? Oh, no!
Sit back down. You on
meds. You can't move.
No, listen to me. This is
what we gonna do. Listen.
You gonna help me up.
And you and me, and him.
We have to take him with us.
The three of us, we gonna go
over there and kick some ass.
I can't have nothing happen
to you. Angela would kill me.
After all we been through today,
you still don't trust me?
Man, you still under...
(STATIC ON POLICE RADIO)
FEMALE OFFICER: Have you seen these guys?
DOCTOR: No. Nothing.
Are you sure?
- Come on, we have to get there.
- Come on.
We have to get... Oh, shit!
Oh, you should have
helped me, James.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
BEN: Are my lips chapped?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
OMAR: James, my man.
I'm here with your boys
Santiago and Miggs.
Got somebody who wants
to holler at you.
There are three of them and
they're armed. Don't touch me!
I'm gonna tell you
something, if you touch her,
I'm peeling your wig back,
you understand me?
Ooh! Ooh! Threats. Threats.
JAMES: I know how you look now.
I done seen your face.
OMAR: Keep talking, baby
sister ain't gonna make it.
What's it gonna be, James?
What do you want?
What do I want? I want my money.
- Yeah, I got it.
- Yeah, come on, man,
you gotta hurry up before
we get started without you.
We be there in 30 minutes.
But we right around the corner.
Exactly, but they don't know that.
Right. They just unlocked
the Platinum level player.
Ain't gonna be no cheat codes.
I need you to stay focused.
Follow the plan.
- I'm focused.
- Timing gotta be on point.
Okay.
I'll need you to come in fast.
We gonna get their ass. Mmm!
ANGELA: Don't touch me.
SANTIAGO: I could make you so happy.
(GASPS)
(THUDS)
Hey. Go check that out.
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
- BEN: Damn it, I missed him.
- Ben?
- You again?
- Where you at?
I'm high as a kite.
I can't feel none of this.
- Get off of him.
- BEN: James!
Omar, freeze!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- James!
- You better have my money.
Get off of me.
Stop!
Come here! Come here!
Ben!
No!
I'll be with you in a sec, babe.
It didn't even hurt.
Black Hammer!
Bring my sister into this?
After everything I did for you!
Get up! Get your ass up.
(PANTS)
You are gonna respect me.
Okay, listen. I'm not trying to...
Bitch!
(GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
Ben!
You want some more?
I'm sorry, I just
made a huge mistake.
It's too late for that.
ANGELA: No!
Get off me. Get your hands...
(YELLING)
Ahh! (WHEEZING)
How does it feel to be on
the other side now, huh?
You always think you're
better than everybody,
getting all your citations.
Looking down at all of us?
How does it feel now, huh?
Do it.
Get away from my brother!
- Son of a...
- Great, baby!
Ang, behind you.
James!
(PANTING)
ANGELA: James!
OMAR: Girl, you better bring your little
narrow ass on before
you make me mad!
- James!
- Come on with me.
No!
Get off of me!
- Omar!
- James!
Let her go, man!
Damn, James, you
disappoint me, man.
Make you a nice offer. Nice offer!
You got to turn me down.
You know I don't like
to be disappointed.
That's all right, you
stopped this deal,
but there's always
another deal to be made.
I'm accepting your offer now.
Now?
(LAUGHING)
No. Now, you gonna do
what I tell you to do.
You gonna put your
gun down, you gonna
watch me drive off
with your sister.
That's what's happening now.
You know I can't do that.
How about now?
Huh?
What's it gonna be, James?
ANGELA: Shoot him, James!
You shut your little ass up.
Just keep your narrow ass still.
Girl, you don't hold still
you gonna make me...
- What? What?
- ANGELA: No.
OMAR: Come on, James.
Huh?
Trust me.
OMAR: Clock's ticking!
What's it gonna be?
All right. Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, now you want to
get some act right.
I'm putting it down.
Oh, now you're putting
it down, okay!
Bye, James.
BEN: Kick move.
(GROANS)
How do you like that end?
Damn.
Game over, bitch.
- Oh...
- He getting up.
James...
James, you got him, right?
Let's move.
BEN: I didn't even realize I got
shot till we left the warehouse.
But I didn't panic, though.
Here comes the lieutenant.
So, now what are you going to do?
What you mean?
Well, after three years and all that
overtime, you finally got your man.
I didn't get my man.
We got our man.
BROOKS: I never liked those two.
Hmm.
What?
No, I'm not going
to say it. I'm not.
No. I'll see you at the office.
Did you see that?
Actually, I didn't.
You didn't see the look
that he just gave me?
- No.
- That was a look of respect, James.
I didn't even tell
you when they was
shooting at the warehouse
what I was doing.
Everybody's all over the place,
but I'm locked in on Omar...
JAMES: Omar.
For the record,
I would've never taken your offer.
See, you always missing
the big picture, James.
Yeah, but I ain't
gonna miss your ass.
Oh.
Get his ass out of here.
(AMBULANCE DOORS CLOSING)
Ben held his own, huh?
Did he impress you enough?
We didn't get ourselves killed.
So I guess he did all right.
That was your approval.
You just gave me your blessing.
Did you hear that, Ang?
James, you just gave me
your blessing just now.
James, don't you walk...
Come here, James.
Baby, you gotta help me because
this morphine done worn off.
This shit hurts. James!
I can't chase you because of my
leg, but I wanna give you a hug.
Look at this, ladies.
He has amazing taste.
Great taste, right?
No. Hey...
Just hold on.
I need you at least 15 feet away
from this grill at all times.
James, please don't start.
I can't even believe you over here,
man, after what you did to me.
What I did to you
was not my fault.
- You set me on fire!
- You know what?
On my phone I can go to a website,
and this website will give me
instructions on how to use this machine.
You're not using my grill.
Back off.
Give me your Wi-Fi password.
- No.
- Let me get your wee-fee.
Give me the wee-fee!
Suspect-shot-23.
There's so many other passwords
that you could have chose.
Airplane. Bike.
It's too much, man.
I'm in, watch out. Let me do it.
- Move. No.
- James.
Come on. Stop it.
This is unnecessary.
This is stupid.
- No, get back.
- Will you trust me!
I'm a man that's weeks away from
graduating from the police academy.
Dude, this is symbolic.
- All right.
- Thank you.
But you gotta turn the gas on...
I turned the gas on
five minutes ago!
(SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
BEN: I'm all right, Angela!
(COUGHING)
I'm okay.
Hey, James, you should give
your neighbors a call,
because I think I killed their
dog when I came in hot.
I might have second-degree
burns, people.
Let's just say
third-degree to be safe
because my chest is
blistering up as we speak.
SUJAIDR
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/g8y7
Help other users to choose the best subtitles