Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Do you have to fight with
your lazy relatives all day?
- I telegraphed him that we come today.
- You telegraphed him 8 o'clock.
But in the morning or in the evening?
That's it. He thinks we
arrive in the evening.
Shit!
Please empty this bottle or
you won't get a good night kiss.
They ordered the commission to
regulate the wildlife stock.
- They don't come just because of you.
- Why do we need such things?
Last weekend they killed
more than 200 elephants.
This is a gun, you
don't need it. Get away.
Why are the big ones so angry?
- Toga is back, that's why they are angry.
- Toga is back?
He always tries to get into
the pride, but doesn't know how.
When they see the conflicts here
they won't expand your contract.
Just because of Toga.
Then it's over with your
animals and your family too.
- How is your antelope?
- Great, just like me.
As long as your pets
won't come too close.
But I don't have blood everywhere.
They don't use napkins.
And Toga is a lone wolf.
Nobody cleans him up.
Look at this.
Now they arrive, although
I'm waiting for my family.
He became an alpha animal because
this is the only way to study them.
Respect for Hank's studies,
the commission is overwhelmed.
We are here to congratulate.
Then Africa will be soon be
the land of Liger and Tigons.
A mixture between tiger and lion.
Get away!
I declare war, Hank!
We will kill them all! And you!
The animals were nervous because of a
lion who does not belong to the pride.
Normally he lives anywhere else.
I saw him 200 miles away from here.
I think he and Robbie are brothers.
They both have a huge black mane.
They also act similar.
One of your children
likes thumb-sucking.
Please behave.
When I get into their
conflicts they fight me.
You won't find a whip in this
house. Or anything like this.
If you love them, they love you.
When I want them to trust me
I have to accept their rules.
And they must accept me as
one of their pride. Understand?
He likes this very much... Au!
Don't be evil! I told you before!
They only play, they don't
know how strong they are.
Were are you going to sleep
when your family is here?
I mean what is your wife thinking?
Of course I will sleep in the
same bed with Madelaine. Why?
Get away, you hurt my foot.
I think Madelaine will sleep alone,
reading a book and cursing you.
This is Marc. If you drink a beer
you have to be careful. He loves beer.
Your lions are drinking beer?
I bet your family will run
away soon after seeing this.
Why is he dancing like
this? He want to marry me?
She does not know...
Are you crazy? Don't be so rough!
Okay, this is better. Please
don't say anything now.
I don't want to hear a word.
Okay, what should I say? Can I help you?
- Take me to the living room?
- And the lions?
- They do nothing because I'm hurt.
- I hope they know it.
Tell me why you didn't
get here with dad?
- Because of your and Melanie's school.
- We were old enough.
No. I know you.
You never trusted us.
This is unique.
As long she has milk
she let all kids come.
No matter what race.
Look, Margie, what I have.
Two more babies for you.
They are cute. Little leopards.
You will feed them, okay?
Please be nice to your new mother.
Don't bite your mother.
Yes, you are hungry.
And what about you?
Don't run away. Good guys. See you.
Are you crazy? Tiger on the boat...
I can sing a song. Hopefully
the tigers run away.
You hate me singing?
Hey, do you know why elephants
have such long trunks?
Then you can differ them from the frogs.
You have such a long
nose for the same reason.
When I see you I like
to eat frog's legs.
I don't suppose you want to scare
me with your Karate for old people.
One hit left, one hit right,
you won't get me in the middle.
Stop it! Now!
Stop it! We don't need
this at the moment.
- Idiot!
- Stop it!
Stop it now!
Look the animal!
- What animal?
- You!
I was so beautiful for you father.
Your animals do not care.
Look the boat, you can throw it away.
- Where's the second?
- Rocco, where are you?
Good. And now get out of the water.
Or I will throw with mud.
Stop shooting, you will hurt us!
What can I do, the animal will hurt you!
- How much bullets are left?
- Five.
I wanted to visit a
baseball game with him.
I will never see him
again but you don't care!
Stop be hysterical.
Your father is still alive, believe me.
He will come soon.
You also wanted to
get away from Chicago.
But we didn't know what
trouble this causes.
All will be good.
I hope you are right.
Come, relax.
No!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org