Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
BOB DYLAN: Rainy Day Women
Well, they'll stone you
when you're trying to be so good
They'll stone you
just like they said they would
when you're tryin' to go home
Then they'll stone you
when you're there all alone
But I would not feel so all alone
Everybody must get stoned
Well, they'll stone you
when you're walkin' on the street
They'll stone you
when you're tryin' to keep your seat
when you're walkin' on the floor
They'll stone you
when you're walkin' to the door
But I would not feel so all alone
Everybody must get stoned
Well, they'll stone you and say that it's the end
Then they'll stone you
and then they'll come back again
They'll stone you
when you're riding in your car
when you're playing your guitar
Yes, but I would not feel so all alone
Everybody must get stoned
Oh, say, can you see
By the dawn's early light
What so proudly we hailed
At the twilight's last gleaming
(Star-Spangled Banner solo)
Our forces are ready.
I know they will acquit themselves
as they always have.
There has never been a finer fighting force
than you are going to join.
I have a dream today.
Let's get a joint. Let's get ripped.
Let's proudly gather around the flag.
Did we administer another dose?
He's already got more LSD running through him
than any man in history.
"Hippy" means someone who's hip,
who's turned on.
Great to be here.
- All right, let's bleed it in.
- Here we go.
The brainwaves are going right off the scope.
Cut the film.
And lights up. Take off his headphones.
Son, how do you feel?
We can't expect a verbal response.
Did you like the movie, son?
Let's get right to it. Son, listen closely, son.
Would you go to war?
Would you fight for your country?
That's a positive response.
You see, Sid. The increased dosage
makes all the difference in the world.
It's like night and day.
(Scientists laugh)
Of course, you know what the implications are.
A little more testing,
and the defence departments go-ahead,
we'll turn these anti-Vietnam protestors
into loyal soldiers in no time.
We can win this war.
(Groans)
Ah.
I've got to split now, man.
Hey, thanks for the acid.
Peace.
Peace! (Echoes)
When the truth is found
To be lies
And all the joy
Within you dies
Don't you want somebody to love?
Don't you need somebody to love?
Wouldn't you love somebody to love?
You better find somebody to love...
Hey, man.
Excuse me. What is this shit?
I didn't write this.
What happened to "Raise your bloody fist
and smash the cancerous sore
of the imperialist system", man?
Sammy, we're gonna bust some heavy walls
with this. Dig this concept.
We're gonna ask everybody in the world,
next May Day, at one o'clock,
to stop what they're doing, drop their bullshit,
and take a breath together.
A pause, man. A world pause.
- Here we go.
- Come on. Listen to me.
Oneness breaks down man's uptight concepts
of money, personal property,
uniforms, shirts and ties,
reserved parking spaces.
It blows it all to hell.
How many copies do you want for the rally
this afternoon?
5,000. Sammy?
- Shotgun.
1984 is gonna be outstanding, man.
No materialism, no wars, enlightened leaders.
Good smoke, man.
It's gonna be beautiful.
You better find somebody to love
Wow. Petra, what it is?
It's photo-pointillism.
That's what I call it.
Hey, that's enormously groovy, man.
I just love the feel of the paint on my hands.
This is definitely my thing.
Er, like, what is it a picture of?
I don't know.
Like, I dropped the camera and it just went off.
But now it's definitely talking to me.
Right. Hey, what's it shouting?
Sit. Sit down.
Everyone, sit down. Let's go.
Do you like to dress like that, son?
It's my job, sir.
Take that hat off.
First man is Fred Wouk.
Second man is Hesus Monteya.
They're wanted for draft evasion, inciting riots,
possession of illegal substances.
Excuse me, sir. How old are these photographs?
You have something in your teeth.
- What?
- In your teeth. Right there.
I followed them from Seattle to Haight Ashbury...
Thank you, sir.
...to the Democratic convention in Chicago
and now here.
Intelligence reports that they will be attending
an anti-war demonstration today in New York.
I am aware of the strains upon the youth
of today.
But where are these people taking us?
And what's wrong with collecting baseball cards,
driving in the country in your Chevy convertible,
falling in love,
the Mills Bro... the Mills Brothers?
I'm gonna buy a paper doll
that I can call my own
A doll that other fellas cannot steal
And when those flirty, flirty guys,
with their flirty, flirty eyes
(Hums)
Do you like that song, son?
- Oh, yes, sir.
- Liar!
- Sucklehoney?
- Huh?
You know, Leila did my reading yesterday.
Yeah.
She said we'd be together a long time from now.
- She said that?
- Mm-hm.
The card came up.
- The card came up?
- Yeah.
You know, the one with the man and the woman
holding hands facing the sun
with little baby children.
Cos she said that she saw children.
And I want to have lots and lots of children.
She said with my artwork I could do that.
- She say that?
- Yeah.
Mm-hm.
I really love you.
I love you too, baby.
The first days are the hardest days
(Knocking)
Don't you worry any more
Cos when life looks like easy street
There is danger at your door
Think this through with me
Hello, hello.
- I'm eating rice-a-roni.
- Yes, I see. Ma'am?
You want some? I'll fix you a plate.
No. Thank you.
My name is Brubaker. I'm from
the Justice Department, special task force.
I have federal warrants
for the arrests of these two individuals.
Would you look at these, please?
What are they wanted for?
Draft evasion, conspiring to undermine
the government of the United States.
Oh. Since when is it a crime
to speak your mind?
Pardon me, you just have something here.
Oh.
Oh, God.
Oh, what the hell is this?
Oh, my God.
Lunch.
(Laughs)
Who knows what else is in there, right?
Well, I guess I'll just take a bath later.
Maybe not later, but...soon.
Listen, I don't know these people,
but, if you need some help,
my door is always open.
Ma'am, as a matter of fact,
I would like to come inside.
Get a warrant.
That was a federal pig. He's looking for you
and Hesus, and he says he's coming back.
- That's Brubaker.
- Has that pig got radar? He keeps following us.
We've got to drop out of sight
unless we want to do serious time.
- Hey, Ronnie, thanks for covering.
- Oh, please. I enjoy it.
You got room in your bag for these, man?
Come on, Sammy. Move your ass.
Er, Fred, listen. I'm gonna stay.
- How come?
- We've got to split.
I've been looking at all this shit
and I haven't finished anything.
Look, the Atomic Raspberry Banana.
I can't write this shit on the run.
This is where it's at. I've got to stay here
long enough to finish one of these.
- Is that cool?
- Very cool.
Everybody's got to follow their own path.
You stay here and write.
I love you, man.
- I'll always be here for you.
- I'm gonna miss you, Sammy.
I'll miss you too, Fred.
- Do you know where you're going?
- Oh, hey, no.
I never know where I'm going.
Consequently, I don't know when I'll be back.
Maybe I'm there already. Who knows.
Fred, I've just got to pack these brushes.
Er... Petra.
Here, honey, put this down, just a minute.
What?
OK, listen.
Remember when I said that you needed
some time to yourself
because you'd never been on your own?
- You want to break up?
- No.
I just can't do this with you.
I'm coming back
so please be cool and understand.
OK, let's split.
It's OK, you know,
because I've decided to, like, drop out
and devote all my time to getting into my work.
- Come on.
- I'm at a real critical point right now.
I got this great idea, like, how art is everything.
- Come on.
- The window of insanity,
the documenter of madness,
the collective aesthetic kept safe from the war...
- Mister, your cab is here.
- I'll be here till you get back.
OK. I love you.
Oh, no, wait! Wait, I've got to get a picture.
Yeah. That's great, Ronnie.
(Cock crows)
(Bird calls)
Hey, can I get a hit off that, man?
What?
Let me get a hit off that joint.
- Huh?
- Yes.
Yeah, sure, man.
Wow, it fish-lipped it.
- Are you hallucinating?
- Huh?
Man, those research assholes
sure fucked you up.
What makes you think that, man?
(Both laugh)
(Coughs)
Hey, man, this should loosen your scales, man.
Have another hit, brother.
Hey, suck on it, fish.
Ooh, good.
- Hesus?
- Huh?
Let's go get some lunch.
Ah. Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Sure, man.
Anything but fish.
Hey, Fred. Hey! Fred!
Hey, Hesus.
Fred, we gotta talk.
I just came back from over the mountain.
- I ran into these tourists.
- Tourists?
Just listen to me here, man.
They want to make a trade
for some of our grass.
They've got chocolate, a radio, new jeans.
You know the commune rules -
no contact with the outside.
Then we've got to change the rules, man!
I've been in this jungle for 20 years, all right.
Everything I own has holes in it.
I have not had a candy bar since 191.
Yeah, well, anyway,
I want a new pair of jeans, man. I really do.
OK, cool it out. We'll put it to a vote.
Maybe other people feel the same way you do.
I know I could use a new pair of jeans myself.
But then, that's where it starts.
It starts with a new pair of blue jeans.
That's where what starts?
Well, pretty soon you'll be trading on
a regular basis -
boots, cigarettes, instant coffee.
Those pens that when you turn them
upside down, the bathing suit goes off the girl.
Yeah, right.
But one day you'll wake up
and you'll look around and you'll say:
I want more.
I want the house with the two-car garage.
I've got to have the pool with the sauna,
and no home is complete
without the automatic gates.
Automatic gates are cool.
But then you'll have to expand.
So, you'll cut down a few trees.
I wouldn't trim our trees. They're cool.
Just a few trees, and put yourself up
a shopping centre, right over there.
Because now you're monopolising.
You'll hire lawyers, accountants, assistants.
You're taking a big bite out of life,
but you're still hungry.
Wait! There's a delicatessen.
But you're on a highway stuck in a traffic jam.
You've got no time to eat any more.
"My God, I'm late for a three o'clock meeting!"
You'll honk your horn and scream,
"Get out of my way, you son of a bitch,
before I kill you with my car!"
Suddenly your arm gets all tense
and your chest starts to hurt,
and you can't breathe, you're suffocating,
and, my God, the pain in your arm. The pain!
And why?
Because you wanted a new pair of blue jeans.
Wow.
Yeah, you're right. Fuck it. Fuck it.
What can I say? It's true.
Wait a minute. Hey, wait a minute.
Why are you giving up so easily?
You want something, right?
Yeah.
- But you just said...
- So what? I'm just one guy.
Fight for it. Petition it.
You should get together a list of names.
Fred, man, where am I gonna get a list?
(Explosion)
- What the fuck was that?
CREEDENCE CLEARWATER REVIVAL:
Run Through The Jungle
Thought it was a nightmare
(Gunfire)
They told me: Don't go walkin' slow
The Devil's on the loose
Better run through the jungle
I'm in trouble here.
What is the status of the papers?
I've got the papers but I need help.
The papers must not fall into the wrong hands.
This is imperative. Do you copy?
- Do you copy?
- Copy.
Satan cries: Take aim!
Better run through the jungle
Better run through the jungle...
(Grunting)
- It's coming from down there.
- Who the fuck could it be?
(Explosion)
- Shit!
Are you American?
Please.
- Oh, man.
- Please.
Sit still. We'll take care of you.
No. Take this. Destroy.
Don't let them use it...
They'll use it against you.
- Who?
- Do it for your country.
Is he dead, man?
He's very dead.
(Explosion)
Come on, man, let's split.
(Helicopter overhead)
So, what's the plan, man?
Me and Hesus are going back to the States.
- Huh?
- What? Why?
Because the United States
is going to invade here.
They want to get rid of the Communists
and set up their own puppet regime.
- When's this supposed to happen?
- By spring.
And this is the evidence.
We've got it here in our hands.
This is Vietnam all over again.
Imperative to find out who they are.
Do you copy?
They look like hippies.
See? It's karma.
Maybe this time we can break it to the press
before it ever gets going.
Hesus, we're going back to New York, man.
Ah.
Pastrami.
Wow. Lots of new buildings, man.
Hey, that's the same.
My mother took me there one time.
And left me.
Hey, we're home, my man.
- Let's go eat.
- Yeah, eat.
Cool.
Let's get some pizza, man.
Two suspects heading south on 6th Avenue.
I like marijuana
You like marijuana
We like marijuana too
I want to be a hippy and I want to get stoned
On mari, marijuana
I want to be a runaway,
got to leave home for mari, marijuana
Remember the teenybops
sniffing airplane glue?
Mari, marijuana
He used to freak out in Central Park too
for mari, marijuana
I want to get high but I never knew why
Here comes the car
but I've got to say goodbye
For mari, marijuana
Urgh. What is that?
Mari, marijuana
This is a nightmare.
- Hey, Ronnie.
- Ronnie.
Looking good.
Oh, my God!
Oh, God!
So, who are all these people up there?
Who are those people?
I don't know.
When I opened up this place, I had no idea.
I just figured it'd be nice to have a space
where the old gang could get together and talk
once in a while.
People came, I made food.
More people came, I made more food.
And then, one night, Mick Jagger shows up.
- It was all over.
- Whoa.
They came, and they came in droves.
It was like some horror movie.
I couldn't keep them out.
I kept changing the menu,
I charged outrageous prices.
It didn't matter. They kept coming.
Who are all those people up there?
Maybe it's better not to know.
You want to hang out here? Lt'll be my pleasure.
Thanks, Ronnie.
Far out!
Oh, Ronnie, my jacket.
Goddamn it.
That's wonderful.
Hesus, check this out. Oh, Ronnie, thank you.
Thank you. Wow.
Wow.
Hesus, look at us, man.
That was the day we left.
Hey, Ronnie...
have you got any scissors?
(Opera music blasts out)
You deserve better.
You deserve him.
If I'm guilty of anything, it's moderation.
- Love is nothing.
- Love is everything.
He gave you those and I wanted them.
He liked your mother.
I am indulgent. But that's me.
He liked your mother a lot.
I want your hair.
I'm not the one in love. Or am I?
I live for this moment here.
(Operatic singing)
La Fleck, by Princess Petra.
Hello, Dr Heimer. It's Petra.
I just saw one of my new commercials
and I'm having that feeling again.
Nothing. I'm feeling... nothing.
Excuse me. They have to leave.
Are you ready for them yet?
OK.
Could you hold for just a second?
Did you watch it? What did you think?
I think our girl did a fabulous job.
My people at the agency are flipping out.
We're just fantastic...
What happened to the bell?
I wanted a bell sound
when the girl changed from white to La Fleck.
What happened?
You see, with this commercial
I was going for an artistic thing.
A world where there are no bells,
where bells are an intrusion to the visual... thing.
A world where a person can be wearing white
and then... zim, zim, zim...
they're wearing art
and there are no bells.
I have a theory, Eema.
A theory about bells.
We had an outrageously expensive survey
done, which showed, if used correctly,
a bell sound could subliminally seduce
consumers into buying our product.
Which, in case nobody told you, is not art.
They're fucking rags with blotches on them!
So fuck art, Eema, and put the bells back in!
But of course.
I knew there was something missing.
Now that you mention it, it was the bells.
Dingaling-aling.
We'll have lots of bells, won't we?
Who makes commercials without bells?
Sorry, Dr Heimer, where was I?
Yes, um... life's spotty.
I can't seem to get anything solid going.
I know I do.
But I've been looking inside of myself for so long
that it hurts to think of anybody else.
(Phone rings)
Bring it up.
(Door chimes)
(Knocking)
(Yells)
Wow!
Check this out!
BOTH: Cool!
This is great.
Look at the view.
Where's the lobster?
Where's the lobster? Dig it.
- Aren't you Dial-a-lobster?
- It's Fred and Hesus.
I didn't order Mexican.
- Mexican!
- (They laugh)
Petra, it's me.
Fred. Fred Wouk.
My God. Hesus?
I am the lobster. Cuc-koo-ca-choo.
Baby.
Petra, it's so good to see you.
Wow! Barbecue sauce.
Barbecue sauce, wow. Dig it.
Mm. Taste it.
Mm. Isn't that good?
This is, like, an amazing pad.
Is this your pad?
- Fred Wouk.
- Petra Black.
What are you doing here?
We just got into town
so we thought we'd look you up.
I'm sitting here in absolute shock. I mean, you...
You still look like dirty, filthy hippies.
- It's great.
- You look great too. Doesn't she?
Could you try and eat over the box?
It's the help's night off.
Hoo-hoo-hoo! Help's night off!
- Could you pass the caviar, please?
- But of course.
What's this?
- No.
- Whoa!
(Stereo on)
Guys, it was really great seeing you,
but I'm not feeling that well, so...
I thought so. What's wrong, baby?
It's just been... It's just not worth going into.
Why don't you just give me your number?
Come on, babe, I'm here. Talk to me.
I don't want to bother you with my problems.
Babe, it's me - Fred. You can tell me anything.
Listen, I know. I don't want to talk to anybody.
So, why don't you just leave
and we'll get together real soon?
You know, I am picking up these
"Please stay, Fred, I need to talk to you" vibes.
All right. I need for you to leave now.
- I'm sorry.
- Uh-huh. No.
- Get out!
- I'm here, babe. I'm right here. Talk to me.
What the hell's wrong with you? Get the fuck out.
I think you need a hug.
I don't even know you.
Get the fuck away from my stereo!
Babe, let me hug you. Let me hug you.
You take one more step
and I'll motherfucking kill you!
OK. Peace.
Like, I'm sorry. I sense you have
a great deal of fear, and you're hurting.
We used to be so close.
I thought you could use a hug.
I'm wrong.
I'm sorry.
(Music starts up)
Wooh!
Hey! Come on! Boogaloo! Dingaling!
Shake it, baby!
Wooh!
Come on, Petra, loosen up!
Keep your eyes on the road
and your hands upon the wheel
Upon the wheel...
(Thunder rumbles)
Sir?
Still working on your autobiography, sir?
Tears of shame ran down the cheeks
of the fat ten-year-old.
"Bend over," my father commanded,
"and bare your buttocks to me."
This was taken on 6th Avenue and 51 st Street.
My God.
- I know these men.
- Are they terrorists?
They're much worse.
They're idealists.
And I can't believe I'm coming home
There's a mission overdue
After years apart
Me and my heart...
I'm so stoned.
How about some frugen glas?
Frugen haagen... Haagen frugen...
I'm so hungry.
Hey.
How you doing?
I'm really into coloured chicks.
You must have gone crazy down there
with no TV, no music, no newspapers.
God, you missed everything.
Watergate, Ford, Carter, the hostage crisis,
Three Mile Island.
All In The Family, M* A*S*H,
Mary Hartman, Mary Hartman.
Star Search,
Battle Of The Network Stars.
Saturday Night Live.
Men Who Hate Women
And The Women Who Love Them.
Women Who Hate Women...
...And The Men Who Love Them.
Iran and the Contras.
Gaddafi, Khomeini.
Patty Nails.
Pee-wee Herman.
New Coke.
There's a picture of Sammy.
I haven't seen Sammy in a long time.
We hung out after you left.
- He's married now.
- Really?
Oh, God.
- See that guy?
- Mm-hm.
- That's Emil.
- Emil.
He's a nutritionist and crystal healer.
He reaffirmed my sexuality
by increasing my bran intake.
We were very much in love.
Yeah.
Petra?
You need to get happy.
Let's go boogie.
Subway. Wow.
Hi. Fred Wouk. How are you?
Good to meet you.
SIGUE SIGUE SPUTNIK: Success
Sex, fun, success
Luxury - give it me!
Nothing more and nothing less
Than success...
- Petra, hi.
- Lan, hi. This is a friend of mine. Fred Wouk.
- Hi, Fred.
- How are you doing? Good to meet you.
So, Fred, what do you do?
I draw things. I meditate, I build huts.
- I'm really good with my hands.
- That's great.
Actually, I'm in New York right now
because I'm trying to stop a war.
- (Laughs)
- Petra, how are you? Where've you been?
So, what do you do, man?
- You drinking?
- Sure.
- Two gin and tonics.
- Gin and tonic, yeah.
I don't know what you'd call me.
People give me their money to invest in stock,
but I don't do that.
What do you do with their money?
I take it and I buy art.
I bought a house.
Really hot car.
Sometimes, Fred, I just give the shit away.
That's really beautiful, man.
Oh, yeah? I think so too.
- Hey, good luck with your war.
- Thank you very much. Yeah.
Success!
Rolex Rolls Royce Romeo
Say hello to Savile Row
Take a cheque from Coutts & Co
Limousines - all systems go!
My nipples are popping.
It's the air conditioning.
Sex, fun, success!
- Let's dance.
- Fred, this is Mona and Wanda.
- Hiya, Mona.
- Hi.
Wanda, what's happening, babe?
Mm, bless your heart.
Ow! Damn!
Luxury - give it me!
I am getting on the peace train
and I am never getting off.
Nice lighter, man.
So I hear you live in a jungle. What do you do?
I grow things, I build huts.
You're an architect?
So, what do you do, man?
- I'm a writer.
- Really?
That's great, cos I've got this story
that maybe you can help me with.
Yeah, er... Amos, hi.
- How are you?
- When did you get here?
- What are you up to?
- I'm completely bored tonight.
- It's a terrible scene.
- No-one's interesting any more.
Petra, I know this guy Jay is a friend of yours,
but, like, he's really rude.
Jay's a bit of a genius.
Don't say anything or he'll eat you alive.
- I think the scene is over.
- Maybe we could go someplace else.
Excuse me, but I have to tell you this.
We were talking, and this guy walks in and...
What are you looking at him for? Look at me.
I have no idea what's going on here.
I'm sorry. OK?
(Laughs)
- No, it's not OK. Look...
- Hey, don't touch me.
Ooh, you're really uptight, aren't you?
- Look...
- Get your hands off me, OK?
No, it's not OK.
I am violating your space on purpose.
OK? OK?
Touching is a part of communication.
If you ask me,
you could use a little communication.
You've probably had this problem all your life.
We can work it out.
What's his friend like?
Oh, wow. Haven't had these in...
Wow, never had these.
Wonder what they are.
Ah...
(Sobbing)
FRED: Oh, man.
You've got to go easy on yourself.
(Sobs) I know. I know.
He was my uncle.
He said it was just gonna be a fishing trip.
I had a really nice time tonight.
Me too, babe.
I guess I'd better go to bed.
Yeah, it's late.
- Good night.
Night.
Ah... listen...
I think you're really beautiful.
I'm not sure, but I think I was getting these
"Please don't sleep on the floor,
come share my bed" vibes.
I don't know. Maybe it's cos I spent
20 years in the jungle
getting it on with anything I could attract
with a piece of fruit, but...
you really turn me on.
You always did.
20 years in the jungle?
A safe... single... man.
The couple from the co-op board
are supposed to be here at three,
but Deedee says they're always early
so I think we should be ready by two.
She says they're lovely people.
Lloyd and April Stool.
- Sammy?
- Mm-hm.
Can we try and be positive about this?
Well... we're broke, June.
We're completely broke.
That's impossible.
You make over $300,000 a year.
I know, but we cannot make it.
Well, you know, we eat out much too much.
Now, I would be willing to cook
on a regular basis.
That's a huge saving, Sammy.
What the hell are you talking about?
Are you crazy?
June, we are talking about real money here,
darling. After-tax dollars.
What are you saying, Sammy?
That it's a fait accompli, that we should
just roll over on our backs and die?
I mean, look around you, Sammy.
Look at this place.
We need more space. We need more closets.
We need... We need...
- We need more!
- Yes, June, we do.
You're right. So why don't we just sit down
and figure it out?
- We can figure it out, honey.
- I know.
You know, I was thinking.
We don't have to fly to see your parents
for Hanukkah.
We'll just tell them things are very tight right now
and we can't.
- They'll understand.
- I can't do that, June.
Please, I can't.
There are other things on this list.
- There's your thigh reduction appointments.
- No.
- How about we sell the boat?
- I need the boat.
(Phone rings)
Hello?
Yeah, this is him.
Oh, what can I do for you?
Huh?
Er... well...
That was a really long time ago.
If the FBI wants any information on me,
they can just call my lawyer.
Yeah?
Well, can I get your name?
No, I just want... I want your name, OK?
Fred Wouk.
How do you spell that?
No, the "Wouk" part.
Fred Wouk.
Fred?
Fred, oh, man.
I'm sorry, man, I... It's just been, you know...
I don't know. It's been a really long time.
But you got a kid, man? That's outta sight.
Let me get your address.
Yeah, sure, I got it.
You can reach me at Petra's. Yeah.
All right, give me that again.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hm. Got it.
Oh, I'll be hanging out here
at least another couple of weeks. Yeah. Right.
Groovy. I can't wait to see you, Sammy.
OK, later, man.
How long did you say you were staying for?
As long as you want, baby.
There.
Mm.
(Whirring)
- Yeah?
MAN: Somebody to see Miss Black.
Oh? Yeah. Excellent.
Yeah, come on up.
- Who was that?
- Er... somebody.
(Doorbell)
Yes?
- Miss Black?
- Yes.
My name is Brubaker.
I'm with the Justice Department.
Have you seen these two men?
What's this about?
- Hey, wait a minute!
- Petra, what's going on?
No, no, it's all right. I got it. Keep looking.
Now, why don't you just be a good little boy
and come down here?
That's right. Come on. Come on.
Fred.
- You know...
(Glass smashing)
...you could save us all a lot of trouble
if you just told me where those papers are.
No way.
Fred, I think you should give him
whatever it is he wants.
I have nothing to do with this.
They're just house guests.
Please! Do not insult my intelligence, lady.
You two go back 20 years.
Hey, where's your partner, anyway? Huh?
Blandish?
Blandish...
Blandish, come out. Where are you?
(Stammers) You just tell your friend
to come out now.
(Bird screeching)
(Western film music)
(Crack of whip)
(Thundering horse hooves)
(Horse whinnies)
(Crack of whip)
You looking for me... hippy?
Aarrghh!
Hesus, you OK?
- Yeah, I'm cool.
- Have you got the papers?
- Yeah.
- Let's get out of here.
- Don't be foolish.
- Come on, Petra.
- What?
- They know who you are. It's not safe.
I am not committed to this involvement!
(Doorbell)
- Hi. You must be June.
- You must be April.
- Lloyd Stool.
- Hello, Lloyd. Hello.
Please come in, won't you?
Sammy, the Stools are here!
- Hello.
- Hi. Sammy.
- Pleasure to meet you. I'm April.
- Hi, April.
- Lloyd Stool.
- Lloyd. Yes, it's very nice to meet you.
- What a lovely home you have here.
- Oh, April, thank you.
Yes... and... we brought you some butter cookies.
(Gasps) Oh, how very thoughtful of you.
Oh, you're so thoughtful and so on time.
- Well, we're thrilled to be here.
- We're delighted you're here. So, drinks?
- I'm a Molson's man myself. (Breaks wind)
- Oh, Lloyd.
I'll have a little white wine with a splash of soda.
We'll call it a spritzer.
OK.
- (Lloyd coughs)
- April, please.
Oh, thank you.
Oh.
Well...
spritzers for the ladies.
- April.
- Thank you.
- June.
- Thank you, darling.
Ale for the men.
May I say something?
Ahhh.
I think you two are lovely people.
So, to put us all at ease,
I want you to think of us
not as some kind of inquisition,
but more as a welcoming wagon.
As far as I'm concerned,
you two will make wonderful neighbours.
(Gasps) April, thank you.
- So let's get that bottle out and celebrate.
- (Laughs)
Lloyd, what say?
Well...
I think there might be some reason...
...for celebration.
A toast. Welcome to the Huxley.
- Oh, Lloyd, April!
- That's great.
- Oh.
- Honey.
Mm.
- I wonder who that could be.
- Um...
I'll get it, dear.
- Lloyd, April, do have some hors d'ouevres.
- Thank you, June.
Sammy, hi! Great kissing. Can we come in?
- I can't believe you're here.
- I really need your help.
Um... June, April, Lloyd. Um...
- These are some friends of mine.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Lloyd Stool.
- Hey, blood.
- Look, man, the pigs are after us.
- Pigs?
Look, it's a long story, but we really need some...
Petra!
I told you we cannot call the police.
- (Petra sobs)
- Hey, Sammy, have you got a beer, man?
- In the fridge.
- Oh, yeah.
- Sammy.
- Huh?
Who are these people?
W...
Sammy, can Petra crash on your couch?
She really needs a lie down.
I don't think so, Sammy.
- Have you got an opener, man?
- On the side of the bar.
Oh, yeah.
- Groovy. Here it is.
- (Whispers) Stop him.
- Petra, I want you to lie down.
- (She gasps)
- Petra, stop it.
- Really good to see you.
You too, man. Look at the suit. Whoo!
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah.
- (Petra screams)
- What's going on?
Hey, man, what have you got?
Cement or something?
Sammy, look, we've got
these secret documents, man...
We were in the jungle
and these guys started firing...
- Listen...
- There was bleeding...
Stop! Man, stop.
I've got these people out there.
- I'm trying to buy a co-op.
- Co-op?
- Oh.
- These people out there, the Stools...
- Stools?
- Yeah. Lloyd and April.
- (Laughs)
- They're named the Stools?
It's not funny. It's not... (Laughs)
- Sammy.
- It sounds like a movie: Here Come The Stools.
- Who are these people?
- Oh, we're the Stools!
- You're going to have to leave.
- Sammy, man.
- I want them out.
- Excuse me. I was talking to Sammy.
- I want them out now!
- Hey, lady, back off!
- OK?
- All right, Fred. All right, June.
- Fred, come here. I need to talk to you.
- Sure.
- Listen to me.
- You Sammy's old lady?
- Come back in a couple of hours.
- We got nowhere to go, man.
We're all really scared. Sammy...
I need to talk to somebody. OK? Huh?
Say yes.
- All right, it's cool.
- If we lose this apartment...
June, relax, would you?
You guys just stay in here.
- Right on.
- I mean it. Stay in here.
BOTH: We're here, man.
- (Sobbing)
- What is this person doing on my bed?
I don't want her on my bed.
I'm having a very bad feeling.
I'm very sorry about this.
- They're friends of Sammy's...
- Old, old, old friends.
- I haven't seen them in...
- I've never even met them - ever.
FRED: The guy died right in my arms.
Yeah, he did give me the documents.
- Yeah, I'll hold.
- Christ, I need a Valium.
- What's a Valium?
- Oh, God, I'm in hell!
No, I don't have any.
No. Hey, man, I don't have any pictures.
No. But, see, I do have the documents.
What?
Yeah, you can call it a bloodbath if you want to.
But, see, I have these documents and that's...
No. No, I don't...
Yes. No. No, I don't have any pictures.
Excuse me? Excuse me?
What the fuck is wrong with you,
you yellowjournalist media pig?
I am not listening to you. (Hangs up)
Maybe somebody would like another drink?
I'll have another, Professor.
Wild Turkey.
Anybody got a Valium?
Petra needs two Valium.
Oh, food. Wow, I'm starving.
Oh, I left mine at home.
My name's April.
Ohh. Hey, a real pleasure to know you, April.
Oh.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
I'm only sitting for a minute.
Oh.
Eat up.
Well, what do you say
we get this party moving, right?
Come on, shake your body, baby,
do the conga
Know you can't control yourself any longer
Come on, shake your body, baby,
do the conga
Know you can't control yourself any longer...
Hey, Mrs Stool, let's dance.
- Oh, well, I never thought you'd ask, Hesus.
- All right, let's go.
Ahh.
- All right! Shake them buns!
- Ooh! Like this?
Yeah.
Hey, let 'em flap.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, here, let me.
Open wide for chunky!
Cool.
So you've been talking to the newspapers?
Yes, I have.
I don't know what your politics are,
but I've just got to say
newspapers are so screwed up.
- Pardon my French.
- Really?
I happen to have a few friends
who are associated with the popular press.
- Maybe I can help you.
- Really?
Hey, toro! Hey-hey.
Ol!
So...
what's the plot?
Arriba! Arriba!
OK. Ready, man?
We have these secret documents
that prove there's going to be a war.
I think maybe I have a solution for you.
Already?
Have you written your Congressman?
- That's a great idea, Lloyd.
- Good idea.
Hey, come on, follow me!
Ah, da da-da-da da-da! Hey, still back there?
Wooh, yeah-yeah!
(Boing!)
- Ooh!
- (Laughs) Look what you've got.
- Oh.
Oh, I wouldn't. I wouldn't.
- Magic fingers!
- Ooh!
They were going to put up some low-income
housing right across the street from the Huxley.
Would've ruined the neighbourhood.
A lot of people thought it was a no-win situation.
- Not me.
- Not Lloyd.
No, sir.
I telephoned my Congressman
and got action just like that.
JUNE: Clever man.
Wait a minute.
You're telling me that some poor,
underprivileged human beings
were denied a place to live
because you called your Congressman?
Yes! The system works.
You are a psychotic pig.
I don't know these people.
Did I say that to you, Lloyd? I've never met them.
- Oh.
- I'll just relieve myself.
Oh, OK. Need a hand?
You can bring all three of them.
My friend, it's a hard world.
Life is what you make it
and we make it what we can.
But there's never a cause to be abusive
at a cocktail party.
- Absolutely right.
- Never.
What is wrong with you, Sammy?
Have you changed that much? Huh?
Nah... fuck this.
I tell you time and time again,
we'll be feeling the repercussions
of the drug culture for years to come.
- Years.
- We should be going.
- Oh, Lloyd, please... Do something.
- April, where are you?
- Lloyd, I'm sorry.
- April, come out of the bathroom.
So, at that very moment,
with this gun pointed at my head,
I saw this... this image of myself,
this sort of um...
Joni Mitchell, Isadora Duncan,
naked wood nymph kind of a thing,
and it was this...
it was this... this precious spirit
that was gonna die if he pulled the trigger.
It was beautiful.
And...
Now that there's no gun pointed at my head,
of course, I can't see it any more.
FRED: Petra, we're leaving.
What shall I do? Tell me.
Should I be spontaneous?
Please, Lloyd. Please don't go!
Sammy, do something.
Hey, Sammy, what happened to you, man?
You used to make fun of people like yourself.
Sorry I took so long.
Sammy, thanks for letting us crash at your pad.
It was really groovy.
Cool.
What are you gonna do now?
I dunno. We'll probably go back to Ronnie's.
It's not your problem.
Hesus, let's go!
(Sitar music)
Hey.
Peace.
Far out.
One more. Come on, come on.
Pretend you're walking.
Whoa!
Come on.
We're going toward the door now, sweetheart.
Toward the door.
Hey...
do you have to go now?
Oh, yeah, well, my friends, you know...
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- We could see a movie together some time.
- That'd be a good idea.
- Great.
- God bless.
- You be good.
- Ooh!
Sammy, thanks for the cheese, man.
- Have you been drinking?
- (Slurs) Just a little, honey.
Hey, catch you round.
- It's late. I'm afraid we have to be leaving.
- Please don't go.
What can I say to assure you that these
are not the kind of people we know?
I've always been against low-income housing.
Fuck the poor!
Please give us another chance,
I'm begging you, Lloyd.
- June.
- Please.
- Give us another chance. I'm begging you.
- June. June, come on.
Look out that window. Look out there.
In another day or so the last brick will be up.
I'll have no sunshine, no air, no view - I'll die!
I'm sure you can understand that approving you
and your husband at this time
would not be in the best interests
of the Huxley tenants.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- No.
- It's all right.
Put your sweater on.
Don't worry. We'll get a bigger co-op
with more things in it. OK? Lt'll have more.
- I'm never taking you any place again.
- I don't care.
- I hate you. I hate your mother.
- I'm driving.
- This isn't happening to me.
- Put your head down and take deep breaths.
- It's like Invasion Of The Hippy People.
- What's happening?
Can I just sit here for a second, Lloyd?
- (June sobs)
- Don't fight.
- What's this?
- (Lloyd groans)
Oh, don't you like it?
(Continues sobbing)
Lloyd,
may I walk you out?
(Thud)
I'm fucking the... janitor.
- Of course.
- (June sobs)
Ta-da!
- Petra, you look so sweet.
- Wow. Wow, you look trippy.
- You look good.
(Knock at door)
Hi.
Er... I came to apologise.
I was a schmuck back there.
You know? I felt really bad when you guys left.
You came to me for help. I'm sorry.
Huh?
Ungowa.
Hey, check these out.
- Shotgun?
PETRA: Cool.
Yeah. Yeah, shotgun.
- Good one. Ooh.
- (Coughs)
(Laughs) A flash.
Hey, man, did Ronnie seal this place off
when we left?
- Yeah, she did.
- It's the same.
Yeah, it is. Exactly.
Wow.
Ohh.
- Hey, your book, man.
- Hey, Sammy.
- Wow, man.
- Are you still writing, man? You were great.
No... I don't write any more.
- Too bad.
- Yeah. I own... tanning salons.
BOTH: Huh?
- People pay me to get a tan.
BOTH: Oh.
Wow.
Hey, like, how do you get the sun to shine
just on those guys who pay, man?
(Laughs) Right. Listen, um...
You guys, tell me what's happening. OK?
Because I'm here 100%. Just lay it out for me.
We were walking down the street and...
and then these FBI guys grab us, man,
and then they throw us in this car.
I freak out cos I don't know what's happening.
I start choking on this one guy, and beating him,
and then we crash.
And then there's blood and... a fish.
- You choked an FBI agent?
- No, a fish.
Start at the beginning with the dead CIA agent.
- See, these revolutionaries...
- Dead CIA?
Er... guys, am I in any danger here?
BOTH: Oh, no.
Er, I'm having heavy dja vu, guys.
There's a man here
from the Justice Department.
- Oh.
- Oh, shit, they found us.
OK. I'll stall him. You go out the back way.
Hey, Sammy, let's go. Petra, come on. Hesus!
Isn't this exciting?
Oh, man. Should I call my wife?
Nah.
God, I haven't sat in this park for years.
Yeah, not since that time you belly-danced
naked in the fountain.
So what are we doing?
We're taking over the campus.
Hah.
Ungowa.
Dig it.
But I don't know...
Hey, guys, why don't we just sing?
Wouldn't that be nice? We could sing songs.
Kumbaya, my Lord
Kumbaya
Come on, guys, just sing with me.
Kumbaya, my Lord...
Oh, what the hell?
SAMMY: OK, we got a war in Central America.
That's good. What else?
FRED: What do you mean?
I mean, we have the floor.
We can say what we want to say about anything,
so we have a responsibility to say it.
So, what else do we want to say?
OK, well...
I'm a little out of touch.
What's going on with the planet?
- You mean, what are we grieving about?
- Grievances, right. Well, um...
- The cost of real estate is outrageous.
- Good. OK. So, housing.
I mean, I paid two million dollars for my place
and I still pay $2,000 a month maintenance.
- Believe that?
- Are you crazy?
Well, don't forget I've got walk-in closets.
There's also nuclear energy. That's a problem.
OK. What's going on with that?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
Pollution.
There's the normal, everyday pollution
that nobody talks about any more,
and then there's this acid rain.
Acid rain? What is acid rain?
- Well, it's just pollution.
- No, no. It gets in the rain, man.
- What does?
- The acid.
It's from the chemicals
going up in the smokestacks.
Cheap perfumes. That sort of thing.
It goes up and gets in the clouds.
It turns into acid.
When it rains back down, it kills lakes.
- That's it.
- It kills forests.
- How about a Ring Ding?
- Here, dude.
- Whoa. (Crash)
- This is going on right now?
- What is anybody doing about it?
- It's like the ozone thing.
- The ozone thing?
- Yeah.
I know what that is. That has
something to do with the deodorants.
No.
Scientists figured out that we blew a hole
in the upper atmosphere.
- We blew a hole in the atmosphere?
- Yeah, man. It's the um...
It's the fluorizones. Or er...
Sammy!
Fluorides. No, shit, that's toothpaste.
- It's um...it's the sprays.
- It's the deodorants.
OK, it's the aerosols,
from years and years of spraying this stuff.
It goes way up in the atmosphere,
blows a hole in the ozone and that can kill us.
- Are you hearing this?
- Oh, yeah, I got it.
You know what, we've got the housing.
We've got nuclear energy, we've got pollution.
We could dump those under big business.
And we need some more money going to Aids.
- Aids?
- Aids.
It's this er... wrath of God, sort of plague thing
that's killing people all over the planet.
- Crack!
- Crack? Crack?
Yeah, man, it's bad shit.
They smoke it.
It's like turning people into coconuts.
It's taken the old romantic edge off of drugs.
- Cruise missiles that can destroy us in minutes.
- There's 40 wars going on right now.
- Homeless. The homeless.
- Homeless, that's good. Cos that's bad.
- Farm foreclosures.
- Farms, yeah, man.
They're paying farmers not to grow.
They say there's too much food.
Too much? There are people starving.
And inflation's
gonna completely wipe out money.
I mean, that's happening right now.
The oceans and the trees are dying. What else?
- You know what really pisses me off?
- What?
They're colourising black-and-white movies.
I just saw It's A Wonderful Life in colour,
and I have to admit I just loved it.
Are you crazy?
They look like they have hepatitis.
- I loved it.
- Are you hearing this?
Don't you understand it is a total violation
of the director's point of view.
(Clattering)
Let's leave that one off the list.
There are people dying,
and you tell me there is acid in the forest.
There are missiles, there are plagues.
I'm standing here and it's like...
And it's like... I'm getting these...
"I don't care about my planet" vibes, right?
And I mean, it's like you people
act like you don't care at all.
Where is your outrage?
- I am outraged.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
I am outraged!
My name is Anus McVitie and I'm truly outraged
for I'm a victim of acid rain.
Oh, man, Sammy, your eyes.
Hey, I don't want acid rain.
- It's cool, it's cool.
- Cos I wouldn't like the jungle, man.
It's cool, it's cool.
Sammy, what have you done about these?
Have you done one thing about any of them?
- Huh?
- What the hell are you talking about?
Where were you, man? You disappeared.
There's holes in the atmosphere.
Why don't you know about any of this stuff?
- Yeah, Fred, where were you?
- Where was I?
You wanna know where I was?
I'll tell you where I was.
The war was coming to an end, right?
So things were slowing down.
Well, I got an idea.
I was going to create a utopian society.
Yeah.
It was going to be beautiful.
What happened?
We had our first meeting. We er...
We built our huts. We er...
...planted our grass.
We harvested our grass.
- We smoked the grass.
- Dig it.
PETRA: Then what happened?
- Fred?
- Wait a minute, I'm trying to remember.
There's nothing to remember.
You've been stoned for 20 years.
Where do you get the gall to come up here
and lay all this crap on us?
You're pointing fingers and shit
and you are wrong!
For the last two decades you've been in Oz
blowing your brains out with grass.
What am I going to say to you, man?
He's right.
I ran away.
I totally copped out.
- It's OK, Fred.
- No.
No.
It's not OK.
What are we gonna do?
Oh, what is the difference, man?
I mean...
What's the difference if we did do something
or we didn't, or we might do something?
The thing is, we're here now,
so just be here now.
That's all I gotta say.
I know where we were after the harvest, man.
We were dreaming about tonight.
We were dreaming about a night
when we could all be together again.
And here we are... 20 years later.
It's blowing my mind.
We've been brought back together for a reason,
man. It's destiny, I know it. You know?
That's all I gotta say.
Who cares if we dropped out?
What difference does it make?
Here we are, man. You know?
We're together.
We've got a second chance. You know?
And it's like in the olden days, man.
It's like, if it's only for one night,
anything's possible. (Chuckles)
You know, it's like the future of the world
is in our hands one more time.
(Laughter)
There's been a fever
Stand up and fight...
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Some assholes
have locked us out of our classes.
What does that mean? Are we off?
Stand up for hope
We are the answer
To it all...
Hello, students of NYU.
Stand up and fight
We're gonna stand up and fight
Hippies have taken over the campus.
Sound familiar? Well, that's exactly what
has happened here at New York University.
Four unidentified demonstrators
have taken over Wilson Hall
in protest against the war in Central America.
You may be asking
which war in Central America.
If so, count yourself among the many students
here who are equally confused.
How's that?
OFFICER: It's the top floor.
The police are here.
Somebody better do something.
Come on, man.
Look at the people down there,
it's like a concert.
OK. Cool. OK.
- How's my hair?
- Beautiful.
- OK, guys, give me a good first line.
- Fred, listen, I got something for you.
Listen, I couldn't sleep last night,
so I wrote you that.
- Sammy...
- You don't have to use it.
This is great, man. Thanks.
Thank you very much.
Yeah. Mm.
- Yeah. I say...
- (Grunts) Ungowa!
- Dig it.
- All right, man.
Oh...
Hi. Hi.
First let me apologise
for taking over this building. I er...
I know you're all eager to get to your classes.
But what we're doing here is very important.
In a couple of months
there is going to be a secret US operation
to overthrow a small Central American country
and start a war.
That's a war in which Americans
will be asked to fight.
I came here to tell you about a war.
But I realise that something more important,
more fundamental has got to be said.
Oh.
- Where's the rest of it?
- There's another page.
No, there's not.
(Papers rustle)
Ah...
I ran out of papers, man. I smoked it.
You want some?
Er...
Last night I found out that pretty soon this planet,
our hope, our Mother Earth...
...will not be able to support life.
We won't be able to breathe,
we won't be able to swim,
we won't be able to walk in the sun.
Now, I believe
that God made us from this earth
with a purpose.
To be her ears, to be her eyes.
But we stopped seeing and we're not listening.
And pretty soon if we don't open our hearts,
and our minds, then that's it.
The end.
I know a lot has changed since the '60s.
But I still believe that in each one of us,
in every individual, there is this light.
This spirit.
It's a beautiful spirit and it says, "I want to live.
I want to live in peace.
I want to live in beauty.
I want to live the way God designed it."
Now the only way we are going to change
the situation here is...
if you...
and you...
and you, and everybody here...
would get everybody they know.
And everybody they know will get
everybody they know to come together
as one relentless force and fight
for the kind of world we want to live in.
A world for our children.
This is our responsibility.
To serve with love this great spirit
we share with each other,
and with this earth, our home.
LOUDSPEAKER:
Wilson Hall will be closed today.
All scheduled classes will be transferred
to the following locations.
Please listen for your class numbers.
- Behavioural psychology 103...
- Where are you going?
Where is everybody going?
You've got a chance to help here.
Economics 102 will be in the Students' Centre.
I have proof there is going to be a war.
- This is great. Get the disillusionment.
- You've got a chance to help.
There is going to be a war.
Don't you care that our world is dying?
Don't you care about our trees and our oceans?
Please, listen to me.
We have to care.
- Where are they going?
- Come on down, man.
Come on, man.
- English Literature 104, the Nelson Building.
- Come on down, man.
- (Tannoy announcements continue)
- Hey, let's get the fuck out of here.
Let's get out of here.
Come on, come on. Come on.
I wanna go home, man.
I don't know. This is good.
This is very good.
I've been waiting... 20 years
to knock the shit out of you hippy assholes.
And here I am. (Laughs)
So, er... where are the papers?
Eat shit!
See! See!
See, that's what...
It's people like you...
I mean, you just chisel away at a work of art
that it took 200 years to build.
You got it wrong, man.
We love this country.
Well...
- Well, then give me the papers.
- Eat shit!
You are a goddamn traitor and you will
do anything to embarrass this country.
I am an American.
I am duty-bound to make this country better.
- Give me those papers.
- Eat shit.
(Click)
(High-pitched)  Oh, say can you see
By the dawn's early light
O beautiful for spacious skies
For amber waves of green
Doo-wah, diddy, diddy-dum, diddy-do
Doo-wah, diddy, diddy...
All right!
Oh, you think you're a big genius, don't you?
Well, let me tell you, Mr Gandhi,
those plans, those papers...
...they're fake.
- Eat shit.
- Eat shit, I know.
If you could read,
you would've read the first two pages
that state that the plan
is a hypothetical scenario.
You see? It's a game we play.
A big "What if?"
I mean, we're composing plans like that
all the time.
You're a fool.
You're a...
You're a big fat fool.
(Yells) Now where are the goddamn papers?
Newsreel fanfare
I'd like to expose a heinous crime
that's about to be committed by this country.
(Newsreel music)
Excuse me. Are you for or against sending
American soldiers into Central America?
We haven't won anything in so long,
it would be nice.
Sir? Excuse me, sir? Are you for or against
sending American troops into Central America?
Well, I'm a liberal Republican.
I believe we should go to war, but...
I also think
we should put the homeless in uniform
and give them an opportunity
to lead productive lives.
You think about that.
Nuke 'em!
(Machine-gun fire)
(Explosions boom)
So you started a war. Shit happens.
You know, it could be good.
- War. That can be a good thing.
- What?
Listen to what I'm saying.
At least it gets people motivated.
I do feel motivated.
I'm sorry. I'm furious and I'm loving it,
and it's because of you.
I started a fucking war!
Well, that's true.
But now you can try and stop it and maybe
some other things that need stopping.
What for?
We could get the Headroom happening again.
Ronnie?
Are you kidding?
I'd close this place in a second.
Come on, man. I'll keep writing, all right?
We can get the movement happening again.
We'll just make 'em listen.
Yeah. Um...
You can always stay with me and er...
I know that you don't have anybody special
to go home to. And...
We're all here and...
we'd like you to stay...
I'd like you to stay.
Honey...
(Exhales slowly)
I can't stay here.
I'm sorry.
- Hey, Hesus, let's go.
- Fred, let us know where you're going.
I love you, Ronnie.
- Hey, you too.
- Yeah.
Peace.
All right!
The world's rotten! People suck.
Stay.
Just stay, man.
Be good.
BILL MEDLEY: Rude Awakening
Tried to catch the moon
Tried to count the stars
Tried to run as fast as I can
In my darkest hours
I hear a lot of laughter
I've seen a lot of pain...
Look, I don't know where I'm going
so if you wanna stay that's OK.
I'm with you, bro.
I've had enough pizza, man.
What have they done?
Where?
Where have they gone?
Why?
Why have they changed?
In the concrete jungle
I open my eyes
(Sobs)
To a rude awakening
Ungowa.
(Continues sobbing)
Mr Wouk.
Mr Wouk, my name is Lawrence.
Lawrence Tilby. And er...
We all heard you speak at NYU.
And er... let me just tell you,
I live right across the river
and there's this goddamn plant over there.
And they're pouring millions of gallons
of all this toxic crap into the river.
And nobody seems to give a shit.
And after I heard you speak, well,
a few of us got together and...
Seth's got this brother.
- I have a brother who...
- In Cleveland.
And he's got this major problem
where he lives too.
The river caught on fire.
- The river caught on fire?
- Yeah.
So we thought maybe we should do something.
- Co-ordinate some sort of an action.
- Wait a minute.
The water in the river actually caught on fire?
Yeah.
- Oh, I'd like to see that, man.
- (Chuckles)
We wanna co-ordinate
some kind of action between us
and we thought maybe you could help us
put something together.
We're really glad we found you.
We loved what you said at school.
I mean, really.
Yeah, we're not gonna fight some war
that somebody made up.
See, Mr Wouk? Some of us did hear ya.
We did. Oh, yeah.
So... will you help us?
- Hey, Hesus. What is it, man?
(Metallic clattering)
(Coughing and spluttering)
Wow!
So it's true.
The river really did catch on fire.
What do you think, I'm an hallucination?
- (Fish continues spluttering)
- Hey. Peace.
Oh...
Smoked fish.
(Cackles)
Smoked fish!
MIKE AND THE MECHANICS: Revolution
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/3dh49
Help other users to choose the best subtitles