Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
[Man Panting]
Ca Lu, half a click that way,
two-nine-zero.
- I say we go right up the middle.
- Negative.
One round flank up the hill, the
other one right through the swamp.
Heads, you get the hill.
Tails, you get the swamp.
Flip the motherfucker.
- See you in Ca Lu.
- All right.
[Mouths Words]
[Man Speaking
In Vietnamese]
[Vietnamese]
[Vietnamese Continues]
[Shouting]
Delta Two, whats your SITREP?
Over.
What do you got,
Gibson?
Nothing, sir.
Delta One, Delta Two, SITREP. Over.
Two-one, contact!
Contact way out!
[Screams]
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Go, go, go.
Lets get 'em!
Come outta there!
Put your hands on your head!
Get on your knees now!
Come on!
Down, down.
Come on out of there!
Now!
How many you slopes are out here?
Huh? Whats your unit? Whats in it?
Tuan, get over here!
Talk to these motherfuckers!
- Find out how many of them are here!
- [Translating In Vietnamese]
Where are they? Whats in it?
Talk to me, goddamn it!
[Tuan Continues]
Aah!
Two, this is One Actual.
Where are you?
[Gunfire On Radio]
Uuh!
Other side of the tree line.
I'm in the water unable to withdraw.
Unable to withdraw! I'm calling
in a fire mission on this position!
- Hurry up and drop that arty!
- They're all over!
[Static,
Transmission Crackling]
[Man]
Go left! Get out there!
Tell this man to get on that radio
and pull his men off Hodges.
Tell him to break contact
and move his men north of Ca Lu!
[Translating]
Tell him I ain't playin'!
Pull his men off Hodges now!
[Tuan Continues]
I ain't bullshittin'
with you.
Either you call your men off
Hodges,
or this motherfucker's
dead and you're next.
- [Tuan Continues]
- Last warnin'!
Uuh!
Call your men
off Hodges now!
If he does, he can go.
He's got my word on that.
If you don't,
I'll kill you where you stand.
[Tuan Continues]
[Groaning]
[Vietnamese]
[Men Shouting]
[Groaning]
[Man On Radio] Two, this is
One Actual. You still with me?
Crank off a pop-up
if you're still alive.
[Grunts]
You got a reprieve, you hear me?
You don't get to die today.
You got your "Hail Mary."
?? [Blues Rock]
Hey! Its the colonel
with his cover on!
[Cheering, Applause]
All right!
Make way, make way!
- I guess the drinks are on me.
- All right!
At ease!
Listen up.
- ?? [Stops]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
the reason we're all here,
Colonel Hayes Hodges.
[Cheering]
He's calling it a career after
32 years of distinguished service.
All right, all right.
Colonel, we got you a gift
and a surprise,
so don't act like
you're not coming up here.
[All Chanting]
Speech! Speech! Speech!
Speech! Speech!
Speech!
[Cheering]
Hey, my man!
Good to see you.
You damn well better be. I came
halfway 'round the world for this.
Hey, get up here.
[Man]
Speech!
The sword, Colonel.
You know the story, Hayes.
Marine Lieutenant Presley O'Banion
defeated the Barbary pirates...
on the shores of Tripoli
in 1805.
Out of gratitude, the pasha
gave him the Mameluke sword.
Marine officers have
carried one ever since.
Its the symbol
of a warrior,
and you are a warrior.
- [Cheering]
- The best I ever served with.
This man's been riding a desk
for the past 28 years,
but not because he wanted to.
He knows how to fight.
Its in his blood. Ah-ooh!
[Man] What are you
gonna do now, Colonel?
Well, uh... Well.
Heh! No more wars to fight,
no more trials to lose.
- [Clears Throat]
- [Laughter]
So I expect I'll do
some teaching at V.M.I.
I will recon the local restaurants
in a concerted effort...
- to find out what civilians eat.
- [Laughter]
Of course, I intend to continue
serving my country...
by honorably depleting
the trout streams...
of the Southern United States
with my fly rod!
Thats about it.
Lets get outta here.
- I missed you.
- Yeah, I missed you too.
How's the kid,
the smart Hodges?
You know, he studies more than
any two people. I never see him.
- You gotta fix that.
- Yeah.
- Got my orders.
- Oh, yeah? What?
Got command of the 24th
Marine Expeditionary Unit.
- Special Operations capable.
- Congrats. Huh! Congrats.
- Yeah.
- Outstanding.
All I gotta do is lash
'em together, take 'em to sea.
[Quietly]
Thats, uh... outstanding.
You ain't missin' nothin', Hodge.
Its a whole new ball game.
No friends, no enemies,
no front, no rear.
No victories, no defeats,
no Mama, no Papa.
- Yeah.
- We're orphans out there.
Its funny, you know?
One guy walks out through a swamp,
he gets to come home to a desk.
Another guy drives up a hill
and he gets to still be doin' it,
all over the flip
of a goddamn coin.
You know, thats...
Its funny.
You gave good service
to the corps, Hodge.
To think otherwise
would be just plain crazy.
- You'd have gotten your command.
- Oh, yeah, sure.
[Sighs]
[Man On P.A.,
Indistinct]
Whats up, John?
Terry, we've been ordered
to the Arabian Sea, Gulf of Aden.
This comes straight down Second
Division through General Perry.
The American Embassy in Yemen
is surrounded...
by a crowd of demonstrators.
The crowd isn't hostile,
but its large enough...
to spook their government
into pulling their security forces.
Twenty-fourth Marine Expeditionary
Units gonna provide extra security.
We're gonna baby-sit, Colonel.
Just show our presence.
Remember, though, if it turns
hot, we're looking at an evac.
We got an ambassador and his family
there. Let me run you through this.
Here's your
potential L.Z.s.
Marines at the embassy advise we can
gain entrance through the back way.
Here's some stairs where you
can deploy your men to the roof.
These are your
over-watch positions.
I'll take them in
myself quietly.
One platoon, TRAP team,
put everyone else on Ready Five.
My thoughts exactly,
Colonel.
[Indistinct Shouts]
[Chanting In
Native Language]
[Chanting Continues]
[Boy]
Whats wrong, Mommy?
The people are upset
about some things, darling.
- Are they mad at Daddy?
- No, they're not mad at your daddy.
Why are they yelling?
They're trying to get attention
so that people will listen to them.
Sir, state security analysts
are asking for an assessment.
Assessment? We're getting the hell
out of here. Thats the assessment.
The Sixth Fleet marines
are in the air, sir.
If they think I'm gonna
tough this one out, they're crazy.
Tell Mrs. Mourain to start packing.
We're going home.
Shall I indicate
we're ready to evacuate?
Ask them where the hell
are those helicopters!
The ambassador wants to know
where the choppers are.
You heard me.
Where the hell are the choppers?
[Indistinct
Radio Transmission]
[Shouting]
Lock and load!
[Bullets Ricochetting]
[Man On Radio] We're gonna
take a better look before we go in.
[Grunting, Groaning]
Wagon Wheel, this is Red Man.
I'm over the embassy.
This ain't no baby-sit.
Its ugly down there.
[Man On Radio]
Red Man, Wagon Wheel.
Roger that.
Lets go for the evac.
Put it on deck.
We're going in the north side.
[Indistinct Shouts]
There! Go!
- Captain Lee!
- [Lee] Yes, sir!
Nobody comes over those walls
or through those gates. Nobody!
One Alpha, secure all entries.
Tango and Bravo, on the walls!
- Move, move, move!
- Last man! Last man!
Pull back! Pull back!
[Indistinct]
Take cover!
- [Childers] You speak English?
- Yes!
Where's the ambassador?
He's topside! Go topside!
[Man] Take that corner!
Take that side! Move!
Aah!
Move, move, move!
Go, go!
Bravo Two, left!
Move, move, move!
Incoming sniper fire!
Stay down! Stay down!
- Two blue, clear!
- [Mrs. Mourain Yelps]
- Who's Mrs. Mourain?
- L-I'm Mrs. Mourain.
- Where's the ambassador?
- He's in there. Are we leaving?
The helos are outside, ma'am,
but thats up to the ambassador.
Stay away from
the windows, please.
Duck! Ow!
Aah! Colonel! Please!
My God! Are the helicopters here?
What kept you people so long?
We're ready to evacuate, unless you
want to stay and run the embassy.
I want to go right... now!
We called hours ago!
All right, sir, come to me.
Stay calm and come to me.
- Stay calm. Come to me. Stay low.
- We're like targets!
- We're sitting targets!
- Follow Sergeant Mac. Go!
Come on! Down there!
Down there! Right there!
Right there!
Down there! Down there!
Go ahead, ma'am!
Go ahead!
Go ahead, ma'am, go ahead!
Come on, son. Come on!
- Whats your name, son? Justin?
- Justin.
[Sobbing]
Come on, Justin! Come on!
- Justin, whats that you got there?
- A flashlight.
We're gonna ride in a helicopter.
Wanna bring that with you?
- Huh? Come on. Come on!
- Mommy!
Lets go, ma'am, go!
Go, go, go!
All TRAP Unit six,
stay low, stay low!
We got crap coming over the walls
and sniper fire at 100 meters. Over.
Stay low! Sit tight,
sit tight, sit tight!
[Continues, Indistinct]
Colonel, we got three marines hit!
One is K.I.A.
One Alpha says they're gonna
try to breach the front gate!
- Tell them to wait out!
- Roger that!
- [Indistinct Shouts]
- [Helicopter Blades Whirring]
[Man] Put the missus on board
first. Get in there, Mr. Ambassador.
I'll personally recommend you...
Where's the belt?
- I'll personally recommend...
- Hold it!
Where are you going? What? Colonel!
Colonel, we can't wait here!
Come on! Lets get out!
Come on!
Lets go! Christ!
[Man] We're leaving
in just a few seconds.
Lets go! Why are we sitting here?
Why are we sitting here?
- Sir, please! Look at me. Stay calm.
- Lets go!
She's free, sir!
Go!
Hope you know how
to fold this, sir.
Thank you, Colonel.
I'll never forget this.
Sir.
Go!
[Groaning]
[Panting]
- [Grunting, Groaning]
- [Man] Krasevitch is hit!
Corpsman! Corpsman!
Shit!
Goddamn it!
Fuck!
Six, Red Man.
Engage hostile targets
as they appear.
Deadly force is authorized.
How copy? Over.
Red Man, Trans Six Actual.
Negative, negative!
Be advised, I have women
and children in my line of fire.
I got snipers in the buildings
at 400 meters. How copy? Over.
What is it about this order
you don't understand, Captain Lee?
Sir, are you ordering me
to fire into the crowd? Over.
Yes, goddamn it!
Waste the motherfuckers!
Six out.
Engage! Engage!
Open fire!
[Screaming]
Cease fire!
Stay down! There may still be
snipers out there.
Cease fire!
- Cease fire, goddamn it!
- Everybody stay down!
There may still be snipers
out there. Stay down!
Get down!
[Wailing]
[Woman Screaming]
- Sergeant Mac.
- [Mac] Sir?
Contact all stations.
Mission complete.
Launch medevacs.
Dead and wounded out first.
Aye, Colonel.
All stations, this is Red Man.
Mission complete.
Move all medevacs to L.Z.
How copy? Over.
[Car Horn Honks]
[Siren Blaring]
[Man]
The F.B.I. Investigation shows...
that all the bullet holes
in the embassy wall...
came from directly across
the way, from the snipers.
Any weapons or ammo found
among the dead or wounded?
No, sir. Nothing.
However, intelligence suggests...
this could have been
a terrorist operation.
Any proof?
This is a tape from
the embassy security system.
- Want me to thread it up?
- No. I don't want to watch videos.
I don't want to hear about
ammo casings in some building,
'cause here I got
83 dead people...
unarmed...
women, children, old men.
Another hundred or so
critically wounded.
Here I got an international
crisis of mega fucking proportions!
Bill, you know there have been
regular reports...
of a terrorist
plot against this embassy.
This was a regularly scheduled
protest. It was every week.
It was the usual bullshit about
American presence in the gulf.
Have you looked at these?
I mean, I'm just assuming you have,
since they're on the front page
of every newspaper in the world.
Its not that the rest of the
world wants to hold us responsible,
we are responsible!
We can't even have
the appearance of a cover-up.
That does not excuse us
from our duty, Mr. Sokal.
We sent Colonel Childers in there,
and the mission went to shit.
We can't go after the man
who carried out his orders...
and ignore the people
who issued those orders.
Childers ordered the slaughter...
of innocent women and children.
Get that straight right now.
I'll tell you
what we ought to get straight.
We lost three
United States Marines.
They lost 83!
Now, are we gonna go to war
with Yemen over it?
We're covering our ass all over
the Middle East right now, General.
Because of your man's
hotheaded miscalculation,
we are in danger of losing embassies
in Saudi, Jordan and Egypt.
We're in danger
of losing our presence...
with every moderate
in the region.
Now they're gonna scream
"cover up."
The screaming will get so loud we'll
be sending Marines back over there,
and the body count of American
dead is gonna be higher than three.
I see where you're going
with this, Mr. Sokal.
Will you be needing me
anymore today?
No.
No, thats fine, General.
Thank you.
Good day to you, sir.
[Sighs] Where do you think
you're going with that?
- You don't want to look at it.
- Nobody's lookin' at it.
Why should the United States
be held responsible...
for the actions of one man?
What if the crowd
had weapons?
What if this shows
they did fire first?
He could have fired over
their heads, this moron!
Didn't he know where he was?
The Middle East!
He could have isolated
on the snipers.
He could have
avoided confrontation.
He could have done
50 fuckin' things!
Instead, he destroyed a fragile
trust, put his own men in danger...
Fuck this guy!
Forget this tape.
I don't want to watch it.
I don't want to testify about it.
I don't want it to exist.
[Men Shouting In Distance,
Indistinct]
[Women Together]
Good morning, sir.
[Together]
Aye, aye, sir.
- [Man, Indistinct]
- [General] As soon as its time.
General, Colonel Childers
reporting as ordered, sir.
- Give us a minute, Skip.
- Yes, sir.
Colonel, its my duty to inform
you that you've been charged with...
[Sighs]
You know the drill.
This is the Article 32
investigation.
You're facing
a general court-martial...
and charged with violation
of at least three articles...
everything from "breach of peace"
to "conduct unbecoming."
But the bottom line... 83 counts,
violation of Article 118, murder.
You issued an illegal order
to have your marines...
fire into a group
of innocent civilians.
Murder, sir?
I'm the convening authority, so I've
gotta get this B.S. Out of the way.
Sign here, initial here.
You're not a flight risk, so there
won't be any pretrial confinement.
This court-martial convenes
in eight days...
by direct order of
the national command authority.
Do you want me to call
Bob Bennett or one of those guys,
or do you want to go
with base legal?
Terry, goddamn it,
we've been friends for 20 years.
You want to tell me exactly
what the hell happened out there?
I lost marines. The crowd
was hostile. They fired on us.
They fired first, sir.
I want you to know
I did everything in the world...
to keep this from happening.
Its just out
of my hands now.
Thanks a lot.
When's the last time you
actually caught something here?
- Two years.
- [Chuckles]
- I really need your help.
- I'll help. Anything you need.
You want me to take the stand?
I'll be a character witness.
No, you don't understand
what I'm asking.
I want you
to be my lawyer.
[Sighs]
I'm a good enough lawyer to know
you need a better lawyer than me.
'Sides that, I'm short.
Two-nine plus one wake-up,
and I'm gone.
You need one of those
Washington cats.
I don't want some Starbucks
drinker who's never seen combat.
- I need somebody who's been shot at.
- Yeah, I've been shot at.
Thats what I am...
a shot-up marine.
As a matter of fact,
thats all the hell I am.
No, wait a minute.
I'm also a weak lawyer.
I'm a very weak lawyer...
and the government is gonna come
at you with everything they've got.
Major, Bill Sokal. Its a pleasure
to meet you. Come on in.
Let me introduce you.
Gentlemen, this
is Major Mark Biggs.
He'll be prosecuting
the Childers court-martial.
The marines put the major
through Stanford Law,
and he owes them a couple of years
before he takes over the world.
You know General Lowry.
I'd like you to meet the general
of theJoint Chiefs of Staff,
General West, and the secretary
of Defense, Mr. Wyatt.
Have a seat.
Make yourself comfortable.
What I gather from our esteemed NSC
advisor and secretary of state...
is that we've got a trial
in two weeks.
- Seems awfully damned fast.
- Everyone in this room will agree...
its in the national interest that
this trial be moved along quickly.
The Article 32 investigation
was complete and comprehensive.
It all seems to point
in one direction.
Has he got a lawyer yet?
He's requested a military
attorney, Colonel Hayes Hodges.
Second Marine Division, Lejeune.
Any relation to
General H. Lawrence Hodges?
His son.
Larry Hodges was one of this country's
most distinguished officers.
What do we know about
Colonel Hayes Hodges?
He's a guy who got
blown apart in Vietnam,
then went to Georgetown Law
and became a cynic.
Is that about right, Major?
He was 67th in his class
at Georgetown, sir.
He doesn't take too many cases,
doesn't win too many.
He apparently went through an ugly
divorce, had a drinking problem,
- retiring in two weeks.
- Can we guarantee we get this guy?
Sir, if I may
say something?
I am not a hired gun.
I accepted this assignment...
'cause I believe in the merits
of the governments case.
I am not gonna stack the deck
against this guy.
I will try this case
on good evidence only.
I'm glad to hear it.
[Man]
Hold your fire.
- Set that weapon down over here.
- [Man, Indistinct]
[Man, Distant] We need
a couple of canteens up here.
[Helicopter Blades
Whirring]
- [Man] Party incoming!
- You can go.
You can go, goddamn it!
Go on! Dee dee!
Get the fuck out of here
before I change my mind!
Looks like you're going back
to the world, baby.
- Doc!
- [Man] Twenty meters out. Left!
- Right there.
- [Hodges] Anybody else?
[Child Giggles]
I got you now!
- Hey, buddy!
- Hi, Mom.
He looks fabulous.
- Happy anniversary, Mom.
- Oh, thank you. So good to see you.
I wasn't sure you'd make it.
- You look wonderful.
- Thank you.
- How's it feel to be retired?
- Um, crazy.
Good. Oh, you look great.
- Thank you.
- Well, come see Dad...
- There he is.
- And all the family.
Hello, sir.
- Glad you could make it.
- Yes, sir.
[Laughter,
Crowd Chatter]
- [Man] Good to see you, Hayes.
- How are you doing?
Hey, kid. Hey, you.
Remember me?
- The old guy who looks like you.
- Do I know you?
- Yeah.
- Your voice sounds really familiar.
Here's a clue: I was married
to your mom for about five minutes.
- Really? You sure? 'Cause I don't...
- Yeah. [Chuckles]
[Chattering]
- Well, is he guilty?
- Sir?
Your friend
Colonel Childers.
- Guilty of what, sir?
- Come on, Hayes.
You served with him. Is he the rabid
dog we've all been hearing about?
I don't think
I should comment, sir.
Come on, Dad. This is family.
You can lighten up a little.
You know what we said
at the naval academy.
Even if you thought
you weren't responsible,
it went wrong
and you were there.
Since when have you
not had a comment?
Since Childers asked me
to defend him.
[Man] No. Oh, Hayes.
- [Woman] What?
- [Son] Excuse me.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
Why would you do that?
Huh!
- Because he asked me, and I owe him.
- Thats great.
That represents everything
thats wrong with the military.
Wisdom from the one person
in this family...
who has not elected
to serve his country.
Childers must have snapped.
It happens in combat.
I've seen it.
I'm sure you have too.
Thank you for reminding me...
why we have the presumption
of innocence in America.
[Scoffs] What are you, Abraham
Lincoln? You can't hide behind that.
The guy murdered innocent women
and children.
- You hear that on television?
- And newspapers.
- Its all over the place.
- Its Mom and Daïs anniversary.
Don't take this case, son.
This man has trashed
the reputation of the Corps.
He's put us back 20 years.
Is this how you want
to be remembered?
I don't see how I can
turn him down. He saved my life.
Well, I understand that
as well as anyone.
But you don't repay him by
falling senselessly on a grenade.
The way I see it,
this man should find himself...
- the best laywer in the country.
- Somebody better than me?
The guy's
a real marine, Dad.
I mean, if they
can do this to him...
just hang him out to dry...
they can do it to anybody.
Forget that he's my friend.
They can do it to anybody.
That means your medals
and your citations...
won't mean jack shit
when they come after you.
[Metal Clinking]
At least two of his own guys
are gonna testify...
that he didn't have
to open fire, sir.
Nobody reports seeing any
weapons among the demonstrators.
- His psych eval was a disaster.
- What about embassy footage?
Cameras, film, videotape,
home movies, shit like that?
No, I've subpoenaed everything.
The embassy got hit pretty good.
- Most of it was destroyed.
- [Door Opens]
[Man Grunting]
Terry, you know Tom Chandler. He's
gonna help us prepare your case.
Colonel Childers, good to see
you again, sir. Um, all right.
First, we've subpoenaed all
the Article 32 investigator's notes,
the State Departments
notes on Yemen.
Major Biggs has already had
your head checked by their doctor.
I've got you an appointment
with ours.
- No.
- What?
No more multiple choice
questions about self-esteem.
We got the combat fitness reports.
He can forget the psych eval here.
Thats a mistake, Colonel.
Listen, when I turned 18
I joined the Marine Corps.
I asked to be in the infantry.
- I asked to go to Vietnam.
- Terry.
I live for the privilege
of commanding troops.
I think its the greatest honor
an American can have.
You know how many birthdays
and Christmases I missed,
spent rotting in jungles
or in the desert,
just so you could play
war at ROTC?
Childers! You gotta keep
your shit together here, man.
Your court-martial board
is gonna be made up of people...
who mightve spent one day in
Grenada, maybe two days in Kuwait.
They're gonna be beach boys who've
never been anywhere near combat.
They're gonna be people
like Tom Chandler...
sitting right here in front of you.
Thats who you're
making your case to.
We don't have anybody
to back up your case.
Thats because
all my witnesses are dead.
- Okay. So what happened?
- He lost it. He snapped.
Thats good.
We can snap him on the stand.
This doesn't happen in a vacuum.
Lets get a complete history
of Colonel Childers.
Talk to every marine
he ever served with.
My guess is
this has happened before.
We have to be careful here.
This guy is
the warrior's warrior.
A Navy Cross, two Silver Stars
for composure in battle.
He has no wife, no kids,
just the Corps.
He was our best.
Thats why he was sent.
He's not on trial for the
good service he gave the country,
but for what he did
on the wall in Yemen, period.
Major, nobody wants to say it,
but it occurs to me we're trying
to set an example here.
So lets set it and show
the world we mean business.
The first charge supports the death
penalty, and I say we go for it.
No more death.
I'll see that he never gets another
command and I'll put him in jail,
but I will not seek death for a man
who served his country honorably.
I don't want it
brought up again.
We gotta show
Childers' state of mind.
We gotta prove he went out
with intent to kill,
and that is not going to be easy.
Whether a man is charged
with murder or hailed as a hero...
is sometimes a very thin line.
Our case is this: Childers receives
orders that a regularly scheduled,
lawful protest outside
our embassy in Yemen is unruly.
He is to secure
or evacuate the premises.
There has been no violence
prior to his arrival.
Once there, Ambassador Mourain...
does not feel the situation
warrants evacuation.
- Childers ignores him.
- There was sniper fire.
They draw fire from snipers
across the street.
Childers retaliates into an unarmed
crowd in front of the embassy.
A crowd of women and children.
He shot the wrong people.
[Man On Radio]
All right, here's what this means.
Murder... Obviously, he could get
up to the death penalty.
Conduct unbecoming an officer.
Max is dismissal
with a dishonorable discharge,
forfeiture of all pay and allowances
and confinement for one year.
[Woman] What about breach
of peace? What is that?
Breaching the peace is minor.
That means participating in an act
of violent or turbulent nature...
that deprives the community of the
peace and tranquility it deserves.
Its sort of the military equivalent
of the civilian misdemeanor.
- No big deal.
- [Chattering, Shouting]
[Man] There he is!
You goddamn baby killer!
Baby killer!
You're disgusting!
I'm not answering any questions,
all right? Get out of here. Go away.
You fucking baby killer!
Fuck you!
Who the fuck are you
to spit on this uniform? Huh?
You ever play blackjack, Colonel?
Not really.
There are no intangibles.
Its all odds, sir.
You know them, you'll beat
the guy next to you.
You know what cards have been
played, you'll beat the house.
Sometimes you just can't win
no matter what you do.
I saw your man on television
knockin' some zit-faced kid around.
You have to understand the kind of
pressure Childers has been under.
A man with that kind of service...
No, no thanks.
This was a rescue mission
that went bad. Nothing more.
You're aware, Colonel,
we could ask for the death penalty.
You're not serious.
Oh, I'm very serious.
In fact, its been suggested.
What do you think would happen
if a Yemeni killed 83 Americans?
He'd have a trial
that would last for one day,
and they'd take off his head.
Have a seat, Colonel.
Please.
So here it is:
You plead him out. Guilty.
He throws himself at the mercy.
- We'll help him out at sentencing.
- How much help?
I'm not about to promise you
anything, but I'd say...
in the neighborhood of ten
to fifteen, out in seven.
Major,
do you know what the life expectancy
was for a second lieutenant...
dropped into a combat zone
in Vietnam in 1968?
I don't have time
for 20 questions, sir.
Then whats all this shit about
the odds of winning at blackjack?
You got time.
Take a guess.
My guess is your man's going down
'cause he deserves to go down.
I got a question for you, Colonel.
What happened at Ca Lu?
The battle of Ca Lu,
Vietnam.
You were there with Childers.
Something happened. What was it?
Fuck you is what happened
at Ca Lu, Biggs.
Two weeks.
Life expectancy of
a second lieutenant...
in combat in Vietnam
was two weeks.
Sir, I need more time
to prepare this case.
I need your permission
to go to Yemen...
Its all here, Hodge. We did an
exhaustive Article 32 investigation.
This thing happened
3,000 miles away. I need more time.
Colonel, its all here.
We had it brought from Yemen,
and its not unusual to convene...
a court-martial
on short notice.
There could be witnesses, something
the investigators overlooked, sir.
Don't you think Colonel Childers
is entitled all consideration?
Colonel Hodges, I don't care
if you go to China.
We have our marching orders,
and this court-martial...
will convene
at 0900 a week Monday.
- Now, is that clear?
- Yes, sir.
[Man Leading Cadence,
Indistinct]
[Men]
One! Two!
[Doorbell Rings]
...contact the sergeant?
- He's off-base, sir.
[Doorbell Rings]
Terry?
Childers?
Ohh.
Oh, shit.
Its okay.
- [Sighs]
- Its okay.
- I wasn't...
- No, no. I know.
Its okay. Its all right.
I know. Believe me, I know.
[Sighs] Can I leave you alone
with that thing in the house?
Yeah. I ain't goin' six
on you, Hodge.
I'm goin' to Yemen.
If I have to stick your ass
in a hospital till I get back,
- that is what I will do.
- You don't have to do that.
Got your word on that?
[Sighs]
Oh, shit.
They take my uniform away,
they may as well shoot me.
You can live with it, bud.
Believe me.
I'm not gonna shit you.
They offered us a deal.
[Sighs] You plead guilty, its
ten to fifteen. You're out in seven.
- What do you think?
- I think they're out to crucify you.
For a whole lot of reasons,
I say we take it and call it a day.
[Sniffles]
I did what they
asked me to do, Hodge.
I lost marines over there.
If I'm guilty of this,
I'm guilty of everything I've done
in combat for the last 30 years.
[Woman Chattering]
[Man]
I don't know.
Colonel Hodges?
Captain Hustings.
I'm not in uniform and I'm not
saluting because of the snipers.
Please know that I'm saluting
on the inside.
I've got some Kevlar back there
with your name on it.
We're not the most popular team
in town right now, sir.
Hustings, are you a wiseass?
My mother prefers to
think of me as glib, sir.
Very well then. You will most glibly
belay all bullshit and drive on.
Roger that, sir.
I've lined up some people who were
at the scene, as you requested, sir.
- We can start tomorrow.
- Good.
- All right. Here we are.
- Oh. 0700.
Roger that, sir.
The old embassy was
a fifth century palace.
Got pretty shot up.
We're moving the new one
to a bunker outside the city...
behind about a mile
of barbed wire, sir.
- You want me to come with you, sir?
- Negative.
Stay with the vehicle.
Meet me at the hotel.
Yes, sir.
[Shutter Clicks]
[Shutter Clicking]
[Sighs,
Mutters Indistinctly]
[Man Shouts
In Arabic Language]
?? [Drums, Flute]
?? [People Singing
In Arabic Language]
[Shutter Clicks]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5e3nd
Help other users to choose the best subtitles