Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
...what has turned into
a classic Formula 1 season.
...with the weather conditions
so uncertain,
the drivers prepare for...
...the track is still
dangerously wet,
but following a drivers meeting,
a decision has been taken.
Three minutes to go.
Everybody off the grid now.
25 drivers start every season
in Formula 1,
and each year, two of us die.
What kind of person
does a job like this?
Not normal men, for sure.
Rebels,
lunatics,
dreamers.
People who are desperate
to make a mark
and are prepared to die trying.
My name is Niki Lauda,
and racing people know me
for two things.
The first is
my rivalry with him.
Mass is going on slicks.
What about Hunt?
Has he changed?
No, he's going on wets.
I don't know why
it became such a big thing.
We were just drivers
busting each other's balls.
To me this is perfectly normal,
but other people
saw it differently,
that whatever it was between us
went deeper.
The other thing
I'm remembered for
is what happened
on 1 st August 1976,
when I was chasing him
like an asshole.
Yeah, that's the one.
On the second shelf. Thank you.
Trauma trolley, please.
I think the racetrack telephoned
ahead that I was coming.
Hunt. James Hunt.
What's the matter? No one ever
seen a spot of blood before?
- Are you all right?
- Absolutely fine.
We all thought you'd been
in an accident.
I have.
If you call a friendly
disagreement
with another driver
an accident.
What did you disagree about?
It's none of your business.
Sorry.
His wife.
That's going to need
a couple of stitches.
- It's a nasty cut.
- It was a nasty blow.
Done with a bloody crowbar.
- Why? What did you do?
- Nothing.
Only what she asked me to do.
Which was?
I'd be happy to show you
if you like.
Sorry.
I have a theory
why women like racing drivers.
It's not because they respect
what we do,
driving round and round
in circles.
Mostly they think
that's pathetic
and they're probably right.
It's our closeness to death.
The closer you are to death,
the more alive you feel.
The more alive you are.
And they can see that in you.
They feel that in you.
My name is James Hunt.
My father is a stockbroker,
my sister is a barrister
and my brother is an accountant.
And I,
well, I do this.
It's a wonderful way to live.
It's the only way to drive.
As if each day is your last.
I've never been
to a Grand Prix before.
You still haven't.
- This is Formula 3.
- What's that?
That's a lower division,
where idiots like me
mess about
in the hop of being
talent-spotted to race in F1.
- You look disappointed.
- No.
You only slept with me because
you thought I was famous.
That's not true!
Don't worry. I will be one day.
Morning, everyone.
- This is Nursie.
- Gemma.
Nursie, this is Bubbles Horsely,
team manager.
How do you do?
- Bubbles?
- Yeah.
Doc Postlethwaite, our designer.
How do you do?
And Alexander, Lord Hesketh,
the team's owner.
How do you do?
Fine, thanks.
Well done, Superstar!
- That's the car?
- Yep, that's her.
Lotus 59.
1000cc. Cosworth MAE engine.
She's no beauty,
but goes like the clappers.
Nothing to be worried about.
Does it before every race.
Good sign, actually.
Means he's stoked.
All Formula 3 cars
to the assembly area.
Now, please.
...drivers please bring them
to the scrutineering bay now.
All right, Superstar?
Never better, patron.
- Have a gargle with this.
- Thank you.
Quick toke of this.
At Crystal Palace today,
James Hunt's on pole,
with Austrian newcomer
Niki Lauda alongside him
and Dave Walker
completing Row 1.
Row 2 is Mike Beuttler
and Dave Morgan,
with Tony Trimmer
and Gerry Birrell.
Who's that?
He's new.
- Some German.
- Austrian.
He's been here since 5 a.m.
Walking the track.
You might actually have
to concentrate today, James.
You'll need these.
Okay, start her up.
Ah! What music!
They could never
have imagined it,
those pioneers
who invented the automobile,
that it would
possess us like this,
in our imaginations, our dreams.
Nursie, men love women,
but even more than that,
men love cars!
- Come on, James!
- It's James! Go on, James!
Go, James!
Hunt's still in the lead,
but Niki Lauda
is right on his tail!
Hunt and Lauda are proving
to be in a class of their own.
They're leaving the pack
far behind.
Herr Red Devil's on his tail.
Lauda takes a look down
the inside...
...and he's sold him a dummy!
Lauda is through!
He's in the lead!
Hunt will be determined
to make up for that mistake.
Hunt's in Laudaxs slipstream.
Lauda's not leaving any gap.
The Lotus goes for the inside.
It's an aggressive move
from Hunt.
There's contact!
The leaders have spun out!
Lauda's facing the wrong way!
The back marker's gone through!
You can see why Hunter's
fellow drivers call him
"Hunt the Shunt."
Asshole!
- Go on, James!
- The Kraut's out of it!
Lauda is clearly furious.
There's every reason to expect
sharp words in the pit.
It's going to be victory
for Hunt.
It's going to be an ignominious
defeat for Niki Lauda.
So James Hunt scores
his third major Formula 3 win
of the season here,
at Crystal Palace,
after a desperate battle
with Niki Lauda.
Lauda was unable so restart
after Hunt's aggressive move
caused them both to spin out
in the last lap of the race.
Hard luck.
Better luck next time.
Hey, asshole!
That was my line.
I had that corner.
You mean the one
that you spun out of
and finished facing
the other way?
I think that corner had you.
That move was total suicide.
What if I hadn't braked?
- We'd have crashed.
- But we didn't, did we?
Thanks to your impeccable
survival instincts.
Fuck you!
What's your name?
James Simon Wallis Hunt.
Remember it,
my little Jerry friend.
- Jawohl! Remember ze name.
- It's very simple.
Hunt, it rhymes with cunt!
A word that happens
to describe you perfectly.
Who was that?
I've no idea.
He looks like a rat, doesn't he?
In my hometown, Vienna,
my family's famous
for one thing:
Business.
My grandfather
was a businessman,
my father, too.
So when they heard I wanted
to race cars for a living,
they had a few things to say.
Never!
Good.
So if my family
wasn't going to help me,
I decided to risk everything
and take out a loan myself.
I found a Formula 1 team
with an OK car
and an owner who had run
out of money
and was willing to accept
my terms.
And so, ladies and gentlemen,
I'm delighted to say...
that the winner of the
Guild of Motoring Writers Award
Driver of the Year...
is James Hunt.
Superb news!
- Well done, James.
- Superstar!
Fantastic!
- Well done.
- Thank you so much.
Yes!
My parents always wanted me
to be a doctor
or a stockbroker or something.
They gave me
the first-class education,
but that went all terribly wrong
and I ended up with you lot.
Thank you. I need it more
than you do.
I mean, I have a hot head,
an inability
to tolerate discipline...
- Yes!
- Very true!
I fall out with people
left and right.
The only creatures
I've ever really loved
or treated honorably
are budgerigars.
So in any normal area of life,
I'd be, or I am,
a total liability.
The only thing I've got going
for me is I'm quick in a car.
So thank you for this
and for acknowledging that.
I'm going to give it
to my father
and tell him to put it
on the mantelpiece
and imagine it's a first-class
degree in medicine.
Well done, Superstar.
Another season like that,
I'll move you up
to the big time.
Come on, you don't think
I'm ready now?
You are.
I'm not. I've got
to find you a car first.
Well, go on, then.
Chop chop. Don't wait too long.
You don't want him to do
what Lauda just did.
- Why? What did he do?
- Got himself a drive, with BRM.
How the hell did he do that?
He's a nobody.
He's never won a bloody thing.
Apparently, took out a loan
and bought his way in
with two million
Austrian shillings.
Jesus.
Niki Lauda.
Here for pre-season testing.
BRM?
Sign the release form.
I'll let them know you're here.
- Mr. Stanley.
- Good morning.
- Clay!
Let me introduce you
to our number one driver.
Clay Regazzoni.
- How are you?
- Good.
Pleasure.
And these are your mechanics.
They're reporting
exclusively to you,
as per contract.
Pleasure.
- Do you wanna see the car?
- Sure.
Hello.
There she is. P160.
- Same as Regazzoni's?
- Identical in every detail.
How much does she weigh?
- 600 kilos.
- But that's crazy.
- Why so heavy?
- It's a V12 engine.
That lump weighs
190K on its own.
Okay.
What horsepower are you getting?
- No, no, 450.
- It's not enough.
It needs to be 500.
And the engine needs to be
- We already tried.
- Tried what?
Everything.
We replaced the entire
exhaust system.
- Barely made the difference.
- Are you using magnesium parts?
Now the engine block.
Any mounting or fixing plates,
strip it out also.
When you've done that,
we have to look
at the aerodynamics,
front and rear wing.
Okay, thank you.
Good night.
What was Regazzoni's time?
1:53.
Okay, now put him in my car
and he'll go 2 seconds faster.
- Well, that's impossible.
- No chance.
We've been working on it
all night.
Put Regazzoni in the car.
See what happens.
I don't understand.
Why am I supposed to do this?
I don't know, Clay.
He wants you
to take it for a spin.
Gloves, please.
- I'd say we push it...
- All right.
What did you do to the car?
That's information
I'll share with you
under certain conditions only.
Go on.
A guaranteed place in the team.
And a paid contract
on equal terms
with Regazzoni for two years.
Are you crazy?
Clay's a senior figure in F1.
You're just a rookie!
The only reason we took you on
is because you're paying us.
Well, as of now,
if you want me to stay,
we rip up the contract,
I don't pay you a cent.
That's outrageous!
Was he quicker in my car?
He was, wasn't he?
Did he go two seconds faster?
Two point three.
So, have a think,
work out your priorities
and get back to me.
Hey, Niki.
I know what you're going to say,
that it's none of my business.
What?
If it's the track manager you're
taking on your date tonight.
It's none of your business.
Okay, but if you want my advice,
I'd let this one go.
I'm not questioning your taste.
She is a great girl, but...
Agnes's last boyfriend
was a British Formula 2 driver
who has a reputation
for two things,
for being a little crazy
on the track...
and for going all night
and all day
and all night again in bed.
He's a good driver,
but an immortal fuck apparently.
I don't know about you,
but that's not an act
I'd like to follow.
But if that
doesn't bother you...
What's his name, the driver?
Hunt. James Hunt.
You see, you share information
and I share information.
That's what teammates are for.
- Where the hell are we going?
- I promise it'll be worth it.
Just keep them closed.
Wait for it.
There.
What do you say?
She's Formula 1.
Yes, she is, Superstar.
Your brother and I got together
with the bean counters.
And since the economics
of F1 are not
so significantly different
to the economics of F2,
well, we thought if we were
going to be losing money,
we might as well be doing it
on the big roulette table in F1.
You fat, little, inbred beauty.
Come here.
Actually, credit where it's due,
we got the idea from Niki.
- Who?
- Lauda.
Bought his way in
rather than mess about
in the lower divisions.
I thought:
"Bloody hell, he's right."
No sponsorship, Superstar.
I hope you approve.
No vulgar logos
for cigarettes or condoms.
Just plain white with the flags.
And racing overalls
which read:
"Sex. Breakfast of champions."
So when do we start?
- Soon as you're ready.
- Ready?
I've been waiting for this
my whole life.
VILLAGE OF
WATKINS GLEN
When the season started,
people wondered
whether Lord Hesketh
and his team
of upper-class enthusiasts
were bringing glamour
to the racing community
or just comedy.
Certainly it was the first time
anyone had seen
a butler serving oysters
and caviar in the pits.
But they have made
quite an impact.
6th in France, 4th in Britain
and 3rd in Holland.
All drivers on the track,
caution flags are out.
A severe crash at the Esses.
Red flag.
There's a car off the track.
And reports are reaching me
that there's been
a serious accident
in qualifying.
The identity of the driver
we don't currently have,
but as you can tell from
all the activity going on
towards the track, it was
clearly a grave incident indeed.
We will, of course, have
more information as we get it,
but it is the sight and sound
of F1 nobody likes to see.
- Get your hands off me!
- Hey, come on!
Drivers of top stature we've
lost just in the past 4 seasons
have included Piers Courage,
Jochen Rindt,
Jo Siffert,
Roger Williamson
and today, at Watkins Glen,
Formula 1 has claimed
another driver.
The Tyrrell team
have withdrawn from the race.
Their places on the grid
will be left empty.
- Terrible.
- They should cancel the race.
Why?
He made a mistake,
went into the corner too fast.
It's his fault.
- Is that right?
- It's obvious.
Look at the tyre marks.
So says the nobody, who had
to pay for his own drive.
How's that working out for you,
by the way?
Fine.
How is it at the back?
Not planning
on being there for long.
Ten minutes to the warm-up lap.
Ten minutes.
Asshole.
Arsehole.
Heading into the Grand Hotel
hairpin, second gear.
Turn in hard,
looking for late apex,
gentle with the bar.
Heading into Portier,
second gear,
clip the apex,
light brake, stay in second,
looking for a good exit.
Heading through the tunnel,
gradual right,
up through third,
fourth, fifth...
Is Alexander around?
Yes, he was.
He went back to the house
to take a call.
He'll be back shortly.
He only wanted to show me
his pride and joy.
Rhymes with 'boy'
if you ask me.
And 'toy.'
God, it's so flimsy.
For something
that costs so much.
There's no comfort,
no protection, nothing.
No, it's just
a little coffin, really.
Surrounded by
high-octane fuel in here.
Being driven round 170 mph.
To all intents and purposes,
this thing's a bomb on wheels.
You're James, aren't you?
Yes.
You fit the description.
Is that right?
Suzy. Friend ofAlex's.
Yeah, yeah.
I know exactly.
What was the description?
Mostly positive in terms
of appearance.
Negative only in terms
of character.
I've been told to avoid you.
By whom?
Alexander.
He says you're a bad boy.
Alexander doesn't know
what he's talking about.
I was. I'm not anymore.
The new me is very professional.
Early to bed, early to rise.
All very dull,
but according to the team,
'the best way to keep
beating the goose stepper.'
Is that what you were doing
when I came in?
Yes, visualization techniques,
memorising the circuit,
in this case Monaco,
which is up next.
Personally I've always been
a great believer
in getting there on the day,
putting my foot down
and playing chicken
with everyone else.
But they don't want me
doing that anymore.
They want my body like a temple
and my mind like a monk.
And what about your soul,
your heart?
They've got ideas
about that, too.
They want me to stop
messing around,
settle down, get married
with the next nice girl I meet.
They think
that'd be good for me.
What do you think?
It sounds fucking awful.
But sine they're right
about most things,
they're probably right
about that too.
You don't fancy
getting married, do you?
Suzy.
JUST MARRIED
Hey, hey, hey!
- What's going on with him?
- Nothing. Nothing.
Didn't want to ruin your day.
It's...
- it's the Kraut.
- What about him?
He's just been signed
by Ferrari.
You're kidding me?
Jesus. How did that happen?
Did he buy his way in there too?
Well, the old man took
Regazzoni back
and he insisted on it
apparently.
He says that Niki's a genius
setting up the cars.
It's terrible.
Drives like a pig.
- You can't say that.
- Why not?
- It's a Ferrari!
- It's a shitbox!
It understeers like crazy
and the weight distribution
is a disaster.
It's amazing,
all these facilities
and you make a piece of crap
like this.
"Ferrari family,"
"our good friend
Clay Regazzoni."
You are family and friend
to the commendatore
as long as you win.
The minute you don't,
ciao, ciao.
I totally understand.
It's business.
I would do the same.
But it isn't
just business, is it?
What we do.
It's passion, love.
Which is why we are prepared
to risk our lives for it.
Not me.
If I had more talent
and could earn better money
with something else,
I would.
How do you know you will
make money here?
You haven't yet.
Not yet, but I will.
If you can, I can.
You know, are you ever
not an asshole?
- Why am I an asshole?
- Well...
By now I'm both quicker than you
and better at setting up a car.
You can't deal with it,
so you're the asshole.
Screw you.
I brought you along today
because you seem
like a lonely kind of guy.
I thought if I introduced you
to some nice people,
that could rub off on you.
Forget it.
Make your own friends.
Come on, Clay.
I'm sorry.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
Can you give me a lift
to the nearest town,
anywhere with a train station?
Sure.
Trento's half an hour's drive.
Get in.
What are you doing?
You hear that noise
when you accelerate?
- No.
- Your fan belt is loose.
My what?
And when you brake,
your foot goes all the way down,
which means there's air
in the system.
- Anything else?
- No.
Apart from the rear brakes
are worn out,
the front right tyre
is a bit soft,
which explains why
you're weaving so much.
How can you tell?
- My ass.
- Sorry?
God gave me an OK mind,
but a really good ass which
can feel everything in a car.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
This car is fine.
I just had a service a week ago.
Not a good one.
Yes, a very good one,
very expensive.
This car's as good as new.
Relax.
- You're not in a hurry, are you?
- No.
As long as I'm back
in Maranello Monday morning.
- Marlene.
- Niki.
Yes.
- Thank you.
- My car is your car.
On one condition, though.
It's a piece of shit.
It's dog shit.
But if you drive it,
you make my life, Niki, eh?
Would someone please
tell me what's going on?
- Who are you? Should I know you?
- What, you don't know?
He's Niki Lauda,
Formula 1 driver,
and he just signed with Ferrari.
- Him?
- Yes.
- Impossible.
- Why?
Well, you know,
Formula 1 drivers,
they have long hair,
are sexy...
their shirts are open to here.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Anyway, look at the way
he's driving, like an old man.
There's no need to drive fast.
It just increases
the percentage of risk.
We're not in a hurry.
I'm not being paid.
Right now,
with zero incentive or reward,
why would I drive fast?
Because I'm asking you to.
Usually.
This is an incredible battle
between Niki Lauda
in the red Ferrari
and James Hunt
in the white Hesketh.
...the challenge
of Niki Lauda...
Lauda attacking Hunt.
He gets through on the inside.
Goes wide at the exit.
Hunt is past again.
Once more, Lauda tries
to sneak up the inside.
They're absolutely side by side,
wheel to wheel.
So evenly matched.
Fantastic battle between
these two great drivers.
Hunt is now ahead once more.
But Lauda's coming back
again now.
Lauda once more
sneaks up the inside.
And again he runs wide.
Again the Hesketh...
- Suzy, we're ready, come on.
- Just one second.
- Can we go, yeah?
- Okay, yeah.
We're in the closing laps
of this race at Watkins Glen.
They come down the hill.
And Hunt's got a problem!
Hunt pulls across to the left!
Lauda goes ahead on his own.
A sad end to a wonderful battle.
Hunt pushing off the marshal.
The chequered flag
is waiting for Lauda
and for Ferrari!
The title going to Niki Lauda,
who wins the race,
who wins the World Championship.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Marlene.
With a car like that,
the rest of us
never stood a chance, did we?
Maybe the car being so good
has something to do with me.
Come on, Niki.
You're in a Ferrari.
I'm in a Hesketh.
Equal terms,
the way it was in Formula 3,
- Id' beat you and you know it.
- Never.
You might win one race,
maybe two,
because you're aggressive.
But in the long run,
over the course of a season,
no chance.
Right. Why is that?
Because to be a champion,
it takes more
than just being quick.
It's the whole picture.
You're just a charger
and a party guy.
That's why everybody likes you.
Try saying that
and tell me you're not jealous.
Why would I be jealous?
Think about it.
All that affection,
all those smiles,
is a sign of disrespect.
They don't fear you.
Whereas compared that to me.
Yes, compared to you,
whom no one likes.
- Right.
- Not even his own teammates.
Right.
Because I'm a serious guy.
I go to bed early, I look after
myself, after my car.
- Yes, you're very well-behaved.
- Go to work, kick ass.
And then, after the race,
I go home
instead of going to bars
and talk all this bullshit
with all these assholes.
Arseholes?
You should go home
more often too.
I heard you got married.
Yes, I did.
So where is she,
this mysterious wife?
In New York, working.
You know, I've never
seen you with her once.
No?
Well, maybe that's because
you're always at home,
on your own,
looking after yourself,
being a good little boy.
Take a drink on me, James.
Thank you, Niki.
I might just have two.
Right, Bubbles,
whatever it takes to beat
that prick next year,
just say it,
you're word is my command.
There are no lengths
to which I will not go.
And I mean it.
What the hell's going on?
Where is everybody?
What's the matter?
Do you know
what the date it is today?
Yes. It's November,
the 14th. Why?
Do you have any idea of
the significance of that date?
I don't know.
Time to start killing pheasants?
Actually, it's the deadline
for securing sponsorship
for the forthcoming
Formula 1 season.
Yes?
Which elapsed
at midnight last night
- and we didn't attract any.
- Well, so?
We aren't looking
for sponsorship.
Like you said, condoms
an cigarettes, vulgar, right?
Right.
Except we are, or were.
I've made something
of a miscalculation.
The economics,
Formula 1, realities thereof.
It turns out not like
the lower divisions at all.
What are you saying?
I'm saying it's over, Superstar.
The banks have stepped in,
started laying everyone off.
Probably have
to sell this place.
Oh, Christ.
I need a drive, Pete.
I need you to find me a drive.
I mean, what about Lotus?
You don't wanna know.
- Actually, I do.
- Okay.
They felt your reputation
preceded you.
And what does that mean?
It's my other line.
Look, I'll get back to you.
Peter Hunt.
Fuck!
Don't worry.
Something will turn up.
Doubt that will help
in the meantime.
Why don't we go away
at the weekend?
Skiing.
Before I go back to New York.
Talk to me, James.
Don't make a stranger of me.
You know, Suzy, only a stranger
would invite me skiing
when they know
I haven't got a fucking drive!
I can't watch this.
What were you hoping for anyway?
A well-adjusted knight
in shining armour?
No danger of that.
- Let me give you some advice.
- I'm all ears.
Don't go to men who are willing
to kill themselves
driving in circles
looking for normality.
I never expected normality.
God knows I walked into this
with my eyes open.
I just hoped I'd married someone
who is half as impressive
on the inside
as he is on the outside!
At least there's something
behind the facade.
- James.
- Fuck off to New York, dear.
There must be a moisturiser
or an eye shadow somewhere
that needs your vapid mush
to flog it.
- Hello?
- Hi, James.
It's Peter.
Something's up at McLaren.
- What have you heard?
- Nothing. Why?
I heard Emerson's off.
He's dumped them in it.
Jesus. Get me in there, Pete.
Say anything, just get me
in that room.
I'll come straight to the point.
- Our esteemed lead driver...
- Fitti-fucking-paldi.
Has ditched us for another team
at the last minute.
- Coper-fucking-sucar.
- And we need a replacement.
ASA-fucking-P.
Fortunately a few hands
have already gone up,
good people.
- Jacky Ickx.
- I'm quicker than Jacky.
But he's consistent, dependable.
A grown-up.
Right, and will he go for
that gap when no one else will?
Will he put his life on the line
the day it really matters?
The sponsors like him.
What do you want,
a driver or a brush salesman?
- We wanna be successful.
- Yes, so do I.
But that means beating
Niki Lauda,
not being a show pony
for sponsors.
I heard about this thing
with Niki.
Everyone has.
You really thing
you can beat him?
I'd beat him in a McLaren.
It's the only car out there
as quick as the Ferrari.
Which is why I'm here, begging.
I'll do whatever you ask.
I'll put on a tie,
I'll smile for sponsors,
say the right things.
I can beat this guy, trust me.
Just give me the drive.
Yeah, he can be a loose canon.
And, yeah,
he will drive you all mad,
but in terms of raw talent
and right stuff,
there is no better driver
in the world.
He's the real thing, Teddy.
He's what we all
came into this for.
Nine days out of ten
you'll be pulling your hair out,
but on that tenth day
James will be unbeatable.
That is the day you will wish
you had him in your car.
You'll never win the
championship with Jacky Ickx.
You just might with James.
GRANDE PREMIO DO BRAZIL
INTERLAGOS
JANUARY 1976
Welcome to So Paulo, Brazil,
and the Interlagos circuit
for the first race in the 1976
Formula 1 season,
where the main news is
James Hunt qualified fastest,
beating Niki Lauda's Ferrari
to pole position
by just 200th of a second.
New car.
- I noticed.
- Pole position.
I noticed that too.
Level playing field now,
my ratty little friend.
Yeah.
Let's see where we are
after lap one.
in five races time.
Hunt has the pit lane
pole position,
which should give him
the best chance
of outdragging Lauda's Ferrari.
If ever there was a doubt about
whether Lauda had a serious
challenger to this season,
Hunt and his McLaren have
certainly given us the answer.
BRAZIL
LAUDA WINS
HUNT HAS ENGINE FAILURE
GRAND PRIX
SOUTH AFRICA 76
Here in South Africa,
James Hunt is determined
to make amends after that
disastrous retirement in Brazil.
But it's Lauda who takes
the flag here at Kyalami.
James Hunt comes home second
to confirm his championship
challenge at last
and score his first points
of the season.
That wind you can feel
is me breathing down your neck.
Next time I'll have you.
We'll see in Spain.
SPAIN -HUNT WINS
LAUDA 2ND
James Hunt finally takes
his first victory of the season
here in Spain,
after a brilliant drive.
It was only a matter of time.
- It's too wide.
- Disqualified.
- What?
- You're disqualified.
How can we be disqualified?
- 1.5 cm.
- It's the same car.
...McLaren M23 has proved
very controversial here.
Just make it narrower.
I don't care how.
New rear suspension.
New wishbones.
I wanna make sure this thing
is legal, no doubts.
Then we'd better move the
oil coolers to the old position.
- The wing brackets need...
- Fuck.
What the fuck
d'you think we're doing?
GRAND PRIX
MONACO 76
And with Hunt disqualified
from his Spain win,
his championship here
is not going well.
And now it's all gone wrong
here at Monaco!
His engine is smoking!
Smoke pouring from the engine
of that McLaren!
And James Hunt is out!
Can you tell us what happened?
Sure. It's magic,
we've taken a great car,
a great piece of engineering
and overnight turned it
into a big, huge stinking turd.
BELGIUM
MAY 1976
Shit!
What the hell have you done?
The car's evil!
It's fucking undriveable!
If there's a problem
with the car, we'll fix it.
The car is a piece of shit.
You should be appealing this.
- We are appealing.
- We'll sort it out.
- They're killing us out there.
- Go an get your dick wet.
- You're a wanker!
- Fuck you!
You're fucking wanker!
But this was a good race
for you, no, Niki?
It's good for everyone
that the quickest car
happens to be a legal car.
James, your 50 points behind
Lauda in the championship.
You've had
another retirement today.
What's going wrong?
It's dirty politics
and dirty tricks,
that's what's going wrong.
So as we approach
the halfway point
in this year's Formula 1 season,
Ferrari and Niki Lauda
seem clearly on top
and James Hunt and McLaren
are struggling.
So, five races in,
how's it going so far?
It's fine. Just got a little
problem with an Austrian rat
and his team of Italian cheats
who've destroyed my car.
- What are you talking about?
- About the race in Spain I won.
Yeah, in a car
which is not legal.
Five eighths
of an inch too wide.
You know that doesn't have
the slightest effect on speed.
But you complained
and your team of lawyers
leaned on the authorities.
Now we've had to rebuild the car
- and it's become a monster.
- At least it's a legal monster.
You've had to resort
to cheating.
You're driving an illegal car
and call me a cheater? Pathetic.
- Rules are rules.
- Yes, and rats are rats.
Thank you. Thank you.
Do you really think
it upsets me, James,
calling me a rat
because I look like one?
I don't mind it.
Rats are ugly, sure,
and nobody like them,
but they're very intelligent
and they have
a strong survival instinct.
Wonderful.
Leave this jerk alone.
No wonder she left him.
Anyone seen Suzy?
She's supposed
to be here today.
We didn't wanna tell you
before the race.
Tell me what?
SUZY JOINS THE BURTON SHOW
HUNT'S WIFE SEES ACTOR
AS LIZ FLIES TO MUM
Jesus.
Blonde model Suzy Hunt
stepped on to the dizzy
Elizabeth Taylor-Richard Burton
roundabout of romance
yesterday.
Is that from him?
Yeah.
So when did all this start?
That weekend I went skiing.
Why have you come here, James?
I've got to get you back.
You don't want me back.
You never wanted to be married
in the first place.
- Yes, I did.
- Oh, come on, James.
You did it because you hoped
it might change you,
settle you down,
help with the racing.
No, I didn't.
And who knows, if it
had been just the drinking,
or the dope, or the infidelity
or the moods,
it might even have worked.
- But when it's all of them...
- Yes, I know, I'm terrible.
No, you're not terrible.
You're just who you are
at this point in your life.
God help anyone who wants more.
And Richard Burton,
will he be able
to give you more?
You know, he has quite
the bad boy reputation himself.
What's important is
how it feels to me,
and it feels like he adores me.
James!
Are you and Suzy
getting back together?
It's all very amicable.
My wife has found herself
a new backer...
I mean, lover,
which makes her happy.
And Mr. Burton has found a way
of feeling young again,
which makes him happy.
Let's hope his pockets are deep.
They'll need to be.
And I found a way to be single
and have an ex-wife
without it costing me a penny,
which has to go down
as the biggest win of my career.
I have a flight to catch.
SUZY HUNT RACES
TO RICHARD BURTON
CIRCUIT PAUL RICARD
CHAMPIONNAT DU MONDE
We haven't seen
this sort of intensity
from James Hunt
all season long.
Reports have been coming out
of the McLaren camp all week
that their car is now fully
legal and faster than ever.
FRANCE -HUNT WINS
LAUDA RETIRES
Never mind the bloody wets.
We're still quick.
BRITISH GRAND PRIX
BRANDS HATCH
SUNDAY 18TH JULY 1976
Hunt has really closed
the gap on Lauda
as they head into Druids.
Niki Lauda is under
real pressure from James Hunt
as they go up the hill
into Druids Corner.
And Hunt is in front of Lauda!
So James Hunt
gets the plaudits of the crowd,
the first Briton to win
a British Grand Prix
at Brands Hatch
since Jim Clark in 1964.
At the moment you've got
a terrific edge over the rest,
how have you achieved
this advantage?
Big balls.
Following an inquiry
into the disqualification
of driver James Hunt
from the Spanish Grand Prix,
it has been decided to overturn
this disqualification
and to restore his victory
and reinstate his points.
James!
A few weeks ago you were
out of the running completely
and now you're right back in it.
What's changed?
It's a combination of factors,
not all of which I'm prepared
to discuss here.
But justice being done re
the disqualification in Spain
helps and having my car
back at its best again.
Welcome to the legendary
Nrburgring.
This is a 14.2 mile track,
complete with 185 corners
and bends.
Niki, an autograph?
With the date, please.
The date? Why?
Welcome to the Nrburgring,
the most dangerous circuit
on the season calendar.
In Formula 1 it is known
as "The Graveyard."
The weather conditions
are far from ideal
and latest reports indicate
there is no relief in sight.
Gentlemen.
Well, gentlemen,
please be quiet.
Thank you.
- Niki Lauda.
- Thank you.
I called this meeting because,
as all you drivers know,
the Nrburgring is the most
stupid, barbaric, outdated
and dangerous track
in the world.
You've all seen the rain
that has been falling today.
Those of you with experience
know the ring
needs perfect conditions
to be even remotely acceptable
in terms of risk.
And today, with the rain,
it's anything but perfect,
so I called this meeting
to take vote to cancel the race.
Cancel the race?
There would be no change
to the situation
as far as points is concerned.
The race would simply
be cancelled.
This is bullshit!
If the race is cancelled,
none of us get our race fees.
That's true,
you leave without your fee,
but you might leave
with your life.
It also means that you
would effectively win
the championship.
So I can see why
this suits you just fine.
Why?
There won't be no points
for me either.
No, but there'd be one race less
where I, or anyone else here,
- could catch you.
- James is right.
This is just tactics!
Maybe he's just frightened.
Which asshole said this?
Yes, of course, I'm frightened,
and so are you.
I accept every time
I get in my car
there's 20% chance I could die,
and I can live with it,
but not one percent more.
And today, with the rain,
the risk is more.
I suppose that all depends
on how good you are in the rain.
I have the track record here.
I'm the only person in history
to do the ring in under 7 min.,
so, actually, it's to
my advantage to race here today.
Because I'm quicker
than all of you.
- Come on.
- Fine. Then let's race.
Yeah!
- Niki, let's race.
- Gentlemen, please.
Why are we here, Niki?
Come on.
Well, all those in favor
of cancelling the race.
All those in favor of racing.
Gentlemen, the race is on.
- Ridiculous.
- What a waste of time.
You know, Niki,
every now and then
it helps if people like you.
In places the track
is still dangerously wet,
but following a drivers meeting,
a decision has been taken.
One minute to go.
Jochen's going on slicks.
You wanna change?
- Is Niki gonna change?
- No.
Then we stay on wets too.
- Niki, okay?
- I'm good.
All right, fire her up.
This season's fight
for the F1 World Championship
has so far been the story
of two men.
Thus far it's been going pretty
much the way of Niki Lauda.
But James Hunt
has qualified fastest here.
He is on pole position
for the German Grand Prix
with Niki Lauda alongside
in the blood-red Ferrari.
It's a long race.
If the track starts to dry out,
the wet-weather tyres
will no longer be as quick.
Niki Lauda and James Hunt,
side by side
on the front of the grid,
go away absolutely as one!
Lauda very aggressive
on Hunt there,
forcing the McLaren
onto the grass.
Lauda has the lead right now!
He leads into the first corner!
Hunt is in second place!
Mass storming past Hunt!
He made the right choice to go
with the dry-weather tyres.
Mass passing Lauda now!
Jochen Mass, in the number 12
McLaren, takes the lead!
Jochen Mass, the clear leader,
with everybody else
making the decision
to change tyres
after just one lap of this race.
Come on, let's go!
See? I told you to go on slicks.
You should've taken my advice.
Fuck off. Where's Niki?
Behind you.
He made the same mistake.
Come on!
Come on! What's going on?
The tyre-changing frenzy caused
a huge reshuffling of the pack,
- with Mass in the lead now.
- You're clear. Go!
Lauda urging
his mechanics to hurry.
It's a disaster! Come on!
What's going on, you assholes?
This race has gone wrong
for him so far.
His championship rival,
James Hunt,
is a long way up the road.
Lauda passing car after car.
He's just going past
Mario Andretti's Lotus there.
Niki!
Get me out!
Help me!
Several cars are involved.
Looks like it might be
one of the Ferraris.
- Come this way!
- Come on, come on!
Keep trying.
- Come this way.
- Okay.
The flood, which swept down
Big Thompson Canyon in Colorado,
was the worst
since records began.
In Formula 1 today,
victory celebrations were muted
after a horrific accident
involving world champion
Niki Lauda.
Due to safety concerns
before the race,
the Austrian had said
he would not take part,
but in the end he did.
He was making up for lost
time when he went off the track,
puncturing the Ferrari's
fuel tank.
Brett Lunger was unable
to avoid the flaming wreck
but was unhurt and joined
other drivers to rescue Lauda,
who was taken to Manheim
Hospital with severe burns,
the incident reminding us again
of the dangers of Formula 1.
Niki Lauda was trapped
for almost a minute
in a searing inferno
of 800-plus degrees.
14 DAYS LATER
28th DAY IN HOSPITAL
29th AUGUST 1976
ITALIAN GRAND PRIX
FREE PRACTICE SEPTEMBER 1976
- Morning, chaps.
- Hey, here's the man.
Looking good.
- What's going on?
- Jesus. It's Niki.
- What about him?
- He's here.
- What?
- He's racing.
Niki.
It's that bad, huh?
No.
In hospital, I asked them
straight, no bullshit,
how bad my appearance would be.
They said with time
it would be fine.
But it won't.
I can tell,
seeing your reaction.
I'll spend the rest of my life
with a face
that frightens people.
You know, Niki, I tried to write
you a letter at the time,
to apologise.
The drivers' meeting in Germany,
before the race.
- I swayed the room.
- Yes, you did.
That race should never
have gone ahead.
No, it shouldn't.
So in many ways I feel
responsible for what happened...
You were.
But, trust me,
watching you win those races,
while I was fighting
for my life...
you were equally responsible
for getting me back in the car.
- How are you feeling, Niki?
- Fine.
Niki,
can you confirm to us exactly
which procedures you had
and the expectations
for you recovery?
Sure.
I had a skin graft operation
where they put half
my right thigh in my face.
Now, it doesn't look too good,
but one unexpected advantage is
it's impossible to perspire
through a skin graft,
so sweat will never run
into my eyes again,
which is good for a driver.
When they heard about
your condition,
Ferrari immediately hired
a replacement driver,
Carlos Reutemann.
Yeah, before ever reaching
the hospital.
- Is Reutemann driving today too?
- Yes.
And keen to make an impression.
So let's see where
Mr. Reutemann finishes
and where I finish today.
James Hunt and McLaren
have caught up a lot
while you were away.
Yes.
So is there a question now
or are you just trying
to piss me off?
You still think you can win?
Yes, of course.
I have the better car.
And possibly
I'm the better driver.
But he's a clever guy
and he's used his time well
while I was lying
half-dead in hospital
to win some points.
And what did your wife say
when she saw your face?
She said, "Sweetie,
you don't need a face to drive.
You just need the right foot."
I'm being serious.
Do you really think
your marriage can survive
with the way you look now?
And I'm being serious too.
Fuck you.
Press conference over.
- That was hairy.
- You know how to get noticed.
I thought it went well,
to be honest.
They don't like it
when it's not going their way.
That's the game.
- See you.
- See you later.
- James, are you all right?
- Good, yeah.
I think I've got something
for you on that last question,
- about Niki.
- You heard about that?
James?
Please, James...
Now go home to your wife
and ask her how you look.
Prick.
So Niki Lauda, just 42 days
after his near-fatal accident
at Nrburgring,
will race here today, at Monza
against all medical advice
and no doubt in incredible pain.
Photographers, please,
clear the grid.
Niki, it's time.
Okay?
Please, clear the grid.
One minute to go.
The returning Niki Lauda
seems overwhelmed.
He's been overtaken
by car after car.
Lauda's off line.
He runs wide onto the grass.
He wrestles it back
onto the track,
but that was a bad moment
for Niki.
Niki Lauda's the reigning
world champion,
but maybe in his current state
he's a danger out there,
to himself and to the rest
of the field.
And Stuck has collided
with Mario Andretti's Lotus!
Niki's boxed in!
He's got nowhere to go!
Niki Lauda's actually
making a move.
He's on Brambilla's tail.
He pulls out of the slipstream
to overtake.
Lauda's starting
to find the form
that early in this race
we believed he'd lost.
Lauda's now lapping faster
than Reutemann
and closing the gap ahead.
Lauda closing
on Carlos Reutemann,
the man called in to be
his replacement
in the Ferrari team.
And there's James Hunt's
McLaren,
smoking stationary
by the side of the road.
This is bad news for Hunt's
championship hopes.
It's Ronnie Peterson
who comes home the winner
here at Monza.
But all eyes are on the man
who finishes a brilliant fourth!
Niki Lauda!
What a race, what a man,
what a season.
With a 4th-place finish
and three priceless points,
Niki Lauda
is a major step closer
to retaining
the World Championship.
So the long, grueling
and incredibly dramatic season
comes down to this final race
in Japan,
in the shadow of Mount Fuji.
Niki Lauda goes into
this deciding race at Fuji
just three points ahead
of James Hunt,
Hunt knowing he must beat
the Austrian fair and square
to take the title.
James, do you think
you can cope with the pressure?
Well, I've never really
understood what that means.
I love my job.
I love competing. I love racing.
Maybe you should ask Niki.
He's the World Champion.
He's got everything to lose.
Mr. Lauda,
are you feeling pressure?
Do I look like
I'm feeling pressure?
I'm World Champion
and on the verge to become
World Champion again.
Hunt now has
the opportunity to win,
but it's not so easy
to become a champion.
You have to really believe it
to make it possible.
James, is there anything
you'd like to add?
If Niki is being tricky
and getting a kicky
out of playing mind games,
then fine, I'm flattered.
The fact is momentum is with me.
I've never felt better.
I fully expect the next
press conference we will have
will be with me
as World Champion.
Intermittent heavy rain
has been forecast
here at Fuji today,
along with strong winds
and occasional fog
rolling in from the mountain.
And so with today's
Japanese Grand Prix to come,
Lauda's lead
a mere three points.
What a way to finish the season.
Hunt or Lauda?
The final chapter will unfold
when we bring you
- extended coverage...
- They've got to cancel the race.
It's lethal out there.
The race is going ahead.
Television rights have been
sold all around the world.
The showdown
between you and Niki
is all anyone wants to see.
With heavy rain continuing
to fall here at Fuji,
a decision
has finally been made.
The 1976 Japanese Grand Prix
will go ahead.
All drivers
to your cars, please.
Five minutes to go.
- All right?
- All right.
- Hold still.
- What the hell are you doing?
To let the condensation out.
- It'll also let the water in.
- Not if you're leading.
Trust me, this race is all
about the start.
- Need a hand here?
- Yeah, hold it, Teddy.
Okay, start the bastard.
Good luck, kid.
Good luck, James!
30 seconds to go.
Electric tension here at Fuji.
80,000 bedraggled race fans
and the racing grudge match
of the decade.
And there's Mario Andretti
in pole position,
James Hunt alongside him.
On row two of the grid,
there is Niki Lauda,
and on row three of the grid,
Joe Schecketer from South Africa
in the six-wheel Tyrrell.
Behind him, the rest
of the 25-car field.
There's the flag and finally
the Japanese Grand Prix
is underway!
In this conditions it must be
almost impossible
to drive a 450-horsepower car!
And it's Andretti
who has the lead,
but Hunt is attacking.
Hunt's going round
the outside ofAndretti!
Niki Lauda
following him through!
Hunt leads into the first
right-hander!
Hunt comes through to complete
his first lap leading the field.
At least he has clear vision
in front of him.
Niki Lauda behind him,
eating his spray.
Lauda is slowing!
Niki Lauda is bringing
the Ferrari no. 1 into the pit!
Some sort of problem,
we can't imagine what,
so early in the race.
What's wrong with the car?
Niki! What's wrong with the car?
Nothing. Car's perfect.
What are you doing?
I'm stopping.
His mechanics are asking
what the problem is.
But wait! Niki Lauda's
getting out of the car!
This is sensational!
The reigning World Champion,
Niki Lauda,
is out of this race.
It's too dangerous.
Niki, you want me to say
there was a problem
with the car, for the media?
No.
Tell them the truth.
Now, what is happening?
They're talking
to the team manager.
Lauda explaining something.
With Lauda out, James Hunt
knows he has to finish
this race in third place
or higher to be World Champion.
But the job's not done yet
for James Hunt.
In these dreadful conditions,
he still has to go the distance.
Fifteen laps to go
here at Fuji.
James Hunt or Niki Lauda?
This extraordinary season
is not over yet.
In this treacherous final round,
can James Hunt hang on?
Hunt in the lead.
Oh, God, his tyres,
they're blistering.
Brambilla very close behind him,
closing on him all the time.
And he's trying to drive
inside James Hunt.
Hunt cuts across
the orange March nose.
Hunt not having that at all.
And he's spinning.
He missed Hunt but almost took
James Hunt out of the race
and out
of the world championship.
Now we find Mario Andretti
closing on James Hunt.
Mario Andretti's
going past Hunt!
Hunt is slowing. James Hunt
seems to have a problem.
Despite this wet conditions,
these wet-weather tyres
wear extremely fast.
Hunt's tyres, they're gone.
Hunt nursing his car
back to the pit stop.
That back marker's
going past Hunt.
LAP 70
4 LAPS TO GO
Look at that left front tyre,
right front tyre, sorry.
No tread on it at all.
And the other one is flat.
Let's go! Let's go!
Okay? When did you break
your gear lever?
Nine or ten laps ago.
- Alistair, we need to lift it!
- Come on!
- At the front!
- Let's go!
Regazzoni's Ferrari and
Jacques Lafitte in the Ligier
have gone ahead.
Come on, hurry!
You did it. You're going
to be World Champion!
Not yet.
A few laps ago, James Hunt
was looking like champion elect.
Now it looks as though
it's all gone wrong for him.
- James.
- Come on!
- Listen.
- What?
Just go easy out there.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying look after yourself.
We want you back in one piece.
You're too far back. There's too
many drivers in front of you.
- There's always next year.
- So that's it? It's over?
Clear!
James!
- Clear!
- Fuck it!
James Hunt rejoins the race
in sixth position.
There are four laps to go.
Surely no way back for the Brit.
Concentrate, Superstar.
Just brings it back
under control!
Sliding the McLaren
on the very edge there.
Hunt's M23 twitching this way
and that under braking.
And he almost loses it
right there.
Hunt on the tail
of Jacques Lafitte
in the blue Ligier.
Don't do it, James.
He's inches away
from the pit wall!
from the Ligier!
James Hunt has made up
another place,
but it's not enough
and this race is running out.
And Watson has spun!
Watson has spun!
Hunt manages to weave his way
between the back marker
and the stationary Penske.
He's catching Regazzoni,
but in these conditions,
it's one thing to catch up,
quite another to overtake.
He's alongside Clay Regazzoni!
This could be
the world championship!
He's got him!
Hunt crosses the line.
He needed to finish third
to score enough points
to be World Champion,
and in the confusion here
we're being told
that he may have finished 5th.
He finished fifth?
Our lap charts show Hunt
in third place.
Well, if the scoreboard's right,
it means he's just missed out
on the championship.
Crushing defeat for Hunt
after such a heroic drive.
I can see the race stewards
conferring,
examining
the official lap charts.
We're just going to have to wait
for their verdict here.
Let's get you
out of here, buddy.
I'm sorry, Teddy. I thought
I could make up the ground.
Sorry? What are you
talking about? You did it!
- Did what?
- Jesus! You crazy bastard!
You came 3rd!
You got the points!
You're champion of the world!
James Hunt is now
officially confirmed
as finishing third
here in Japan,
and that means he
is champion of the world.
Our new World Champion,
James Hunt,
by just one single point.
Did we really win?
World bloody Champion!
- What are you going to do now?
- I shall be getting drunk.
It's wonderful, absolute dream.
And our special guest,
Formula 1 champion, James Hunt.
JAMES HUNT
WORLD CHAMPION
AGAINST ALL ODDS
Wait. Come on.
There's no better motor oil
than Havoline.
- Yes, me too. Where we going?
- Anywhere I want to go.
And I don't have
to hijack it, either.
As long as I pay for it.
I'm starving.
Let's get some food.
- Where are you going?
- You lot go ahead.
I won't be a minute.
Niki!
Good to see you!
I heard you were spending
more and more time
- in one of these.
- Do you fly?
No.
- I don't think they'd insure me.
- You should try.
It's good for discipline.
You have to stay
within the rules,
stick to regulation,
suppress the ego.
It helps with the racing.
And there I was thinking
you were about to wax lyrical
- about the romance of flight.
- No, that's all bullshit.
So what brings you here?
A friend's wedding.
At least I think
it was a wedding.
Might have been a birthday
or something.
It's all a bit of a blur.
- Have you been at Fiorano?
- Pre-season testing.
- You're relentless.
- Thank you.
I'm not sure that was meant
as a compliment.
When do you start testing?
Next week?
No. What, are you nuts?
I didn't just win
the biggest thing of my life
so I could get
right back to work.
Why? You have to.
To prove to all the people
who will always say
you just won it because...
Because of what?
Because of your accident?
Niki, is that other people
or is that you?
I won, okay?
On the all-important day
when it came down to it,
we raced on equal terms,
equally good cars.
And I put my life on the line
and I saw it through.
- And you call that winning?
- Yes.
The risks were totally
unacceptable.
You were prepared to die.
- To me, that's losing.
- Yes, I was. I admit it.
I was prepared to die
to beat you that day.
And that's the effect
you have on me.
You'd pushed me that far.
And it felt great!
I mean, hell, isn't that
what we're in this for?
To stare death in the face
and to cheat it?
Come on,
there's nobility in that.
It's like being knights.
You English,
you're such assholes.
You know my position.
20% risk.
No, Niki, don't bring
the percentages into this.
Don't be a pro.
The minute you do that,
you kill what's good about this.
You kill the sport.
James!
I've got to go.
Careful in this thing.
James.
In hospital, the toughest part
of my treatment was the vacuum.
Pumping the shit
out of my lungs.
It was hell.
And while doing it,
I was watching television.
- You winning all my points.
- Your points?
"That bastard, Hunt," I'd say.
"I hate that guy."
And one day,
the doctor came and said,
"Mr. Lauda, may I offer
a piece of advice?"
"Stop thinking of it as a curse
to have been given
an enemy in life."
"It can be blessing too."
"A wise man gets more
from his enemies
than a fool from his friends."
And you know what?
He was right.
Look at us.
We were both a pair of kids
when we met.
Hot-headed jerks in Formula 3.
Disowned by our families.
Headed nowhere.
And now we're both
champions of the world.
It was not bad.
No, it's not bad.
So don't let me down now.
I need you busting my balls.
- Get back to work.
- I will, Niki, I will.
But I intend to enjoy
myself first.
Some of life needs to be
for pleasure.
What's the point of having a
million cups, medals and planes
if you don't have any fun?
How is that winning?
- James!
- We're gonna leave without you!
James!
I'll see you on race day, champ.
You will...
champ.
You look good, Niki.
The only guy to have burnt his
face and it be an improvement.
Of course he didn't
listen to me.
For James, one world title
was enough.
He had proved
what he needed to prove,
to himself
and anyone who doubted him.
And two years later he retired.
When I saw him next
in London seven years later,
me as champion again,
him as broadcaster,
he was barefoot on a bicycle,
with a flat tyre.
Still living each day
like his last.
When I heard he'd died aged 45,
of a heart attack,
I wasn't surprised.
I was just sad.
People always think of us
as rivals,
but he was among
the very few I liked
and even fewer
that I respected.
He remains the only person
I envied.
SUBTITLED BY
GUSSI, S.A. DE C.V.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/w6x7
Help other users to choose the best subtitles