Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Thank you, sir.
Have a nice day.
Next in line, please.
Ooh, a week in Hawaii.
l'll fill in for you.
Are you sure?
You just take your honeymoon
before l change my mind.
-Thank you.
-There you go, sir.
-Thank you very much.
-Have a nice day, sir.
Next in line, please.
Hey, Darnell. l didn't know
you had an account here.
As a matter of fact, l never
saw you out of the projects.
Shut the fuck up
and empty the fucking drawer!
Empty the drawer!
Next in line, please.
Come on, Darnell.
Darnell, don't do this.
Now come on. Stop, please.
Why are you playing?
lt's not a fucking game.
Empty the fucking drawer!
Hell, no.
l want nothing to do with this.
Everyone get on
the fucking floor now!
Get the fuck on the floor!
Give me the money!
Come on.
Let's get this money, baby!
-Now!
-Get your ass on the floor.
Give him the money.
Lay your ass down! Stay there!
Hurry up!
Fill it up!
Give him the money!
Give him the money, bitch!
And hurry up, God damn it!
l said, hurry up!
Give us everything
in the drawer.
Oh, my God!
-Don't cry now.
-Hurry it up!
Here. Here. Take it.
lt's yours. Go! Go! Go!
Shit.
Oh, my God!
Come on, man!
Everybody stay down!
ls everyone OK?
Why don't we take it
from the top?
l thought we covered everything.
How well did you know
the perpetrator?
l've just known Darnell
from around the way is all.
We live in the same projects.
Frankie, will you do me a favor?
Just tell me one thing,
and we'll get out of here.
Sure.
What's the procedure
when you're being robbed?
Look, sir--
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Now...
what's the procedure
when you're being robbed?
You pull the money clip
from your right-hand drawer...
and then you signal
with the left hand.
You signal with the left.
So you know the procedure.
Yes. The procedure has been
told to me over a million times.
So why is it...
if that procedure's
been drummed into your head...
a million times--
you got that procedure down--
why wouldn't you follow it?
Because he had a gun!
And l went for my clip,
but he shot her.
He shot her
right in front of me.
l'm afraid we're going
to have to let you go.
That you knew the perpetrator
doesn't sit well with us.
Wait. But that's not right.
l haven't done anything wrong!
l can't help who l know!
Mr. Zachary, just last week,
you gave me a promotion...
and now you're going
to take my job away?
What happens the next time one
of your friends robs the bank?
How do we know
you're not in collusion?
Collusion?
Let me tell you something--
l am here at 2:20 sharp
every morning...
and l work my ass off
until quitting time.
Yesterday, l counted
$240,000 by hand for you!
That's how you should know!
l mean...
come on!
This is just not right!
l nearly got blown away in
your tight-ass fucking bank...
and you're going to fire me?
-Calm down.
-You couldn't even wait!
You didn't even bother to ask me
if l was thirsty, sister.
She's involved. l want
everything you have on her.
l thought l said
a Seventies graduation party.
Seventies, Halloween.
What's the difference?
You're the only one
in the neighborhood...
to give a Seventies
graduation party.
Anyway, T.T., Jajuan...
y'all look
awfully groovy tonight.
You like it, girl?
Thank you
for following directions.
Simple directions.
Look at him. Ain't he fine?
Just as handsome
as he wants to be.
l know it.
Can you believe
he's going to college?
Man, l remember when
you was just a little scrub...
always trying
to follow us around and shit.
On that tricycle.
Y'all always trying
to mess up somebody's game.
Please.
What game?
Whatever.
Stony,
you got a ten l can borrow?
We need some more chips.
Stuff running out.
Come on, college boy.
You're the one that's
going to be making all the loot.
You have to stop
spoiling that boy.
You've been taking care of him
since your mama and daddy died.
What you got?
You ain't drinking
none of this shit.
Stevie, what's the problem?
l'm not going.
l ain't going to college.
What? All right, look.
Don't start tripping, OK?
You cannot change your mind.
We got into UCLA,
and that's where we're going.
l ain't changed my mind.
l didn't get a scholarship.
They didn't give you
a scholarship?
But we told them
the only way we could apply--
l know.
All right.
Well, don't worry about it.
l'll take care of it.
lt's probably just because
l'm a January graduate.
How are you going
to take care of it?
You can barely pay the bills
around here.
l'll just get a job.
l'll help around here until--
No. Wrong. We're going
to stick to the plan...
and we are definitely
getting you up out of here.
l ain't hearing what this fool--
Good afternoon, ladies...
and gentlemen.
All right. Listen up.
Now, these good white folks
are trying to recycle...
all of their glasses,
plastics, and aluminum...
and you bitches putting
all the shit in the dumpsters.
You gots to recycle.
Who had 104?
l did.
You didn't
empty the cans in 104.
l'm docking your pay.
That ain't right.
Who are you supposed to be?
Goddamn Mighty Morphin
fucking Power Ranger?
What you going to do?
l'm docking her pay!
Speaking of pay,
l thought you said...
that you was going to pay me
under the table.
They're taking taxes
out of my check.
l don't even got enough money
to pay for my baby-sitter.
On this good earth...
there are three peoples
l don't mess with...
the ''l,'' the ''R,'' and the ''S.''
But l got my baby-sitter!
lf you don't like working
for Luther's Janitorial...
why don't you just take
your broke ass home?
Otherwise, shut the fuck up
and get back to work!
You one cold-hearted
motherfucker, Luther.
Get back to work.
You didn't have
to talk to her like that!
Tisean, you have got to learn
to stand up for yourself.
Did y'all hear
what happened to Frankie?
Our Frankie?
Lorenz and them robbed a bank.
This kid's got 211s
in four cities.
He's wanted
in Nevada, Arizona...
He's damn near professional.
What's he, twenty-one?
-They're getting younger.
-Yeah?
l want everything you got
on his young ass--
where he hangs out,
who he knows, where mom lives.
Everything. l want it all.
Look at that. Check that out.
His hair. What is that?
''A...P''?
What's that, a nickname?
''Asshole, perhaps''?
Oh, fuck off.
Cleo...
when you gonna fix
this raggedy shit?
Never mind my shit, fool.
Frankie, l heard what happened
at the bank the other day.
Keep your head up, girl,
all right?
Up. Up.
Watch this motherfucker.
That's all right.
Your shit is original.
Damn right.
Don't worry,
my shit is going to be tight.
Cleo, you've been fixing up
this car since seventh grade.
Do you know Lorenz and them
got away with twenty grand?
Twenty? Jeez. Damn.
See, that's what the fuck
we need to do--
rob a bank.
No. That's crazy.
Really, though. The four of us
could take a bank.
lf that crackhead Darnell
can rob a bank, we can.
Twenty Gs
would save my life right now.
Stevie needs tuition.
Well, too bad
we ain't some hard-up...
crackhead motherfuckers
like Lorenz and them.
Then we could do some
suicidal shit like rob a bank.
But we ain't crazy, so we can't.
So now you making the rules?
Frankie, please!
Ain't nobody over here
going to be robbing no bank.
You're right.
We ain't going to rob no bank.
Let's just go in there
and blow it the fuck up!
Here you go.
Can you believe after working
at that bank for two years...
l can't get a recommendation
for another job?
All right, l'm going
to hook you up with Luther.
l know you ain't happy,
but you need a job.
Ursula, come here.
How you doing, Ursula?
What's up?
What the fuck is up with that?
She don't talk?
Not really.
Girl, next time l page you,
you better be calling me back.
Excuse me. Drink, please.
What's up, girl?
That's a cute outfit.
Want some?
Hey, Stony, look, girl.
There's Nate Andrews.
Girl, didn't he want you
to work in his car lot for him?
Yes, and that's not all
he wanted.
You going over there?
Yeah. l'm going to see
what he wants.
So how much money could
l make selling cars for you?
Well, it depends.
l mean, you can make...
two Gs a month on commission.
-That much?
-Yeah!
l told you you needed to get
somebody who could help you.
Nate,
before l come work for you...
l need an advance.
There's a little problem
that l need to fix.
Oh! l can do that.
But l mean, Stony Newsome...
you got to give me
a reason to do that.
You know what l mean?
What would that be?
Come on, now. You know.
Let's go for a ride, huh?
So when do l get my advance?
l don't know.
Tomorrow. Maybe the day after.
Nate, before l do this,
l want my check.
Whoa. Look, you're not getting
no check from me...
until l'm done, you understand?
This ain't right.
lt's not even worth it.
Shit.
l'm in a bind, Nate.
Some other time.
l really need this money, Nate.
What the fuck is that?
lt's Frankie.
lt's her first night.
-What's wrong with you?
-Nothing.
Look at this motherfucker.
Bet you he ain't never
held a broom in his life...
and she ain't did no dishes
or washed no clothes.
This is a ugly-ass baby!
You know, white people be
having some old water head...
crying-ass, ugly babies.
l can't unload these things
without dropping them.
Frankie, relax!
How can you stand
the smell of this garbage?
-The shit ain't that bad.
-Ain't that bad?
Cleo, you live in a garage!
Girl, it'll be OK.
And you--stay out of it.
Damn. Look at my nails!
Shit, girl,
you been bitchin' all night.
Stony back there
acting all stank-a-dank-dank.
That's all right.
l got something for that here.
Ow, girl! That hurt.
That's the only way
you get the knot out.
Yep. l rolled this one good.
Blunt talking to me,
motherfucker.
Stop it, girl. Stinky.
There.
Cleo, l done told you
l'm strictly dickly.
l'm going to tell Ursula.
You're going to tell nobody.
Check out Stony.
Look at her. Look at her.
Chronic always get her ass
all quiet.
Look at her sitting over there.
Hey, you fucked up,
ain't you, girl?
What?
What's wrong with them?
You know.
Every time we get high...
you start looking
like Sugar Bear.
For real.
Y'all cold.
You do kind of look like
Sugar Bear.
Fuck all y'all.
Simple bitches.
Cleo, don't get salty.
Damn.
Before they started
laying people off...
they was paying folks fifteen
dollars an hour at that place.
Man. That's good money!
For fifteen dollars an hour,
l'd be all...
''Fuck, l'm right here.
''What l gotta do,
Sir Ass Motherfucker?''
They'd have to pull me off
that damn machine.
Shit.
That overtime would be
twenty-two fifty an hour!
l don't know
what l'm going to do.
Now that Luther's
taking taxes out of my check...
l'm making half as much
as l used to.
Only way we going to see cash
is we take a bank.
Now, see, l'm with that shit.
Y'all niggers
done lost your mind.
We might as well not even talk
about this shit no more.
l'm talking about it.
Ain't nobody going to stop me
from talking about it.
Well, talk is cheap...
nigger.
Wait. l mean, you know?
Frankie,
you gonna get slapped.
What?
You always talking shit.
You want to blow the bank up,
now you want to rob it.
Frankie want to blow up the bank
Frankie want to rob the bank
l ain't heard nothing
about that.
l said, hang up the phone.
You know who that is.
Yeah. l gotta go. l'll be over.
Don't drink up
my champagne, man. Peace.
Champagne?
Whatever. l ain't got time.
Look! Did your sister
come through for you or what?
-Where'd you get this?
-Don't worry about it.
Ain't none of your business.
Just look at the digits.
Stony, there's something
l got to tell you.
Look, l know
this is hardly enough money...
but l will get every--
No. Listen to me.
l didn't get into UCLA...
and l'm not going
because l didn't get accepted.
You didn't get in?
Don't go off on me now.
Don't you tell me
not to go off on you!
Do you have any idea
what l had to go through?
Do you?
l'm not staying around for this.
You are going to hang around
for this, so don't move.
Why did you have to lie to me?
Stony, you know
how long you told me...
that l had to go to college?
Well, l'm sorry, but maybe
that life is just not for me.
Shit.
Who is it?
Lorenz, it's Stevie, man.
Come on. Open up, man.
Hey, Lorenz, chill, man.
Hey, l heard you robbed a bank.
l didn't rob no bank.
l heard your party
was awful good.
You know why l didn't come.
Your sister don't like me.
She be trippin'.
Nah, she cool, man.
To let you tell it.
Here, Mr. UCLA.
Here.
You all right?
-Yeah. l'm straight, man.
-All right.
Hey, that ''AP'' is phat.
''Acorn Projects.''
Man, l thought you knew!
Oh, well...
You want this?
No, man. l'm straight. No.
You know your sister
whup your ass.
My sister
ain't gonna do nothing.
Tamika, hook him up.
He ain't from Acorn.
Fuck all that.
Get the clippers,
hook his ass up.
Take your ass in the kitchen
with your raggly ass.
You talk too much.
Come on!
Ain't nothing funny, man.
Go on. You, too.
All right, man.
Cool. Thanks for the champagne.
Freeze!
Get down on the ground!
Get down now!
Get him down! Get him down!
Get down!
-He's got a gun!
-Wait!
-Waller!
-Check apartment ''L'' now!
Get me an ambulance!
Get me a medic!
-He's up there!
-Get me an ambulance now!
Come on, God damn it!
Stay with me here!
Get me a fucking ambulance!
A fucking champagne bottle.
Open that, quick.
Get down!
Shit! l didn't do nothing!
Goddamn pigs!
What you fucking with me for?
-Man down!
-We've got it covered!
-Get in here!
-Go, go!
God, no!
What have you done?
Excuse me.
This motherfucker.
lf you need to talk,
if you have any questions...
l hope
you won't hesitate to call.
There will be
a full investigation.
-No!
-All right. OK.
Fuck you!
Fuck your investigation!
What have you got?
Stevie Newsome. No priors.
Good student.
Headed for college, l hear.
Both parents killed in
a car accident four years ago.
God damn it.
We can do this.
We can get some wigs,
some sunglasses, and it's on.
Y'all gonna have to do this
without me.
l keep thinking about Darnell
getting killed and Lorenz shot.
That's because Darnell and them
were a bunch of damn fools.
They don't know half
of what l know about banks.
What if something goes wrong?
What if somebody gets hurt?
Listen to me.
You're just scared, baby.
Ain't nobody gonna get hurt.
That's why
this is the perfect crime.
l know this too well.
What about
all them folks' money?
-lnsurance.
-Dumb-ass comment.
Look, we're just taking
away from the system...
that's fucking us all anyway.
You know?
Let's do it.
Excuse me.
How can l help you
today, Miss...?
Dorsey.
l'd like to open up
a new account.
Right this way.
You can open up an interest-
bearing checking account...
with a thousand dollar deposit,
if you like.
-lt's up to you.
-A thousand dollars?
Do you have long lines?
Not too bad. We usually operate
with about fourteen tellers.
Actually, l'm a manager
in corporate banking upstairs.
l don't know what
these folks do down here...
but when l saw you,
l said to myself...
''Self, a woman that fine--''
As fine as you are,
and you are that fine--
''Needs to have
her own personal banker.''
So l couldn't help myself.
She smiles. Come on, now.
Ms. Dorsey, l'm new in town...
and l swear to you,
l don't do this all the time.
l know you don't know me
from Adam.
l don't know
what your plans are tonight...
Do you have plans tonight?
-Are you asking me out?
-Maybe.
Keith, well, l see
you're in new accounts now.
Nigel, thank you. Thank you
for your observation there.
These people
are going to kill me.
Now, can l have your number?
But l'll take yours.
Well, what were you doing
in there?
l was just talking.
But l thought we was here
to case the bank.
That's what l was doing.
He has an inside track.
He works here.
Plus he grabbed me.
Did he ask you out?
Maybe.
So you ain't gonna tell me, huh?
Well, maybe he could
put a smile on my face.
Girl, Luther is gonna kill you
if he sees that baby.
-T.T., What happened?
-l had to bring him with me.
Hey, wait. Whoa!
Don't put him there, please.
Put him over there.
Come on!
-Come on! Move it!
-lt's OK, ma'am.
We can't waste time!
Let's go! Let's go!
Open the elevator!
Open it up! Hurry up!
lt's all right.
l think your son is going
to pull through just fine.
-Yes.
-Can l see him?
You need to speak with Ms. Wells
with Child Protective Services.
No. l know you ain't fixing
to take her son.
Wait, hold the fuck up.
That was an accident.
We was right there,
looking right at him.
lt wasn't two seconds--
l need to talk
to the mother alone.
Ms. Williams, the boy
has been severely poisoned.
l'm sure it was an accident...
but we're going to retain
custody just to be sure...
the child isn't suffering
from neglect.
That's my son.
l would die for him.
He was in an unsafe environment.
He shouldn't have been
at the workplace with you.
l didn't have a choice.
l don't have money
for a baby-sitter.
You're going to have to prove
you can take care of him.
Kids get into poison every day.
Not in the workplace.
To us, that spells neglect.
Now, Jajuan will remain
in our custody...
until you can pay
for proper child care.
What if l can't
come up with the money?
Like l said,
you will get a court date.
At that time, the judge
will decide what will happen.
Please! You can't take my baby.
l'm going to die
without my baby.
Tisean, come on.
l'm gonna die without my baby.
T.T, we're going to handle this.
Fuck this shit.
You know what you got to do.
You know.
You in?
Come on, T.T.
Cleo, take the note
to the merchant teller.
She will have
at least twenty grand.
On Wednesdays,
Sears makes a big deposit...
so she could have
thirty-five thousand.
l give her the note and tell her
not to give me any bait money.
Tell her not to draw
from the right-hand clip.
lf she does,
she's setting off the alarm.
''Don't give me any bait money...
''and if you come out
of that right-hand clip...
''my gun goes in your mouth.''
That's what l'm talking about.
Let's go through plan ''B.''
Plan ''B''?
Fuck this planning shit.
Why can't we just kick butt
with these motherfuckers...
and go up in there
and take all the fucking money?
Why can't you just listen
for once?
Plan ''B,'' Frankie.
Stony, when Cleo goes
to the merchant teller...
you start to survey the line
for the cow.
Cow? There's going to be a cow
up in there?
Stop smoking weed.
Cleo, the cow
is just a small vault on wheels.
They push it
from window to window...
depending on
which teller needs cash.
lf the cow is there,
it'll be open...
and we'll have
at least fifty thousand.
Look here,
let me talk to Black Sam.
Black Sam,
she want to talk to you.
Damn.
Shit.
-So what you need?
-A favor.
Yeah, well, what else is new?
Come on, Black Sam.
After all them cars
l done stole for you?
We're going there, huh?
All right, check it out.
Y'all can roll
with that right there.
We ain't robbin' stagecoaches.
l need something
l can set it off with.
Y'all ain't bullshitting?
We want them guns
we were shooting.
You're tripping.
Y'all can't afford them guns.
That's why it's a favor.
l'll bring them back...
with interest.
With interest, huh?
Check this.
What's up with hooking me up
with your homegirl, Frankie?
lnterest. That's it, Sam.
lt's like that.
l'm going to let y'all
use my shit, right?
But if y'all get caught--
l'm already knowing it. l know.
Yeah, all right.
l'm coming back
for that Uzi, too.
Bruce, go on and hook them up.
The right shit.
All right.
Come on, baby.
What have we got here? Bullshit.
Fucking bullshit.
Now, that's what l ride to.
OK, ready?
Y'all OK?
OK, wait a minute.
Let's just wait.
OK, let's just wait.
Just for a second.
What's wrong?
l can't do this.
Frankie, she's right, OK?
We didn't case this bank.
We cased Downtown Federal.
They're all pretty much
the same.
l ain't feeling this, Frankie.
This ain't right.
Everybody get down
on the ground right now!
Put your hands up!
Everybody stay down!
Go! Go!
-All right!
-Turn around!
All of y'all,
turn the fuck around!
-Don't move!
-Move back! Move back!
Turn around, girl!
What the fuck you looking at?
Give me the money!
Pull out the drawer!
Put the phone down!
Put your arms up!
You better lay down!
-Don't move!
-Y'all just be cool!
Don't move! Don't move!
Stay there.
Fuckers...
what are you looking at?
l'm a bitch with a gun! Two!
We're taking too much time!
-Come on!
-Here we go.
Move it!
We're almost to the door.
Come on! Go, go!
Now, that's how you work it.
That shit was brilliant!
Frankie, we robbed a bank!
Listen to me.
That is a lot of money.
Are we going
to get away with this?
What do you mean?
What does this look like?
ls it ours?
Shit!
Did you lock that door?
-Where have you been?
-l caught the bus.
We weren't ready.
You know we weren't ready.
Look, if l didn't set it off,
we'd be casing banks...
for the next two months.
l had to push off!
lt worked, didn't it?
Look, Tisean, it's over.
We got about...
-What?
-About twelve Gs.
Twelve thousand dollars
in sixty seconds.
Why don't you come over here
and sit down beside me?
OK? Come on.
Sit!
The vehicle stolen
from here today was lDed...
as the getaway car
in that South L.A. bank job.
l want to run prints
on all these.
See if anybody shows up.
All right. Dust everything.
Moi. And...T.T.
T.T.? She ain't getting a cut.
Look, Frankie,
l ain't for your shit tonight.
T.T. needs it
more than any of us.
She didn't do anything.
She walked out.
Who the fuck cares?
She was there.
No! She didn't do nothing,
so she ain't getting nothing.
Forget it.
Frankie,
l don't want your money.
lf you want to kick my ass,
let's get it over with...
because l am sick of your shit.
l need that money.
lt ain't you l'm mad at.
Damn. l'm sorry. l was tripping.
You're my girl.
l need this.
You are so special, Frankie.
Still ain't do shit.
Waller, anything ever come up
on that Francesca Sutton girl?
The bank teller suspected...
of being in collusion
in the Pan-Pacific robbery?
Nothing. Clean as a whistle.
OK, run this again for me.
-Come in for a drink?
-No, thank you.
-You sure?
-Yeah.
All right. Let me get my jacket.
l could have come
and picked you up.
No. l needed the exercise,
thanks.
-You look great.
-Thanks.
-What?
-Nothing.
l've just never been out
with a guy like you before.
A guy like me.
What does that mean?
l see. You must be used
to those roughneck types.
Where are we going to eat?
Maybe you could show me
someplace in your hood.
-ln my hood?
-ln your hood.
No, you ain't trying to flow
like that.
l might be trying to flow
You're probably
from Harvard and all.
As a matter of fact, l am.
l still got to eat.
l'm still very hungry,
so could we please feed a man...
give him some nourishment
or some sustenance?
That's all l'm asking...
Miss You-need-to-starve-
because-you're-from-Harvard.
This is really
a nice restaurant.
lt's black-owned. l like that.
Do you come here often?
No. l've never been.
l just heard about it.
So where are you from?
D.C. Have you ever been?
Nope.
No, but that's where the mayor
got popped basing up, isn't it?
Nobody's perfect, right?
lt's a great town, though.
l really miss it.
Anyway, l came directly
from New York.
You ever been to New York?
Have you ever been
outside Los Angeles?
When l was in New York,
l was working on Wall Street...
and before that, ''B'' School--
Business school. l'm sorry.
l wanted to go
to business school.
Really? Financing? Marketing?
No. Typing and bookkeeping.
l'm sorry.
ls that not professional enough?
lt's just hard for me to believe
that you're this hard...
when you're so beautiful.
And so tough.
Not tough. l don't think
we have anything in common.
l don't want anything from you.
l really don't.
l have no expectations,
no demands.
l am quite content...
just listening to you...
sitting here...
staring into those beautiful,
pretty brown eyes.
Are you cross-eyed?
No. Your head is just small.
My head is small.
Makes my eyes go this way...
because l have to focus in
on your little peanut.
No, l'm just kidding.
This is it.
lt's not much, but it's home.
l took the lease
over from my brother...
who brought me to L.A.
Do you feel free?
Hell, yeah, l feel free.
Well, l don't feel free.
l feel very much caged.
Caged?
What are you doing about it?
What do you mean?
What are you doing
to get out of it?
What are your plans?
Where do you see yourself
in five years, Stony?
l don't know.
That's what l'm saying.
We don't plan for the future,
as a people.
Have you ever thought about it?
Just put some serious thought
into seeing your future?
Well, l worked
really hard to keep...
a roof over
me and my brother's head...
to keep clothes on our back...
And l planned on
sending him to college.
That's great.
Then he should go to college.
He'll go on and accomplish
tremendous things...
and be great and wonderful,
like his sister.
He's dead.
l'm sorry. l didn't realize.
-lt's OK.
-No, it's not.
l'm dealing with it.
You are, aren't you?
ls that a cabernet or a merlot?
Damn.
-Take care of it.
-All right.
Captain Fredricks, sir?
Do you remember
the Pan-Pacific bank robbery...
where four people were killed
and the subsequent arrest...
where a young man
was shot and killed?
We're still getting
bad press with that.
l'd like to bring in
his sister Lita Newsome.
l think
she's one of the bank robbers.
What you got?
Right now l've got a girl
named Francesca Sutton.
She's a teller
at the Pan-Pacific bank...
and l'm relatively certain
she was connected.
Go on.
Francesca Sutton and
Lita Newsome are best friends.
Right,
that's a big coincidence...
but there's also
a physical likeness--
Do you remember the headline?
''lnnocent student
killed by cops.''
Now you want
to bring in his sister...
based on the fact
that she knows someone...
who may be friends
with a bank robber?
You're goddamn right--
What the hell's wrong
with you, Strode? No way!
Can l get a tail on her, sir?
What part of ''no''
don't you understand, Strode?
The ''N'' or the ''O''?
Oh, shit, now.
Watch it!
Fuck them niggers. Yeah!
Watch it, honey.
Here it come now.
Yeah, now.
Shit, girl. What is you--
Cleo, how come you ain't been
to work in a week?
'Cause look what l got here.
l bought my baby
some new things.
Check them out.
Luther said you're fired.
We got to act
like nothing's different.
You need to get to Luther's
and get your job back.
Man, Luther can kiss
my ashy kneecap.
This money got you tripping.
l know you out of money
by now, Cleo.
Now what you going to do?
Rob another goddamn bank.
What the fuck is y'all thinking?
Hold up. We said once, Cleo...
to get us enough change
to get out of here!
That's all it is, Stony.
We need some real money.
l don't know how far out of town
you plan to get, baby sister...
but you ain't
getting far on three grand.
Really?
All right, Louise,
you take Thelma over there...
and y'all go rob another bank
if you all that.
Fuck you.
l know you ain't fin to back
down on us now we need you.
l want some more
motherfucking money.
You are real high...
and you acting real stupid.
You need to get
that gun out my face.
Shit!
Don't you ever fucking
raise a gun to me again!
Or what?
What!
Are you going to hit me,
motherfucker?
Stony,
we go back to first grade!
You been my peeps
for twenty years!
Get off of me!
You know what? l ain't
fucking with you no more.
Yeah, well, fuck you, too!
Fuck her!
Ay, qu linda! Come on in.
How you doing?
l'm all right.
You sure? All right.
Hope you like Mexican food.
We have fajitas, enchiladas,
special sauce.
Have a seat right there.
You say you don't travel a lot.
This is what
we're going to do, Stony.
From here on out, l cook.
We eat.
You pick the country,
starting with Mexico.
Now, sit back. Relax.
Take a load off your feet.
Smell the aroma of Mexico
and the sounds...
What?
l just got a lot on my mind.
You want to talk about it?
What do you think about
friends and money?
l think they don't mix. Why?
l just had
a very big argument...
with one of my best friends
about a money situation...
and l don't think
we're gonna be friends anymore.
Don't you lose that friend
over money.
lt's not worth it.
The money you can replace easy.
Friends--
real friends...you can't.
Don't sweat it.
You have the answer
to everything, don't you?
No, l wouldn't say that.
l'm just sharing
my experience with you.
Who do you think you are?
l'll be your genie
if you let me.
Your every wish is my command.
Cleo, you know you was wrong
for what you did to Stony.
Fuck her! Fuck Stony!
We'll do this without her.
Wait a minute. Let's suppose
Stony put a gun in your face.
What would you do?
l would have slapped you, too.
Come on, now.
l wasn't gonna shoot her.
You know how l get
when l'm faded.
You still was wrong.
T.T., what's my girl gonna do?
l know you got to step
to that judge...
and prove you got some coins
in the bank.
l ain't doing nothing
without Stony.
l don't want to give
that ho no ride.
Why don't you
stop acting like a baby?
Bingo.
Come to me, baby. Oh, yeah.
Grin in that photo.
You love to see it.
Hey, Waller.
Tell me something...
did l or did l not say
all these women run together?
Do you feel me?
l thought that you would.
Work with me, baby.
Look, l'm sorry.
You're sorry.
Let's just put it all behind us.
Come on. We been through worse.
Apology accepted.
But you know you need
to come back in with us.
You ain't got enough money
to get out of town.
You're right about that.
But l want more than that.
l mean, is this the only way?
See, 'cause
l want to be somebody...
who doesn't have to do this,
you know what l'm saying?
Stony, you can go to suburbia
and start a new life...
but we ain't nothing
but hood rats.
Now, l can live with that.
You can't.
The hood is where l belong.
l mean, what am l
going to do in Hollywood...
or Thousand Oaks or some shit?
Man, shit.
Why do we got to roll over
and accept that, though?
We got to have a plan.
What does our future look like?
Where do you see yourself
five years from now?
l don't know...
and l don't care.
And l ain't thinking
about five years from now.
l'm just trying
to get through today.
What the hell?
Cleo, l know you didn't come
to work.
Ain't been to work
and don't call nobody.
l'm broke, Luther.
l know you gonna give me
my old job back...
'cause don't nobody take shit
the way l take shit.
Shut up before l stick that mop
up your ass, Luther.
You better save that
for your little girlfriend.
Well? Get to work!
Ladies...and gentlemen!
There's been a rift
in this family...
and that is not
good for business.
We want a plan like it was.
Back to work, see?
lf only Tisean and Stony
will come rob the bank with us.
We started as a gang of four.
We must always be four.
Don Stony from the Bronx,
what is your opinion?
Should we rob the bank?
Only way l can return
to this family.
lf we do this one more time,
we do it right.
Get enough money to get us
up out of here for good.
T.T., you agree?
Cleomenza, no more
funny-looking underwear...
for your little girlfriend.
Cleomenza...
no more...fancy cars.
The shopping sprees...
Cleomenza, can you respect
our conditions?
Can you live with the terms
that your dons have set forth?
Yes, Godfather.
Tisean Scalina from Detroit...
are you cool with all of this?
And you,
Don Stony from the Bronx...
can you accept
your godfather's terms?
All right, then.
We back in effect.
Next stop is
Balboa Savings & Loan.
Think you can do that?
Hurry up.
You got it?
Come on, Cleo.
What are you doing?
-Pass me a tape.
-No. Let's go.
l ain't going nowhere
till you pass me a tape.
Take that shit and let's go.
-Help me out.
-Please don't.
Come on.
l've been out here all night.
l'm sorry.
Come on. Just a couple
of bucks or something.
l'm sorry, ma'am.
Sir, please, will you stop?
You're annoying
our customers out here.
l'm not hurting anybody.
Come on, man.
l want you to move down
and leave our people alone.
Now, l've been asked
to come out here--
Come on, man.
l'm not hurting anybody.
-You're drunk.
-No, l'm not.
Everybody get the fuck down
right now!
Move it! You, down!
Hands over your head!
Back away from the drawers!
That's right, you!
Move back! Get down!
Open that drawer!
Fill it up! Let's go!
Did you hear what l said? Down!
Back up! Back up!
You, up! Let's go!
Oh, please!
Oh, please, mama!
Bitch,
would you shut the fuck up?
Nobody move!
-What's going on here?
-We're having difficulties--
l'm not bothering anybody.
Come on.
What's happening?
A minute and a half! Come on!
Just get your money.
Don't be a hero. Let's go!
You! Open up the cow!
We need backup over here.
We got a vagrant
that's drunk and disorderly.
Would you send
another unit, please?
Come on! Let's make it!
Move it!
-Let's make it! Come on!
-Cover me!
Don't make me
get ugly up in here...
ladies and gentlemen...
not today.
Hey, you! Keep your hands down!
Everybody face down!
Face down!
Let's go! Let's go!
Keep him in line, girl.
-Down!
-Hey! Come on, let's make it!
Hey! Don't.
Do not.
Where's Cleo?
Come on! Let's go!
Let's go, God damn it!
You are crazy, Cleo.
Holy shit!
Move! Move!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Yeah! We dig that shit!
The way you busted
through that wall!
We did it!
l thought it was over,
with the cops right outside!
Where was you going?
l was coming
to get y'all's asses!
What about T.T.?
The way she got the drop
on the cop!
lf you think of anything else,
give us a call today.
-Where's the girls?
-Took off in the Suburban.
The getaway car was blocked.
They're still out there.
Car theft reports from
near the 21st Street garage.
Getting in way over their heads,
aren't they?
They don't fucking know it.
Man, counting money is
harder than working for Luther.
l'm getting dizzy up here!
Two hundred and ninety-six
thousand and counting!
-What's that?
-seventy-five thousand apiece.
Seventy-five thousand apiece.
That's a lot of money.
l'm rich!
Look at all of this.
Look, this is
what we're going to do.
We're going to keep
scrubbing floors for Luther...
like we've been doing.
Nothing's changed.
We get Jajuan, and in
three days, we are out of here!
l'm going to miss you all.
Well, what happened?
What did she do?
Girl, you know
you coming with us.
l got money!
You run the CDs
from the parking garage?
Yeah. They're clean.
Give these a try.
lt's all connected.
All right.
We'll get these dusted now.
How come we're putting the money
in here instead of at home?
lf the police track us down,
that's the first place to look.
All right.
Stony, listen. l'm substituting
for my boss tonight...
at a party for the National
Association of Bankers...
at the Biltmore,
and l'd like for you to come--
Damn it.
That would be really nice.
Great. Listen,
be here early, like 6:00...
because l don't know
what time the limo's coming...
since you won't let me
pick you up.
Limo?
Black tie. Limo. 6:00.
l'll see you then.
Y'all are real rude.
l know you heard me
on the phone.
Do you like it?
Yeah. You look great.
No, you don't.
No. lt's colorful.
We're late. l'll be right back.
l told Frankie l look
like a box of crayons.
So, you like?
lt's real nice.
You got a bar. You got crystal.
We've been spending
a lot of time together lately...
and it's been nice.
We've been real straightforward
with one another, honest...
but l have lied about one thing.
What have you lied about?
Let's take a little detour.
Alex, do me a favor.
Change of plans.
Take a right at the next light,
and l'll tell you from there.
Should we go?
You're doing great, baby.
Enjoy yourself tonight.
-Champagne?
-Yes. Thank you.
Are you nervous?
-Don't be.
-OK.
You are the most
beautiful lady in the room.
Don't you ever forget that.
Hey, Nigel.
How you doing, buddy?
-How you doing?
-Patrice.
Thank God you're here.
l was getting tired...
of making clever banter
with Ross Milner.
-Hello. l'm Nigel.
-Hi.
You're Miss New Account.
Your follow-up is impressive.
l taught Keith everything
about corporate banking.
l'd like you to meet my--
Lady.
There are some heavy hitters
here--Muchigawa from Sonawa.
Yeah. l saw Storum
from Citibank over there.
Check this out--if a terrorist
blew this place up...
the banking systems
of Japan, Europe...
and the United States
would never recover.
l thought that a room
full of dead bankers...
meant that the world
would be a better place.
My wife.
So, Stony,
are you in banking also?
Yes...in a way.
Wells Fargo, B. of A., Chemical?
l prefer to create
my own personalized portfolio...
reflecting an original, diverse
taste in funding sources.
Well.
Always got me in trouble.
Always raiding sororities.
So he hasn't grown up yet,
but we're working on him.
Right. He seems like a nice guy.
No. He's terrible. l hate him.
He's a good guy.
l want you to know...
this is one of
the best nights of my life.
l've never felt so special.
Do you feel free now?
Well, for now,
but it's not my life.
l've just borrowed
from pieces of yours.
Borrowing's not a bad thing,
as long as you return the favor.
Look at all your friends.
They all own banks.
Where l'm from, you're lucky
to have a bank account.
l just want to get out of here.
Have you ever felt like that...
like you just wanted
to get up and go...
and move forward and you can't?
Baby, you don't
have to go anywhere.
Stay with me
for a little while...
and then you decide
if you want to stick around.
You think about it.
With your fine self.
You crazy.
Hi. l'm Pete Rodney.
l'm taking over for Luther.
Where's Luther?
He ain't cleaning
this building no more.
He got out of the business.
l'm going to--
-Hi.
-How you doing?
This motherfucker
better not touch that money.
Rip it!
-Come on. Come on.
-lt's gone.
l'm going to kill
this motherfucker! Come on.
Yo, Sam. You got company.
Hey, Sam, you seen Luther?
Luther came by here earlier.
Looked like he came
upon some dollars.
Had this shit all permed up.
What's up?
We got twisted, man--
our money and your interest.
That's why
that fool was acting crazy.
See, now you're fucking
with my money, though.
But l know where he at.
He at a hotel
over there on 55th...
55th and Ninth.
Thanks.
Got a little something
for that ass, baby.
Climb out the pussy
for a minute, Luther.
Find it!
Look all around this room.
Tear it up if you have to.
You think you slick, huh?
Check her stuff, too.
You slick, right?
You better be here
for a good goddamn reason.
Money is a good goddamn reason.
Where is it?
What you talking about, money?
l'm going to ask you
one more time.
Where's my money?
Cleo, look, l don't know
nothing about no money.
You don't know
what the fuck l'm talking about?
What the fuck is this, huh?
Look at this shit--
watches and crystal...
and shit you done bought
with my motherfucking money.
Talking all that nonsense.
You don't know what
the hell l'm talking about.
Now look...
l ain't lying.
What the fuck is this?
My money.
All right, bro.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
''Alissa Lyons, 423 Moorpark.''
You didn't see
none of this shit, right?
All right. Just a little
fucking insurance, baby.
Now where the fuck
did Luther hide that money?
l swear l don't know.
Damn it, don't give me that!
You know!
l swear l just met him.
-Come on.
-Give me the money!
Come on!
l'll call you.
l hope so.
This weekend. ltalian.
l'll call you.
Man, l ain't trying to hear
this shit today.
Which one of you girls
smoked Luther?
l'm thinking it was you...
because you're the only one
with any priors.
l don't know what the fuck
you talking about.
l'll tell you what the fuck
l'm talking about.
We're going to take a ride
down to Parker Center.
Man, you ain't
got probable cause for shit.
All you're doing
is participating in a lineup.
And for the record,
having a witness...
is one fuck of a lot better
than probable cause.
Get in the car.
Today!
Take this home. Call the girls.
-They can't see me?
-Just your imagination.
Looks like
they're looking right at me.
Do you see her?
The person
that killed Luther Morris?
Take your time and concentrate.
Face right!
Do you see her--
the person that killed
Luther Morris?
No. lt's not her.
Be sure now.
Do you see her--
the person that killed
Luther Morris?
Look at her!
Get a real good look,
real close.
Right there. See her?
The person that smoked Luther.
Nope.
Can l go now?
You're real cute.
They got Cleo,
and y'all fucking killed Luther!
He wouldn't give up the money.
He was about to kill Cleo,
so Tisean shot him.
Now l got Cleo in trouble.
-Damn it! Shit!
-l'm sorry, Stony.
Look...
they're going to be
after all of us.
We're going to take that bank
downtown. Are you in?
No, l ain't in! Hell, no!
You ain't got no fucking choice.
And you don't tell me what
fucking choices l have, Frankie!
That's armed robbery...
and it's murder.
You said we weren't going
to hurt anybody, Frankie.
Girl, l got to have money
before my court date.
l have to.
And l can't go to jail...
for killing nobody.
l need you.
l really need you.
Cleo, what happened?
You all right?
Baby, go pack our shit.
Them motherfuckers
was all over me...
but l represented.
Now the problem is,
they on our ass now...
and we got to do two things--
rob another bank
and get the fuck out of here--
or we going to be in jail
by tomorrow morning.
l say we hit Downtown Federal.
That's where
the most money's at.
l'm telling y'all, we could get
five hundred thousand.
Fuck it. We hitting that shit.
Simple as that.
Look, Stony, we hot!
We all facing a murder rap!
Does it have to be
Downtown Federal?
What the fuck is that?
What, did you go and play us...
over that bumpy at the bank?
Fine.
lt's on.
l know you have a court date
tomorrow.
Good luck, Tisean.
Thanks, Ms. Wells.
l think everything's
going to be OK.
l'm sure it is.
Come here.
Everything's going to be
just fine.
Come on. Let's go.
OK, ladies, will that be all?
Some more coffee.
l don't think you should be
drinking so much coffee.
You making me nervous.
How the fuck is my drinking
coffee making you nervous?
-l don't know. lt just is.
-OK, OK. Listen up.
Nobody's ever successfully
robbed this bank.
l wish you would stop
saying that.
The nearest freeway
is a mile away.
We got to stick to the plan,
all right?
l know y'all sick of wearing
them wigs.
What you got?
l got some other stuff
in the car.
Thank you, ladies.
Cover my share until l finish
robbing this bank.
Shoot, l'm broke.
Don't look over here. l am, too.
Y'all...
we don't have enough money
to pay the bill.
We're in.
Bullshit.
-What the fuck is this?
-What are you doing?
Trying to find some mood music.
Fuck it. Radio.
Look at that.
Yo, what's up with that dress?
You going dancing or something?
What you got?
One for you...
one for you.
Check it out.
There has been
a rash of these robberies...
in the Los Angeles area
as far east as Pasadena...
and as far north as
the San Fernando Valley.
They seem to know
the inner workings of each bank.
Wigs and sunglasses
aid them in their disguise.
Their m.o. is ''in and out.''
Please do not be misled
by the fact...
that these four bandits
are females.
Once they get in here,
it's not going to be...
''Stick them up
and give me your dough.''
Your lives are going to be
in jeopardy, and that's a fact.
These girls are the real deal.
They've gotten real good at
casing the banks they knock off.
Yes. Keith Weston, please.
What the fuck are you doing?
They know the intricacies
of bank security systems...
and more importantly, they know
how to get around them.
They may even have a contact
on the inside, so be aware.
Obviously,
they don't appear this way...
when they're on the street.
This is Keith.
Keith, listen to me.
l need you to meet me
at the soul-food restaurant...
in five minutes.
Baby, why--
l'm leaving right now.
You be there.
Come on. Let's do this.
T.T.
Detective Strode.
You have a question?
Are we done here?
Actually,
we're just wrapping up.
l'm going to leave
a copy of that tape here.
-Thank you for your time.
-l'll show you out the back.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
Please be safe.
Please be careful.
All right. Y'all do your thing.
Now get down and don't move!
-Get the fuck down!
-Get down, everybody!
Don't move!
-Get down!
-l said down!
Get the fuck on the ground!
Right now! You!
Put your hands up!
Down!
Don't fuck with me today!
Put your hands up! That's right.
Down!
Can l get you anything?
No, thank you.
All units, silent alarm...
Downtown Federal building,
Seventh and Spring.
Proceed with extreme caution.
Suspects armed and dangerous.
Can you believe this?
-God damn it!
-Shit!
Don't move!
Let's make it!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Don't move!
We got a minute and a half.
You, down! You, don't move!
Get some more money.
Don't be greedy. Let's go now!
Get it now!
Let's go.
Don't move!
Stay down!
Hands out in front of you!
Come on!
Let's go!
Don't move.
Don't make me hurt nobody.
That's right,
ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Yeah, we goin'.
Move it!
Ladies and gentlemen,
nice and smooth.
Stay down! Don't move!
Lita Newsome!
Don't do this!
Put the gun down. Put it down!
Don't do this. Cleo!
Fuck you.
l know the deal. l do.
And l'm sorry about
your brother.
l'm sorry about Stevie.
l'm sorry he's dead,
l swear to God.
But don't do this!
Stevie was enough!
He was enough.
No more killing!
Put the weapon down.
Stevie was enough.
Stony, put it down.
Come on.
There you go.
What are you doing?
Motherfucker!
Help me.
Hold on!
Come on, baby. Come on!
Come on. Come on.
Let's go. Let's go!
Hurry up!
Back it up, back it up!
You'll be OK.
Come on, Frankie!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
What happened?
What happened to her?
We robbed this motherfucker,
and she gonna be all right!
Frankie, listen. l need you
to drive this car really fast...
and get us
to the hospital, OK? Go!
This motherfucker's
not going to make it.
We got to switch cars!
You do what you got to do.
You listen to me!
You are gonna make it
through this.
You understand me?
lt doesn't hurt.
We've been through
a lot together, haven't we?
-l'm OK.
-That's what l want to hear.
l want to hear you're OK.
Yes, l know you OK.
Just hold on for me, baby, OK?
Come on, Frankie, man,
drive this car!
You better tell them
to hurry up.
Come on, you guys!
He gonna be mad at you.
You don't worry about Keith, OK?
lf you're worried about
that tattoo...
you're going to get over
that hole.
You know what l could use
right now?
l could use a banana flamb.
Remember
those banana flambs we had
that time at that restaurant?
They were so good.
Remember?
Come on, Stony,
we got it started!
Let's get her! Come on! Come on!
-Sorry, T.T.
-We can't stay. Let's go!
Come on, let's move it!
Suspects are coming closer now.
Police reports
indicate that the women...
are from Los Angeles.
They've been identified...
as Lita Newsome,
Francesca Sutton...
Tisean Williams,
and Cleopatra Simms.
You've just seen
these alleged bank robbers...
avoid an L.A.P.D. blockade
on the First Street bridge.
However, the police
are still on the suspects' tail.
We'll try to follow the action
as best we can...
You got to drive faster!
Faster! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
That was a close one.
Here we go again...
the suspects
barely getting away this time.
l don't see any police vehicles
in pursuit at the moment...
but the L.A.P.D. helicopter
next to ours...
has clearly got a bead on them.
l just checked with the L.A.P.D.
liaison, by the way.
He's reporting
that this 1962 Chevy lmpala...
Go! Go! Go! Go!
l'm going!
l think l lost them.
You lost them ! You're good.
We have visual contact
with suspects' vehicle...
on Second Street tunnel.
-Shit!
-Damn!
Damn it!
What are you doing?
-Come on.
-Fuck!
OK, let's think.
Let's think. Let's think.
-All right, get out.
-What?
Get out
and lean up against the wall...
and in sixty seconds,
l want you to run that way.
Cleo, fuck, no! Hell, no!
Stony, shut up!
We got to split up!
We got to.
Look, l'll catch up to y'all
later, l promise.
-What about the money?
-Just hold on to it.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
All right, motherfuckers.
Suspects are on the move.
You want it? Here it go.
Here we go! Me and you!
They're gonna ram us!
We got to dump these clothes.
l love you.
Oh, God. You be careful, OK?
And now the police
are all over the suspects' tail.
Ain't that your girls?
Hell, yeah.
Damn. That's fucked up.
l just checked with the L.A.P.D.
liaison, by the way.
He's reporting
that this 1962 Chevy...
They through.
Helicopters and shit.
Ain't no escapin' that shit.
Get set!
Hold your positions!
Step out of your vehicle...
with your hands in the air.
keeping your hands in the air.
We've just had...
a horrible moment here.
This is...
our greatest fears
for what would happen today.
This is the most...
tragic culmination
of the day's events.
Damn.
Dad, sit down.
Freeze! Drop the bag! Get your
hands where we can see them !
Slowly turn around
and drop your weapon!
Get your hands up!
Wait!
Wait now. You wait, Waller!
God damn it, you wait.
Listen to me.
l'm taking it off here.
l'm not carrying, OK?
l got nothin'. You wait!
Tisean is dead.
Cleo is dead. She's dead.
All you got is you...
and now you got to save you.
Do you understand me?
Now, l need you on the ground.
Wait!
What's the procedure when
you got a gun at your head, huh?
What's the fucking procedure...
when you got a gun at your head?
lt's over.
We did it!
Cleo! Sit!
Man, l remember
you was just a little scrub...
always trying
to follow us around.
Stony, l'm glad you're safe.
l am.
Thank you.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/qt29
Help other users to choose the best subtitles