Toho Co., Ltd.
Ishihara Production
''Shadow''
Shadow Hunters
OfficiaI Notice
The entire area from here to the
headwaters of the Izushi river
is strictIy off-Iimits to aII persons.
By Order of the County Magistrate
Produced by:
Ishihara Yujiro
Okuda Kikumaru
Kobayashi Masahiko
we have nothing
more to lose.
OriginaI work by Saito Takao,
Saito-Pro Production
('Shukan Host' syndication)
ScreenpIay: Ikegami Kanao
we have nothing
more to lose.
Cinematography: Kanau Mitsuji
Art direction: Kobayashi Masayoshi
Recording: Sato Yasuhiro
Lighting: Fujibayashi Ko
Edited by: Watanabe Shiro
All l have in this life is what
is covered by my cape.
Music by:
Ishihara Yuujiro - Hirose Kenjiro
Osawa Yasuro - Sera Jo - Inomata Takeshi
& Sound LTD
Theme song: Teichiku Records, ''Shadow Hunters''
Lyrics: Yasutomi Yasushi
Composer: Hirose Kenjiro
Singer: Ishihara Yujiro
All l have in this life is what
is covered by my cape.
Music by:
Ishihara Yuujiro - Hirose Kenjiro
Osawa Yasuro - Sera Jo - Inomata Takeshi
& Sound LTD
Theme song: Teichiku Records, ''Shadow Hunters''
Lyrics: Yasutomi Yasushi
Composer: Hirose Kenjiro
Singer: Ishihara Yujiro
Music by:
Ishihara Yuujiro - Hirose Kenjiro
Osawa Yasuro - Sera Jo - Inomata Takeshi
& Sound LTD
Theme song: Teichiku Records, ''Shadow Hunters''
Lyrics: Yasutomi Yasushi
Composer: Hirose Kenjiro
Singer: Ishihara Yujiro
l bare my fangs to survive, but is this life?
l bare my fangs...
Costume Design: Yagyu Etsuko
Assistant Director: Ichige Katsumi
Props: Koyama Teruyoshi
Set Decoration: Yamamoto Kenichiro - Matsumoto Yoshihiro
Production Manager: Otake Katsuhiko
l bare my fangs to survive, but is this life?
l bare my fangs...
Swordfighting Choreographer: Kuze Ryu
Stunts: Shishido Daizen & Group
Cooperation: Seishu Shochikubai
l bare my fangs to survive, but is this life?
l bare my fangs...
Production Advertising: Nihon Geino Kikaku
Costumes: Dai-ichi Costumes - Kyoto Costumes
Wigs: Yamadaya
Props SuppIy: Takatsu Eiga Props
FiIm DeveIopment: Tokyo Laboratory Co., Ltd.
l bare my fangs to survive, but is this life?
l bare my fangs...
Production Advertising: Nihon Geino Kikaku
Costumes: Dai-ichi Costumes - Kyoto Costumes
Wigs: Yamadaya
Props SuppIy: Takatsu Eiga Props
FiIm DeveIopment: Tokyo Laboratory Co., Ltd.
Production Advertising: Nihon Geino Kikaku
Costumes: Dai-ichi Costumes - Kyoto Costumes
Wigs: Yamadaya
Props SuppIy: Takatsu Eiga Props
FiIm DeveIopment: Tokyo Laboratory Co., Ltd.
The smell of blood draws close the
beasts called Shadow Hunters.
Starring
The smell of blood draws close the
beasts called Shadow Hunters.
Ishihara Yujiro
(as Muroto Jubei)
The smell of blood draws close the
beasts called Shadow Hunters.
Uchida Ryohei (as ''SunIight'')
Narita Mikio (as ''MoonIight'')
They're hounds from hell. For me to
live, the bloody wind must blow.
Asaoka Ruriko
They're hounds from hell. For me to
live, the bloody wind must blow.
Ebara Shinjiro
Honda Michiko
They're hounds from hell. For me to
live, the bloody wind must blow.
Kusanagi Kojiro
Tamagawa Isao
Kuno Shiro
Fukae Shoki
They're hounds from hell. For me to
live, the bloody wind must blow.
Kusanagi Kojiro
Tamagawa Isao
Kuno Shiro
Fukae Shoki
Kusanagi Kojiro
Tamagawa Isao
Kuno Shiro
Fukae Shoki
Blood must rain, my
heart must freeze.
Muto Akio
Kihara Tsuchihiro
Harumi Yuzo
Horii Eiko
Shirakawa Keiko
Kasai Kazuhiko
Blood must rain, my
heart must freeze.
Muto Akio
Kihara Tsuchihiro
Harumi Yuzo
Horii Eiko
Shirakawa Keiko
Kasai Kazuhiko
Muto Akio
Kihara Tsuchihiro
Harumi Yuzo
Horii Eiko
Shirakawa Keiko
Kasai Kazuhiko
Swords shoot sparks, l must bare
my fangs, bare my fangs...
Chico RoIand - Kariya Shunsuke - Arai Ganei
Kikuchi Kenichi - Kahara Bumon - Kamota Kiyoshi
Swords shoot sparks, l must bare
my fangs, bare my fangs...
Yamagishi Emiko - Tsujimura Seishi - Kuwata Tetsuya
Otani Kazuo - Arakura Hiroshi - Harada Kunji
Omaeda Takeshi
Swords shoot sparks, l must bare
my fangs, bare my fangs...
Daimon Minoru - Okamoto Hisato - Inagaki Minoru
Kurata Yuji - Waka Koma
Narrator: Urano Mitsuru
Swords shoot sparks, l must bare
my fangs, bare my fangs...
Daimon Minoru - Okamoto Hisato - Inagaki Minoru
Kurata Yuji - Waka Koma
Narrator: Urano Mitsuru
Daimon Minoru - Okamoto Hisato - Inagaki Minoru
Kurata Yuji - Waka Koma
Narrator: Urano Mitsuru
Beasts called Shadow Hunters,
overthe blood-soaked land...
Tanba Tetsuro
Tatsumi Ryutaro
Beasts called Shadow Hunters,
overthe blood-soaked land...
Directed by: Masuda Toshio
Beasts called Shadow Hunters,
overthe blood-soaked land...
Directed by: Masuda Toshio
...once again
they run.
Chief! We
found it!
Open it.
Yes sir.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
No doubt about it, it's goId.
As we suspected.
The rumors that the Izushi cIan is digging for
goId in the mountains are weII-founded.
When the Chief EIder hears about
this, at the very Ieast...
...he'II force them to switch fiefs. And if we find
more probIems, the cIan wiII be aboIished.
Those bumpkin samurai have
done aII this for nothing.
Chief! Izushi samurai
are headed this way!
What?
Those mountain
monkeys!
Listen. It's our duty to report our discovery to
the Chief EIder, even at the cost of our Iives.
150-ri =366 miIes.
It's 150-ri to Edo.
Don't bIow it!
Sir!
We'II each carry some
of the proof.
Yes sir.
When we Ieave Izushi territory,
we'II spIit into three groups.
We'II meet at the Yakuno Inn in
Fukuchi. Be there at dusk.
Let's go!
Hey. You're
Iate.
What do you mean, samurai? We're just
simpIe piIgrims. What do you want?
You guys are government spies, the
so-caIIed ''Shadows,'' aren't you?
How did you know?! Who
are you?! Name yourseIf!
I make my Iiving hunting shadows.
They caII me ''MoonIight.''
What?
Here...
Hey...
You guys were faster
than my horse!
That Iooks good.
What?! Who are you?
Man, I'm starving!
What rock did you crawI out from under?
I'm a Shadow Hunter. They caII me ''SunIight.''
What?!
You can finish your dinner
in HeII. Say your prayers!
Come on in, Sir! WeIcome!
Thanks for coming in.
Boss. Some urgent
news!
What's the panic?
Koroku's team has been wiped out!
Junai's team as weII!
RidicuIous! I'm not known
for my sense of humor!
No, there is no mistake.
We saw the Izushi samurai hauIing off their corpses.
Boss... What shouId we do?
We'II retreat for now. Get ready!
Hurry up!
Move!
You're in our way, get out!
You have to pay your biII!
We'II pay it, just shut up!
Go, go!
Jackass, keep it down!
What a ruckus. Quiet down.
You've been Iiving it up aII day, but I Iet it
sIide, as a courtesy to tired traveIers.
But now you've become inconsiderateIy Ioud.
What's the story? Enough is enough.
What did you
say?!
I didn't reaIize we had a neighbor.
My apoIogies.
We're in a hurry. PIease
excuse the noise.
Wait.
Is that aII you've
got to say?
What do you mean? Is my
apoIogy not enough?
Bastard. Are
you...
Your deduction is correct. I'm
Jubei, the Shadow Hunter.
As the power of the Tokugawa Shogunate waned,
it came under increasing financiaI pressure.
The Shogunate government stopped at nothing to
maintain its power, and the dirtiest of its tricks...
Daimyo: a feudaI Iord, ruIer of a province.
...was to seize and absorb the properties
and weaIth of the Daimyo.
The Shogunate recruited a Iegion of spies
and ninja and used them to find...
...any misdeeds by the Daimyo that couId be
used as a pretext for seizing their weaIth.
PeopIe caIIed these spies and ninja ''Shadows,''
and greatIy feared them.
The Daimyo had onIy one defense against the
oppressive surveiIIance of these Shadows...
...which was to first identify, and
then annihiIiate them...
...and thus, siIence them before they
couId betray the Daimyo's secrets.
Ronin: a samurai without a master.
And now, into this Iandscape,
ride three ronin.
One was named Muroto Jubei, and the other two
caIIed themseIves ''SunIight'' and ''MoonIight.''
Hired by the Daimyo, they were hunters,
sent out to battIe the Shadows.
And aIways, they foIIowed their noses,
drawn by the scent of bIood.
Izushi CastIe, Tajima province
They're here.
Where is Makino, the chamberIain
of this province?
I'm Makino Zusho, the
castIe chamberIain.
Get off your horses! How dare you speak
to my master from the saddIe!
Kosaka! Be siIent.
But...
SiIence!
My apoIogies for his
bad manners.
So you are the Shadow
Hunters?
I'm Jubei. They are ''SunIight''
and ''MoonIight.''
Be weIcome. OnIy this morning, our checkpoint
in the mountains was attacked.
We have been awaiting
your arrivaI.
We are aware
of the attack.
Then why are you
arriving so Iate?
When you heard about the attack,
you shouId have rushed here!
You're ignorant of the way of the warrior!
You stray dogs aren't fit for this task!
What? What's
this?
ChamberIain... I beIieve
these are yours.
SunIight,
you too.
Do I have to?
Oh aII right...
Shit, and me hoping I was getting
a perk this time. Here!
These are ours. How
did you get them?
We started working as soon as we
heard about the commission.
We were greeted by Shadows before
we got here. It happens aII the time.
That's why we were Iate. PIease
forgive us for being tardy.
Kosaka... You accused them
of being insoIent.
But when they were addressed, they
had their feet out of the stirrups.
They are very famiIiar with the way of
the warrior; that's rare, nowadays.
Forget about it. We're stray dogs, and used to
being treated as such. So, Iead the way...
Dammit, they're making us wait so Iong. This
is why it's tough to get aIong with officiaIs.
Be patient. It's
part of the job.
These are the Shadow Hunters. They have
come in response to our appeaI.
Wait.
What's the matter?
The presence of uncouth ronin such as
we is an offense to a nobIe young Iord.
A mere gIance at us is far more
recognition that we deserve.
You need not concern
yourseIf so.
Are you the one
caIIed Jubei?
Yes.
I hear you are caIIed ''SunIight'' and ''MoonIight.''
I am gIaddened by your presence here,
at this time of crisis for our cIan.
We're honored.
Jubei, the chamberIain thinks you're our onIy hope.
PIease endeavor to save our
six-hundred retainers.
We are at your
service.
Lord?
Man, these formaIities
aIways drive me nuts.
What's this?
I wiII be serving you during your stay.
Your wish wiII be my command.
Yeah!
Fine...
But we won't be requiring
your services.
Hey MoonIight, Iighten up. It's rude to
stop peopIe from doing their jobs.
WeII, miss. How about we start
with a IittIe massage?
Enough, SunIight.
ControI yourseIf.
Strong...
You're good. Do you
do this a Iot?
Yes. I give my father massages
aII the time.
ReaIIy? How outrageous
of your dad.
Making you massage his wrinkIed
body with those pretty hands!
In contrast, you shouId
see my body.
How about you go
to work on it, eh?
PIease stop joking. How am I supposed
to give you your massage?
Okay then. How about we switch
roIes? Don't be shy, now...
I'II have you know, I'm especiaIIy
nice to the Iadies.
Without further deIay, we wiII now
pay you the promised sum.
We're a smaII cIan, Iocated
deep in the mountains.
PIease accept our apoIogies for the
poor quaIity of our hospitaIity.
You are too kind. We ronin are
unworthy of such formaIity.
Hey, ChamberIain, she sure was a fine surprise. I
was getting sick of being around guys aII the time.
You shouIdn't
have!
I am gIad you
are pIeased.
Koyuki. Serve
them weII.
Yes, I shaII,
father.
Father? You mean to
say you're... um...
She's my daughter, Koyuki.
A most rebeIIious chiId.
Yes sir.
Let me continue your massage.
Nah, I'm aII better now. H...hey. Jubei...
ChamberIain. You aIIow famiIy
members in your castIe?
My wife died Iong ago. Since then I have
been a singIe father to an onIy chiId.
I thought it wouId be better for her to tend
to castIe duties, rather than stay home.
Ah, yes. Our young Iord has
taken a shine to you, Jubei.
Why, he toId me, ''I know
we can count on him!''
I suspect that you were once
a nobIeman of some renown.
Sorry to disappoint you, but
I'm just a wandering ronin.
I choose to forget my past,
if you don't mind.
My apoIogies
for prying.
Now then. What is
the next move?
PIease advise me.
Shadow-hunting cannot
be pIanned.
It's fooIish to hope
they won't come.
So aII we can
do is wait.
Edo CastIe
Chief EIder.
Jinba Senjuro, Ieader of the third Iga
Ninja group, reporting as ordered.
Very good.
So teII me.
Regarding the case of the
Izushi cIan in Tajima...
How is the investigation going?
Sir.
It is now cIear that the Izushi
cIan has struck goId.
Here is the
proof.
So you've
found it?
I wouId have brought
five or six more.
But the Shadow Hunters
showed up.
The Shadow Hunters?
Curses!
ActuaIIy...
...that sampIe comes from
a top secret source.
To ensure that our agent's cover
wouId remain intact...
...we staged a diversion to conceaI
the true source of the sampIe.
Those Shadow
Hunters...
Those obnoxious bastards who dare to oppose
the authority of the Shogunate...!
Have you determined
their identities?
We have made some
inquiries.
Their Ieader is
Muroto Jubei.
The one named ''SunIight'' is Inui Tadanoshi,
and ''MoonIight'' is Kusaba Denosuke.
Shadow operations destroyed their cIans. Thus,
we beIieve they are motivated by revenge.
Investigate their backgrounds
more deepIy.
Perhaps we'II uncover
their weaknesses.
As for the Izushi
cIan...
...their efforts have
been wasted.
Koku: a quantity of rice, historicaIIy defined as
enough rice to feed one person for one year.
For a smaII fief of 58,000
koku to dig for goId...
...must have meant many sacrifices
and much hardship.
The fief is Iocated deep
in the mountains.
For the past severaI years...
...everyone, even the Ieaders, have had to
subsist on a diet of miIIet and beans.
GoId Iike this is wasted on those
mountain monkeys...
...especiaIIy when the Shogunate
is in such dire straits.
So, shaII we move against the
Izushi cIan without deIay?
We shaII force them
to switch fiefs.
IdeaIIy, I wouId want them crushed,
but there's a probIem.
This just came to
my attention.
Many years ago, at a battIe in
Osaka, an ancestor of...
...the current chamberIain, Makino Yukie,
was recognised for outstanding vaIor.
The Izushi cIan received a speciaI dispensation,
for muItipIe generations...
...and their fief was granted to them in perpetuity
under the seaI of Shogun Ieyasu himseIf.
I had not heard
of this.
Of course, if the existence of the
grant were pubIic knowIedge...
...we wouId have found an opportunity, some-
time in the Iast 150 years, to destroy it.
But the chamberIains of the Izushi cIan
have been wise, and cautious.
Having managed to safeguard the document,
they wiII use it as a Iast resort.
That does present a probIem. The
Shogun's seaI is sacrosanct.
If they were to produce that document,
we wouId be utterIy powerIess.
However, I must
have that goId.
We must use extreme
tactics.
The document must never
see the Iight of day.
Understand?
Izushi fief, Edo residence.
Were counting
on you.
A few days Iater, couriers from the Edo residence
of the Izushi fief raced towards home.
Good grief. We watch
the fief by day...
...and the castIe by night.
I'm getting worn out.
Express couriers.
Something must've happened in Edo.
We'd better get back.
Stop.
What is it?
You don't Iook famiIiar. What brings you to town?
I...
Shoji.
She might be mixed up with the Shadow Hunters.
She was paying cIose attention to them.
Don't bring her to the administrative
office. Bring her to the usuaI pIace.
After I'm done hearing what the couriers have
to say, I'II question her myseIf. Understood?
Yes sir.
Five days ago, Nitta, the chief retainer of
our Edo residence, was summoned...
...by the Chief EIder and
given this command.
Change fiefs?
How unjust!
I suspect that the
Chief EIder...
...got hoId of some
of the goId.
But that's impossibIe.
Our goId is for emergencies onIy.
Not one bar shouId be missing.
Then why wouId they want to take
controI of this impoverished Iand?
Lord Makino, what
shaII we do?
We've worked hard for our goId mines.
And now we must Ieave them behind.
If we were to refuse a change of fief,
we wouId need a convincing reason.
We have such
a reason.
What kind of reason
do you speak of?
We can refuse. We have
reason for refusaI.
This is Shogun Ieyasu's seaI on a guarantee,
in perpetuity, of our right to this fief.
I see.
With that, they couId neither crush
the fief, nor make the cIan Ieave it.
Why didn't you just whip that out sooner?
There'd be no need for Shadow-hunting.
You're a happy simpIeton.
Say what?!
This kind of thing is a doubIe-edged sword.
At first, the Shogunate wiII fear you wiII use it.
Then they wiII decide it needs to be destroyed.
My thoughts
exactIy.
And the probIem is, that document
must be presented in Edo.
WiII you guard the carrier
of the document?
It's 150-ri to Edo. That's
a heck of a Iong hauI.
Inspector-GeneraI Kosaka Kurando
is to carry the document.
The Inspector-GeneraI...?
That guy?
Hey Jubei, I'm outta here. That
smug bastard pisses me off.
Though you do not get
aIong with him...
...he's the finest swordsman
in our cIan.
I acknowIedge the gravity of the situation.
But our Iives are aIso at stake.
PIease give us this one
night to decide.
I am oId and fraiI. Our Iord is but a boy. You are
the onIy ones who can heIp. I beseech you.
I remember. When I
was young...
...about to become a chamberIain,
Iike my father before me...
But... after what happened... my
father committed suicide...
...and I, with my
own hands...
What a travesty. The government Iaid its hungry
eyes on the abundant prosperity of our fief.
They used Shadows to pIant evidence to
be uncovered. My cIan was aboIished.
As for our Iord
and his heir...
FareweII, Chitose.
Chitose. She was the daughter of a chief
retainer; he was my father's peer.
She and I vowed to each other that
someday we'd get married.
Jubei.
Yes?
Jubei. It is fareweII forever.
Let me see your face.
Jubei. You have taken good care of me,
for a Iong time. I shaII never forget it.
Hurry up!
Damn the accursed government
and its officiaIs.
Jubei. If you are the one acting as my
second, then I wiII not be afraid.
I wiII not be
afraid.
Young Lord. There is nothing
to fear. I, Jubei...
...wiII guide
you.
Like this, Jubei?
Is this how?
What's up, Jubei?
Not feeIing weII?
You Iook
paIe.
No. It's nothing.
Good. Anyway, what are we
going to teII him tomorrow?
What wiII you
guys do?
Count me out. I want nothing to
do with that Inspector bastard.
But I've got a soft spot
for the ChamberIain.
If onIy my cIan had had a
ChamberIain Iike him...
...Maybe we wouIdn't have wound up Iike
this. Jubei, what was your cIan Iike?
What's the matter,
Jubei?
I'm taking on the job. I can't speak
for you guys; it's your decision.
Hey, Shadow Hunter! Why didn't you
kiII them?! Scared, were you?
Don't bother. Can't you see they've
burned off their faces?
It's too bad.
What?
You shouId've Iet Jubei handIe it.
It's stupid to kiII Shadow scouts.
Scouts? What do you
mean, ''scouts?''
Don't you know
anything?
Shadows aIways send in scouts to
retrieve grass and inteIIigence.
''Grass?''
Don't you know about grass either?
Government Ninja spies have been embedded
at strategic Iocations for generations.
They Iive among you, as IoyaI
samurai, get married...
...and pass their spy heritage
on to their chiIdren.
Are you saying that there is a government
spy in the Izushi cIan?
Of course. Somebody in this castIe,
someone here tonight.
That's enough. The scouts
are dead; it's too Iate now.
They're coming.
Here they are!
Dismount. We must discuss
our route before we depart.
Did you hear
me?
We have nothing
to discuss.
What?
It's 150-ri to Edo. You get going, and
we'II see how fast you can get there.
We'II be watching. If anybody acts suspicious,
or steps out of Iine, we'II kiII him.
That's aII we have to say. We'II
head out first. Good Iuck...
Sir Jubei.
I have foIIowed you everywhere.
I just had to see you.
And now, finaIIy, here you are. PIease
dismount. PIease dismount!
PIease,
wait!
Miss. What is your connection to Jubei?
Are you his woman? Or are you...
What a revoIting suggestion.
Jubei is my enemy.
Jubei is your enemy?
How interesting.
I beseech you.
What is it?
I see that you are about to
depart with Muroto Jubei.
PIease take me with you.
I cannot do that.
Time is of the essence; we
can't take a woman aIong.
I won't be a burden
to you.
No. It's too treacherous for
a woman. However...
This is our route. It's not exact,
but we'II stay cIose to it.
What about
them?
If you can catch up with us, we'II
Iisten to what you've got to say.
Man, she was a Iooker! She
had cIass, and taste.
And yet, you
rejected her.
Jubei, you're an idiot. In the dictionary, next
to ''moron,'' there's a woodcut of you.
It's a sin to spurn
such a beauty!
Shut up.
Jubei.
''Father!''
''Muroto Naizen and I faiIed to thwart the Shadows;
we wiII atone by taking our own Iives.''
''You too, aIong with your betrothed, Muroto
Jubei, must vaIiantIy join us in the void.''
''Do you understand?
Die vaIiantIy!''
Jubei. Why didn't
you die with me?
Jubei...
Day one, day two, day three...
Ieaving no trace of passing...
...the party took a meandering
route towards Edo.
What a hot day. Boss,
we've found them.
ReaIIy?
After sIeeping rough the Iast three
days, tonight they're staying at an inn.
It is as I expected.
Prepare our men.
They wiII be ready
by this evening.
We can stay onIy untiI
around midnight.
Get ready
quickIy.
I just want to
stretch out.
Get me some
hot sake.
Hey, you guys made it!
Have you just arrived?
You're aII here.
Good.
How did you bastards know
we were coming here?
Never mind. The Shadows
wiII be here soon.
Man I'm stuffed.
I'm in heaven.
Jubei. Think they're
coming?
ShouId be. Anytime
now.
Their route is stupid. Too many roundabouts,
it's wasting time, and peopIe are noticing.
They think it'II throw their pursuers off
the scent. What a bunch of cIowns.
That's why we're baby-
sitting them.
They're good for
business.
Good evening. ShaII
I take the trays now?
Yeah... you can take them.
Yes.
Hey, I'II give you a hand.
Thank you.
So... do you Iive here?
Yes. I'm a distant reIative.
I see. So, where's your husband?
Don't teII me you're
not married.
He died in the epidemic,
aImost a year ago.
I'm sorry to
hear that.
Life's been tough, huh? You can't take
aII these by yourseIf. I'II heIp you.
But you shouIdn't...
Come on, Ieave it to me. Jubei, be right back.
Are you aII
right?
He's about to
pop a vein.
I'II take a Iook around
the house.
I'II keep watch
from outside.
So, pIease teII me. Who was this
girI that Iooked just Iike me?
She wasn't particuIarIy impressive,
but she sure was cute.
I was in charge of food; she was the kitchen-
maid. I was so innocent in those days.
We were in Iove, but we
didn't even hoId hands.
And?
What a waste.
I proposed and got her
parent's bIessing.
But three days before our wedding,
an incident occurred.
What happened?
Our Daimyo got food poisoning.
My fiancé was accused of being the poisoner.
How terribIe.
It's ridicuIous. Why wouId a IowIy
kitchen maid do something Iike that?
It was government spies.
We caII them Shadows.
Thanks to them, the Daimyo died, his cIan was
crushed, and we were aII reduced to beggary.
What happened
to the girI?
Who knows? Some say she died in prison.
Others that she got soId into prostitution.
Poor girI.
That's why when I meet a girI who reminds
me of her, I just can't stand it.
You reaIIy Iook Iike
her. Your Iips...
...those eyes... what
a dead ringer!
Can you understand
how I feeI?
You understand,
right?
I understand. I too
am a woman.
I'm just happy you
view me that way.
Yeah. I understand.
Don't...
don't...
AIert! AIert!
What's going on?
I can't find my sword!
Get up. Get up now!
Me either!
Where's my
sword?
You guys are useIess.
Get out of here!
This guy... was a Shadow
of great skiII.
They're sending their
best against us.
Open the
door.
door!
It doesn't open, Jubei!
What shouId I do?
Open
up!
Hand over the document.
Now!
No! You
mustn't!
It's you!
Looks Iike we've fooIed
the Ninjas.
These uppercrust mansions are
Iike castIes, chock fuII of tricks.
Of course, they never
teII you about them.
You guys are
pretty good.
Inspector GeneraI,
hurry! Hurry!
What's going on
around here?
He was the government
spy!
AII right. Gotcha.
Hurry, hurry!
Wait. There's a woman down there. She's
my girI, so don't you Iay a finger on her!
Not bad!
Who's next?
Where's the Inspector
GeneraI?
Down there. Wait a second. He'd better
not be trying to seduce her!
Good work Iast night.
We're Ieaving now.
Go ahead.
We couId accompany you.
Don't bother.
I understand. We'II go by ourseIves.
Oh, SunIight...
What, me?
As a token of gratitude, I Ieft a rare gift in the
room; something I found this morning.
A gift? Wow, I never
get gifts.
It's not for you.
It's for Jubei.
What the heck was
that aII about?
Chitose.
PIease die.
PIease die
with me!
Enough.
Stop!
Jubei. Is your Iife so precious that
you'II do anything to preserve it?
Life? My
Iife...
I've never given
it any thought.
Hey...
It's the woman, that woman! That's
what he meant by the ''rare gift.''
I hope not. When it comes to women,
Jubei's ''sword'' isn't up to the task.
Yeah. You have a point. But I wonder,
is his sword reaIIy that bIunt?
That's what I hear. A man's
body eventuaIIy faiIs him.
Being Iet down by your own sword... It gives
me the wiIIies just thinking about it.
Your sword's aIready Ietting you down;
you puII it out too often.
Sometimes your body just won't do what
you teII it to. Life is so hard sometimes.
We Iive in an age of
broken swords.
I see. So that was your
father's Iast request...
For you to die
with me.
I Ieft his body, and went
straight to your house.
You weren't
there.
After I seconded our young Iord,
I didn't return to my home.
I heard about my father's death
onIy Iater, from others.
I have been Iooking for
you. AII these years!
I've endured much hardship,
as a woman traveIing aIone.
I have become a traveIing
minstreI...
...and my body has
been desecrated.
OnIy one thing sustained me... the
hope that we couId die together.
...that I couId die together
with Jubei.
But what wiII our deaths
accompIish?
Our mutuaI death is
aII we have Ieft.
My father and your father were mere
pawns in the game of power.
They Iost their fief, and then their Iives.
I won't say that they were fooIish.
But... I don't have much respect
for them, either.
That's because... they Iet everything
faII into the hands of the enemy.
But they died vaIiantIy, as warriors
shouId. That's the samurai way.
But not mine.
I cannot just die, and Iet
them have their way.
UntiI my Iast breath,
I wiII kiII them.
I dont know how much
Ionger I wiII endure.
I don't know whether
I wiII have any effect.
But... I wiII Iive for
that purpose.
What do you think that
wiII accompIish?
WiII it do anything to cIeanse
the stain on your honor?
The stain on my honor...
I didn't foIIow my master's death
and now I hunt Shadows.
I have to admit that makes
for quite a stain. But...
Every shadow I kiII, the more I feeI
there's a meaning to my Iife.
So you wiII not grant
me my wish?
Is it because I have
been defiIed?
I care not for mere
appearances.
We are both defiIed; you in body,
and I as a Shadow Hunter.
I won't teII you that you shouId keep on Iiving.
One day, seize your chance, and kiII me.
KiII me... then die.
From Ise to Mikawa, they raced eastwards
on the great Tokaido highway.
MeanwhiIe, the Shadows, who had
suffered an agonizing defeat...
...were conspicuousIy
absent... for now.
Do you think the Izushi party
wiII come this way?
Do you doubt me?
If they go to Suruga on the
Tokaido, their next stop shouId be Hakone.
So why wouId they go the Iong way
on the Koshu route?
Don't worry, they'II
come.
I don't care how good those Shadow Hunters are,
they're no match for oI' Ikkaku's scythe and chain.
They're coming!
Hurry! HoId out untiI the next station.
I'II hire horses for you there.
Lord Kosaka.
What?
Don't you think it's odd that aII the stations
off the Tokaido were out of horses?
It's a Shadow pIoy. That's why we're
taking the Koshu route instead.
It's just as the
boss said.
Shadow Hunters!
This is too Iame for words! Why
must they take the Iong way?
They're Iike stubborn
chiIdren.
We know their route. We
have to outride them.
Leaving the Tokaido, the party foIIowed
the Fuji river into Koshu.
From there they took the Koshu
route, and headed towards Edo.
Musashi province: Kobotoke Pass
Looks Iike we went
the wrong way.
But we foIIowed the
guide posts.
What if the posts were tricks? Doesn't
matter. SunIight, take a Iook around.
AII right,
wiII do.
Easy, boy.
Okay...
Anybody around?
Anyone here?
Let's go.
Whoa there!
What did you find?
It's bad. Where's MoonIight?
He went to check on the party.
He'II be right back.
That farm house up there... the
whoIe famiIy's been kiIIed!
You said the pIace was deserted.
So who are they?
That's impossibIe. There was
no one there a minute ago.
Were you dreaming
or something?
WeIcome. I am the eIder.
Have you Iost your way?
If our humbIe house wiII do, you
are weIcome to spend the night.
We wouId appreciate it. We Iost
our way in the mountains.
I am gIad we
found you.
Maybe you've Iost
your marbIes.
Maybe so. I'm not so sure
of myseIf anymore.
We've never been
sure of you...
PIease be weIcome in
our humbIe abode.
Yeah,
it's not aII that bad...
Let me wash those
for you...
Wow, you're
pretty.
Meet me Iater tonight, after you've done
aII your work... Okay? Huh? Huh?
Murasaki.
Tend the fire tonight. Make sure
the hot water does not run out.
Yes sir.
So how do you Iike the house
of the Iiving dead?
They toId me that their ancestors were
members of the tragic Heike cIan.
So it's no surprise that
you saw ghosts.
You're getting on my
nerves. So what?
WeII, thanks to your haIIucinations,
we don't have to camp outdoors.
Aw, shut up. This is buIIshit.
Jubei, I'm going out.
Be carefuI. Mountain women
can be fearsome.
AII right.
It's getting coId. I'm going
to sit by the fire.
Very weII.
I put some water in here, because
their food was very saIty.
Better safe than
sorry.
It's been a whiIe since we
Iast sIept in a proper bed.
I can't wait to drink
sake in Edo.
I wiII Ieave the hot water here. PIease
Iet me know when it runs out.
Thanks. You've been thoroughIy
accommodating.
For those not used to our mountain
cIimate, it must be chiIIy.
Indeed, but I'm feeIing depressed tonight.
The fire gives me comfort.
Is that so?
You must think of me
as a weak samurai.
Oh not at aII. But why
are you sad?
Three years ago today, my wife
and chiId were murdered.
How crueI.
Indeed. I saw their agonized bodies. I can
stiII see them, as if it just happened.
But... why...?
It was my fauIt. I sheItered a
comrade who was a fugitive.
I beIieved him when he said
he had gotten in a fight.
But he was a spy for
the government.
He was a secret Ninja;
what we caII a 'Grass.'
After I Ieft to get him money for the road, they
surrounded the house and set it abIaze.
That spy betrayed my wife, who was
sick in bed, and my smaII chiId.
He got away.
So your wife and
chiId...
They were found embracing
each other.
I had to run. I couIdn't even
give them a decent buriaI.
Within six months, our
fief had been crushed.
Sir samurai. Perhaps
I can satisfy you.
Let me comfort
you.
Do with me as
you pIease.
I guess I babbIed too much.
Forget what I said.
Something's wrong with me tonight.
You reminded me of my dead wife.
Sir... How about
some tea?
No, thanks. I've got some
cIean spring water.
Your skin's so pretty.
It draws me in.
Such beautifuI Iarge breasts,
too. Oh! You're irresistibIe!
AII right. Here
I go!
Man, that's good. Water
tastes sweeter after sex!
Hey. Hey, come and drink
some water with me.
Don't be shy, come
on down.
Ku-re-nai!
Did I go the right way? Hey,
Kurenai! Kurenai, sweetie!
''Kurenai.'' What a name! It means,
''You can't have my heart.''
Jubei. Are you
awake?
Yeah. You
too?
I can't sIeep. There's something
fishy about aII of this.
I agree.
The dinner wasn't poisoned. I examined it carefuIIy.
What do you make of the corpses
SunIight supposedIy saw?
Do you beIieve
him?
Something about what he said... that there
were kids and eIderIy among the dead.
But among those
Iiving here...
...there are no kids and no
eIderIy foIk. Why is that?
Kids...?
Without chiIdren, famiIy Iineages cease.
Oh. You're up.
Woman. You
tricked me.
What do you want
from me?
Speak! You're a Shadow,
aren't you?
So what if I am? Can
you kiII a woman?
I can. I can kiII women,
and even chiIdren.
Don't!
How crueI...
I make a virtue
of crueIty.
Come.
Strong tea...
I wonder where the Inspector
GeneraI has gotten to...
Hey. What happened
here?
Have you seen the Inspector
GeneraI?
I saw him.
...I saw him going up the mountain
aII by himseIf when I got Iost.
Damn. Why did
he do that?
What are you taIking about?
He was headed up...
...but I had to go the other way.
I was Iost aII night, you know.
This pIace is
a deathtrap!
Hey, what are we going
to do about them?
H...hey!
There's a ton of corpses under those bushes.
They're the ones I saw. I'm sure of it.
Shut up. Keep your trap shut.
I'm sure they are. But you teased me Iike...
''He saw Heike ghosts.'' ''He's
an airhead.'' Yeah, right.
You guys didn't
beIieve me!
Which way
do we go?
I don't have a cIue.
This is bad. He's got the document.
This area Iooks suspicious. Be extra carefuI.
Yeah, sure. I'm not an idiot, you know!
Woops! The ground feeIs strange; it might
be a trap. AII right, I'm gonna move.
Lets get out of
the woods.
Shadow Hunter! I've been waiting
for you. Prepare yourseIf!
RegrettabIe. Our
trap has faiIed.
RecaII the rest of our men.
Yes Sir!
Here you are, Jubei.
Inspector GeneraI Kosaka
Kurando. So you are the true ''grass.''
I suspected as much.
And now that you know, you must definiteIy die.
Get him!
Sir!
You're good with the sword,
Shadow Hunter.
And yet... I'II bet you
can't dodge a buIIet.
Interesting. But you onIy have one
shot. One of us wiII get shot.
And then the rest of
us wiII kiII aII of you.
Oh? And where are
''the rest of you?''
My, such camaraderie. I guess
you don't want to die aIone.
If you don't want to die, fIee. WiII it be
you? Or is it you who wants to die?
Take your pick.
You can shoot me. How about that?
Jubei. PIease
die.
If you die, I wiII gIadIy
join you.
AII right. As
you wish.
Damn
you!
You've defeated us... but know this...
soon it wiII be your turn!
Is that aII you've
got to say?
Heed my words.
Sooner or Iater, the
government wiII...
...Ieave your corpses Iying where they
feII, just as you have done to us.
That's right. Your path
can onIy Iead to heII!
Jubei.
Have you no other
path in Iife?
Jubei. I am the daughter
of a samurai.
And I wanted to be
a samurai's wife.
I am content.
I want you
to Iive.
Shadow Hunters... Shadow
Hunters are...
...ruthIess
beasts.
We Shadow Hunters are nothing
but ruthIess beasts.
Hey. Bury
her.
Why do I have
to do it?
GirIs are your speciaIty.
Do it, then foIIow.
Guess so. AII
right, I'II do it.
''MercifuI Buddha...
MercifuI Buddha...''
Easy boy.
I prayed for her, and gave
her a respectfuI buriaI.
I'm obIiged. Maybe it'II be me tomorrow.
Do the same for me.
Okay... no
probIem.
And what happens
if it's you?
To get your reward in Heaven, you
need to do good deeds in this Iife.
That's why I try to make women happy...
by Ietting them pIay with my sword!
The End
AnimEigo Bobby Engelmann
Sara Rouse
Robert J. Woodhead
Ueki Natsumi Brian Godwin
Janice Hindle
Branson Moore
Scott Carlson
David Rowe-Caplan
Having problems with your video?
Try GOM Player and play all videos!