Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
[Bell Tolling]
[Clearing Throat]
What is it, Latham?
It's nearly 10:00,
Inspector. I have
a carriage waiting.
Carriage? What carriage?
You wanted to look
at that place in the park.
Don't you recall, sir?
Oh, yes.
Yes, of course.
Confounded nuisance,
spending one's time
on routine investigations.
I'd hardly call
this routine, sir.
What would
you call it?
Why, l-l...
I'd say it was
highly unusual...
a man being attacked
by a werewolf
in a London park.
Werewolf?
I'm surprised at you, Latham.
I always looked upon you
as an intelligent man.
Where on earth did you
get this "werewolf" idea?
I know, you've been
looking at the papers.
Well, they are full of it.
Bosh! From what I understand
of the case, the man
was nipped by a stray dog.
Oh, it was much worse
than that, sir. He was
very badly slashed.
He swears that
it was not an animal
that attacked him.
I suppose he was
accosted by a man...
who suddenly
sprouted hairy ears
and long fangs.
No, sir.
No ears, and no fangs.
As a matter of fact,
it wasn't a man.
It was a woman.
A little early
to be visiting
grog shops, isn't it?
Oh, sir, I never
touch a drop...
before 6:00 in the evening.
Come along.
Yes, sir.
Fine morning,
isn't it?
Much too fine...
to be wasting it
on minor things
like stray dogs.
Well, Miss Allenby,
are you prepared to
accept defeat gracefully?
You haven't defeated me
yet, Mr. Lanfield.
[Chuckles]
We are certainly formal
this morning, aren't we,
Phyllis?
[Chuckles]
Yes, we are.
Much too formal for two people
who are to be married next week.
Next December.
Next week.
This race is
merely a formality.
You sure you don't want
the handicap I offered you?
No, thank you.
All right.
Do you mind if I review
the terms of the race?
Just to refresh your memory.
As a lawyer, I don't want
any loopholes.
I'll save you
the trouble, sir.
"We race to the road
in the glen, and the winner
names our wedding day."
Which will be
next December, because
I'm going to win!
And I adore
winter weddings.
And I detest them.
That's why
I'm going to win.
You ready?
Ready.
Start counting.
One, two, three...
go!
Well, Miss Allenby,
I won fairly and squarely,
and next week you'll
become Mrs. Barry Lanfield.
You should have taken
that five-length handicap
I offered you.
I'm glad I didn't,
Barry. You see, l...
I didn't really
want to wait
till next December.
You didn't?
[Latham] Aha. You see?
They're woman's footprints,
Inspector. There's no doubt.
She came along the meadow,
and probably went through
this hedge.
You know, that fellow
might have been
telling the truth...
about a female werewolf
attacking him.
[Inspector]
Stop that nonsense about
a werewolf attacking anybody.
I'm sorry, Inspector.
Is there a way we can
get through this brush?
[Man] Here's a spot, sir.
All right, we'll have
a look on the other side.
[Latham]
Yes, well, let me help
you, sir. Thank you.
What's the
matter, Phyllis?
You look frightened.
Oh, why... those
voices startled me.
Shall we go?
Yes, now that we have an
audience, the spell is broken.
We seem to have interrupted
a romantic moment.
Mm.
You know, when I was
courtin' my missus, we used
to go horseback ridin'.
Did you?
Yeah.
Then we got married,
and she refused
to go near a horse
from that moment on.
She only pretended
to like riding until
she got me well-hooked.
When you're quite
finished mooning about
your courting days,
perhaps we can get on
with the business in hand.
I'm sorry, Inspector.
Uh, come on.
You look very thoughtful.
I have many things
on my mind.
After all, I'm to be
a bride next week.
That's not
what's troubling you.
Are you upset because of what
the constables were saying?
Frankly, I am.
It's not a very
comfortable feeling,
to know that such
weird things
are taking place...
in the park so close
to where one lives.
[Chuckles] But certainly you
don't believe those newspaper
stories about werewolves?
That's just sensational trash,
the sort of thing one reads
in penny dreadfuls...
if one reads
penny dreadfuls.
You don't read them,
do you?
Oh, of course not.
It's just that l...
I guess I'm on edge,
because...
Well, there's no man
in our house.
Your worries will be over
next week, when you move
into my diggings.
In the meantime,
I don't think you'll be
roaming the park at nights.
Not if I can help it.
[Growling]
[Loud Barking]
Oh, Hannah.
Yes, Miss Carol.
Will you do something
for me while you're
doing the marketing?
Of course, miss.
You want me
to fetch something?
No, I want you to
deliver something.
Please leave this at
the chemist on the corner
near the greengrocer.
Just say that someone
will call for it
this afternoon.
Will you do that?
Oh, ho! So it's Cupid
I'm playing this fine morning!
[Laughing]
Yes. And the note
is very important.
They always are
at your age.
[Laughs]
Don't fret. I'll see that
it's delivered quickly.
Thank you very much, Hannah.
Hannah.!
Yes, Mrs. Winthrop?
L-Is there something else
you've thought of for me
to bring from the market?
No. I'll take that note
Carol handed to you.
Note? What note?
Quickly. I saw you
put it in your basket.
But, mother,
it's only a...
I'll see what it is.
Give it to me
before I lose patience
and discharge you.
I'm sorry, Miss Carol.
Run along and
do your marketing.
Hmmph!
I thought so.
Mother, you've
no right to...
To keep you from making
a fool of yourself...
over a worthless fellow
like Dwight Severn?
Is that what
you were about to say?
I love Dwight.
And he's not worthless.
He's fine and sweet
and considerate and...
And hasn't a penny
to his name.
Come in the house, Carol.
I want to talk to you.
[Banging]
Sit down.
I'm certain you imagine
yourself madly in love with this
starving young artist of yours.
But have you given any thought
to what happens to us...
the moment Phyllis
marries Barry Lanfield?
I imagine
things will go on
pretty much the same.
Of course, we'll miss her.
It's not as simple
as that, Carol.
That's why I'm delving
into the past now,
to tell you of certain
things I probably should have
explained to you long ago.
The reason
I haven't told you is...
that your happiness
has always been
uppermost in my mind.
First, I think
you should know...
you're not Phyllis's cousin.
You're not related
to her in any way.
I don't understand.
You're her aunt, and...
No. I'm not related
to her, either.
I'm only the woman
who might have married
Reginald Allenby.
Reginald Allenby?
Phyllis's father?
Yes.
This is the note
he sent me the day before
I married your father.
Read it.
"My own darling,
I know that nothing I can
say will change your mind.
"I wish you every
happiness, even though
my heart tells me...
"I shall never quite
get over loving you,
Reggie."
Of course,
he did get over it.
Disappointed suitors
generally do.
He married Phyllis's mother
just one year after
I married your father...
a man as penniless as
the precious young man
you wish to marry.
And when your father died,
leaving me with a small child
and practically no money,
I had to fend for myself.
That's how I happened
to become the housekeeper...
of the Allenby's
London house.
[Softly]
This house.
This house
isn't ours?
No, it belongs
to the Allenby estate,
meaning Phyllis,
because she's the only heir.
[Dog Barking]
[Phyllis] Barry.!
Stop it!
Go away!
[Barking]
Barry!
Stop it. Go away.
- Barry!
- Get back!
[Growling]
Come here, Rolf.
You know, I really
can't understand it.
He's so gentle around
everyone but Phyllis.
He was anything but gentle
a moment ago.
Why don't you get rid
of them, Mrs. Winthrop?
I bought them for
protection. You know what's
been going on in the park.
Perhaps if Phyllis
tried to make
friends with them.
Talk to them, Phyllis.
Let him know you're
not afraid of him.
There might be something
in what she says, darling.
Try petting him;
see what happens.
[Breathing Deeply]
[Growling, Snarling,
Barking]
Oh, no. No.
Take him away, please!
Very well, my dear.
Come along. I'll lock
him in the garden.
I'm sorry I'm such
a coward, Barry.
I don't blame you
for being afraid,
the way he was carrying on.
[Barking Continues]
[Dogs Barking]
[Dog Howling]
[Door Opening]
Oh! Oh, Aunt Martha!
You startled me.
I'm sorry, Phyllis.
I heard you
stirring about.
I thought I'd just look in
and say good night.
What in the world
is that?
It's a lantern.
But why did you
hang it out there?
I thought it might
keep the dogs from
making such a racket.
They've been
at it all evening.
Come now, my dear.
You can tell me the truth.
What do you mean?
I'm familiar with that
old Scottish superstition...
of hanging out a lighted
lantern when dogs howl,
to drive away the evil spirits.
But you're far too intelligent
to believe in anything so silly.
Am I? I wonder.
Certainly you are.
Oh, leave it there!
But why?
Why, because I want
it there.
Isn't that
reason enough?
Just as you say, dear.
Wait! Aunt Martha,
I'm sorry.
It's just that
I'm all on edge.
Those dogs and
their constant howling
are driving me frantic.
And things that
have been happening
in the park...
You poor child.
You really are upset,
aren't you?
You mustn't let yourself
go to pieces like this.
Now, get into bed.
I'll fetch you
some warm milk
from downstairs.
You'll sleep so soundly
you won't even hear the dogs.
Into bed with you.
I'll only be a minute.
[Martha]
Carol.!
Where are you going?
Answer my question.
I was going out
for a breath of air.
It was stuffy in my room.
Why do you lie to me?
You were stealing out
of the house...
to meet Dwight Severn.
Go to your room.
At once.
Here you are, darling.
Drink it.
And let's forget
all about your nerves
being on edge.
Oh, thank you, Aunt Martha.
That's very sweet of you.
[Dogs Barking,
Howling]
Dismal sound,
ain't it, 'Erbert?
Like lost souls
looking for a place
to rest.
Nothing quite as fancy,
Alfred, if you ask me.
More like lost wolves
looking for someone
to tear to pieces.
Yes, 'orrible,
ain't it?
They do say the 'owling
of a dog means death.
In that case, half of London
must be at death's door
at this minute.
[Screaming]
That's no dog.
Sounds like a child.
Here, come on!
[Exhales]
Blood.
[Sighs]
Good morning.
Why, Phyllis,
what's the matter?
It's happened.
I knew it would happen.
What are you
talking about?
Look.
Your slippers
are covered with mud!
Yes.
And the hem of my robe...
it's wet. As though I'd been
walking in wet grass.
But you couldn't
have been out!
Blood on my hands.
Oh, Aunt Martha,
what have I done?
Where did I go last night?
Stop it, Phyllis.
You couldn't have been out.
It's impossible!
But my hands...
the robe...
the slippers...
and I had
the most horrible dream.
I was walking on
a desolate moor at night.
I was stalking someone.
To kill him.
Oh, it's the Allenby curse.
I'm sure of it!
Nonsense.
There's no such thing.
If there isn't,
I must be subject
to spells of insanity.
I know you're upset,
Phyllis, but
you're not insane.
Now, get dressed.
Come down to breakfast.
Act as if nothing
has happened.
We don't want Carol
to suspect that
anything's wrong.
Understand?
You don't look well
this morning, Miss Phyllis.
Is somethin' ailin' you?
Phyllis is
perfectly well,
Hannah.
Now run along
and fetch
Carol's breakfast.
She'll be down
in a minute.
Just as you say, mum.
Do you think
Hannah suspects?
Of course not.
But she stared at me
so strangely.
Be quiet.
Good morning,
Mother. Phyllis.
Good morning, dear.
Good morning,
Miss Carol.
Hannah.
Oh, how dreadful!
What is it,
Carol?
A small boy was killed
last night in the park
near Denham Lane.
Torn to pieces by
an animal of some kind.
[Hannah]
Denham Lane.!
Why, that's close by here.
[Carol]
Yes, just a short way.
Less than a mile I'd say.
[Hannah]
Not more than half a mile,
if you ask me.
Hannah, get some more tea.
What are you waiting for?
Get it!
Yes, ma'am.
It seems that
the body of the child
was horribly mangled.
[Gasps]
Carol, please!
[Sobs]
Help me
get her upstairs.
[Sobbing Continues]
[Exhales]
Hello, Barry.
Good morning, Carol.
Is Phyllis ready?
I promised I'd drive her
to the dressmaker's
this morning.
I'm afraid she can't
go with you, Barry.
Why not?
She's ill.
Not too ill
to receive a visitor,
I hope.
I don't know.
I'll go to her room
and ask her. Come in.
I just can't live
with myself knowing that
I murdered that child.
You murdered no one.
Now, you must stop
talking about it.
Or even thinking about it.
The idea that a frail girl
like you could literally...
tear a boy of ten to pieces
is utterly ridiculous.
I wish I could
believe that.
[Knocking]
[Liquid Pouring]
- Is that you, Carol?
- Yes, Mother.
What is it?
Barry's here.
I explained that you were ill
and he wants to see you.
Shall I have him come up?
Oh, no. No, don't
let him come up.
Tell him I can't see him.
I never want to see him again.
You can't possibly
mean that, Phyllis.
Of course she doesn't mean it.
Explain she's sleeping and asked
not to be disturbed. Tell him
she'll see him tomorrow.
Oh, but I won't be able
to see him tomorrow.
I'm positive you will,
my dear. Drink this.
It will calm
your nerves.
Please, Phyllis.
You're keeping Barry
waiting, Carol.
I'm never going
to see Barry again,
Aunt Martha.
I just couldn't.
[Sighing]
I'd feel...
I'd feel unclean.
Psst! Hannah.
Oh! What're you doin'
here, Mr. Barry?
Not so loud. Go on with
your work. I want to
ask you some questions.
How's Phyllis
this morning?
She seems
much better, sir.
[Whispering]
She's in the garden now.
Gettin' some sun.
That's strange.
Mrs. Winthrop
told me she was
too ill to see me.
She's been
telling me that
for two days now.
Mrs. Winthrop is peculiar,
if you ask me.
Only don't tell her
I said so.
I won't, if you'll
let me go through
here to the garden.
Go ahead!
What's holdin' ya?
[Whispering]
And if ya get caught, I'll
swear I never set eyes on ya.
And I'll
confirm it.
[Sighs]
Hello, darling.
Barry!
How did you get here?
I'll tell you
about that later.
First, I want
to talk to you.
Why have you been
avoiding me, Phyllis?
I've been trying to see you
for the past two days.
Is that any way to treat
the man you're going to
marry next Wednesday?
Barry, please.
I can't talk about it now.
[Sighs]
Phyllis,
what's the matter?
It's Barry.
Will you please
ask him to go?
Barry, I didn't know
you were here.
Where did Phyllis go?
I've got to talk to her.
You'd better not.
You've upset her
enough already.
How could I have upset
her? I merely walked
into the garden...
and asked her why
she's been avoiding me.
Perhaps she's been avoiding you
because she didn't want you
to see her while she was ill.
She's a sensitive girl.
Don't force the issue when
she's feeling as she does now.
What's wrong with her,
Mrs. Winthrop?
What's come over her?
You'd think a girl
about to be married
would be in great spirits.
It's just a case of nerves.
I'm sure it's nothing serious.
In a couple of days,
when she's feeling better,
she'll be a different person.
In the meantime,
I'll take good care of her.
You'd better go now.
Hello, Barry.
Good afternoon,
Carol.
I know, you've been calling
on the bride-to-be.
How is she?
I wish I knew.
Carol, will you come
for a drive with me?
I'd like to talk to you.
All right.
[Carriage Rattling]
[Dog Barking]
[Dogs Barking]
Good evening.
Are you the lady
of the house?
I'm a lady.
But I only work here.
Who are you?
My name is Latham,
Criminal Investigation
Department, Scotland Yard.
Oh. Come in.
Thank you.
I'll call Mrs. Winthrop
right away.
Well, don't bother.
You can give me
the information I want.
Uh, how many people
live in this house?
Four. Mrs. Winthrop,
her daughter, her niece
and meself.
No men?
Not a man.
Mm.
Are there any dogs
about the place?
Yes, indeed!
And vicious beasts
they are.
Every night
they keep me awake with
their barkin' and howlin'.
You'd be doin' me
a great favor
if you'd take them away.
That's what
you'd be doin'.
Mm.
It's a gentleman
from Scotland Yard,
askin' about the dogs.
Latham is
the name, ma'am.
How do you do?
I'm Mrs. Winthrop.
That will be all,
Hannah.
I presume all dogs
are under suspicion,
in view of the
strange happenings
in the park.
If you wish me to
get rid of them, l...
Oh, I had nothing...
like that in mind,
Mrs. Winthrop.
I imagine that you keep
them for protection.
I can't say that
I blame you, with no men
about the place.
I don't suppose you allow
the dogs to roam at large?
Certainly not.
They're locked in the garden
most of the time.
Especially at night.
Mm.
Have you noticed
any suspicious characters
about the place?
No, I haven't.
Uh, tell me,
have the police any clue
as to who murdered
that boy in the park?
Well, not exactly a clue,
as you might say.
Of course,
we've narrowed it down
to where we feel certain...
that it's an animal
from this neighborhood.
Or a person.
A person?
Mm.
My own theory, Mrs. Winthrop,
is that it's a were...
[Clears Throat]
That a madman or a woman
is responsible.
And that's why I'm
checking all the houses
in this neighborhood.
So, if you do see
any suspicious characters,
notify the police
at once, won't you?
I certainly will.
Yes.
Well, thank you very much,
ma'am. Good night.
Good night.
[Door Closes]
[Dogs Barking]
[Dog Howling]
[Barking, Howling
Continue]
Oh, it can't be!
[Knocking]
Come in!
Do you mind?
Of course not.
I'm glad you're still up.
I want to talk to you.
What are you doing
with the cotton?
Oh, l...
I'm stuffing my ears,
so I won't hear
those awful dogs.
Before you
shut yourself off
from the world entirely,
do you mind if I ask you
a couple of questions?
Not at all.
Did you ever notice...
what nice, broad
shoulders I have?
- What do you mean?
- We've been confiding
in each other for years.
- Isn't there something
you'd like to tell me?
- No. Why do you ask?
I went riding with Barry
this afternoon, and we talked
about you most of the time.
We both feel that the thing
that's upsetting you is more
sinister than howling dogs.
If you'd tell me what it is,
perhaps I can help.
Thanks. But there's
nothing you can do.
There's nothing
anybody can do.
All right. But sometimes
it's bad to keep things
to one's self.
I'm keeping nothing from you,
Carol, i-it's just that
I'd like to be left alone.
Forget that I mentioned it.
I won't bring it up again.
I'm sorry, Carol.
I didn't mean to be nasty.
Please forgive me.
There's nothing
to forgive.
But if you ever do want
to unload your troubles,
remember what
I said about these
broad shoulders of mine.
And Barry has a nice
set of shoulders, too.
What did Carol want?
She just dropped in
to say good night.
I thought perhaps
she brought you
a message from Barry.
She went riding
with him this afternoon.
Yes. I know.
I brought the coffee
you asked for,
but I think you're
making a mistake drinking
at this time of night.
You won't sleep a wink.
That's exactly
why I'm having it.
I don't intend to sleep.
I'm going to fight this thing.
I'm going to make sure
I don't leave the house tonight.
Aren't you being
a little foolish?
Rest will do you more
good than anything else.
It's no use, Aunt Martha.
My mind's made up.
As you wish.
[Door Opens,
Closes]
[Locking]
[Dogs Barking]
[Strikes Match]
[Dogs Barking Louder]
Go on, lad.
Good evening, Constable.
Good evening, sir!
Yes, well, now, these
are your reinforcements.
Inspector Pierce wants the park
patrolled by officers travelling
in pairs, until further notice.
Very good, sir.
You men pair off with
the regular patrolmen.
They'll show you
the ropes.
Very good. All right.
I say, Constable.
What's your theory about
these strange goings-on?
Well, there are quite
a few stray dogs roaming
the parks these nights.
I'm sure that one of
the bolder ones has been
attacking the people.
Mm. Well, that's
the Inspector's theory too.
Has it ever occurred to you
that it might be a werewolf?
You're pulling
my leg, aren't you?
There are
no such things.
Mm.
Well, the Inspector
thinks that, too.
Well, good night.
Good night, sir.
[Dogs Barking]
Oh! Well, Constable,
anything new?
No, sir.
Everything is
comparatively quiet.
With the exception
of a few dogs howling.
At the rate we're rounding
'em up, there'll be no dogs
to howl tomorrow night.
I suppose that you're still
of the opinion that when...
the park is
cleared of the dogs,
the attacks will stop.
Oh, certainly, sir.
Aren't you?
I'm not so sure.
Well, um, see you later.
Well, there's a barmy one.
He has an idea
there's a werewolf
at the bottom of all this.
Barmy's what
I calls it, too.
Yes.
[Grunting,
Snarling]
[Snarling Continues]
[Latham Shouting]
Don't.!
[Latham Screaming]
Help.!
Help! Con...
Constable!
Help!
Const...
Constable!
What happened, sir?
She's done me in.
She, sir?
The wolf-woman!
[Choking]
We'd better get him
to a hospital.
I'm afraid it's
a bit late for that.
He's a goner.
Aunt Martha.
How did you
get in here?
Through the door,
of course.
But I had it locked.
It wasn't locked,
Phyllis.
[Shudders]
Oh, it's happened
again.
What have I done?
I don't know.
Your new white dress
is torn and muddy.
And your shoes...
[Knocking]
Compose yourself.
[Knocking Continues]
Is that you,
Carol?
Yes, Mother.
May I come in?
Certainly, dear.
Good morning,
Phyllis.
Good morning, Carol.
Barry's downstairs.
He suggested we
go riding with him.
Would you tell him
I'm not up to it
this morning?
Of course.
But won't you see him
for a few moments?
He's terribly worried
about you.
No, I can't see him.
She had a very restless night.
She's in no condition
to have visitors.
That's not going to be
much consolation for Barry.
Any message you'd like me
to give him?
No. No message.
By the way,
have you heard the news?
What news?
A Scotland Yard man was murdered
in the park last night...
by a madwoman
who made a noise
like an animal.
The morning paper
is full of it.
[Door Opens, Closes]
I murdered him!
Hush, child.
You did nothing of the kind.
I know I did.
I'm going to a doctor.
I can't stand this.
You'll do nothing of the sort.
I won't permit it.
If you told your story
to a doctor,
he's have you committed
to an asylum.
You don't want that,
do you?
No.
[Sighs]
Look.
That must be the place
where the man was murdered
last night.
I suppose so.
If I could only talk to Phyllis,
I'm sure that I could get her
to tell me what's wrong.
Then why don't you?
How can I?
Your mother insists
she's too ill to see me.
Haven't you ever
overruled a woman?
Good morning, Barry.
Good morning,
Mrs. Winthrop.
Won't you come in?
Carol's in the garden
if you'd like to see her.
I didn't come to see Carol.
I'm going to take Phyllis
for a drive in the country.
You must be joking.
She's much too ill
to leave the house.
Suppose we let her
be the judge of that,
Mrs. Winthrop.
See here.
You can't go upstairs.
Why not? Phyllis is
going to be my wife.
I insist on seeing her.
I'm sure she'll
refuse to go with you.
Cheer up, sobersides.
After all, this is better than
moping in bed at home.
Isn't it?
Yes, I suppose it is.
Whoa.
You don't know
what a relief it is
to see you perking up.
It's good for ya
to get away from that house.
I wonder why your Aunt Martha
was so insistent
I couldn't see you.
Aunt Martha was acting
for my own good,
to protect me.
To protect you?
From what?
Look, darling,
I know something's been
bothering you, and...
I want you to tell me
what it is.
It isn't anything so serious
we can't overcome it together.
After all, we are
going to be married.
We can't be
married, Barry. Ever.
Why not?
L-I can't
tell you that.
It's... It's just that
it wouldn't be fair to you.
I think I understand.
You're not going to let me in
for the curse of the Allenbys
and all that sort of thing.
Is that it?
How did you know?
Carol mentioned
your being so frightened
of howling dogs of late,
and I merely
added up the facts.
Please, let's not
talk about it anymore.
We've got to talk about it.
You can't let yourself
go to pieces
over a thing like that.
I'm sure you place no stock
in that silly legend...
about your family
being cursed by the wolves.
I'm not sure.
I know you scoff
at the Allenby curse,
but ever since
my parents were killed,
I've had
the strangest dreams,
dreams in which it seemed
I lived a long time ago.
I took part
in pagan rites.
I assumed
the form of a wolf.
I even hunted
with the wolves.
Those dreams
are easily explained.
Someone probably
told you weird stories
about the Allenby curse...
when you were a child.
Certainly, you don't believe
in werewolves, do you?
Many people do.
There was an ancient tribe,
the Hirpini,
which worshipped wolves.
But that was
centuries ago.
Yes.
But even today
in Scotland, on the nights
when the dogs howl,
people hang out
lighted lanterns
to ward off evil spirits.
You've been reading up
on the subject,
haven't you?
Yes, I have.
Plato and Pythagoras
on the transmigration
of souls,
I suppose.
Yes.
Don't tell me you've
overlooked Shakespeare.
Let's see, now.
Merchant of Venice,
wasn't it?
"Thou almost makes me
waver in my faith,
"to hold opinion
with Pythagoras,
"that souls of animals
infuse themselves
into the trunks of men.
"Thy currish spirit
governed by a wolf...
"who hanged
for human slaughter.
"Even from the gallows
did his fell soul fleet,
"and whilst thou layest
in thy unhallowed dam...
"infused itself in thee,.
For thy desires
are wolfish, bloody,
starved and ravenous. "
[Sobbing]
Barry!
Stop it!
Oh, darling.
I'm sorry. L...
I didn't realize
it would hit you like this.
[Sobbing]
I'm so
terribly frightened.
Hold me tight,
awfully tight!
I'm taking
personal charge tonight.
These are my orders:
You are to arrest
any person, man or woman,
who cannot give
a satisfactory reason
for being in the park.
Furthermore, if anyone
tries to avoid questioning
by running away,
you are to shoot
after a single command
to halt.
You've been provided
with firearms
for this emergency.
We'll start patrolling
at once.
All right, men.
To your posts.
I think I'll take a turn
in the park myself,
Constable.
Very good, sir.
All right.
Good evening.
Hold on, sir.
What are you doing
in the park at this hour?
Frankly,
I'm doing a little
private investigating.
Planning to capture
the she-wolf single-handed,
I presume.
Something like that.
These weird stories
in the newspapers fascinate me.
I'll have to trouble you
for your name.
My name is
Barry Lanfield.
Your occupation?
I'm a barrister
in partnership
with my father.
Not Sir Sidney Lanfield?
Yes.
Any credentials
to prove it?
Certainly.
[Man Shouting]
[Snarling, Growling]
[Man]
Help.! Help.!
Stop.! Help.!
Well,
what's happened, sir?
L... I was sitting
on that bench,
and this woman...
or whatever it was...
howled and...
and grabbed me
by the throat.
There!
There she is now.
After her, men.
After her.!
Did you get a look
at her face?
No,
l-I was much too busy
protecting myself.
She seemed
terribly strong
for a woman.
Dwight,
what happened?
I was waiting for you
to show up,
when this wolf-woman...
evidently decided
to make me
her next victim.
You poor darling.
Are you badly hurt?
Pretty badly mussed up,
but nothing serious.
Barry!
Hello, Carol.
What are you
doing here?
I might ask you
the same question.
Dwight just
answered that.
I came here
to meet him.
Dwight, this is
Barry Lanfield.
Barry, Dwight Severn.
How do you do?
Hello.
Just to make things cozy,
I'm Constable Ernie 'Obbs.
Now that we all know
each other,
suppose we go to park patrol
headquarters and get acquainted
with the inspector.
He might 'ave
a few questions
to ask too.
Come on, now.
[Knocking]
Good evening, Barry.
Good evening.
Come in.
I'll run upstairs and see
if Phyllis is able to see you.
Later.
First I'd like to
ask you some questions.
My, you sound serious.
I am. Shall we go
into the library?
Certainly.
You may cross-examine me,
Barrister,
but do you mind
if I sit down
while you're doing it?
I think much better
when I'm sitting down.
What I'm going to ask you
will require a bit of thinking...
quick thinking.
Did you know that I saw you
leave the house last night
and followed you to the park?
So that's how you happened to
be there when I met Dwight.
Yes.
And that's also how
I happened to discover
that you were the she-wolf.
- Barry, you must be joking.
- No, I'm quite serious.
You can't possibly
be serious, Barry.
But I am.
Of course, you may not recall
everything you did.
Insane people seldom do
when under stress.
I'm perfectly sane,
and I was under no stress.
I went to the park
for only one reason:
To meet Dwight Severn.
I've been meeting him
three nights a week
for the past two months.
You're certain you went
directly to the meeting place?
I am certain.
Do you mind
if I ask a question?
Go ahead.
How did you happen
to see me when I left
the house last night?
I was worried
about Phyllis.
I decided to watch
the house all night.
Something she said
when we were riding yesterday
made me think that...
You suspect that
she might be the she-wolf,
don't you?
I did...
until I saw you
steal out of the house.
Now I don't know
what to think.
Good evening, Barry.
Good evening,
Mrs. Winthrop.
Why didn't you let me know Barry
was calling, Carol? I would've
made you a cup of chocolate.
I'll make it now.
Please don't bother,
Mrs. Winthrop.
I just dropped by
hoping I might see Phyllis.
I'm afraid
you can't, Barry.
She's been terribly upset
since you took her riding
yesterday afternoon.
I don't know
why it is,
but you seem to be
a disturbing influence.
Perhaps she'll feel better
in the morning.
I'll drop around again then.
Good night.
[Door Closes]
You little fool!
I heard you say you've been
meeting Dwight Severn...
three times a week.
All right, Mother.
You know now.
I've been seeing Dwight,
and I'm going to continue
to see him.
And please don't lecture me
again on why I should
marry Barry Lanfield.
In fact, I'll be
very happy when he
and Phyllis are married.
It will stop you from
making him a constant
topic of conversation.
Barry will never
marry Phyllis.
She's insane.
[Dogs Barking]
[Barking Continues]
Phyllis.
May I come in, Carol?
I must talk to you.
Surely.
Do come in.
Well, I see
you've decided to make
a bold front of it...
instead of
sneaking out to meet
your starving artist.
I'm not going
to meet Dwight,
Mother.
I'm going to get
the police.
The police?
But why?
Phyllis has just told me
the whole story.
What are you talking about?
Her belief that she's
a werewolf. She showed me
all the evidence too.
At least you know now
that I was speaking the truth
when I said she's insane.
I don't believe
she is insane.
I think she's the victim
of a terrible hoax.
That's why I'm going to
ask the police
to investigate.
That's ridiculous.
If you call in the police,
Phyllis will be placed
in an asylum.
I'm calling them
at her request,
Mother.
[Door Opens]
I brought you
a glass of warm milk.
I don't believe
I'll have any,
Aunt Martha.
You must drink it.
It'll quiet your nerves.
You'll want to be
completely at ease when you
tell your story to the police.
You know about Carol
calling the police?
Certainly, my dear, and I'm glad
you've decided to bring
everything out into the open,
to clear up
this terrible thing,
whatever it is.
It's been quite a strain
on me too.
Drink it, Phyllis.
The police will ask you
hundreds of questions.
Do you think they'll
take me away tonight?
Probably not.
Perhaps you won't even
have to go to an asylum.
Maybe we can arrange
to have you taken care of...
in a private institution
until you're cured.
Take some more milk,
Phyllis.
Drink it all.
Do you think
I can be cured?
Of course.
Doctors accomplish wonders
with the human mind.
Finish it, dear.
I'll take the glass.
How do you feel?
Answer me.
I feel terribly sleepy,
as if I'd been drugged.
You're right.
I drugged you.
So I wouldn't hear
the dogs?
No, Phyllis.
I'm going to kill you.
Kill me?
Yes.
You see, if the police came
while you were still alive,
they would investigate
the strange story
you would tell them.
They would
call in a doctor,
and he would find
that you are perfectly sane.
So I'm going to kill you.
But why?
Because I planned all this
to get you out of the way.
When I discovered
you still believed in
the curse of the Allenbys,
I decided to
drive you insane.
It would mean
much to me...
and to Carol.
For me, it would mean
that I could stay on here
in this house I love...
that I managed
for so many years.
For Carol, it would mean
that she could marry a man
not beneath her station,
a man like
Barry Lanfield, who...
So I began by killing
the little boy in the park,
led you to believe
you did it.
Oh, no.
Later, I killed that...
meddling fool from
Scotland Yard...
because he was getting
too close to the truth.
And my plan will still
succeed, Phyllis,
although
it's changed slightly.
When the police come,
I shall tell them
of your strange actions lately.
Barry and Carol
will bear me out.
They will call it...
suicide, my dear,
through fear
of insanity.
[Shuddering,
Sobbing]
[Door Opens]
Hannah!
I heard you.
Now I know what
you've been doing...
with that drug
you kept hid
in my kitchen cupboard.
Be quiet.
No!
I'm going
for the police.
What's happened here?
Mother!
She's a murderer.
It's the she-wolf
herself.
Phyllis.
Phyllis,
are you all right?
It's Barry, darling.
She's going to kill me.
She killed the others.
No, dear.
She'll never kill
anyone else.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4kwxe
Help other users to choose the best subtitles