Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Sheriff Boone.
They said you were the one to call.
What are they? Cultists?
Satanists?
Amateurs.
Sheriff, I need your light.
What are you doing?
No wonder this didn't work.
What didn't work?
Well, they summoned something,
but they couldn't hold it.
Light, Sheriff.
Light!
Well, that's not good.
Who are you?
It's all right.
Come here.
Oh.
Well, you are something special.
Those idiots didn't know
what to do with you, did they?
That's all right.
It's okay.
I know all about you.
I know where you're from.
I know what you need.
May I show you something?
Don't be scared.
Here.
A pretty crown for a pretty princess.
Hmm?
I want to help you
because you are perfect.
There.
Now we can be friends.
Tell me what you want.
- You know what I want.
- Say it.
Look at me.
Look at me, slut.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- It's fine. Whatever.
- Oh, no. God.
- I'm sorry, no.
- No, no, no. Hey.
Hey, it's cool, it's fine.
- No...
- "Slut" is cool. Slut, I can do slut...
- Slut.
- Okay, ready?
I don't know. Okay.
Take two.
Okay.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Just... It's like...
Like, this is why
we can't role play, you know?
'Cause, like, am I supposed to be me
- or am I supposed to be...
- Yeah, you're you.
And you're like a slut, right?
No, right?
Sorry, I don't know.
God, can't we just be Jonah and Eva?
- Eva's who I want.
- I know.
I just wanted to make sure
you remember that this weekend.
I will. Of course I will.
You know I want you to have fun,
I do, and strippers are one thing...
Who said anything about strippers?
I did and I say they're fine.
Get some ones, some fives, put a few
girls through college, everybody wins.
Just stay away from the seedy dives, yeah.
The seedy dives?
You know, the ones where the girls
don't really want to be there.
Oh, God. Eva, no,
I'm not into that kind of stuff.
- You know me.
- I do.
I also know your brother.
Heads up, pussies!
We gotta lay down
some ground rules, all right?
Rule number one, no texting
or calling girlfriends slash fiancées
once we make landfall, all right?
This is dude time.
We don't want anything
getting back to the bride-to-be.
All right? I've seen that shit
happen and it's brutal.
Yo, ear buds out.
- Oh, what's up?
- Come on, man.
All right, matter of fact,
everyone give me their cell phones.
All right?
- Hey, watch the road.
- I got it, I got it, relax.
- Please don't kill me.
- Relax, all right?
I don't want you guys sending out
any damn tweets,
get my main man in trouble over here
while he's trying to get his freak on.
All right, rule number two.
We say "yes".
We don't say "maybe", we don't say,
"Gee, I don't know. I've never..."
And we damn sure don't say "no".
We say "yes" to living
and "yes" to living it up!
Do you feel me?
- Yes!
"Gee, I don't know, I've never..."
- That's it.
- Whatever happened to Vegas?
Vegas is shit, man. It's hot as balls
and it smells like hot balls.
Trust me. Garden City is where we want to be.
See that? That's the spot.
The hottest place on the East Coast, baby!
Let's light this up!
Woo-hoo!
This place sucks.
Uh, no, it's... It's okay.
She's wearing flip-flops.
I almost forgot.
- I got some groomsmen's gifts for you guys.
- What?
- Thanks for coming.
- Such a Boy Scout.
Love you.
Classic Jonah. Always prepared.
- Oh, cool, you hate 'em.
- No, we don't.
- Yeah, you do.
- No.
No, you never know when you need
to open a tiny bottle of beer.
Stop. You know what?
We love them. Thank you, Jonah.
Don't we?
I love it, Jonah.
Let's drink till they're hot.
I know, man. It should've been you.
What? No.
Hey, look,
I wouldn't want the responsibility.
No, I want you to have it, man.
You are my best man.
You are.
See, like, this is the difference, like,
when I tell you that I had
to pick Mac over you, you get it,
but if I were to tell him, like,
"I'm picking you over my brother,"
he'd just never let it go.
Look, it's fine. Who cares?
How are you feeling?
You ready for next week?
Oh, yeah. I feel great.
I mean, I'm not nervous,
but then that kind of makes me nervous,
you know what I mean? Does that make sense?
It's gonna be fine, buddy.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Hey, big boy.
- Hi.
- How about a dance?
- Oh. You know what? He would love one.
I got it.
- Okay.
- Enjoy, my man.
Thank you. Oh, here?
Yeah, it's just kind of like
I'm not really feeling anything right now,
but I feel like I should be
feeling something, you know?
I guess so. Yeah.
Like, what if I'm actually really nervous,
but I put, like, all my emotions on mute
or something just so I can get through it,
and I wake up in like a year or a month
or something and I realize
that I'm trapped
and I just totally freak out?
No way, man. Eva is awesome.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna be great.
- You two are perfect for each other.
- She's the best.
- It's... Yeah, it's disgusting.
Yeah, I love her.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's alcohol abuse, dude. Don't spill it.
Yo, brother, it's declined.
All right.
Use that one.
I'll take another one.
Bullshit, isn't it?
- Excuse me?
- The club.
I can read it on your face.
Yeah? Well, stop reading my face.
Sorry. It's just...
You hear all these stories about Garden City,
it's supposed to be
the greatest underground party scene.
Well, there's nothing here
I couldn't see in Tampa.
My baby brother's getting married next week
and I'm the best man, and I have to deliver.
I hear ya.
Look, I know a place.
I'm talking... A place.
This thing is dripping with pussy,
the music's amazing.
The vibe.
Makes this place
look like fucking Sunday school.
I can probably get you in.
But only if you and your boys are serious.
Or you can stay here, drink
that bottle, go home and pass out,
and in your drunken dreams,
maybe come close to the things I've seen.
A toast to Jonah.
All right? Man of the hour,
and lamb for the slaughter.
He's younger than me, he's less
handsome, much thinner penis...
That's not true.
- Don't interrupt.
- It's not.
But in spite of all that,
you're moving on up, man.
And you're marrying up. God, she's got money.
You're surpassing me, bro.
You're making an honest woman
out of Eva, and a man out of yourself.
Cheers.
Mmm.
Thank you, bro.
Yes, sir.
And that concludes opening ceremonies.
What?
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
- Oh, no, no, no.
- No.
Here you go. That's for you.
- Shrooms.
- Yup.
Like an old friend.
- Here you go.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yup.
- Wow.
Mmm.
See this Wyatt Earp son of a bitch
over here at the end of the bar?
Says he can show us to the real Garden City.
That guy?
There's this club, man.
It's very underground.
He's going there now
and he says we can follow him.
Uh, no.
We don't say "no".
Rule number two, no "no's".
Rule number four...
Always trust a dude with a dick duster
on his face like that, man.
It's a con.
- You think so?
- Yes.
Then we vote.
Look, if you guys came here
with a matching set of sack, all right,
and you came here to do
what you came here to do,
then you seize your destiny
and you show your support,
and you gobble that mushroom down
like a Mario Brother.
I already did mine.
- Rand's in. Yeah!
- I didn't say that. No.
Actually, I'm kind of tired.
What? You can be tired
when you're married and Eva's fat.
How about it, Duncan?
- I'm the designated driver.
- Hey, we'll cab it. Don't worry about it.
I'm not leaving my car here
in this shady-ass strip mall.
As long as we get there
in 30 minutes or so, we're fine.
All right.
I'm in.
- Oh, yes.
- Oh, nice.
Attaboy.
I think I took two.
Jonah! Jonah!
- Jonah! Jonah! Jonah!
- I've never shroomed!
- Really?
- Jonah!
Woo! Attaboy!
How far away is this place?
He said it's hard to tell sometimes.
"It's hard to tell"?
Why?
It moves.
The hell does that mean?
How are you holding up?
You got 10 minutes or so, man.
- See any colors yet?
- I see red...
Taillights. And that's it.
There's nothing else out here, man.
- Hey, man, this is a bad idea, man.
- Yeah, Mac.
Seriously, we should probably
just turn around.
Come on. Jonah is the man of the night.
I think we should listen to Jonah.
Jonah says, "Go." So let's go.
- He just said, "Turn around."
- Jonah said, "Go." I'm speaking for Jonah.
Jonah says, "Go." Let's go.
We don't even know where this place is.
- Really, man.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. He's turning.
- Follow him, follow him.
- Okay, okay.
Right there, right there, right there.
He's gonna kill us all out here
and it's gonna be your fault.
Just relax.
This guy has us on a dirt road, man.
Where the hell are we? I love it.
Well, we're out in the woods.
That's for certain.
Only good things happen in the woods.
Everybody knows that.
Arbor Day.
Arbor Day happens in the woods.
What is this guy doing?
Okay, now he just turned off.
He just turned off, man. Don't lose him.
- Shit.
- Oh, shit.
All right, dude.
Welcome to 50 North, 40 West.
Are you guys coming?
After you.
Brought you some new friends.
Boys, step inside.
Hey.
You all right, man?
I'm messed up, man.
This place is messed up.
Yeah, it is.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have some first-timers
with us here tonight!
They're here for a very special occasion
and that calls
for some very special treatment.
Ladies and gentlemen, put your paws together.
Happy stag party!
Jonah!
Did you set this up?
Don't look at me, man.
No.
Look at me.
Gentlemen, welcome.
Thank you so much for coming.
I'm the proprietor and you can call me Nyx.
Coming up next, the lovely Miss Torin.
You boys
are with me.
So, Jonah, we have worlds
of experiences here.
What is your particular flavor of poison?
Um...
- Who's the best man?
- Here.
What's he want?
- Something wild.
- Mmm-hmm.
- And private.
- All right.
Yeah, but... But no sex.
No sex as in the act
or no sex as in no gender?
Uh...
The act.
He's getting married next week.
Got it.
I have just the thing.
Gentlemen, come right on in.
Make yourselves comfortable.
Well, money is no object.
Well, of course it is.
That's all it is.
And what are objects,
ultimately, but worthless?
But, what in this world has worth?
Experience!
And experiences are what I deal in.
So, you're saying there's no charge.
Now, did I say that?
All right.
You ready to do this?
- Sure.
- All right!
Oh, no, no, no.
This is just for Jonah.
This is a private show.
The more men in the room,
the more diluted the experience.
Well, I don't know.
- What?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- Are you married yet?
- Mmm-mmm.
- Are you married?
- No.
Not yet, technically.
So do it for us.
Do it for me.
Yeah, what do you say?
They buy the ticket, you take the ride.
Hmm? Hmm?
Hold this for me.
Yeah.
Hey.
Keep your pants on?
Yeah.
You ready for a peek behind door number one?
And away we go.
Have fun.
Shit!
Can you see me?
Now we talk payment.
I want the fondest memory of your mother
from each of you.
All of you.
Now, you give me that,
and Jonah will have a night
he will never forget.
I'm sorry.
You want us to tell you about the best time
that we had with our mothers?
No. I want the memory of it.
Now, it won't take but a moment,
and the most beautiful part about it is,
is you won't even miss it.
You can't miss a memory
you can't even remember, now can you?
That's right.
Do we have a deal?
Deal.
Yeah, okay.
Sure.
All right, gentlemen, I'm gonna
need you all to look at your shoes.
Our what?
Look at your shoes.
What am I looking for?
Go on.
Look at your shoes.
Look down.
Look down
and think of mother.
And we're done.
- That's it?
- That's it!
Paid in full. Go on!
Go have a great evening!
Come on, get out of here! Scat.
Can I get a receipt or something?
Get the fuck out!
Okay.
I'm sorry. Am I supposed
to do something or...
My parents are asleep.
Eva.
Hit me. We are paid in full.
Okay? I want one of them
worm drinks right there.
It's a leech.
Leech drink.
You're not scaring me, okay?
If I don't like it, my funeral.
What do you call this?
Murder.
Hmm?
Cheers.
Nicely done, Duncan.
Whoa!
Hey, dude, you tatted up?
What?
No, I'm not tatted up.
No, right here.
Haven't seen that before.
Hey, hey, hey, wait, wait, wait.
You got one too.
Did you do this?
What's the matter? You don't remember?
Don't go.
Hello?
Did you say something?
Oh, shit.
Hi. Hi. Can you hear me?
Hey.
Are you... Are you okay in there?
Like, do...
Do they have you locked up? Can you get out?
I'm a little high.
This might be a stupid question.
Are you okay in there?
Where are you?
Shit.
Whoa!
Dude...
Shit.
I'm sorry.
- It's, it's cool.
- Yeah. It's fine.
Happens to the best of us, man.
- I didn't mean it.
- It's fine.
- Let's go.
- I didn't mean to.
Let's get, uh...
Let's get this cleaned up, dude.
Who was she?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Jesus.
Come on, man. Really?
Here, grab him and put him over here, man.
All right.
Shit.
Come on. Come on, let's get out, man.
- We have overstayed our welcome.
- I need you to come with me.
- What?
- Come with me.
What happened back there, man?
- Is he all right?
- Oh, he... He puked.
All right, take him to the car,
get it started, be ready to go.
- What?
- Just trust me.
What's going on?
I'm about to do something really stupid.
Are you sure you know where we're going?
Yeah, I counted the doors.
- Jonah. Jonah. What the hell is this place?
- Shh...
I wasn't even gonna come in, you know.
- Thought I'd go easy tonight.
- Shit.
When I bumped into those guys,
it was like it was meant to be, you know?
I think I got lucky there.
I get four.
Full house, right?
One for each of the boys I brought in.
New fish?
Hey, you be sure
to tell him thank you for me.
For letting me see my baby again.
Jonah. Jonah, what is going on?
- There's a girl.
- What?
In a booth. She's locked up.
No, locked in, so guys can get to her, right?
Look, come on, man. Elliot's sick
and I'm seeing some really weird shit.
- Give me your knife.
- Why?
- Just give it to me.
- Jonah, stop this.
This is like sex trafficking
or something. Yeah.
Man, of course, Mac would bring us
to a place with sex trafficking.
- You had sex with her?
- No.
Then what happened?
I don't know, really. She, uh... She sang.
- What?
- She sang, okay?
Just give me the knife.
It's ridiculous. What are they doing?
I killed her.
Who did you kill, buddy?
I don't know.
I don't know who she was.
She was young.
What did they put in that drink?
Our memories.
Two memories.
What if you're right?
What if it is sex traffickers, huh?
You know the type of people
you don't wanna mess with?
It's sex traffickers. That's who, Jonah.
They are going to know that it's you.
That Nyx guy, he'll know.
- We can't leave her here.
- Can't we make an anonymous phone call?
Look, I think she needs help, man.
Like, like, now and not later.
This is crazy.
Isn't that what tonight's about? Right?
It's like the last hurrah for crazy, right?
We say "yes," okay?
Tonight we say, "Yes."
Got it.
Yes. Hello, we're, um, here to rescue you.
- Hi.
- Okay.
Hey, you okay?
You want my shirt?
- Here you go.
- Jonah, come on.
- We need to leave.
- Hang on.
Here you go.
Take this.
Yeah, you're okay.
Yeah, yeah. There you go.
There you go.
You're fine. Yeah.
All right, hi.
My name's Jonah and this is Rand.
We can take you out of here if you wanna go.
Do you wanna go?
- You do? Okay.
- She wants to go. Come on.
Okay, come on. Let's go, please.
- Which way?
- I don't remember.
- I thought you said you counted the doors.
- It wasn't like this before.
There's someone back here, Jonah. Pick away.
I don't know.
She does.
Shit.
Hey. Hey!
Hey, hey. Hey, look, it's cool, man.
We're trying to find away out of here.
Can you help us find a way out of here?
Look, look. You don't have to do this.
Take her, Jonah. Run!
Whoa, whoa, Rand. What are you...
Oh, my God.
Stop it, please. Please.
Stop it.
What are you... What are you doing?
Can't we worry about that later, please?
- Bind.
- What?
Bind.
What?
What is taking so long?
We should go back inside.
They said they'd meet us here.
Yeah, but I want another drink.
Open the door! Open it.
- Where's Rand?
- He was with you.
- We got separated.
- What the hell happened?
There was a girl in the back, she was
locked up, so we let her out, you know.
Thought she was there against her will.
Okay, we're out of here, man.
We gotta wait for Rand.
Mac, we gotta wait for Rand.
This is crap.
Wait, Mac.
There he is. There he is. There he is.
Get the hell out of here. Go, go, go, go.
Go. Go, go, go.
What the hell are you laughing about?
- What's he laughing at?
- Is that your blood?
This is fucked. This is fucked.
What the hell is going on?
- Where's the girl?
- I don't know.
She's not a girl, man. She's something else.
Like a transsexual?
- That could be cool.
- No!
Hey, hey. What do you mean something else?
Look out!
Is everyone okay?
Yeah. Shit.
Who's...
That's my jacket.
Hey, there's Elliot. Elliot?
Dude, he's alive.
Elliot!
- Shit.
- What the hell is that?
Oh, God. God. Fuck.
Shit.
There's a car coming.
- Get him, get him, get him.
- I'll flag him. I'll flag him.
Hey. Hey, help! Please stop.
Hey... Ahh!
Hey, wait!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
They're coming back.
- Let's go.
- Everybody's dying.
Then let's not! Come on.
Damn it.
We're gonna need that boy now.
Luckily, we have something
that's his under the C-A-R.
Oh.
Well, hey there.
Oh, boy.
Wait, wait. Where are we going?
You don't know, either.
We're going this way, Mac, okay?
So I can get a signal on my phone
and I can call the police.
So I can tell them that two
of my friends are dead.
We don't know if that one guy
is actually dead.
"One guy"? His name is Rand, man.
Rand.
He's been my best friend for, like,
15 years and you don't even know his name.
Yeah, I do.
And Rand might not be dead.
Well, that one guy might not be dead. Wow.
I'm trying to help.
Oh. Oh, well, thank you, Mac.
Thank you so much for your help.
This has been so much fun.
Thank you for taking your dick out and
swinging it all over in front of everybody
and thanks for getting two
of my actual friends killed, too.
Thank you for that.
I didn't tell you to mess with anything.
And I didn't tell you to let
anyone out of any booth.
Wait, shut up.
What is that?
Run.
- Shit.
- Oh, God.
You okay?
- Come on.
- It smells like shit.
Hold on.
- It's quicksand.
- It's not quicksand.
- Well, I'm about to lose my shoe.
- Come on!
What does she want?
Me.
When I let her out of that booth she, like...
She, like, sniffed me.
That's why she took Elliot 'cause he's...
he's wearing my jacket.
Why don't you lose your clothes then?
- Come on, dude.
- Stop it!
It's not the first time I've seen your dick.
It's not the clothes, you dumb-ass.
The clothes smell like me.
Oh, shit. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Great idea.
Shit.
- Get down.
- Shit.
Shh...
Let's get back to the road.
If we follow it, we can find some place.
How's your ankle? Can you walk?
No. But I can run.
Oh, shit. Hold on.
Who are you?
What... What?
I'm Rand.
Wilson. Rand Wilson.
Who are you, Rand Wilson?
I'm... I'm nobody...
No, that's who you're going to be
if you don't answer my questions.
What do you want with the Lilith, hmm?
Who are you?
Is it that little prick shaman
down in Panama City?
- No.
- Was it him?
No. I don't know anything about that, okay?
I told you. It was...
It was our friend, Jonah.
Yeah, it was...
It was his bachelor party. Yeah.
And the man... And the man there,
he brought us here.
We followed him...
You bought it all with good memories,
so your friend Jonah could spend some time
with one of my star attractions.
That's great.
So why did he let her go?
I don't know. I don't know, okay?
I don't. He thought you
had her locked up in there.
Oh, I did have her locked up in there for
some very good reasons, as you have seen.
Oh, thank God.
- Hey, you okay, son?
- No. No.
- I'm not okay, officers.
- All right, sit down.
- Sit, sit. Please.
- No.
His friends... Our friends are dead.
I'm afraid, there's someone following us.
Hold on now. Who is following you?
Shit, shit.
We went to this club in the swamp.
And... It's... it's 50-something.
This guy...
Hey, why don't you get these boys some water?
- All right, just catch your breath. Breathe.
- Ma'am, get some water for these boys.
- All right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
And the check too, please.
- We're busy.
- Found 'em.
Couple of cops picked 'em up
at a diner on the edge of town.
Well, what do you know about that?
Take 'em into the church,
make everything ready.
- So that's really it, huh?
- Yes.
That's all of it?
Just some failed knight in shining armor bit?
Yes, I swear... I swear to God,
that's it. That's it, yes.
Well, that does make things easier.
No. God. Please, wait. Wait.
Please, don't. Please, don't.
- Please, don't.
- I wouldn't move if I was you.
Now, you know, I think you owe
my associate, Barry, here an apology.
Because of your friend's thoughtless
actions he now has a very deep
personal family tragedy to deal with.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, okay?
- Tell him!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Please. I just... I wanna leave.
I wanna go home. I'm so sorry.
We both know your brother is irreplaceable.
Don't blame the Lilith.
- Blame them.
- No, no, no, please.
No. I said, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. Please. I wanna go home.
- Shh.
What is he doing? What are you doing?
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Well, um...
He's gonna hurt you for a while
and I'm gonna watch.
I told you everything I know, okay?
I believe you. I believe you. I know.
God! Please, no.
Please, please. Please stop. Please stop.
But you boys stuck your hand
in the fire tonight
and it is my right to see you get burned.
Why? Why?
Why?
'Cause you messed
with the wrong motherfucker.
No!
But she took off into the woods.
I don't know where she went.
Oh, but you guys got away.
Yeah. We followed the road.
- This is the first place that we saw.
- All right, you boys on something?
- No. No. We absolutely are not.
- Yes, yes.
Please take me to the station.
Just get me out of here, please.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Jonah.
Come on, man. Come... No, come on.
- They said take him to the church.
- Wait, who said that?
Who said that? Wait.
What the...
They work for him.
Up.
Hey.
- Go.
- No.
No.
I like you.
Mac?
Holy shit.
Stop. No. Please.
Eva.
Jonah.
Wow. You guys really did a number on him.
I want all of it.
Every blow, every scream,
every drop of piss in his pants.
Let's give Jonah something
to really think about, hmm?
You got it.
Rand...
Look down.
Now bear with us.
In a moment,
you won't even recall the worst of it.
Got it.
See that he gets it.
Don't leave until you're sure he has.
Eva.
Shit, I shouldn't have called.
I interrupted your party.
No, no, no.
I actually really need
to hear your voice right now.
Are you okay?
Um, yeah. It's stupid. I just...
I had this dream
that I couldn't find you and then...
When I woke up,
you weren't here and I even got up
and went to look for you in the kitchen.
Don't know, then I just got
this bad feeling like...
Like I needed to talk to you.
I really wanna talk to you right now too.
I don't know if I, uh, if I can right now.
Jonah, Jonah.
Hello? Eva?
Can you...
Listen, listen. Uh, something happened. Um...
Elliot...
He's dead and...
- And Rand, he's...
- Are you there?
- Hello?
- Damn it.
Eva, Eva, listen to me.
Uh, listen. I don't know if you can hear me.
But, um...
My phone's about to die
and I just wanna tell you that I love you.
I love you so much.
That's scary. What did you do?
Nothing. No.
I just...
Really wanted to say it.
There's no place in the world I'd rather be
than home with you right now.
- Yeah.
- Are you there?
Hello?
Rough night?
Get the hell out of here.
Brought you a drink.
- I'm not thirsty.
- I'm not patient.
I was supposed to be off work two hours ago.
So you gonna drink that or not?
Because if not...
I'm supposed to kill you.
Okay, okay.
Right.
Good boy.
'Cause you messed
with the wrong motherfucker.
No, wait. Please.
Jonah, are you...
There you are.
Hi, Jonah.
Well, as you can feel, or
remember feeling, I've obviously
put Rand into a great deal of pain.
Now, he's not dead. Not yet.
But that can change.
And will.
If we can't make a deal.
So, you have my girl and I,
obviously, have your man.
So, let's make a trade. Hmm?
No games, no tricks.
Everybody can walk away with what they want.
My associate will give you
all the details and, uh...
I'll be seeing you soon.
Toodle-oo.
He wants to make a trade.
It's your choice, man.
I'm just the messenger.
But that girl, I don't have her.
She's not with me.
She's following you.
Taking you to him is as good as taking her.
Then take me to him.
Yes, sir.
Tick tock, Jonah.
Your old friend's inside and I don't wanna
be here when the new one shows up.
My, my!
Hell is empty and the devils are all here.
You look horrible.
Where's Rand?
No hello, no nothing. Rude.
Come on. I'll take you to him.
So she didn't catch you?
She did.
Well, you don't look too worse for wear.
That's something.
I mean, she likes you.
Thing is, you've been chosen.
You know they mate for life.
We'll use that.
You didn't have to hurt Rand,
you could've just brought me here.
No, I didn't have to.
I was willing to and I did.
Don't forget that.
Just... do what you're told, Jonah.
And you'll be banging away
at Mrs. Jonah by suppertime tomorrow.
Defy me
and your boy Rand
gets a bullet in the brain
he'll be thinking about forever.
What is this?
Think of it like a shock collar for dogs.
Except for her kind.
Helps prevent incidents like
this evening. Keeps her in line,
makes her more susceptible to suggestion.
No, no, no, no. That's for you.
You're going to put it on her.
- Me?
- Yes, you.
Why do you think I brought you here?
She and I have a...
complicated history.
Besides, you're probably the only one
she trusts enough to let get close.
Magic?
Sure.
Magic.
Like everything else, people like you
will just never understand.
Now, when our little transaction is complete,
you and, uh, Mr. Gimpy are free to go.
Don't worry. Won't be long.
Rand. God. Rand.
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry, Rand. I'm so sorry.
They did this to you...
What'd they do?
Wha...
What's up?
- What did you say?
- Jonah.
What?
What did they do to me?
Listen to me.
I'm going home to Eva
and I'm taking you with me.
All right?
Hmm.
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
Rand?
Jonah, are you okay?
Help me, Joey.
Lily!
So pretty!
Come on, Lily.
Stand in the center. Come on.
Come on, Lily, it's time to go.
Lily,
stand in the center.
Or he dies.
Come on, now. That's right.
There we go.
Good.
You were much younger then.
You've made it a lot easier. You're up.
I'm sorry.
You came here for me and...
It was a trap.
I didn't know
what you were.
What he was.
I just want to go home.
Do you?
She's a killer, Jonah. You know that.
Now put her back where she belongs.
She belongs to me.
Do it. Now.
How about we go home?
Both of us.
To our own homes.
And we just leave it at that.
You're wasting time.
Do it.
Do it now!
Okay?
You...
are on my very last nerve, you know that?
We are gonna try this one more time.
Good to see you, shit tits.
Get the fuck out of here.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Here, take this.
Okay.
Cut Rand loose.
Come here.
Come here. Come on. Come on.
You circus freak.
What?
You... piece of shit.
Atta girl.
Come on, Jonah.
Huh.
Don't go anywhere.
Jonah, run!
No!
Rand, cover your ears.
Cover your ears!
Please.
- Shit, Jonah.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Don't go.
Shit.
Oh, no.
Jonah!
- It's okay. It's okay.
- Hold on, Jonah. Just leave.
Jonah.
Honey!
Let's get this special night started.
I'm sleepy.
Some of us had to wake up at 6:00.
Happy anniversary.
Eva.
When did you come down here?
Hey!
What the hell! What are you doing here?
That... That's Eva.
My wife.
You can't be here.
You gotta go.
Okay?
Go.
Okay? Okay.
No!
Get off her, please! I'll go!
I'll go.
Please, just don't hurt her.
Jonah!
No!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/85u8a
Help other users to choose the best subtitles