In the beginning, God created the
the heavens and the earth.
and God said:
"Let there be light."
and there was light.
Then, God separated
the water and the sky ...
... He formed the seas and the land.
then, he covered the land ...
... with trees, ...
... and plants.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Then, He fill the world ...
... with all the creatures
of the sea, ...
... of  the air, ...
... and all the creatures
of the ground.
And then ...
... He made ...
... us.
To live in paradise.
Until ...
... Adam and Eve
disobeyed God,
... and ate the forbidden fruit.
And with one choice ...
... they learned of good ...
... and evil.
Since then,
since Cain killed Abel, ...
... God have seen too much
evil in human hearts.
Wrong choices,
wrong decisions.
That's why ...
This has happened.
our Creator decided
to cleanse the earth.
God warned me.
He told me to build ark.
An ark to save
our family and all the animals.
Every other living creature ...
... would die.
And on the seventh day, ...
God ... rested.
NAZARETH, GALILEE
Mary, my betrothed,,
... you have the most beautiful eyes
I've ever seen, ...
... and the sweetest smile.
In the name of Herod and Rome!
taxes are owed!
What's this?
We will take this man.
Dont you see you're
interrupting the scriptures?
And you!
No!
This must be a mistake.
We're worshipping God here.
Your God, your problem.
Joseph
Come on!
This is the house of God!
Take it!
Time to pay up!
Get back to your father's house,
be quick.
Pay us!
Leave us here!
Bring back that woman!
Move!
Get out of my way!
Mary..
Give that back!
Mary ...
The Lord is with you.
Dont be afraid.
You will soon give birth
to a son.
He will be the
Son of the Most High.
The Holy Spirit will move in you.
Dont be afraid.
I'm the Lord's servant.
The Holy One to be born, ...
... will be called... Son of God.
Mary!
Tell me what's going on, Mary! please
Not here!
You're pregnant?!
What have you done?
What on earth have you done?
There has been no one, I swear.
well there must've been someone,
I'm not stupid!
I'm still a virgin.
This is the work of God.
I do not know
why Ive been chosen, ...
But Im telling you
the truth.
You must believe me.
I thought I knew you.
Please, please Joseph.
I need you to be my husband.
I need you to be the
father to this child.
Child of God.
Please, my love,
pls trust me.
Mary, God hasnt do this,
to people like us
If this be your work, Lord,
please help...
help us ...
Joseph, son of David, ...
be at peace.
Take Mary as your wife.
She is pure.
The Child she carries is
from God
Isabel!
Treacherous!
Treacherous whore!
It's not my fault.
that God chose me.
I dont ask for this to happen!
Did she know about anything?
She's pregnant
Who loves you now?
I will!
I believe her!
And I will take her
as my wife.
If she'll still have
me
within a few months of marrying , ...
... Joseph and Mary are forced to
leave Nazareth.
Mary!
Are you ready?
To better control their subject
... Rome has ordered a census.
All men must return
to the town of their birth.
Come on.
Joseph takes his new wife
to Bethlehem.
a hundred miles of treacherous open
road, ...
... with a baby due any day
Mary and Joseph are alone
against the world.
But others are being drawn
towards them.
a prophecy from the time
of Moses ...
... predicts the birth of a Great
King of the Jews.
Announced in the
heavens.
"A star shall come out
of Jacob, ... "
"... And a scepter
shall rise out of lsrael. "
Hold on!
He's coming out, Joseph,
he's coming out!
Hold on, I gotta find
us somewhere!
Hello?
Stop! Can somebody help us?
He's coming!
He's coming, Joseph,
now!
I'm coming!
All right, come on!
Hold on!
Stay with me!
Sire, the astrologer,
Balthazar.
Here come.
Wine?
You're very gracious, your Majesty.
Id rather not.
I wonder, what can you
tell me of the new king?
King?
...of the Jews, yes.
What news of Him?
King of the Jew?
Am I missing something?
Did not you come here to
see the king of the Jews?
Are not you are looking at
Herod, king of the Jews?
Of course.
Then who is claiming
to be king?
No one.
He's not born yet.
It is a prophecy,
heralded by the Star.
Surely your scribes would
receive revelation ...
Stars? Prophecies?
You interrupt my meal
for this?
Please, if you dont mind ...
Herod knows nothing.
We follow the star.
Where is this treacherous prophecy?
Have you found it?
Ah, here!
Read it!
Isaiah.
"Therefore the Lord Himself will
give a sign. "
Look, look there!
"A young woman will conceive
and give birth to a son. "
Help us! please!
"He will be called wonderful ..."
Mary, I got you!
"... Counselling ..."
Help us!
"... Mighty God, ..."
"... Everlasting Father, ..."
"... Prince of Peace."
Come on ...
But I am the one
who brings peace!
Do you think some
child could do that?
Is it written where this mighty
prince would be born?
Micah says it will
be..  Bethlehem.
Bethlehem?
Bethlehem!
Gather the troops!
Our son.
Praise be to God.
Lady, I believe your Son is the
promised King of these people.
What is his name?
Jesus.
His name Jesus.
Mary!
We have to leave.
Now!
I cant explain,
just trust me.
When Herod hears a
a new king is being born in Bethlehem,
... he orders the murder
of every infant boys.
Kill any you find!
This way!
no! dont
Hurry! Kill them all!
My son!
Get the boy!
Nooo!
The massacre of the innocents.
One Child escapes.
Herod will never know ...
... that the slaughter in Bethlehem
was for nothing.
He's dying.
his last paranoid act,
... execution of his eldest son
for plotting against it.
Father, please!
When Herod dies, ...
... the people sense an opportunity
to win their freedom.
Israel explodes.
the Romans' response,
is brutal.
Stay together!
the uprising is crushed.
In Galilee alone,
two thousand are crucified.
GALILEE
Jesus and His family
returned from Egypt.
There, Jesus.
We're almost home.
A decade of darkness has
fallen over Israel.
Joseph!
What've they done?
We must trust in God's plan.
As He trusts in us.
25 YEARS LATER
Rome has taken direct control
of Jerusalem and Judea.
Herod's son, Antipas, ...
..awaits the arrival of the 4th Roman
governor in 20 years,
... the arrogant and ruthless,
Pontius Pilate.
Greretings, Prefect.
Welcome to Judea.
I hope you're time here
will be prosperous and peaceful.
I intend to make sure it is.
Orders from Ceasar's, this descent
must stop.
For Pilate and Antipas, ...
... any gathering of people
is a threat.
Repent and your sins
shall be forgiven!
At the River Jordan, ...
... crowds flocked
to John the Baptist.
I baptize you,
preparing for the new kingdom.
as you are cleansed ...
So all Israel ...
shall be cleansed!
Are you the Messiah?
Here. Im waiting.
You said there was trouble
In the desert ...
The people are flocking
to this wild  man, John.
They think he's a prophet.
Some even call him the Messiah.
Do you truly repent?
God's ax is ready
Every tree that does not
produce good fruit ...
Will cut down ...
and thrown into the fire.
All flesh shall see
the salvation of God!
And what is a Messiah?
the Redeemer of the Jews.
Anointed by God
to set them free.
Then you need to keep an eye on
your Messiah.
Then is One to come,
greater than me, ...
... Who will baptize with fire!
I'm just a voice in the wilderness,
preparing the way for the ...
... Lord.
Dont stop.
surely, I need
You to baptize me.
John, what you are doing is
right..
Baptize Me.
After his baptism, Jesus
enters the wilderness.
For 40 days, his spirit is tested, ...
... preparing him to the
challenges to come.
Satan...
If you are the Son of God, ...
Command that ...
this stone becomes bread.
Man shall not live by bread alone, ...
But one very word ...
that comes from the mouth of God.
If God loves you,
throw yourself down, ...
His ... angels will lift you
up in their hands.
How dare you put God to the
test!
If you will bow down and worship me, ...
... I will give you the
whole world.
Crucify Him!
Get away from me, Satan!
I worship the Lord, my God, ...
and serve Him only!
Jesus resists Satan's temptations,
... and prepares to
begin His mission.
But it would be without
John the Baptist.
He has been arrested by Antipas.
Come on, scum!
Get in!
The Sea of Galilee
Do you need help?
Im in no need of any help.
Besides, nothing to help with.
Hey, what are you doing?
You cant just
climbed into my boat!
Yes, you're right.
Give me a helping hand.
What do you think you're doing?
We're going fishing.
There are no fish out there,
this time of  day.
In fact, there are no fish out here
anytime the day.
Peter ...
just give me an hour, ...
And I will give you
a whole new life.
Who says I want one?
I tell you,
there's no fish out there.
What am I going to do with you?
You and your dangerous mouth.
Listen.
To a sedicious fool?
I dont think so.
It's the God's message.
"The kingdom of heaven is near!"
So you do claimed to be the Messiah?
No.
But you think he's coming?
He's already here.
He's here.
Out there.
Speaking God's truth.
Opening the hearts of all men.
How did this happen?
What did you do?
I'm giving you the chance
to change your life.
Peter, come with me.
Give up catching fish and
I will make you the fisher of men.
What are we gonna do?
Change the world.
He will bring a new age of
righteousness and justice!
His power will draw all men
to a new world! All people.....
SUNDAY
The week before Passover
Passover is the biggest
Jewish festival of the year.
Thousands come to Jerusalem, ...
... to thank God for
releasing their ancestors
... from Egyptian slavery.
Look, it's Jesus!
Messiah!
Jesus's entrance, creates a storm.
the prophet Zechariah predicted
that a new King of the Jews ...
... would enter the city
on a donkey.
Messiah! Messiah!
Messiah ...
Where is he now?
He's just entered the city,
on a donkey.
"See, your king comes to you, ..."
"... righteous and victorious, ..."
"... humble and
riding on a  donkey. "
Where is he headed?
Towards the temple.
This agitator from Galilee, he's a trouble
the crowds, how're they
responding?
And the Romans have never heard of them ?
Yet.
No. So far.
He must not interfere
with Passover.
God will bring His
wrath down upon all of usl.
And, who knows what Pilate
would do.
If the crowds ran out of control
Nicodemus, go with Malchus.
If he enters the temple,
watch Him.
Do not blink.
I need to know everything.
Go.
The Kingdom is coming!
Messiah!
It Barabbas.
King of Israel, why dont you make
us free?
Save us
from the Romans, Lord.
We come in peace, Barabbas.
Messiah!
Move! Get out of the way!
Get back!
He's going to the temple!
The temple is the holiest place
in the Bible.
During the festival times,
selling sacrificial animal
... and changing money has become
a thriving business.
Did you exchange money?
Yes, yes.
Exchange your money here!
Two, five ...
Exchange here!
What are you doing?
Jesus, please!
Is it not written?
Wait!
"My house ..."
"My house shall be called a
house of prayer. "
But you ...
You have made it the
den of thieves.
Who are you to
tell us these?
We teach the law,
not you
You pray lofty prayers..
And love your shows of
piloting the temple.
Hypocrites!
You can not
serve God and money.
This is outrageous.
and will it never help!
He's clever.
The crowd worship him.
There is something
unusual about him.
There is nothing
unusual about Him!
Apart from his ability
to cause havoc!
If He returns, challenge Him
Make his supporters
see their Messiah ...
for the  simple-minded peasant
that He is
MONDAY
4 DAYS TO PASSOVER
In the week leading upto Passover, ...
Jewish pilgrims visit  ...
the temple daily.
Alms for the poor!
God bless you.
Jesus also returns to preach
to ever larger crowds.
It is much harder for a rich
person ...
To enter the
Kingdom of God
Than it is for a camel to go
through the eye of a needle.
The most  important thing is
that you should love your neighbor ...
As you love ...
yourself.
Teacher!
They say you are learner.
So, tell us ...
Should we pay taxes?
To the Romans?
No! No!
No way!
It's a trap.
So, Teacher ...
should we?
Pay the Romans taxes? or?
Do not pay!
Israel!
Tell him!
Whose face is on the coin?
Ceasars.
Then give to Caesar ...
What is Ceasar's.
And give to God ...
What is God's.
Messiah! Messiah!
High Priest, that man,
there, with Jesus.
He approached me.
He wants to help us.
Really?
That could be useful.
You better get the better
of Him.
yet I may have
found the way to deal with him.
WEDNESDAY
2 DAYS TO PASSOVER
Teachers of the Law -
obey them.
Do everything
they tell you.
But dont do what
they do
They dont practice
what they preach.
Everything they do is done
for others to see.
You only have one Father, ...
... And He is in heaven.
You only have one Teacher, ...
and He is the Christ.
Messiah! Messiah!
Do you see all
these great buildings?
Not one stone of this place,
not one stone, ...
... Will be left standing.
He said he would
destroy the temple!
He said what?
Not one stone
will be left standing.
He threatens to
destroy the Temple.
We must move swiftly,
but softly.
We can not arrest Him openly
or his supporters will run wild .
No, not at the Passover,
No!
We must bring him in quietly,
That night before Passover.
Malchus, what's the name
of that follower of His
that you pointed out to me ?
Judas, High Priest.
Judas, yes ...
Bring him to me.
Here.
PILATE'S RESIDENCE
Sir.
We're eating!
Sir, a Jew has
been causing trouble in the temple.
So?
Yesterday he attacked
the money changers.
Today he says
would destroy the temple.
He has a large number of supporters.
What's his name?
They call him
Jesus of Nazareth.
My servants talk about Him.
He's  canvass is vesmus
But you keep an eye of the crowds
if they started to get out of hand,
I'll shut the temple
Festival or no
festival
Rabbi ...
I am Nicodemus.
Welcome.
I came here of my own accord.
The High Priest knows nothing of this
What is he doing here?
Surely he does not want to
sit with us.
Judas.
Your friend from Galilee
has caused quite  stir.
One can not deny that he has
followers ...
Especially amongst the ...
less well educated element
But you, Judas ...
I'm intrigued
He ... he has the power.
It's hard for me to put into words.
The power to cause trouble.
To stir things up.
Attacking money changers, ...
Threatening to ...
destroy the temple, ...
the Holy of holies.
If He were the Son of God,
If
Would he abuse
the house of the God
the true Messiah will unite Israel ,
not divide it
What do you want with him?
Just talk .
If the Romans step in
can you imagine the slaughter?
It would mean
the end of the temple
the end ... of our faith
the end ... of our nation .
Is that what you want , Judas?
Judas , you are His friend.
Bring him here.
Discreetly
Let us try to stop this,
while we still can
And what's in it for me
Good
We shall expect to hear from
you presently
They say you can
perform miracles .
That you have seen
Kingdom of God
You can see the kingdom of God .
But you must
born again .
Born again?
How can you be born? again ?
You must be reborn..
not in the flesh ..
... but in spirit .
The wind blows where it wishes .
you wont know where it comes from
or where it goes
And so it is, when the
Spirit enters you
God so loved the world
That He gave His One and Only son
Believe in Him,
and you will have eternal life
The Closer it gets to Passover ,
... the tenser it gets in Jerusalem.
Just 30 years ago, the Romans
killed thousands,
... during  Passover demonstrations.
Roman thieves!
Roman scums!
This is a mess!
I must inform Pilates
Since Ive been prefects,
You Jews, have tested my
patience to breaking point
Now i beowned it..
yes but..
Im speaking!
If the disturbances that took place
today are repeated tomorrow
I will shut the temple
immediately
there will be no
Passover
I will put this city
under curfew
I will crush any rebellion
Do I make myself
absolutely clear
We thank you Lord
by whose word, everything
comes to be
Amen.
This is our last meal together
..before I die
What do you mean?
I'm going to be betrayed to my enemies
arrested..
..and condemned to death
Malchus, any word from
Judas?
Nothing, High Priest.
I wont wait it even much longer
Malchus, we arrest this false
prophet tonight.
How do we know
He is a false prophet ?
Has he fulfilled any of the signs
of a true Messiah?
as its written in our scriptures?
Well, Nicodemus, has he?
He will be tried
according to our law.
we remove this man, or the Romans
will destroy everything
Removed ?
Executed ?
Yes , Nicodemus .
the life of one peasant for the
future of God's nation
Dont be afraid
trust in God
trust in Me also
you know the way to where
Im going
we dont know where You're
going, how come we know the way?
the Truth ... and ...
the Life..
Take it.
Eat..
This,
this is my body...
This is my blood
Remember Me by
Doing this.
Im going to the Father
and I'll always be with you..
But now, I must tell you..
That one of you here,
will betray Me.
Who?
Whoever eats this.
Im not,
I will not betray you..
Do it quickly.
Let him go .
You will all fall away
Rabbi,
I will not fall away.
I will lay down my life
for you..
Will you?
I will.
Peter, I tell you,
before dawn..
you will deny me,
three times..
Judas . Where is He?
I...
Do you know where He is now?
I know where He going
Lead my servant
Garden Of Gethsemane
Wake up!
And keep awake.
The time has come
the Spirit is willing ,
but the flesh is weak
I must pray.
Father..
I know,
It must be
as You will it
Father,
Take this from Me,
Spare Me!
Lord , I know
You are pleased with me, ...
for You sustain me in
sincerity
We thank you, our Ancestors,
for watching over us.
Father..
Praise the Lord,
God of Israel
everlasting and everlasting
Amen and Amen,
if You will it, Father
if You will it,
Your will
is mine
Do what you came for
Traitor!!
Take Him!
No! Jesus!
Run! Jesus!
Run ! Run , Jesus !
Peter !
He who lives by the sword,
dies by the sword...
Run!
Come on you who!
Take Him back
What about this one?
Get out of here!
Come on !
I wont leave Him! Peter!
Come on!
Come on , Mary!
Get up!
Enough!
Keep Him moving
Drag Him...
tell Caiaphas we have Jesus,
Yes Sir,
not you
" Therefore, night trials
involving death penalty , ... "
may not be held on the eve of
Sabbath
or on the eve of a feast day "
The best scholars say, we must hold
our trials by daylight
but the trial is tonight
You can not confer this,
it is not legal
Our scholars say, it must be in court,
in daylight and public
It is necessary.
Why the rush?
You know why.
Pilate will close the
temple.
We must be rid of this
Jesus.
But what if He really is
who they say He is?
We are to decide precisely that..
now with God's guidance.
God demands we obey the law!
Let me remind you
what the law says:
"Anyone who shows contempt
for the judge or for the priest, shall
be put to death"
Anyone!
Tell me, speak to me
why letting them do this
to you?
no, no. no
get back
have you seen the man they arrested?
have you seen the man they arrested?!
Get back!
Brothers and sisters, thank you for
coming to this hour
You know I would not have ask
you, if it were not so serious
Ah...
Get Him up..
Jesus of Nazareth
You are charged ...
with blasphemy .
Mary?
Oh, Mary...
What has happened ?
Where is my son?
Jesus has been arrested?
Arrested ?
We did not know where
they could've taken him .
arrested?
at night?
They want to keep it secret..
they dont want any protest..
He has employed demons
to heal.
He has threatened to
destroy the temple of our Lord
brothers, we must
listen before we judge
And so I invite, the Prophet,
to speak.
Tell us the message You bring
from God
Nothing?
Nothing to say?
Surely.
Tell us this ...
Are You The Chosen One?
Are you the Son of God?
I am.
And you will see Me coming
with the clouds of heaven
... sitting at the right hand of God .
This is repulsive!
With God? Impartia!
Fool! Blasphemer!
We have heard enough!
There is only one verdict
Guilty .
This is wrong!
This brings shame on our
consent.
Does it not? Brothers,
the sentence is death.
JERUSALEM
12 DAYS TO PASSOVER
You're Passover robes,
High Priest.
The sentence is death but it can not
be by stoning.
That's penalty for
blasphemy
the crowds..
he has thousands
of supporters
it could be disastrous,
I dare not risk it.
Pilate.
Pilate could do it .
He has the authority .
Why would Romans
execute Jesus?
Pilate is charged with keeping
peace in Judea.
It's in our common interest .
I must make him see that.
Let it be known ! Jesus of Nazareth
has been tried ...
... by Supreme Court of Elders .
And He has been found guilty
blasphemy , ...
and of threatening to ...
destroy the Temple .
What do you want with him ?
Just talk.
The sentence...
... is death!
You ! Take back your money !
You .
I 've seen you before .
You know him .
No.
I dont know him .
You call him Rabbi .
He's nothing to do with me .
You know him .
I've seen you with Him .
I dont know him .
Peter , ...
... you will deny me
three times .
Dont be afraid .
Take him to Pilate !
Where is my wife ?
It's late .
Please come Sir, come quickly!
Claudia , what?
I ...
I saw a man ...
... in a dream.
a man being beaten ...
... and killed .
an innocent man!
A holy man .
A good man .
Help Claudia back to bed .
No!
It was you who killed him .
One of you here ...
... will betray me .
Sir , the High Priest Caiaphas and his
elders are here to see you .
Prefect , good morning .
Prefect , we need your help .
We have convicted a
dangerous criminal.
His sentence must be death.
So?
Execute him.
We can not .
This close to Passover , ...
... it will make us impure.
So do it after Passover .
He is an immediate threat ...
... not only to us ,
but to you..
This is a tense time ...
When my people celebrate ...
their deliverance from
past  oppressors,
He claims ...
to be our king .
And is sweeping up  the crowds
into a rebellion .
Rebellion that could
tear Jerusalem apart.
Ceasar would not be pleased .
His name ?
Jesus of Nazareth .
You better not be
wasting my time .
I 'll see the prisoner .
You ! Stop ! Please!
Please! Wait!! Please!
You know Jesus .
You spoke to Him.
Please, where's my son ?
He's gone .
Gone? Where ?
No.
Please .
the Romans have Him .
The Romans?
He's never said anything
against Romans.
So ...
Tell me who You are .
Are you the King of the Jews ?
are you  asking?
or is it a question coming
from others?
Are You a king ?
That's what Your own people and
chief priests ...
tell me You claimed to be.
My kingdom ...
... is not of this world .
If it were , ...
my servant would fight for arrest.
My kingdom is from another place .
You are a king then,
You say ,
that I am a king .
I have been born
... and come into the world , ...
to testify to the Truth .
Everyone on the side
of truth ...
... listens to me.
Truth?
What is a truth ?
That's Him.
The Man I saw in my dream .
That's Him!
They want Him crucified .
but you cant .
they say
He could start a revolution .
You musnt !
If dont, Caiaphas would blame
any rebellion on me .
Ceasar will see it
as my failure.
He's warned me once.
He's not going to warn me again .
I'll be finished.
We'll be finished.
He's guilty of nothing
more than being deluded
He has broken the law
Your law, not Ceasar's .
get Him out and teach Him
some respect.
Forty lashes !
Forty lashes ?
Nothing more?
Prefect ...
We can not be held responsible ...
... for what the people may do
today, ...
with their eyes on
God,
if you release a man
who has broken
our sacred laws .
the people?
Ceasar decrees ...
I can release ...
a prisoner at  the Passover .
Let the people decide which of the
prisoners I hold..
... would be crucified.
Come on !
Step your feet !
Here!
Faster!
What have they
done to him  ?
They're gonna kill Him !
It's as if He knows this must
happen.
So you are a king .
Every king needs a crown .
Get up !
Let them in .
Yes. You .
You and you .
You .
Go .
Yes.
You .
Wait there /
No, not you . Back . Back !
No! Step back!
Not you .No pushing!
Do not push !
Let us through . /
Let me through!
Get back !
No. No.
Yes.
No.
Close the gate !
Hey ! Mary !
Mary. Move .
Move! Let's go!
Today, Passover begins .
And your emperor,
Tiberius Caesar, ...
makes you a gesture
of goodwill..
The release of a prisoner..
... chosen by you .
I give you a choice .
Barabbas .
a dangerous agitator,
... a murderer..
Or this preacher , ...
... who claims to be your King.
He's not our king !
We  have no
King but Caesar .
You must decide .
We chose Barabbas .
Release Barabbas .
Barabbas .
Give us Barabbas !
Release Barabbas !
Barabbas!
Barabbas ! Barabbas !
Jesus! Jesus!
You choose a murderer?
Give us Barabbas !
Do it!
Go!
And the prophet ?
How could this blasphemer
be our king ?
He's a liar !
He's not our king !
Crucify Him!
Crucify Him !
Kill him !
Spare Him!
Save Him!
Kill Him !
Crucify Him !
Crucify Him!
How can you condemn this Man
and spare a murderer?
Crucify Him !
Blasphemer !
Very well!
Crucify Him !
Crucify the blasphemer !
Let Him die !
No!
You! Back!
Get back!
Release him !
Move!
Roman scum!
How can they
treat Him like this ?
John , I need to see Him .
I need to see my Son.
Get back !
Get back!
Move away!
back them off!
Hosanna !
Move!
This is so wrong , how can
they treat Him like that ?
Get back!!
Roman murderer !
Not ! Jesus !
Somebody help Him !
Show Him mercy !
No!
Get back! Get back!
My Son ...
Dont be afraid .
Everything is possible
wtih God..
Move forward!
Jesus ! Jesus !
Please, she's His mother !
Hey !
Get back!
somebody help Him !
Release Him!
Please !
You !
Help Him carry the cross !
Fast !
My Lord ...
What will the sign of
His cross say, Prefect?
Put in Aramaic ,
Latin and Greek -
" Jesus of Nazareth ,
the King of the Jews . "
He was never
our king .
And it must read ,
" This man said ... "
" ... I am King of the Jews . "
It stays as I've  commanded .
"the King of the Jews . "
Cowards !
Go away!
Go !
Thank you .
Come on !
Come on ! Move !
Move it!
Move!
Come on !
Hey , come on !
Faster ! Move!
Come on !
You ! Leave!
Leave!
Move!
Come on , King !
Come on !
Come on .
Get Him up on the cross !
Come on !
Over there .
Pull the rope!
Faster !
You're going to
regret this .
Hardly the first Jew
we've killed.
He was different .
He was chosen by the gods .
He thought He was.
He'd be forgotten
in a week.
Hey , carry Him up there !
Ready !
Come on !
Wait !
My son ...
King of the Jews !
Do you see this
Temple from there ?
Leave Him !
Father !
Forgive them , ...
for they know not
what they do .
You go first .
Shit .
Arent you the Messiah?
Why dont You save Yourself
and us?
Our punishment is just
but this Man,
has done nothing wrong.
Remember me when
You come into Your kingdom.
Truly I say to you , ...
Today
you will be
with me in paradise .
Mother , ...
This is your son ... !
John , ...
This is your mother ... !
My God , ...
Why have you forsaken me ?
I thirst .
It's finished .
Father , ...
... into Your hands ...
... I commend my spirit .
Claudia ! /
Jesus is a noble man!
Take the body away !
Wait !
I have an order
from Pontius Pilate .
This body is ours.
Give it to them !
3 DAYS LATER
Where were you?
You were suppose
to be His rock .
I 've failed Him .
Now I can not ask Him
to forgive me .
Come back if you need anything .
I will.
Have a safe journey
back to Galilee .
Bless you .
Who are you looking for?
If you'd taken Him ,
tell me where He is.
Mary ...
Teacher?
Go and tell
our brothers ...
I'm here .
Peter ! Peter !
Everyone!
The tomb is open .
He's alive !
What ?
I saw Him .
This is not possible .
No, I saw Him .
Mary, maybe it was someone
else
You think I'm mad ?
Peter, see the tomb
yourself .
Please.
Peter ?
Now do you believe me ?
But He's gone .
Gone?
No.
He's back .
Yes , it is still fresh .
Fresh bread .
Thank you .
A cup . I need
a cup and some wine .
What happened ?
His body .
His blood .
" I am the way , ... "
" ...the Truth ... "
" ... and the Life . ''
No.
No, this isnt real .
God .
Thomas ...
stop doubting...
And believe..
It is you .
Because you see Me , ...
...you believe .
Blessed are those ...
... who have not seen Me ...
and yet  have believed..
40 DAYS LATER
I do not know why
they run from me .
They should be grateful in
saving them from God's judgment .
They even care about God?
No .
They abandoned God for
this dirty, uneducated scum.
Come on !
Who are you ?
Tell me who you are ?
I am Jesus , ...
whom you persecute.
No!
Jesus is dead !
No! No!
My eyes gone blind .
Lord?
Ananias .
Go to the street
called Straight.
Ask for a man
they called ...
... Paul of Tarsus .
Paul ?
But he beats us .
He arrestes your followers
everywhere .
I have chosen him to proclaim
my name to the world , ...
... to the Gentiles , ...
their kings ... ...
... and the sons of Israel .
Go .
Who's there?
Who are you ?
Speak.
I'm one of those
you want to destroy.
Forgive me.
I have wronged you.
I have wronged God.
My soul is on fire.
Help me .
I have chosen him to proclaim
my name to the world .
Shh ...
Im sent by God .
For you .
I know you .
You came to my house .
No!
No! No!
Dont leave me !
No! Dont leave me!
Shh ...
I , Ananias , ...
baptize you ... , Paul ,
in the name of Jesus Christ , ...
for He has chosen ... to
change the world in His name .
In the name of Jesus Christ .
JERUSALEM
They say that Paul of Tarsus has
recovered from his blindness,
and join the
Galileans.
I 'll find him for you .
and then ?
Will I have to send someone
after you?
No.
Let them go .
as Gamaliel said ,
if this is man's work
... it will not succeed.
But if it's Gods...
... we can not fight it .
Driven from  Jerusalem , ...
...the disciples become
missionaries.
Apostles .
Spreading the seeds of the new
faith, far and wide.
Peter ...
... you have done so much .
I'm proud of you,
my fisher of men .
My Lord.
I 've done what
You told me.
We preach your words
throughout Judea .
That is just the beginning .
There are many across
the world ...
... who will want to hear you .
Without You, ...
it's just ... -
Open up,
in the name of Rome !
Answer it.
Remember , ...
... the door is open for everyone .
You must come with us .
Centurion Cornelius
wants you.
Remember , the door is open
to everyone .
The angel came to me , ...
and told me ...
to find you ...
to listen to all
you have to say .
Please, save me .
I'm just a man like you .
It's Jesus who
can save you .
Come.
I , Peter , ...
baptize you ... , Cornelius , ...
... in the name of the Father , the Son ...
and ... the Holy Spirit.
Cornelius is the first Roman ...
... to be baptized
in the name of Jesus Christ .
Thank you .
You are welcome.
Come with me .
All of you..
Everyone who believes
in Jesus , ...
... receives forgiveness in His name .
Everyone .
Peter, ...
Come with me ... ...
and I will make you ...
the fisher of man .
What are we gonna
do?
Change the world .
20 YEARS LATER
The disciples take the Gospel
to the world's great cities.
Antioch , Corinth , Rome .
Bringing hope to the oppressed .
I bring good news to
relieve your suffering .
News of a Great Teacher .
Jesus Christ .
Open your hearts to Jesus , ...
and you will have
everlasting life .
Come here!
Get him out of there !
But preaching of the New Kingdom
threatens those in power .
Who are you ?
Brothers and sisters , ...
we rejoice in
our suffering .
Because we know that
suffering ...
produces perseverance..
perseverance creates character
character, hope .
Christian tradition says all the Disciples
die for their cause.
Peter was crucified in Rome,
upside down.
Matthew is killed in Ethiopia .
Thomas in southern India.
And John is poisoned in Rome.
Paul..
They're coming
for you .
Take this .
Something must survive.
If not me,
my words, at least.
Go. Go.
Ive fought
a good fight .
Ive finished the race .
And I  kept the faith .
Paul is beheaded by the Romans,
... but his words live on.
His letters form
nearly half of the New Testament .
But the final chapter is yet
to be written.
The Romans fail
to kill John.
In frustration , they exiled him
to field colony in Greece.
An island called Patmos.
Here , John live out his days.
and writes Revelation.
... The last book of the Bible.
people today ...
... they called You King ,
they think You are
the Messiah..
Who do you think I am?
You are the Son of God .
What if He's not The One?
We're risking our lives,
for what ?
He has shown us His power
We must have faith in Him .
Dont be afraid .
Trust in God .
Trust in Me, also.
You know the way
to where I am going.
We do not know where You're going ,
how come we know the way?
I am the Way ...
the Truth ...
... and the Life.
I am the Alpha ...
... and the Omega .
the First ...
and ... the Last.
The Beginning ...
... and the End.
My Lord...
I didnt expect death
to come .
There will be no more death , ...
or mourning ...
or crying..
... or pain .
I am making everything new.
Yes.
I am coming soon .
May the Grace of the Lord ...
be with all God's people.
Amen .
Subs by :   leyanne1982
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org