Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
THOMAS: Ninety-eight, ninety-nine, 10,000.
RUDMAN: Thank you.
SAM: Thank you, Thomas.
Looks like your day's off
to a pretty good start.
A fantastic start.
I woke up to a gloriously sunny day,
made love to my wife...
had the finest Swiss cheese omelette
since time began...
and then I won this at the craps table.
Who's got it better than me?
Nobody. What would you like to do now?
I want to celebrate my good fortune
by handing out obscenely excessive tips.
I got your brake pads replaced, Mr. Rudman.
Car is in the garage.
Thank you, Mike. Go have some fun.
That's a very kind gesture.
You might want to be
a little less conspicuous.
[Upbeat jazzy instrumental music]
Could you put that in your pocket, maybe?
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
[Upbeat jazzy instrumental music continues]
Hi.
- Ed Deline.
- AI Kornstein.
Enjoying the pool, are you, Al?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Would you get Mr. Kornstein a cabana?
- That one over there.
- Yes, sir.
You have a nice stay there, Al.
- Hi, honey.
- Hi.
JILLIAN: Is it lunch already?
I got through with my meeting a little early.
Refill your water, Mrs. Deline?
No water. Thanks.
Sweetheart, I can answer for myself.
Right.
I want to talk to you
about something at lunch.
Sure.
Mark.
MARK: How are you?
ED: How you doing?
- Good. Nice to see you.
- Nice to see you.
Thanks a lot for coming back.
- Thanks for having us.
- Thank you.
MARK: Jillian.
JILLIAN: Hi, Mark.
You look more beautiful
every time I see you.
Thank you. Hi.
Nice to see you. Wanna go to lunch?
I'd love to,
but the guys are waiting for me to rehearse.
So, how about a rain check?
Yeah, rain check. Great. Absolutely.
- I got you dinner reservations.
- Great. Thank you.
And I got you the tickets
for the Sugar Ray concert.
Great.
[Sam exclaims]
SAM: Okay.
GIRL: I'm so sorry.
SAM: Can we get some napkins?
RUDMAN: Thank you. It's okay.
RUDMAN: Don't worry about it. It's okay.
- Whoa. Wait a minute.
- My money is gone.
Bump-and-run. White male,
brown leather jacket. Out the door.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
White female. Pink shirt, green skirt.
[Fast-paced instrumental music]
A guy just got robbed at the casino.
I'll be right back. Don't let her move, okay?
[Tyres screeching]
Excuse me.
I'd like to take you somewhere
where we can talk a little bit. Okay?
If you don't mind.
[Fast-paced instrumental music continues]
[Car approaching]
[Thief grunts]
Can I give you a ride?
[Panting] I was gonna catch him, you know.
[Theme music]
Congratulations.
You two just won the daily double.
You both have priors,
and you're both on our surveillance tapes.
I didn't do anything.
Is it a crime
to accidentally bump into someone?
I don't even know this jerk.
You lying bitch. It was her idea.
These two are really stand-up individuals.
Fortunately, we have a very fine
justice system here in the state of Nevada...
and they'll figure out
how long you two know each other...
and also figure out how long
each one of you have to spend in jail.
What I'm interested in is where you dumped
the cash and the wallet.
ED: Please.
THIEF: I don't know.
Cooperation is really your best bet
at this point.
Why, do you ask?
If you don't, the cops will put you in a cell
with some very friendly guys.
I don't remember.
One night in there, they'll be able to fit
a submarine up your rear end.
I was running. Look around where I ran.
Ed, is that cooperation?
- Let me think. No.
- No.
ED: No, let's call the cops.
MIKE: We have both of them in custody,
they'll be turned over to the police...
RUDMAN: Did they get my wallet back?
Not yet. But we're gonna reimburse you
for the money.
It's not so much the money as my daughter.
She's 8 years old.
She wrote me a poem last Father's Day.
I keep it in my wallet.
[Mike sighs]
Well, we got them.
Do you have to be present
at every single security incident?
You have a staff of people working for you.
An involved boss sets a good example.
What about setting
a good example as a husband?
JILLIAN: You're never home.
I come here to see you, and you run off
every time the phone rings.
Do you have any idea what I was about to
say before you "got them"?
Yes, I do.
That's what I thought.
I was gonna say that I wanted
to discuss something really important.
Right. Well, go ahead. I'm here.
I'm all ears. Let's go.
I want to start working again.
But you don't need a job.
What the heck would you do, anyway?
Something that would allow me
to interact with other human beings.
JILLIAN: Ever since Delinda
left the house, I...
Do you have any idea what I do all day?
I go to the club. If I'm not at the club,
I go to the spa.
I know a lot of people who want that job.
I meant, I know you have an appointment
at the spa today.
If that's something
you don't feel like doing, great.
You don't get it. No.
I want variety. I want some excitement.
I understand that.
- No, you don't.
- I do.
Look, we'll talk the minute
your massage is over. We'll talk.
I want you to call me the minute the...
Do you see what I'm talking about?
DANNY: I gotta tell you, Sarasvati.
It just looks like a bunch of numbers to me.
SARASVATl: You see this 500?
DANNY: Yeah.
SARASVATl: That signifies a $500 payout.
Thrice in three days. Same machine.
Thrice in three days?
That doesn't seem that unusual.
Yes, given the laws of randomness,
this would normally not be noteworthy.
But if you look at the particular sequence
of mathematical events...
Do I have to?
Do you know what
Sarasvati means in Sanskrit?
Goddess of learning. I know what I'm doing.
All right. I'll check it out.
[Singing] Well, she knows me
through and through
And she knows just what to do
And how to please me
She's a lady
Whoa, whoa, whoa she's a lady
Talking about the little lady
And the lady is mine
[People applauding and cheering]
Thank you!
And now we will take a short break,
and we'll be back momentarily.
Mary.
I want to thank you for providing me this...
return singing engagement
at the Bella Sera Lounge.
You're welcome.
I book all the talent here now...
and I've had guests tell me
how much they enjoy your singing.
If I may ask, former booker
Mr. Johnny Joosten left so suddenly.
- Is he all right?
- Yeah.
He just had a little misunderstanding
with the IRS.
He'll be back in about 18 months.
- Miss Connell?
- Yeah?
Rose Gluck.
I believe we had a meeting scheduled.
We do?
COSME: We will talk later.
MARY: Definitely.
We spoke on the phone.
And look how beautiful you are in person.
I'm with GTM. Gluck Talent Management.
MARY: Yeah.
- You had a singer you wanted to audition.
- Ben Laden.
Let me say that the name, on a less creative
type, might be considered a negative.
But in this case it's worked into his act
in ways so hilarious...
Okay, we didn't schedule a meeting.
In fact, I told you that our talent schedule
is booked for the year.
So, the mere fact that I am even here...
sans officially scheduled meet time must
portend such an incredible confidence...
such freakish certainty in the magnitude
of Ben Laden's talent...
- Call me next year.
- I'd stake my reputation on it...
Don't take my word for it.
If you would just give me five minutes
of your nightmarishly busy schedule...
I'll bring Mr. Laden in
to mesmerise you in person.
ROSE: What do you think?
Five minutes. Tonight at 5:00.
Five minutes. Thank you.
No offence. The little Chinese man?
He's Filipino.
Ben Laden makes this guy sound like
nails on a chalkboard.
Ciao, ciao.
Bye-bye. Thank you!
"Ciao, ciao?"
DANNY: Ed.
ED: Yeah?
We couldn't find Rudman's wallet.
I had eight guys looking for it.
Someone must have picked it up.
That's too bad.
He had his daughter's poem in there.
- She can write another poem.
- What is the matter with you?
Did you ever hear of anything
called sentimental value?
Yes, sir. That's my mistake.
Sarasvati said that the payoff pattern
at one of your slot machines is off.
A little off or a lot off?
- Not a lot yet, but...
- Talk to me about it later.
ED: Excuse me.
Afternoon, Mr. Deline.
Afternoon. Listen. Excuse me.
ED: Robin.
ROBIN: Yeah.
Is my wife still here?
Robin, it's really not that hard.
Is my wife here?
She was checking in, but then she left.
She say why?
No, she didn't.
Robin, you know,
I'm pretty good at reading people.
Right now I'm reading that
there's something you don't wanna tell me.
ED: Is that correct?
She left with Mr. McGrath of Sugar Ray.
Mark McGrath?
[Solemn instrumental music]
[Phone dialling]
JILLIAN: [On machine] Hi! Deline residence.
Leave a message.
[Answering machine beeps]
Honey, it's me.
I tried you on your cell phone.
I guess you're not at home, either.
So, I was just kind of
wondering where the heck could you be.
Call me when you get this message.
[Door opening]
DANNY: Ed?
I looked at the tape of the new slot.
It's one guy.
He's pulled $500 out of the same machine
three straight days.
Maybe he's just lucky...
Anyway, what is $1,500?
The guy ain't breaking the bank, is he?
Same machine? Same amount?
DANNY: Sarasvati looked at the numbers,
said the odds were off the chart.
Fine. Pull the machine in. All right?
Okay.
- Danny.
- Yeah?
ED: Let me ask you a question.
If you were married and...
[Scoffs]
What the heck am I asking you for?
I got razor blades lasted longer
than your most serious relationship.
If I were married, what?
See, Jillian, she's pissed off because...
I left her at lunch today
chasing after them two cretins.
If we could schedule every situation,
we'd all be home by 6:00.
Yeah, see, that's another thing, too.
She says I'm not home enough.
And she wants human interaction.
What the heck does that mean?
- Well...
- I know what it means.
Jillian, she was supposed to...
have this appointment at the spa today...
Never mind. I don't know why I'm telling you
this stuff anyway.
If Jillian's upset about something,
you should just talk to her.
Forget it, kid. Get out of here.
And go I.D. That guy on the slots. All right?
[Phone rings]
Yeah?
Okay. We'll be right down.
There's a guy down there
that says he found Rudman's wallet.
Mr. Walker, hi. I'm Ed Deline.
ED: This is Danny McCoy.
DANNY: Hey.
We understand you found
one of our guests' stolen property.
- Yeah, I think so.
- Thank you.
I was walking down Harmon,
I found that in the bushes.
I heard about the robbery,
so I figured that must be the victim's.
And when I read that poem,
I thought I'd get it back as soon as I could.
I have a son.
I know what something like that means.
"I love you, Dad, because you're nice.
I love you once, I love you twice.
"I love you 'cause you don't get mad,
I love you 'cause you're always Dad."
Wow. Almost makes me wanna have kids.
- Yeah.
- Almost.
You don't have to be a smart-ass
about stuff like that.
I wasn't. I was just...
And this was lying next to the wallet. $9,500.
I hope that's all of it.
Yeah, $9,500. That's what they took.
GREG: All right. I'm glad it all worked out.
ED: Listen. Wait.
Let us give you a reward or something.
No, thanks...
but that's not necessary.
I'm just glad I was able to help.
If you don't want cash,
how about a show or a room?
You know, Sugar Ray's playing.
They're good.
WALKER: No.
Really, that's fine. Thank you.
But I'll think a good thought for you.
Wow.
Refuses a reward, returns $10,000 in cash,
and thinks a good thought for us?
Somebody got to
nominate him for sainthood.
CROUPIER: Winner!
[Women cheering]
[Slot machine beeping]
[Door closing]
Eddie?
Honey, I'm really sorry
I jumped all over you at lunch.
You're the president of operations.
I know you have to set the standard
for everybody else.
I know you have to be involved in everything.
I apologise.
Forget about it.
So, what else happened today?
Nothing, really...
Well, actually...
some guy returned that wallet
that was stolen earlier today.
Cash, cards, everything.
- Wow! That was really nice.
- Yes, it was.
- Hope you gave him a big reward.
- He didn't want one.
[Scoffs]
JILLIAN: Maybe he said he didn't want one.
Some guy brings back thousands of dollars
and he gets a slap on the back?
JILLIAN: How does that reflect
on the Montecito?
How does that reflect on you?
Okay, I'll see to it that he gets a reward.
Good.
- So, how was your massage?
- Fabulous.
Come on. Walk me out.
The rating card he used
was issued to a Benjamin Dover.
Ben Dover. That was the first hint
that something was going on.
It was obvious
from the mathematical progressions.
DANNY: Yeah. The address he used
doesn't exist.
DANNY: This is the man
who submitted the application...
for the card that this man used.
So, what do you say, Sarasvati?
Something rotten in Vegas?
This will teach you not to doubt me.
[All chuckling]
Let's get an I.D. Quit talking back.
[Singing] That's what I want
That's what I want!
Your loving gives me a thrill
But your loving don't pay the bills
Except for a couple of those chickies
over there at the bar!
It's very nice, Ben,
but it's not quite what we're looking for.
Thank you.
Hang on. Just wait.
ROSE: Mare! Listen!
Read you loud and clear.
Boatload of talent, but you've seen it before.
You want unique. Right? Hip, but unique.
Look, I already gave you five minutes.
I don't wanna hire Ben Laden.
Understood. I got another client.
Why I didn't think of him before...
I should be dragged naked
over broken glass. He's exactly...
Leave now or I call security.
Something's been just sticking up here.
You remember when you said
your massage was fabulous?
I checked the spa, and they said
you cancelled your appointment there.
What, you think I'm lying to you?
What are you doing
checking up on me anyway?
I'm not checking up on you.
I happened to be there.
The masseuse I like called me
and told me she was running late...
so I cancelled that first appointment.
I went on a few errands
and then I went back later.
Okay.
- You don't believe me?
- Yes. No. I didn't say that.
- Can we just get through this week? Okay?
- Yeah.
Jillian. Wow, you look...
I got an I.D. On that slots winner
we were talking about.
DANNY: It's a local guy. Chester Cobb.
ED: Right.
And he's using somebody else's rating card,
which doesn't really add up.
Would you mind putting that file
on my desk?
ED: But first I'd like you to find
this Greg Walker guy...
- and get him a reward, okay?
- He doesn't want a reward.
I know that, but we gotta find him
and give him one.
ED: Make sure it's a generous one, too.
We can't have a guy like that...
nice guy like that,
walking out of our casino empty-handed.
ED: It just doesn't make us look very good.
Don't you agree?
He's just trying to get back
on my good side.
It's a private joke. I don't know.
[Chuckling nervously]
Anyway, call upstairs and get started
on the Walker thing. Thanks.
Come on, honey.
DANNY: Will you put that on Ed's desk?
MAN: Sure.
Mitch, what do you got for me
on Greg Walker?
Facial recognition matches his photo
from the casino to a 12-year-old photo I. D...
for a government job in Colorado,
but that's it.
Last 12 years, there's been
no employment and financial records...
no medical records.
It's like the guy fell off the face of the Earth.
He said he found the wallet on Harmon.
I'll check there first. Thank you.
[Upbeat instrumental music]
DANNY: Are you sure? All right, thanks.
Have you seen this man?
- Excuse me. Have you seen this man?
- No. Sorry.
Hey.
Keep it.
DANNY: Wait a minute.
DANNY: Have you seen this guy?
Yeah. I've seen that guy before.
Lives down there.
[Upbeat instrumental music continues]
- Greg?
- Yeah.
What...
We were very impressed by your good deed.
The more we thought about it, the more
we felt obligated to show our gratitude.
I told you, I don't want a reward.
Mr. Walker, it's obvious
you're in a bit of a down cycle right now.
I haven't heard that one.
"A bit of a down cycle."
You think a few hundred bucks,
a few nights on clean sheets...
Will remind me of what I used to have?
You're right. Which is why I don't want it.
You may not believe this, Mr. McCoy,
but 10 years ago I had a life.
I had a great house in Denver.
I was married. Great son.
I guess I still have a son.
Anyway, if you asked me
how I ended up here...
the fact is, I couldn't really tell you.
- You said you had a kid.
- He's not a kid anymore.
- Kevin turned 22 last month.
- Why don't we bring him here?
- You'd like to see him again?
- I don't even know where he lives.
We'll find him. We'll fly him here.
We'll put him up.
Bring him down in a Montecito limo
and take him to the alley where I live.
No. We'll clean you up.
We'll put new clothes on you.
- We'll put you in a room.
- How do I explain it?
Your old man's been a bum for 10 years?
I can't do it.
We'll come up with a story...
some reason why you've been out of touch
for so long.
Whatever that reason is,
you're back and now you want to reconnect.
[Sighs]
I always loved my boy.
I still do, no matter what.
Which is why he'll understand.
He'll forgive you.
[Computer beeps]
Hey, honey.
Hi, Daddy.
- You got a minute?
- Yeah. What's up?
[Ed sighs]
Have you noticed any changes
in your mother lately?
Other than her hair? Why? What's going on?
She changed her hair?
She lightened it last week
and had it styled a little differently.
I didn't notice that.
Word of advice, Dad:
Women hate it
when men don't notice stuff like that.
- Right.
- Maybe that's the change.
She's pissed off.
No, I don't think...
Has she said anything about being in a rut...
or wanting to experience new things?
She said something like that.
I think it's a phase.
Just something
she's got to get out of her system.
Right. That's probably it.
SAM: We'll send the G-4 to pick up
Walker's son and put him in a suite.
Put Walker in a suite...
get him clothes to make him look like
he belongs in a suite...
and then get our PR person
to come up with a plausible...
"this is why I've been gone
for the past 10 years" explanation.
So, is this a casino
or a frigging Oprah episode?
Ed's the one that wants this.
Ed, I found Greg Walker.
We thought of a great reward for him.
But it's gonna cost a little more
than we expected.
- I know you wanted...
- You just handle it, okay?
ED: Mike!
MIKE: Yeah?
I took a look at the slot machine
you pulled off the floor.
- I think I got it figured out.
- Real good.
Meet me in my office, okay?
- I'm still on duty.
- No, in my office.
The Montecito rating card was the trigger.
The magnetic strip was pre-programmed
with an algorithm...
that caused the random number generator
to pay out a jackpot after three plays.
Put the card in, three plays later, you win.
You think they were working with
somebody in-house?
I doubt it. Anyone here would need hours
with the machine...
and it's been on the floor the whole time.
I'm assuming it's somebody
connected with the manufacturer.
Most likely.
Well, thanks, Mike.
ED: Wait one minute, will you?
Sit down, will you?
Mike, you been doing some
real good work for us.
Thanks, but this wasn't that tough to crack.
Well, the fact is that...
one of these days very soon...
I'm gonna want you to transfer
over here with us.
Think I'd like that.
Except for the pay cut.
[Mike chuckling]
In the meantime,
as a deputy of the surveillance team...
I got an assignment for you.
It's a little delicate.
Find the guy who rigged this.
No. I got that handled.
This one...
I'm gonna need somebody that...
you know, I really, really trust.
And that's you, Mike.
I'm on it. What's the job?
I need you to follow Jillian.
Come again, sir?
For a couple of days,
I need you to watch her.
This is a joke, right, Mr. D.?
You see me smiling?
[People cheering]
Listen, Mare. Don't call security. Don't freak.
- You don't have to stop walking.
- I don't intend to.
I just want to introduce to you
Montecito's next great comic, Hard Drive!
ROSE: Because Gallagher, Carrot Top...
I don't need to tell you that these days
it's prop comedy that's all up in here.
- You want to see time fly?
- Don't throw that clock.
Okay, listen. Don't worry.
The physical shtick?
Okay, both of you, out!
Kick it into gear, Hard Drive. Go.
If I told you you had a beautiful body,
would you hold it against me?
If you're not gone by the time I get back,
I'm reporting you for stalking.
We'll come back tomorrow
with the impressions. You'll kill.
SAM: I already know it. I'm just gonna...
DANNY: If he has any questions...
SAM: Wow!
Looking good!
It's sort of like
what I used to wear to work, only nicer.
Top button.
What did you do?
I was a government claims adjustor.
- You sure he's coming?
- Yeah. He arrives tomorrow.
DANNY: Sam, you wanna
run through that story?
Yes. You worked for the
International Red Cross in Angola.
Then a hospital supply company in Kuwait.
GREG: And why didn't I call him?
SAM: No phone.
But they have phones in Kuwait and Angola.
- Yes, there are phones...
- Yeah, I told the PR guy that...
and he said that the...
"You didn't have a phone in Angola
because you were out in the jungle...
"and you couldn't afford a satellite phone...
"and when you got back to the city
his number had changed and"...
- Do you really think this is gonna work?
- Yeah.
- I don't.
- I don't either. This is stupid.
Roger, the PR guy, can't fill in 10 years
of Greg's life on a few note cards.
I think you should tell your son the truth.
You could try that.
[Rock instrumental music]
This is wrong.
It's wrong and a waste of time.
ED: Mitch, Mike call?
No.
This Chester Cobb guy, the guy that
keeps winning all the time at the slots...
This is the tape we pulled.
See that rating card?
That triggers the payoff.
He's probably keeping the amount
low enough so he doesn't attract attention.
Meanwhile, he's hitting us
all the time $500, $500, $500...
- We got an address on the guy, Danny?
- Yeah. He lives out in Arden.
DANNY: I'd go down there,
but Greg Walker's kid's coming in.
[Cell phone ringing]
DANNY: Surveillance.
ED: Is that Mike?
DANNY: All right.
Jammed escalator.
[Rock instrumental music]
You see, Ed? She's not up to anything.
Probably rolling to the mall.
Rolling to the mall...
after a quick stop at an apartment building.
JILLIAN: Hey!
MARK: Good to see you.
JILLIAN: Good to see you.
This is getting a little funky.
Ed's gonna kill this guy.
[Energetic instrumental music]
SAM: Hi!
KEVIN: Hi.
SAM: You must be Kevin.
KEVIN: Yeah.
- I'm Sam from the Montecito.
- That plane was great.
I still can't believe I was randomly selected.
SAM: Yes, well, that's crazy.
- And they were holding hands?
- Yeah.
It was definitely his apartment building?
Yeah. I picked him up from there.
Thank you, Mike. Good job.
I'm sorry about this, Mr. D.
Where was Sam when she called?
They were pulling into the driveway.
- Which means?
- Any second.
Greg, this is your son.
My God, you're all grown up.
Kevin.
I'm sorry.
- This whole thing was a setup?
- No.
Your dad wanted to see you,
and we thought...
Well, if he wanted to see me,
why didn't he pick up the phone?
You think some private jet and a suite
makes that all okay?
Screw you.
I've survived 10 years without you.
I don't think another 50 will be a problem.
I'm gonna be at the bar downstairs.
KEVIN: When your plane is ready
to fly me home, just let me know.
GREG: Kevin.
Kevin!
[Door slamming shut]
That went well.
[Woman shouting in the background]
CHESTER: Christ, Mom,
I told you not to come...
ED: Chester Cobb?
No, he don't live here no more.
Excuse me.
You can't come in here, man.
What are you doing?
- Hey, I'm gonna call the cops.
- Go ahead.
I'm from the Montecito Hotel.
But you probably figured that out, right?
Wait a minute.
This is about my payouts, huh?
There you go.
I played and I won fair and square, man.
I'm sorry.
Really? Fair and square.
You got that rating card?
- You know, the one that makes you win?
- Rating card?
- I never even heard of that.
- Right.
Come here, Ches.
I'd like you, if you don't mind,
just to have a seat right here.
CHESTER: Okay. Fine.
ED: There you go.
And if you don't mind...
I'm president of operations
for the Montecito.
Now, could you possibly know why...
the president of the largest hotel
in Las Vegas is here...
in this hole with a lowlife like you?
ED: I'm gonna tell you, Chester.
See, today,
I got some very unfortunate news.
My wife may have been unfaithful.
To be honest with you, hearing that hurt.
I mean, it hurt enough that I just felt like
I wanted to beat somebody.
I'm talking, like, inflicting pain.
All right, now...
I have got friends in this building.
If I scream, they will come down here
and kick your ass.
I guess that's an ass-kicking
I'm gonna have to take.
[Stammering]
The rating card?
Sets off something inside the machine.
I get it from a guy that works at the factory.
His name's Ben something.
I meet him at the mall. We split the money.
[Machine bell dinging]
Tell Ben you wanna talk to him right now.
[Woman screaming excitedly]
I feel responsible.
I mean, I did arrange the whole thing.
- You had no way of knowing.
- Now he's even more depressed.
Take a guy who lives in a cardboard box
and make his life worse?
That's quite an accomplishment.
MIKE: Those must be the slot guys
he picked up.
- Take these guys into the holding room.
- Yes, sir.
Heard you single-handedly took care
of that slot thing.
- Well done, Mr. D.
- Yeah, thanks.
It was a rough mission.
Now I got this other thing
I gotta take care of.
Jillian's picking me up in an hour.
Our plane is taking some people back
to Los Angeles.
Should be back in a few hours.
We should be able to get you out of here
around midnight.
I don't want to run into my dad. Is he gone?
I'm not sure.
I just want you to know that all of this...
the setup, the surprise,
all of this was my idea.
So don't blame your dad.
He had nothing to do with this.
We convinced him of it.
I met your dad because
he returned a stolen wallet...
along with $10,000 in cash.
So he's honest.
Tell him to join the Boy Scouts.
Your dad's homeless. You know that?
He lives on the street.
He's made mistakes. He knows that.
He's devastated by it.
But I'm telling you, he really is sorry...
and he still loves his son.
[Kevin sighs]
They say Vegas is a city
of second chances, right?
That's all he wants.
Just talk to him.
JILLIAN: Ready, honey?
Wait a minute.
I gotta talk to you for a minute.
- Now?
- Yeah.
The concert starts in 15 minutes.
What do you got going on
with this Mark McGrath?
- Nothing.
- You were at his apartment yesterday.
- You had me followed?
- No. You were seen there.
And I don't remember
you telling me anything about it.
There's nothing going on
between Mark and me.
I went to his apartment because...
Can we talk about this tonight at dinner?
- I promise you I will tell you everything.
- Yeah.
JILLIAN: You know me better than that.
I can't believe we're having
this conversation on our 30th anniversary.
- Did you plan out the evening like I asked?
- I planned it.
You didn't ask.
The Sugar Ray concert
and dinner at Mystique.
So, now I gotta listen to this guy sing?
ROSE: Quarters. Both these are quarters.
ROSE: Quarters. There you go. Good luck.
Break the bank.
MARY: Rose?
MAN: Thanks a lot.
ROSE: Hey.
MARY: You work here now?
Yeah, well. Actually, I applied a while ago.
They just happened to call me yesterday.
Coincidentally, right after
Ben Laden fired me, so...
You just need a client with some talent.
ROSE: What are you gonna do?
ROSE: There you go.
MARY: Cosme!
Cosme, did you say
you were looking for an agent?
- Yes, that is correct.
- Yeah? Okay.
MARY: Rose Gluck?
- I'd like you to meet Cosme.
- Cosme!
ROSE: Just the one name. That's fantastic.
I saw you the other night.
You are an incredibly talented young man.
Rose Gluck, Gluck Talent Management.
[Singing] All the things that I used to say
All the words that got in the way
All the things that I used to know
Have gone out the window
All the things that she used to bring
All the songs that she used to sing
All the favourite TVshows
Have gone out the window
When it's over
[Crowd cheering]
MARK: Thank you very much!
You're too kind.
We have a special request right now
from a beautiful lady...
to the man that she loves
on the occasion of their 30th anniversary.
You know what? Wait. Jillian.
Bring Ed on up here. Come on up.
[Audience cheering]
MARK: Come on up, guys.
Jillian and Ed Deline.
Come on up.
Give it up!
Ed's the boss around these parts,
so be on your best behaviour.
It's their 30th anniversary.
Come on! Let me hear you!
I've been dealing with Jillian all week here...
and she kept telling me how much
she loves you more and more each day.
I think that's pretty special after 30 years.
So one more time,
please give it up for them.
[Audience cheering and applauding]
Got a special song for you guys.
So take a seat.
Song's called "Every Morning." Hit it, Ross.
[Cheering and applauding intensifies]
[Soft guitar music playing]
[Singing] Every morning
there's a halo hanging from a corner
Of my husband's four-post bed
I know it's not mine
but I'll see if I can use it
For the rest of my life again
Couldn't understand
How did word get out
Once again, as predicted
Left my broken heart open
And Ed ripped it out
[Singing] Every morning
Every morning when I wake up
Don't say a word
Ed always rights the wrong
Ed always rights
[Romantic music continues]
I'll get my stuff and
we'll get out of here. Okay?
That was so much fun!
[Jillian sighs]
ED: I meant to give this to you earlier.
Anyway, happy anniversary.
[Jillian gasps]
Eddie!
It's got 30 diamonds.
It's amazing!
JILLIAN: Thank you.
You know, it was so important to me
to surprise you.
You know, it never occurred to me
what I was putting you through.
You understand, right?
Right. I understand now, yeah.
[Jillian chuckles]
I can't believe you actually thought
that I'd fall for somebody that young.
It's the thing to do now, isn't it?
There isn't another man on this Earth...
that I would even consider.
[Romantic music resumes]
ED: Come here, baby.
That was smooth.
Do that again.
Oh, my God.
DELINDA: Nothing urgent.
I'll lock the door!
[Door closing]
ED: High tech.
Subtitles by The_Viper
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/yrgv
Help other users to choose the best subtitles