Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
The battle between Heaven
and Hell has waged eternal,
their armies fueled
by souls harvested on Earth.
The devil, Malebolgia, has sent
a lieutenant to Earth...
to recruit men to turn the
world into a place of death...
in exchange
for wealth and power...
a place that provides enough
souls to complete his army...
and allow Armageddon to begin.
All the Dark Lord needs now
is a great soldier,
someone who can lead his hordes
to the gates of Heaven...
and burn them down.
Like him,
I killed in the name of good,
but the violence of my life...
pulled my soul
towards the darkness.
But I fought and freed my soul.
Now I watch for others like me.
Men are the ones
who create evil on Earth.
It is
the choices they make...
that enslave their souls
to Hell.
This is the test.
The leader of the Algerian
Revolutionary Front...
was killed yesterday along
with 26 innocent civilians...
in a vicious rocket attack
in Hong Kong.
There has been an outpouring
of anti-U.S. Sentiment...
sweeping across the globe.
Protesters in Libya, Bosnia,
France, Moscow...
and the United States...
are denouncing...
Simmons is the best.
Simmons is not the problem!
He's overseas
killing the bad guys...
like the hero he thinks he is.
We made a deal, Wynn.
Where the hell...
is the ultimate weapon
you promised?
This isn't a game we're playing.
Engineering a biological weapon
is an exact science.
You want it done right,
you do it my way.
This five-year plan of yours
just chaps my buttocks.
I'm making you a guarantee.
Just keep certain agencies
off my back...
and make damn sure I get
all that I've been promised.
If I say you're the man,
you're the man.
You do for me, in no time
you'll be running this place.
When the big piòata breaks,
you'll get it all.
Just make sure you keep
your end of the bargain.
P.S.
There's one more item
on our "to do" list.
It requires
your personal attention.
We need you to help recruit
a very special soldier for us.
Your all-time favorite killer,
Al Simmons.
Simmons? He's doing a great job
where he is.
Why do you want him?
Why do you people
always question?
Why ask "Why?"
When "How?" is so much more fun?
Oh... not again.
- Wanda, do me a favor.
- Yeah?
Buy your man a watch.
He's on his way out.
Do me a favor.
What's that?
Make sure he's back
for dinner tomorrow night.
I'll do my best.
Make sure he's back
for dinner, Terry.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Spaz.
Same routine, all right?
Guard the house. Guard Wanda.
Great guard dog.
Here.
Al, what happened last night?
Look at this.
What a friggin' mess.
We were supposed
to take out bad guys,
not innocent bystanders.
Another Jason Wynn special.
What do you mean?
An awful lot of Wynn's ops
have screwed the pooch lately.
Don't worry, Al. Lighten up.
I got your back.
Semper fi.
Good to go.
All right.
I'm going to
keep my eye on Wynn.
Vehicle secure.
The airport kill zone...
was supposed to be clear
of civilians.
An unfortunate
but necessary sacrifice.
You want someone
filling body bags, send Priest.
If you can't handle it,
I will.
I will send whoever
wherever I choose.
You will follow orders
and do your job.
Got a problem
with that, soldier?
Yes, I do, sir...
and I want out.
I always knew
you'd lose your nerve.
You don't quit us, son.
We are not
the U.S. Postal Service.
Have you read
your profile recently?
You are a borderline psychopath,
perfect for government service.
No guilt, no fear.
You're a killing machine.
- You're wrong about me, Wynn.
- Am I?
Have you
stopped to consider...
that you won't be happy
doing anything else?
I made up my mind.
Nothing I can say
to change it?
Nothing.
I'll arrange
for your transfer...
right after we've run
this last operation.
North Korean refinery secretly
producing biological weapons.
It's up to us
to take out the plant...
and carefully destroy
all the biochemical viruses.
Come on, son.
This is top priority.
Let's get it over with.
What the hell is going on here?
Priorities have changed, Al.
There's a town nearby.
If you release the virus,
they'll all die.
A town with approximately
8,000 experimental hosts.
Are you out of your damn mind?
I'm not going
to let you do this.
Looks like I'm up
for a promotion.
You wipe his ass, too?
You son of a bitch.
You knew what was
going on all along.
I do believe he's catching on.
Enjoy your retirement,
old friend.
Oh, and by the way,
don't worry about Wanda.
I'll take good care of her.
You touch her,
and you're a dead man.
You're the dead man.
See you in Hell, Al.
Aw, look who was left
in the oven too long.
I told him well-done,
not burnt.
I'm gonna have fun with you.
Hey, mister,
you don't look so good.
Hey, mister, you thirsty?
Get the...
Get lost, kid.
What are you looking at,
old man?
You tell me.
You've been gone
a long time, friend.
What are you talking about?
Where am I?
Rat city.
Part of the alley.
I sleep over there.
This is a holy place.
All are welcome here.
Here, Zack, here.
Yeah, right.
Don't loiter!
Let's go! Let's go!
You're welcome to join us...
if you choose.
I got a home.
A new Hellspawn has emerged
from the darkness.
Reborn on Earth...
drawn to the alley
by an unknown force...
his necroplasmic body
wracked by pain...
his memories fragmented.
To him, North Korea
was moments ago.
Malebolgia kept him secluded
in darkness five long years...
while things on Earth
changed in ways...
that will only feed his anger
and desire for revenge.
He sets out
to reclaim his humanity.
How much is left
remains to be seen.
One...
two...
three!
I don't have a choice.
I'll always love you...
forever.
Spaz.
Kids, I got more tricks
than your local hooker.
Here you go.
They say it's a trick,
but it's snot.
Little girl,
where are you going?
Want some candy?
Cyan!
You OK, baby?
Terry!
I like children... fried.
What's going on?
This man
was lying next to Cyan.
Are you OK, honey?
What are you doing
back here, huh?
What is it?
Beat it
before I call the cops.
Come on, get out of here.
There you are. I've been
looking everywhere for you.
Bad Crispy! Bad Crispy!
Clown not like.
Sorry for the turbulence, folks.
He's harmless.
Just a freak accident
with some Jiffy Pop.
Just get out of here
and take him.
Oh, what an adorable
little girl.
Can I keep her?
Hey.
Of course not.
No pets allowed.
A little something
for Lolita here?
Baby exorcist.
Come on,
my barbecued friend.
Don't want to keep...
that side order
of potato salad waiting.
- He knew my name.
- Are you sure?
Come on.
Let's get the kids inside.
You can't get married.
Wanda's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
I'm there for you, buddy.
This is my last mission.
Wait for me.
I just don't
want to lose you, baby.
You will never lose me.
I promise.
The master and I
are going to have words.
He knows I hate clowns.
God, I hate them.
I hate them all.
I hate Bozo, Ronald, Chuckles...
with their freakin' dumb noses
and their lousy party hats!
I don't mind being
short, fat, and ugly,
but the pay sucks!
Easy with that face.
I'm eating.
What does this remind you of?
No, naughty boy.
Oops. A wet one.
I hope I didn't
stain my underwear.
Look at that.
Skid marks.
Get away from me, you freak.
Coming from a monster,
that really hurts my feelings.
Come back here, scrotum-face.
I'm not done with you yet.
Feels like my skin
is about to explode.
That's your viral necroplasm
going through its larval stage.
Move over.
Pretty soon
you'll get hair in funny places,
and you'll start
thinking about girls.
Getting a chubby, studly?
A half guy, semi?
Just get me to a hospital.
A hospital?
Have you looked in a mirror,
burnt man walking?
Even the entire cast of "ER"
couldn't put you together again.
How do I put this to you?
You're pushing up daisies.
You're in permanent nap time.
You're fertilizer.
Is any of this sinking in?
You're dead.
D-e-d. Dead.
I guess five years
feeding earthworms...
has eaten what little brain
there was in there.
What are you?
Allow me
to kick-start your memory.
Hang on. These flashbacks
can be killers.
You're the dead man.
See you in Hell, Al.
This is the bargain.
If you lead my army,
you can see Wanda again.
What is your answer?
I will lead your army!
Anything for Wanda!
If you fail me, you will die.
Avenge your murder.
Kill Jason Wynn.
Malebolgia spent five years
preparing the Earth...
for your arrival, mister.
A little death,
a little destruction...
perfect marriage.
Speaking of marriage...
guess who's not
your fiancée anymore.
And the winners
are Wanda and Terry.
Multiplying like rabbits.
And humpin' and porkin'...
and doin' it and likin' it.
You stay away from her.
I don't want Wanda.
I want you
to take care of Wynn.
Then you and the army
can kick some angelic buttocks.
And in return
for your services,
we'll get Wanda back for you.
You could have
every Wanda on the planet.
Why settle for leftovers?
I love this guy.
You kill me.
Go ahead, stud.
This is all
some sadistic game of Wynn's.
And when I catch him...
he'll wish he had killed me
when he had the chance.
That's it!
That's the spirit.
Just think of me
as your guardian angel.
The clown from Hell.
You're Jimmy Stewart,
and I'm Clarence.
"Uh, well, well,
every time somebody farts,
a demon gets his wings."
Oops, twins.
Get away from me,
you fudge-packing midget!
You still don't get it,
do you, Amnesia Boy?
We'll have to dig
a little deeper.
What is this?
This is where old folks
go after Florida, son.
What is that you say?
Can I dig up my body now?
Why, certainly.
Of course you can.
If you strike oil,
half of it is mine.
Start digging.
Hail, Satan, lord of all
that we can see.
In the name of Luther,
Bialy, and Levinson,
I command thee to appear!
Told you we need
a bigger pentagram.
How about we get back to
that sacrifice-a-virgin idea?
I like that!
You know what I need here, man?
A fresh skull, man!
Yeah, you.
- Get away!
- Fresh!
Every time you go out there,
you come back
a little bit more dead inside.
Oh, come on.
You scream like a girl.
Do it like this.
Someone's a little angry
'cause they died and went to...
Hello, my mutant,
hello, my carcass,
hello, my bug-infested corpse.
Did, like, Satan send you guys?
God hogs up
all the good followers,
and we get all the retards.
What's up with that face?
Get your hands off me!
Help.
What is that?
Shocked and amazed
at the wonders of necroflesh?
You're not alone.
For a limited time only,
you, too, can have
this handsome epidermis...
for the eensy price of your soul
and a buttload of pain.
- Let's get out of here!
- Oh, my God!
I hate weekend Satanists,
don't you?
Look at you.
From spawn larva to full-fledged
Hellspawn in record time.
What... is this?
You were tied to the tracks,
and that stupid train just kept
running over you, didn't it?
Running over you.
In the name of the people
and things of Hell,
I dub thee...
Spawn, general of Hell's army.
Arise, Your Crispness!
Arise, Duke of Deep-Fried!
Sultan of Sizzling!
Emir of Ooey-Gooey!
So I suck as a clown.
Bite me.
Do your job, I'll be the first
to kiss your black butt,
but if you can't hack it,
I'll Fed Ex
your worthless carcass...
back to the frying pan,
where Malebolgia will be
waiting for us.
You'll wake up the dead.
That's you.
Dead people can still die.
All I got to do
is cut off your head.
Oh, God.
Did you have
to use the "G" word?
Wanda...
What have I done?
You done
with this Hallmark moment?
I can't take any more of this
sentimental crap. Come on.
I'll come back
when your armor hardens.
Don't play with it.
You'll go blind.
I have a few more details
to attend to,
and then we can play.
Yuck!
I hate anchovies.
That tastes so good,
I could kick some puppies!
This freak stuff
will come in handy...
when I get my hands on Wynn.
You're letting them get to you.
Easy, friend.
Every choice
has its consequences.
Who are you?
An assassin... like you.
I killed for the kingdom
of Saxony 500 years ago.
I am Cogliostro.
That's all you need to know...
for now.
Are there any normal people
left on Earth?
Or is everyone
just back from Hell?
How do you address
the accusations from some...
that the CIA
only acts to protect...
the government's
economic interests...
in the regions of conflict?
I think the government
has been attentive...
to the sensitivities
of the nations involved.
Since the unfortunate incident
in Southeast Asia last week,
Director Wynn has been meeting
with several world leaders...
in an attempt to quell
the proliferation...
of global conflicts.
Has this produced results?
Last week's peace summit
between Arabs and Israelis...
was disrupted by bomb threats
from the Christian Coalition.
Fitzgerald may be
a spineless bureaucrat,
but he's doing
a great P.R. Job for me.
The world is going
to Hell in a handbasket.
Thanks to him, it's just
another story on the 5:00 news.
Like lambs to the slaughter.
The best is yet to come.
There it is, Jess.
Finally ready.
HEAT-16.
Makes the Ebola virus
look like a skin rash.
That North Korean biochemical
operation really paid off.
We harvested the ultimate weapon
from those diseased bodies,
and now we have
the only vaccine.
- Was there ever any doubt?
- Never.
We have weapons in place
to disperse HEAT-16...
over half
of this godforsaken globe.
Soon the whole world
will be at my command.
Anyone who refuses
to join my consortium...
won't be around to argue.
Time to get reacquainted,
Jason.
Director Wynn,
Terry Fitzgerald is here.
Send him in.
Speak of the devil. Come in.
Good to see you.
Director, the car
is waiting downstairs.
Good.
You know Agent Priest.
Yes. Could I have
a word with you... alone?
Of course.
Would you excuse us?
Glad you dropped by, son.
I want to commend you
on your handling of the media.
Those rumors about me
were becoming a real headache.
- Let's have a drink.
- Thank you.
I know we've been
covering up problems...
with our missions overseas.
I really can't keep
lying like this, sir.
Lying? Really?
I'd like to put
a team together,
analyze the field op data,
get to the bottom of it.
But you're not
an analyst anymore.
There's no reason
not to take a look, sir.
- On the contrary.
- Beg your pardon?
Tell me...
how are Cyan and Wanda?
Little girl
just had a birthday, didn't she?
They're both fine.
I'm glad to hear that.
Now, let's get
something straight.
I run this organization
the way I see fit,
and I will do whatever is
necessary to keep it that way.
Your job is to make damn sure
the public agrees with me.
That clear enough?
Good.
The car is waiting.
Achmed and Abdullah.
Achmed, my friend.
Good to see you.
Abdullah, good to see you.
Up.
This one here.
Excuse us.
Excuse me, sir.
Urgent call.
Gentlemen...
Have you made a decision?
Your HEAT-16 test
was very impressive.
How do you control
delivery of the weapon?
It's the latest
in nanotechnology.
Let me assure you,
the weapon is problem-free.
We've already placed orders
with several of our allies.
You're becoming
quite a powerful man.
Your consortium will soon rival
the United Nations.
Not at all, sir.
I'm just a facilitator.
Thank you.
My partners
are the beneficiaries.
To my partners, gentlemen.
- Code red security breach, sir.
- Where?
At the armory.
A detail's en route.
I'm on my way.
Damn it.
Agent Priest has arrived.
Wait here.
There's been a break-in at A-6,
the armory.
- Who?
- We don't know.
There's a security detail
downstairs with Priest.
Let's get out of here.
You!
Who are you?
What's the matter, Jason?
You don't recognize
your own handiwork?
You left me to die
in that biochem plant, remember?
Simmons!
You sent me to Hell!
I'm here to return the favor!
I trusted you.
Jesus.
How could you marry Wanda?
How could you?
Al, when you died...
Wanda was devastated.
Do you know about Cyan?
Time to die, Jason.
Nice outfit, asshole.
Damn.
What the Hell is that?
It's Simmons!
What are you talking about?
That thing is Simmons!
I want you to nail him now!
It's a little early
for Halloween.
Where you're going,
every day's Halloween.
You don't have the guts.
You're right.
Coming, coming.
Will that be the same
or separate checks, lady?
Just when I was getting sick
of you whining about Wanda,
you do us proud.
So congrats
on your first mission.
Go ahead.
Run!
Holy shit!
Shoot on sight.
I say again...
shoot on sight.
Get a light on him!
There!
- You see him?
- No, sir!
Where the hell did he go?
Negative, sir!
- There he is!
- All right! Take him!
What have we got here?
Gunshot wound
to the head, Doc.
Oh, she's dead.
Come on.
Easy.
Make some room here.
Put her around the back.
Why didn't you warn me
about Simmons?
Spawn was ready
sooner than I expected,
so don't get
your panties in a wad.
Always bitching at me...
"Why didn't you tell me
about Simmons?"
it was going to hurt?"
"Am I going to go to Hell?"
Oh, grow up,
you syphilitic ball-sac.
At least you had fun
compared to them.
Fun? Does this look
like Playland to you?
He killed Priest!
He damn near killed me!
You say that
like it's a bad thing.
No, Jerky.
Jerky, Spawn's a big idiot.
Look, he's been through Hell.
As soon as he finishes
one more little detail,
he'll be ready to join us.
I've done my part.
How about yours?
How we doing on your front?
HEAT-16 is ready to go.
It better be.
The army's ready.
The Spawn's ready.
The HEAT-16
completes the picture.
Congrat-a-freak-a-lations.
What's Simmons got to do
with all this?
He's just the highest-scoring
killer of all time.
If we hadn't recruited him,
the other side would have.
I almost forgot again.
Memo from Brimstone Breath...
we're going to rig
a fancy-schmancy device...
that connects your heartbeat
to the HEAT-16 bomb,
so if your heart stops ticking,
the bomb goes off.
We don't want
any smart-ass fruitcake...
taking you out
ahead of schedule.
An insurance policy from Hell,
the good hands people.
That's a good idea.
I like that.
I want your special attention
dealing with Spawn, you hear me?
Gladly.
Good.
Now, stay sharp.
The night is young.
Ladies?
Ooh, Clownie.
Ah, yes.
Have you ever ridden
a clown's pink pony?
I think it's about time.
When all the world is mine,
I will personally
fry your lard-ass.
As you've seen,
the terrible North Korean
biochemical disaster...
unleashed a whole host
of new diseases.
Ten thousand people died
in the first month...
after the disaster
five years ago.
Millions have contracted
these fatal diseases...
diphtheria, cholera,
smallpox...
diseases that had been
virtually wiped out.
Thought I was getting rid
of the world's vermin,
and I turn out to be
one of them.
The number of sick and dying
children continues to grow.
It's up to us to put an end...
to the suffering
of these innocent children.
Spaz!
What happened to you?
I was playing with Spaz,
and I fell down.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm OK.
Wow. Your face is weird.
Cool.
What's your name?
Spawn.
I'm Cyan.
You have your mother's eyes.
I knew her a long time ago.
Let's get you
back to your mother.
My, my, my.
What a pretty little dress.
I wonder if she's got it
in my size?
Spawnie, Spawnie,
he's our man.
If he can't kill 'em,
no one can.
Yay, Spawnie!
"S" to the "p"
to the "a" to the "awn".
Go, Spawnie,
go, Spawnie!
You fool!
I put you on Earth...
to make sure Spawn keeps
his end of the bargain.
Why'd you pick him
to lead the army anyway?
What are you thinking?
It should be me.
I had the tenure.
It's not fair!
And that's exactly
the kind of talk...
we don't tolerate
around here, right, boss?
Enough!
Spawn must choose...
to murder Wynn
and release the virus.
Then my army will be complete.
Now, now, boss...
This is your last chance.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Cyan!
Honey, didn't I tell you
not to leave my sight?
I was playing with Spaz,
and I fell down,
and Spawn came and helped me.
You're not supposed to talk
to strangers, either.
Spawn's not a stranger, Mommy.
- We're going home right now.
- What's going on?
- What is going on?
- I'll explain later.
No, explain now.
I'm not going through
this again. No secrets.
Wynn was attacked
at the reception.
I don't want
to take any chances.
Trust me.
Go home.
Fix your seat belt, honey.
What the hell is going on?
Daddy, what about Spaz?
Spaz?
Go home, Spaz.
He knows the way back home
better than we do.
Let's go, Terry.
You don't want to be
where I'm going.
But it's your funeral.
Hey, what the hell
are you doing?
Puking up decent food, boy?
It's rotten.
You think we eat so good you can
just spit up what you like?
Don't talk back to me.
Eat this!
No, don't!
He's my dad.
Keep away from him.
B.P. And heart rate?
One-thirty-four over 77,
heart rate, 60.
Let's increase the flow
to 3.5.
We're ready for the monitor.
I'll make a small incision...
so that we can insert
this heart monitor.
You'll feel a slight pinch.
Awesome hardware.
What will you do with it?
Throw someone
a going-away party.
Need any help?
Listen, kid...
I'm not looking
to make friends.
- What's your name?
- Zack.
I'm Al.
That's Spaz.
Breathe normally, Director.
The system is now operational.
As per your orders,
Director Wynn,
if your vital signs flatline
for any reason,
the device will uplink
and detonate the HEAT-16 bombs.
No one would dare kill you.
Good work, Doc.
What a double cross.
I got Wynn to kill Spawn
and create the HEAT-16 bomb.
Now I get Spawn to murder Wynn
and release the virus.
If all goes well,
it should hurt like hell.
I can't believe I actually
got Wynn to get operated.
What a maroon.
It's going to send Earth
into a tailspin...
of death and destruction.
It's time.
Sometimes I wake up at night
down in the alley and wonder...
Is this Hell?
Not yet...
but soon.
Heads up.
Got one.
Who's your new friend, Spawn?
- Get out of here, Zack.
- But...
- Go!
Miss me?
Here's Clownie!
It was you who told Wynn
to kill me.
Guilty as charged.
Before I blow
your fat circus ass away,
tell me why you picked me
to lead your war.
If it isn't Curious Crispy.
The evil's been there...
since you were soup
in your mama's crotch.
Your DNA spelled DOA,
and we just nursed it along.
Those assassin missions were
just training for what's coming.
Let's get down to business.
Wynn's finally got
that HEAT-16 virus bomb working.
Made especially for you.
Get things started with
a big, wet, infectious...
All you have to do is just
lead us to the holy land,
so we can burn it down.
You filthy
little piece of vermin.
What makes you think
I would join your army?
You can take your army
and shove it.
Sounds like a country song...
"Take your army and shove it".
You've got that "I want to beat
the fat little man"...
look in your eye.
I'm going to cut you
into 50 pieces...
and mail you to every state.
I'll take your intestines and...
I don't know how you put up
with this crap.
You're a bigger fool
than I thought...
if you think you're going
to wreck my plans.
You'll do what you promised.
Put down my dog.
Nice doggie.
Heel, fetch...
No, I got it.
Play dead!
You want to do it the hard way?
I warned you.
I'll just
have to teach you a lesson.
No more clowning around.
I'm not the vindicator...
or the victimizer...
or the vaporizer
or the vibrator.
I'm...
the violator!
Good Lord!
I ain't staying!
Damn alley ain't safe no more!
We're going.
Violator, one,
Spawnie-boy, zero.
You've been violated,
girlie-man, huh?
I could have killed you
like that.
Is that a little more surprise
than you wanted?
Twinkle, twinkle,
little Spawn.
You look like crap.
Go fertilize my lawn.
You're not excited yet?
Helter-skelter's coming down
with or without you.
Either you lead the army,
or Wynn plays
pin-the-tail on Wanda.
"Hey, Wanda, come on,
give me that sweet stuff."
"Oh, no. Oh, please,
Wynn, don't."
"Somebody help me."
Forget Terry.
It's my turn to ride
the Wanda carousel of love.
Stay away from her.
Your choice.
See you at Wanda's.
Last one there
gets her rotten eggs.
Wynn and Wanda
sitting in a tree,
s-u-c-k-i-n-g.
First comes love...
The truth
has taken its toll on you.
I'm going to kill
that asshole.
You still haven't learned.
Clearance granted.
Downloading secure files.
Gotcha, Jason.
I can't afford to be wrong.
Still with us, I see.
Your vengeance...
their pain.
Wynn, Wanda...
none of this is worth the cost.
Those are the only things
that matter to me now.
Al Simmons is dead.
Let him go.
I am Simmons, old man.
You're Spawn now,
but that doesn't mean
you have to be what they want.
You're still
letting them get to you.
Your anger is your weakness.
They'll use it to rob you
of any humanity you have left.
Al Simmons knew that violence...
only makes for
more pain and suffering.
He tried to leave off killing,
give himself a second chance.
Your old life is gone.
Accept that.
I still love Wanda.
Put her in the past.
It's the only way
you can be free.
She's the only reason
I'm here.
The war between
Heaven and Hell...
depends on the choices we make,
and those choices
require sacrifice.
That's the test.
I didn't know
this was going to happen.
I'm going to nail that scumbag.
Kiss it good-bye, Clown.
This is just what they want.
You're playing their game.
Then I'll play dirty.
- Guns are useless.
- You got a better idea?
I might.
You've been using
your armor only by reflex.
You must learn to control it.
It has trillions
of neuroconnections.
They're a living extension
of your own instincts,
instantly translating
your thought...
into physical reality,
so long as you stay
clear and focused.
So... that's how it works.
- Cool!
- Now try your chains.
You must visualize
your objective.
The armor does the rest.
All right, Yoda. Wait.
You ready?
All right, go!
Not bad.
Don't get cocky.
You've a lot more to learn.
Your cape has its own powers.
I have to get to Wanda's.
Take care of your powers.
When you drain them,
you die.
Won't be needing these.
You're catching on.
Or this.
I want you to return Spaz to me.
No matter how you find him.
Understand?
Now...
the final test.
Get out of my way!
I'll get Spawn so worked up,
he'll kill Wynn
without blinking.
When I'm done with you,
they'll change your name
to "Stain".
Look, Ma, no hands!
I love the smell...
of burning asphalt
in the morning!
Send a boy to do a clown's job?
It's an honor to be
a Hellspawn, you hear me?
That's not fair!
Time for some necro-goo!
Open wide and say "Aah"!
See you at Wanda's!
Reading secure files.
Christ.
Wynn is out of his mind.
I'm thirsty.
OK, baby.
You want some water?
Establishing connection.
What have you got?
Black bag ops,
assassination lists, everything.
Wynn's been using A-6
to run a criminal consortium.
He's got some biological weapon
called HEAT-16.
It's all there?
I want to get it
on tonight's news.
I'm e-mailing you a copy.
It should be enough
to bury Wynn.
Great.
Daddy?
Hey, sweetheart.
What are you doing here?
Some unfinished business.
You disappoint me, Terry.
You can't release the virus.
Millions of people will die.
Only those
who refuse to join me.
You're a very lucky man.
Whatever it is you want,
just take it and go.
I intend to.
Let's go.
On the floor.
The kid stays with me.
Answer the door.
Go on.
It's all right, sweetheart.
Peek-a-boo.
I see you.
This place
is hard to find in the dark.
I smell you're not
wearing any panties.
Hello, Cyan. Remember me?
You were at my birthday party.
No duh.
What are you,
a regular Einstein?
You sure know
how to raise them.
Don't you touch her.
Back off, hero.
I'm back by popular demand.
Big as life and twice as rotten.
Does wonders for my asthma.
Where's Spawn?
Let's cut the crap.
Spawn's on his way.
You ready to play?
Of course I am.
You better be.
You don't know how much
your heart means to me.
Bring 'em, Jerky.
Come on.
Help me, please.
Careful.
Don't make me nervous.
I might nick something vital.
- Get away from her.
- I can't do that.
She wants me.
You touch her,
and you die slow.
All right, Spawn.
No more fun and games.
Either you join Hell's army,
or she dies...
after I'm done.
I will rip your heart out!
Let her go.
So what's it gonna be?
Time's running out.
Too late.
It's all your fault, Spawn.
She was doing fine
till you showed up.
Now you've got nothing
left to lose.
You're a soulless corpse!
Nothing!
You're wrong.
I've still got you.
Don't be afraid.
- You can't kill me.
- Is that right?
If my heart stops,
the virus is released,
and everybody
in the world dies.
Like you said...
I've got nothing else to lose.
That's right.
Feel the burn.
Get used to it.
It's payback time.
See you in Hell, Jason.
If you kill me, you kill her!
I'm through
doing Hell's dirty work.
You worthless bag of...
How could you let him kill me?
The most important thing in your
entire freakin' universe!
Whatever happened to love,
honor, respect?
You pansy bacon-crisp!
You should have killed him!
Popped his head like a zit.
It feels... so good.
And feel that butt.
It feels so... hairy.
Joke's over.
You should have killed Jason
when you had the chance.
Never.
What do you mean never?
Never?
Do you know how hard
I've been working on this?
You set me up,
you malignant sow!
What do you think you got
the pacemaker for?
Your perfect
attendance record,
you spoon-sucking dipstick?
I was counting on
Spawn killing you.
Then you would get his soul...
and kick-start
the apocalypse now.
I say destroy the cosmos,
ask questions later.
But first...
first, I want to slaughter
each and every one of you.
And then I'm gonna have a little
creme de Wanda.
I'll let you watch, too.
Yummy yum.
Tastes like chicken.
Cogliostro!
Come and get me!
He'll be back.
Concentrate on healing.
Come on!
I may not be able
to hold him off alone.
Come on down to my world
and die, suckers!
All right,
you overgrown gecko...
Come and get your throat cut.
If you won't lead my army,
then you must die.
Never!
Bring me Spawn's head.
You will never escape me.
It's all right now, baby.
Come on.
They belong together.
There's no place for me here.
Maybe you're the one
after all.
You were checking me out
from the start, weren't you?
I'm too old for this.
Not as quick as I used to be.
I've fought this war
long enough.
It's time for someone
to take over.
What if I sided with Clown?
I'd have killed you.
Right.
- I followed him here.
- Thanks, kid.
Use your armor!
Concentrate!
Bite this!
Cut off his head!
You'll pay for this.
It's not over yet.
I'll gum you to death.
I'll bite you.
Wanda, what do you think
about a little head?
This is your last chance
to join up.
Think about it.
Come on.
You'll pay for this.
Give my regards to your boss.
Tell him he's next.
I'm gonna die!
Not bad for a dead man.
Beginner's luck.
Come on, folks.
Let's move back, please.
Is it true the documents
you've uncovered...
implicate Jason Wynn?
Yes. For the past five years,
I unwittingly participated...
in Jason Wynn's illegal
manipulation of the A-6...
to further his ambitions
for worldwide power.
What took you
so long to respond?
Are the HEAT-16 bombs
still a danger?
The entire HEAT-16 weapon system
has already been destroyed.
Do you have
any further comments?
Something I should have done
a long time ago.
The documents I release
to all media outlets...
will answer the rest
of your questions.
Thank you.
Natalie Ford reporting live.
Spawn has stopped...
Malebolgia's plans
to destroy the Earth.
The choice has been made.
For now.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org