Subtitle created by - Aorion -
"Standoff (2016)" ^ ( Run time 01:26:02 )
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, no.
I can't even remember
what got us started, babe.
You're too stubborn, Carter.
Sam, slow down,
watch where you're going.
You said you're gonna
clean up that field.
STANDOFF
And so, we remember Crayton,
for what he had accomplished,
for his family,
a gift that we would treasure
You told Aunt Jane you quit.
Yeah, well. I gave up half of
my day to drive you up here.
So, let's call it a truce and go wish
you parents happy anniversary, okay, Bird.
Don't call me that.
Okay, Isabelle.
Look, why don't we pay
our respects real quick?
I don't want you to come.
Fine, but leave the camera
here with me, okay?
You know you can't hide
behind that thing forever.
Okay, just don't take
any pictures of the service
Okay.
Here you go.
I'll be right here.
I'm serious about not
taking any pictures, Bird.
Isabelle.
Hi.
I've been taking real
good care of your camera.
I...
And so, we remember Crayton,
for what he had accomplished,
May we leave here
with but one overarching
thought in out minds.
That Crayton will always...
Father?
Please.
Ah!
Okay!
Okay.
Please.
I understand it's...
it is over but...
Please, I'm asking you...
We can talk about this.
We can sit down.
We can make some kind of a deal.
I... Just...
I'm begging you.
I'm begging you to
please just don't....
Shhhh.
Take a good look.
You only get one.
- I don't know you.
- But, you know my employer.
You know you don't challenge
a man in his position.
Plea... Please.
I've shown you my face.
So, you're already dead.
Don't forget your book.
Roger.
Isabelle!
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm looking for
a little girl in a red dress.
Oh.
There's the little angel right now.
Roger!
No!
Help!
Help me!
HELP!
Help me, please!
Help me!
Help!
Hey.
Whoa, whoa whoa.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
I can help you.
What happened?
Tell me what happened?
Somebody hurt?
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Hey, you took some potshot, did you?
Pssst!
Get back! Get back!
Give it up, mister!
You ain't getting through to me!
Just making sure you know your place.
MY PLACE?
Where is that, huh?
I'm sitting pretty on a high ground!
You waste your clip burying
bullets in the furniture.
That 45 ain't gonna cut a hole
through to me and you know it.
Not with that fucking
condom it's wearing.
Well, well, well.
That man knows his guns.
So do I.
Ohhh!
Pitiful range you got with that candy ass
20 gauge you're riding up there.
You ain't nothing but
a quail hunter, boy.
And I damn sure ain't
no small game, you hear?
You know, it's still enough to tear
you apart this close, asshole.
Eh, you're right.
You know you're going to need
something damn sizable substantial
if you really want to
rough up with me.
I've got plenty, buddy!
You just try and come up 'em
fucking stairs again, okay!
I will blow your
fucking head clean off!
I'm getting the police
on the line, right now!
Phone's dead.
Looks like I caught you
in a bad time.
I got a cell phone, asshole!
I know, dipshit.
I'm looking at it.
Shit!
You really ought to
keep this on you at all times.
You know, for emergency and such.
I'm just saying.
Well, it don't matter anyway.
The nearest cop is at least
a half an hour away from here
and I won't need but
a few minutes of your time.
You sound like
you're selling me sometin'.
Maybe I am,
maybe I ain't, friend.
Look.
Here's the situation.
That adorable little Muppet you got
up there, she's seen my face.
Hell, if she was a snake,
she would have bit me.
So, if I don't put a hole in
her head, and I mean like right quick,
somebody is going to do the same
thing to me and I can't allow that.
So, what I need you to do
is send her down,
So I can tidy things up a bit,
you understand?
Yeah.
You think she can identify you.
Ohhh.
Yes, I know she will,
as quick as a frog can lick flies.
But, you, on the other hand
you didn't see fuck all,
except the masked gunman.
I can give less than
two shit about you.
All I want is the girl.
So, why don't you
send her on down here,
let me handle my business
and I'll be gone.
Look, son.
I understand the....
unfortunate and the...
complex morale dilemma
that you're facing here.
The wrap is real simple.
The little lady seen my face
Now, she's got to pay the price,
like everybody else.
That's how it works.
As far as you should be concerned,
she's already dead.
Now the sooner you allow me,
to prove that little point to you.
The sooner you can
get back to your...
perfect little life here.
Now, I know you're bleeding up there.
And that does make time a factor,
so, here's what you're going to do.
You're going to send
the girl down to me.
Get yourself to a hospital,
get yourself fixed up.
I'm going to take care of
my business and that will be that.
What do you say?
Believe me when I tell you, son.
You do not want to
fight me on this thing.
This will only devolve
into a battle of wills
and my will is strong than
anyone you have ever met.
Yeah?
Well, you and me ain't never
been introduced, asshole.
My name is Carter Greene.
This is my house!
And so long as I'm still breathing,
you ain't gonna harm a hair
on this child's head.
Listen, you just send the
little lady down here, right now.
This is not the time to play hero
and I am the last individual
on god's green Earth
that you want to butt heads with.
You hear me?
Oh yeah, I heard you.
I hear you and
you sound really scary.
Fuck you, farmer Jim!
You're alone out here on the frontier.
No friends! No family! No cops!
No help at all!
This the wild west, son!
The wild fucking west!
There ain't no guards coming
out here to save your ass!
It's just you and me
and 'em murderer crows
waiting to pick over
our dead bones!
So, you take a breather.
You let that sink in.
But, don't take too long, yeah?
Wouldn't want to get too much blood
all over your white trash finest.
I need your help.
I want you to go to the bathroom
and get the first aid kit.
It's under the sink, go.
Come to Papa.
Alright, set it down.
Open it up.
Come here.
You're going to help me, okay?
Okay.
Now, get it real hot, okay?
You just hold it on there.
Alright, let's put it down.
Don't look.
More.
Alright, more, more, more.
Come on.
Okay.
You're suppose to swallow them.
Not when it hurts
as bad as I do.
Go-Go in the other room.
In a box, there are
some light bulbs, okay?
Bring me all of them.
And some... water.
Bring me some water.
I said all of them, go.
Towels, bring me some towels.
The bathroom, go.
Go.
Please.
Good.
Ain't no farmer.
Now, even if we're not here,
we'll hear him if he tries
to climb the upstairs.
Cool.
What's the water for?
For drinking.
Oh.
You want some?
So, what's your name?
Isabelle.
But everyone calls me, Bird,
I don't like it though.
Bird?
How'd you get a
colorful name like that?
My dad gave it to me.
My mom said he started
calling me his little bird
when I was real small because
I never wanted to eat.
He died though.
They both did.
Car crash.
Car.
I'm sorry.
How did you get into
this mess anyway?
He shot Roger at the cemetery.
Roger?
Aunt Jane's boyfriend.
Jesus.
I'm sorry.
You apologize a lot for someone
who didn't do anything wrong.
Uh, no.
I just, you know.
It's too bad your uncle's dead
and...
Wasn't my uncle.
I should've been nicer to him.
He's a monster.
He's no monster.
Hey.
Don't give him the satisfaction.
He's no monster.
Yes, he is.
You're all alone?
Those big companies moved in and...
this whole valley's a graveyard.
Crops are alive.
Houses are dead.
There's nobody here
but scarecrows.
And you.
And me.
How many bullets you have?
Just one.
That's it?
You don't have anymore
packed in a box or something.
I'm afraid not.
Last shell in the house.
Don't worry.
He doesn't know that.
Can we go out the window?
I may not ever make
it with this leg,
you can climb out on your own.
But, I won't be there to protect you,
that's just what he wants.
Now, we're stuck here until help comes,
he leaves.
Thank you.
No, don't mention it, Isabelle.
Just...
Just doing what's right.
Call me Bird if you want.
I thought you didn't like that name.
Depends on who's using it.
Well, please to meet you, Bird.
I'm Carter, in case you missed it.
That's a nice camera you got there.
What're you... Taking pictures
of the cemetery or something?
Him.
I caught a picture of him
without his mask on.
Does he know that?
I think so.
Oh, that's great.
Give me the film.
Harry, come down!
How's Bernard?
Let me ask you.
What's with all the boxes, huh?
Fixing the jump ship?
Hm?
I bet you wished you schedule
the big move a day earlier, huh?
So, hey, man.
What happened to your family, huh?
What? They up and
leave your sorry ass?
Is this a broken home
I'm sitting in?
Come on, bad ass, talk to me!
Don't be shy!
Shit, you can confide in me.
Oh, whoa!
Look at here.
Soldier boy.
You, a soldier boy.
Damn good one, from the
looks of this photograph.
Look at you,
all spit and polish
with your shiny medals
and your pretty ribbon.
Hey, where were you?
Huh? Hey, look.
I'm ex-military too, man.
Black ops, you know, real jackal shit.
Where were you?
Iraq?
No, no, no.
Afghanistan.
Hey, sergeant Greene.
As one ex-military man to another;
I salute you and
thank you for your service.
Damn.
Nice looking woman
you had there, boy.
Real nice looking.
Hey, you don't mind if I get her
number when this is all over, do you?
- Just shut up!
- Heyyy.
SHUT YOUR FUCKING MOUTH!
Oh, come on, sergeant Greene.
I'm just fucking with you
a little bit.
Ain't no need for you to get
all furiously articulate on me.
Hey...
Just want to thank you.
Took the liberty of...
dipping into you little reserve.
I've been feeling nice and warm,
I hope you got something up there
to keep you chill oloy too.
Oh, and...
All bullshit aside.
Just between you and me.
I understand where you're
coming from with all this, man.
I understand,
I got a little girl myself.
She ain't but...
Well, she can't be no older than...
the lady up there and...
She means the world to me.
Uh.
Nothing I wouldn't do
for that little girl.
I mean, that's why
I'm in this line of work.
You know, I got a family
that depends on me
and I can't let one
little loose end
with a pony tail take them
away from me, can I?
I mean, you can't let her
get in the way
of you taking care of your
responsibilities either.
Right?
I mean...
What's more important?
The life of a stranger or...
or the future of your family.
You feel me?
- Take this.
- Man, am I right?
Put it at the back
of the toilet.
In the toilet?
- In the-In the tank.
- Oh.
- Put it in the tank.
- Okay.
Hey.
Let me ask you this.
You want to see
your son again, right?
I mean, am I right?
Well, you ain't wrong wrong , mister.
Whatcha think I got to lose, man,
I aint' lost?
The kid stays with me.
All right?
Why don't you just go home
to your own daughter, huh?
No can do, partner.
No can do.
Once I sink my teeth into something
I don't pull them out,
until the thing is dead.
Yeah, you sure about that, pal?
Now, I wouldn't bet on you
lasting too long
with that buckshot in your gut.
Oh, shit, man. By my standard,
this ain't nothing but a flash wound.
Well, my's a flash wound
by anybody's standards, so...
We'll just see who drops first.
Well, I got a feeling that
that's gonna be you
once I burn this mother fucker
to the ground.
What you got to say to that?
I'm way ahead of you, asshole.
Now, you know,
just as well as I do,
the kid's got a picture of you
without your mask on.
You see, I got you, man.
Film's in a safe place.
it's in a Ziploc bag
under the fucking water.
You know damn well there's a
decent chance that film will survive
the fire for the cops to find.
I got to think, man.
That's well past the
level of acceptable risk!
For such a tiny professional as yourself!
You know your sneering condescending act
really sucks right about now, soldier boy.
You should've stuck to
that pure hearted yoco bit.
That shit was working for you.
Whatever you say, chief.
Oh, I want to break you into
a million pieces, mother fucker.
A million tiny fucking pieces.
You want to play with me?
Alright, then.
It's feeling to get ugly
after this bitch.
All quiet on the western front, kid?
That's right.
Same as yesterday.
Same as every yesterday.
I tell you. I don't know how this place keeps
self together between my rounds.
Baker, it's either gets and like it.
Just swallow and smile, kid.
Ed, I got a question for you.
When you old dogs're going
to stop calling me kid?
Till you earn your wings.
Don't take offense.
That's just how it is around these parts.
And how do I earn my wings?
Well, you can start by getting
your ass over to Clem Sagers' place
Them teenagers been
messing around on his land.
Again?
You see something, kid?
It's probably nothing,
I'll-I'll get back to you.
(Carter.)
(Where's Sam?
Where's Sam, Carter?)
Bird.
Bird, I need a drink.
More water?
No.
There's some other bottles
up in the attic.
Aunt Jane gets angry
when she drinks.
Yeah. Well,
I get angry when I don't drink.
Hey.
Listen.
Go get me a bottle.
Where did you get that?
I'm sorry, I'll put it back.
Put it back.
Put it back now.
Mara.
I could never say this,
to you face to face.
Even though you told me
over and over again that
it wasn't my fault.
Your eyes never hid the truth.
I killed our son.
I let him die.
I want you know that you did
the right thing leaving me.
You mother fucker.
I hope one day you find it
in your heart to forgive me.
I'm so sorry I was so weak,
Carter.
God damn, sergeant Greene.
That sure is a whole
lot of apologies.
Exactly how many kids
did you get killed?
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me!
Well. Now I know why you
had that cannon so handy.
You packed the place up,
got drunk, then you stopped
and thought about it.
Decided that,
life wasn't worth living anymore, was it?
What the hell.
Don't let this little fiasco with
the kid ruin you whole afternoon.
By all means, go ahead,
act like the two of us
ain't even here
and blow your god damn brains out!
Woo hoo hoo.
But, no, seriously, man.
I know where you're coming from though.
I do.
Shit, she ain't your kid.
Can't turn back time.
Believe me, I've tried.
But, you know I'm
going to win this thing.
Even tombstone courage runs out.
You need to go head on
and give in to the beast.
Send the little lady
down here to me.
Come and get her.
Hello!
Hey!
You guys wanna order some pizza?
I'm sorry.
No, don't be sorry.
I...
I shouldn't have yelled at you.
What was your son's name?
Sam.
You missed him?
Everyday.
I missed my parents too.
There ain't no quitting me.
What?
"There ain't no quitting me."
Just something my dad used to say.
It always made me feel safe.
You think I'll see him
when I die?
Hey, don't talk like that, okay?
Help will be here soon.
Don't say that, Carter,
I'm not stupid.
Alright.
Maybe help ain't coming.
But, I can promise you this.
I won't let him get you.
You hear me?
You believe me?
Why did your wife leave?
Me.
This place.
Reminded...
her of him.
I just wish...
just...
wish...
I believe you.
Just keeping you on your toes, buddy.
Here, have another one.
How you all doing up there?
I could ask you the same question,
you little sack of shit.
You know you sound
like a sick animal.
Just hunting around
for a corner to die in.
You feeling kind of cold?
Kind of weak?
Yeah.
You're going into shock, pal.
You're gonna die,
soon.
Unless you get to a hospital.
Fuck you, I'm fine!
I ain't going no where till that little
bitch's pushing up daisies, period!
That suits me just fine, mister.
Nothing bleeds forever.
Another few hours,
you be lying face down in
a puddle of your own fluids.
Hey, you don't worry though!
I'll let your daughter know you died
defending the future of your family.
Oh, outstanding, sergeant Greene,
out-fucking-standing!
You beat me at my own game!
You're master of psychological warfare!
Next thing you know, you'll
have me tidying up the place
and giving you a blow job
on the way out!
Brilliant!
- Sorry.
- What're you doing?
No film in that camera.
Yeah, it just makes me feel safe.
Stupid, I know.
We all got our ways
in dealing with stuff.
What?
What is it?
Shit.
Just reminds me.
We got a problem.
How big?
It's big.
There's a generator in the basement
that runs the whole power, you see.
I haven't filled it up in days.
It's running on the fumes.
I don't understand?
It would be night soon, Bird.
Without any power, the whole house
would be pitch black.
There's no way I can keep him
from trying something in the dark.
Not with one shot.
What does that mean?
It means I got to
get you out of here.
While it's still light up.
But your leg.
I'm not going with you.
I'm gonna help you climb out
a window so you can run for help.
But you said that's what he wants.
I know what I said, Bird,
but things are different now, okay?
You got to trust me on this.
This is your best chance.
Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Hey. Is the... shooting range in
Red Pepper open for the fall yet?
What's that, kid?
The shooting range on Red Pepper,
is it open now?
No.
Why?
I'm not sure.
I'm...
I'm at the cemetery and
I heard...
What's that?
What did you hear, kid?
Kid?
Nothing.
I'm looking into something,
I'll get back to you.
And stop calling me kid.
Alright, let's go.
What if he realizes you aren't
guarding the stairs anymore.
He hit the broken glass,
we'll hear him, come on.
Now, I want you to climb down
on this roof, right?
There's a crate, jump down
on it and run like hell.
Alright?
Hey, hey.
Even if he hears you, you'll be
a little speck on the horizon
by the time he gets outside.
I don't want to do this.
Neither do I, Bird,
but we have to.
We don't have a choice.
- Come on, give me the camera.
- No.
Come on.
I'll take good care of it.
Don't you trust me?
Come on.
Bird.
I...
Okay, keep the camera.
Come on, go.
That's it.
Stay low.
Okay, go.
Go on.
That's it.
You got it.
Afternoon, officer.
What the fuck?
Shit.
Shit!
Carter.
What?
He hid the police car in the hanger.
Where is he now?
He's far. He's walking
back around the front.
Freeze!
Put your fucking
hands up in the air.
Hands up.
That's right.
It's over.
It's time for you to leave.
I ain't got my glasses on
but that looks that same
candy ass 20 gauge you been
counting on this whole time.
Heavy on power.
Shit for range.
That's all you got, ain't it?
You got, until the count of five,
to turn around and get
the FUCK off my property!
You got to be kidding me.
You probably couldn't even nick me
with that potty trainer from up there.
Let alone make a kill shot, hell.
How many bullets you got left, Jethro?
I got plenty!
Alright!
Don't you worry about it. I got
six reloads waiting on your ass!
Good. God damn!
Six reloads!
You practically swimming
in ammunitions up there.
Well, why no go ahead
and try you luck.
You might sink a pellet in
my eye, take me down.
Come on, what's you waiting on?
Fire away!
I'm not going to kill you
if I don't have to.
When I first go to this dump
you spit fire at me
just to say howdy-do.
Now you want to play trigger shy,
I don't buy that for a minute.
Are you riding on just
one shell up there, partner?
You are, aren't you?
And if you take a shot
at this range and MISS,
it's over.
I don't think you could
afford to take that risk.
Let's ask the little lady.
5.
I ain't going no where.
You might as well save
your breath go on and shoot.
4.
Look, I'm betting if I pull my pistol out
I can shoot you there.
3!
I suggest you ought to shoot me
or get your ass back inside.
2!
One!
Shit!
I ain't calling you a liar, sergeant Greene.
But you got to the most
merciful man I've ever met.
Hey, little lady.
I just want to shoot you.
Yeah, you made the right call, soldier boy.
Yes, indeed.
Who are you to gamble
with that little girl's life.
Let's see if you'll gamble
with somebody else's.
Roll call!
As you is.
Come on.
Tell us a little bit about yourself.
You sick son of a bitch.
Don't you disappoint me, hillbilly.
I said, speak up!
So the man upstairs can hear you.
My name is officer Jerry Baker.
Jerry Baker!
Ha ha ha ha...
Come on,
tell us about the...
about the wife, kids
two car garage.
I have-have a wife
and a son.
Names, damn it!
Give the man names!
My wife's name is Linda.
My son's name...
Alright!
Cut it out!
It ain't going to work.
Just save yourself the effort!
You need to think about it,
sergeant Greene.
You need to think about it real hard.
Get your mind right, you see.
Jerry here, ain't seen my face
just like you, which means...
Technically, he's off the hook.
Also, he's not hurt too bad.
Which means you can probably
get him to the hospital.
But, you're going to have to do it
right quick, I mean like, pronto.
You don't have the leverage
that you think you do, asshole.
Fuck leverage!
Do the math, dipshit!
You send the little lady
down to me right now,
You're saving 2 lives
in exchange for 1.
Not to toot my own horn, but,
that's a hell of a bargain.
Fuck you!
Okay!
You heard him, Jerry.
Have it your way.
Oh, quit your whining.
Hold on. Hold on.
I got something here for you.
Here we go.
- No, no, no.
- Alright.
No.
That's it.
Oh, yeah. That's it.
- Alright?
- What're you doing?
Stand back now.
Oh, god!
What's he doing?
Get out of here.
Go, go upstairs.
Get upstairs, now!
Go.
Don't listen.
Four down,
four to go!
- Your thumbs getting past.
- Oh, you shit fuck.
Listen up, soldier boy!
What's it gonna be?
Me and Jerry Baker waiting
for you to send her ass down.
You piece of shit.
You're a piece of fucking shit,
you know that?
Sticks and stones, my friend.
Alright, have it your way.
- Please.
- Stay with me now.
Just you and me.
Please, stop.
I was going to start
with the toes, but...
I guess I lost the stomach
for the hard stuff.
Hey!
Listen, partner.
It's decision time.
Please, don't.
Please.
Listen, man!
If you don't send that
little girl down here,
with that film,
and I mean right now!
I'm fixing the Jackson Pollock,
Jerry Baker's brains
all over the mother fucking floor.
Man. You kill that guy
is because you want to!
You're just looking for an excuse!
You want to kill somebody!
You go ahead!
You got fucking brain damage!
You're a sick fuck!
And you want to!
Not because...
A simple yes or no
would have worked.
But, you know.
You really piss me off, Jethro.
A matter of fact, you've lost
all your conversation privileges.
Yeah!
Radio silence, starts right now!
And it ends, when you're ready
to send that little girl down!
Now, that suits me just fine, asshole.
I'm sick of hearing your
god damn voice anyway.
Just do me a favour
when you dropped dead
just do it real loud, okay?
So, I can hear it from up here.
I don't hear him walking around anymore.
What's he doing?
Let's find out.
Alright, cock sucker.
Alright, you win.
I got to...
I got to get to a hospital, man.
You-You can have her.
You can have the girl, okay?
You hear me?
You win.
I'm sending her down, alright?
Just...
Just get the fuck out of here
when I do, okay?
He ain't down there.
He must have gone outside again.
I'm gonna sneak down there
want for him to come back in
and blow him in half.
- It's a trick.
- No, no.
I just offered you up
like he won
so that he drops anything
else he got cooking.
He ain't talking back because
he ain't down there.
No, he's waiting for you.
Get in the bathroom,
lock the door.
Carter, don't go.
No time to argue. You get in there.
Go, now!
Don't come out.
Bird.
Carter, are you back?
Hey, now, little lady,
come on out.
Shit!
Whoa!
FUCK!
Fuck.
Damn, that kind of hurt!
Ahh!
This really ain't your day, pal.
Hey, you want to think about
packing it in,
heading to the hospital, huh?
Or somebody gets hurt.
Man.
Think it ain't looking
too good for you, buddy!
This is a lousy place
for the end of the road.
You think this shit is funny, huh?
Okay, hillbilly.
Alright.
I'll show you how funny
this shit is.
That ain't nothing.
Fuck the film.
I'll take my chances.
What're you doing?
Wouldn't you like to know?
Yeah, that's good, man.
Keep moving around,
keep that blood pumping.
Wouldn't want  you to lay down,
close your eyes and
never open them again.
Go fuck yourself.
What?
Trying to help you.
Believe me. That's not
such a bad way to go.
You just kind of...
drift off.
Yeah? What dead mother fucker
did you hear that from?
You know. I'm surprise
you haven't called for backup.
Backup?
That little girl IDs me.
It's my ass, not my employers.
My witness.
My problem.
I'm a contractor, mister.
A professional.
I don't lose.
I don't ask for help.
That's what keeps me employed.
Yeah, well.
It just gonna puts you
in the ground too
you know,
throw in the towel soon, buddy.
I mean, what the fuck
are we doing, man?
This is like a pissing contest for you?
Life ain't nothing but one big
fucking pissing contest, soldier boy
Ain't you been paying attention?
Shit.
I don't die unless the mother fucker
trying to kill me, earns it.
You ain't earned it.
Be damn if I let some chicken shit
like you take me out.
You saying about me.
I'm not the guy
you're fighting, am I?
Yeah.
I'm starting to understand.
You'll never understand
a man like me, chump.
Are you really the monster
you want me to think you are?
You don't have a daughter, do you?
Yeah, I got a daughter.
What.
You think monsters don't breed?
But, how did you get to be
what you are?
Oh, what the fuck is it with you?
You want to be my friend?
You want to be my shrink? Huh?
Or you did just fall in love with
the velvet baritone of my voice.
Come on, man.
You want to know?
Tough guy, huh?
How you get to be like me?
Jesus.
Let's see.
Oh, yeah.
First guy I killed,
brought me up, a bit.
No, a lot.
I couldn't eat,
couldn't sleep.
Can't even look myself in the mirror.
Then something strange happened.
Killed another fellow,
I felt a little better.
The fellow after that, better.
Pretty soon, the more jobs
I got under my belt.
The easier I slept at night.
How many people would that take?
I don't know, I don't count.
Let's just say.
These days I sleep like a baby.
I don't know.
I don't know how you could
live with something like that.
There's something I read once...
stuck with me.
He who makes a beast of himself
loses the pain of being a man.
Wow.
We all got our ways
in dealing with stuff.
Guess for you, it's killing people.
I kill 'cos it's my job,
I take orders.
You were a soldier,
you know what that's like.
Don't pull that card, pal.
We don't kill kids.
I kill for 2 reasons.
Money and necessity.
I don't kill for pleasure.
I never have, I never will.
Well, why don't we
roll out Jerry Baker
and ask him how
he feels about that, huh?
I was... an intimidation tactic,
pure and simple.
And I'm going to do whatever is necessary
to get a hold of that girl, you know that.
She's got to go.
You don't look the devil in the face
without taking the ride to the bottom floor
The devil.
You really are fucked in the head,
you know that?
Ha.
So, now, I'm crazy, huh?
Well, one of us must be.
Carter.
What?
You okay?
What's the matter?
I'm sorry I got you into this.
Got me into this.
Bird.
Hey.
We're put together for a reason.
Lucky.
What took you so long?
Hey, partner!
Got somebody down here
who wants to talk to you.
Go on, speak up, darling.
Carter.
Mara?
Bingo!
Found her number in your phone.
Gave her a call.
I told her I was a friend of yours.
And I was really worry about you.
That you needed to
see her bad but
you couldn't bring yourself
to make the call.
That's where I come in.
Being the close
loyal friend that I am.
This poor woman drove
half the night to get here,
ain't that right, ma'am?
Carter, I'm sorry.
He told me you were drinking,
I was worried about you.
- You hush now, you hear?
- I'm sorry.
So, what's it gonna be, sergeant Greene?
Looks like we got
our tie breaker, huh?
If you fucking hurt her, man!
I swear to fucking Christ,
you'll never get this kid.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
Somehow, I doubt that, soldier boy.
Well, besides,
she ain't seen my face yet.
Have you, darling?
No.
Just like our old friend, Jerry Baker.
You remember him?
That's right. If you don't send
the kid down here,
she's going to get the same thing.
This time, I'm not
going to be soft about it.
You understand?
I'm gonna do some real exploring.
Really open her up,
see what she can do.
So, you get your mind right,
you send the girl
down here with that film,
and you can have your wife back,
and you all can get on back
to your happily ever after.
How do I know I can trust you?
You can't.
But, if she was my wife,
I'll take the chance just the same.
And seeing this how
we're here on your property,
I'm gonna be real courteous and
I'm gonna give you
to the count of five.
Carter.
Here we go.
Carter, you promised.
Five!
Clock's ticking.
Carter, please.
You promised.
- Four!
- You promised.
- Shhh.
- Please.
Shut up!
Here, you take this.
Don't take too long.
If he tries to come up 'em stairs,
you shoot him.
It will knock you on your ass,
but, you'll hit him
if you just aim downstairs, okay?
It aims real wide.
Three!
What? No.
What are you doing?
I'm going to go see my son.
Carter.
Shhh.
Two!
Come on, sergeant Greene,
don't be stupid.
Alright, that's it.
One.
- Carter.
- Alright!
Okay.
You make the right choice.
I'm proud of you.
Alright, you come on.
You send her down.
You can have your wife.
Carter.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay...
- Shhh!
Well, not that it ain't
nice to see your ugly mug.
But, what the fuck are you doing?
I couldn't do it, man.
I can't send that little girl down here.
I can see that!
Where's the 20 gauge?
She's got it.
You want her?
Go get her.
Are you fucking kidding me?
All she's got to do,
is aim down that stairwell
and pull the fucking trigger, man.
You're drunk,
you're slow.
It'll be like shooting
a fish in a barrel.
That's brilliant.
That's fucking brilliant, soldier boy.
Just go home.
Go home to your daughter.
I don't have a fucking daughter!
I fucking hate kids!
What the fuck does it matter, man?
You win.
You fucking coward!
You didn't have the balls
to make the call, did you?
No!
You give up your responsibility
to the little girl.
And you came crawling down here
with your dick in your fucking hand
to grovel like a dog for mercy!
Fuck you.
I don't do mercy!
I'm gonna do you
both a favor and
end your miserable
fucking lives right now!
Hold on!
Oh, come on, man.
What the hell is that gonna solve, huh?
I thought you didn't
kill for pleasure.
Ain't you been listening?
Huh?
Have I been talking on my ass
all mother fucking day
I'd have told you I have prostate cancer,
if I thought it would help.
- We haven't seen your face,
- Oh, no?
Well, here!
Now, you have.
Nice to fucking meet you.
Carter!
Time's up, girl.
You need to bring your ass down here,
before I killed your brand new daddy.
No, Bird, no.
You stay!
You, stay!
Your choice, Princess.
How many people got
to die because of you?
She's just a kid for Christ sake.
There's no way.
Atta girl, come to papa.
Bird, no! You stay up there.
Go back!
Oh, my god.
Damn, girl.
You know, you're about
the toughest mark I ever had!
- Whoa.
- Bird, don't!
What the?
Come on, honey.
Honey, get back here.
Where're you going?
We need help, right away.
Please come, right away.
He's been shot.
We need an ambulance, right away.
Hi, pumpkin.
Scary, huh?
No.
Do it.
A fucking dud?
All this god damn time.
A fucking dud.
Just do it.
What do you think I am?
Some kind of monster?
Carter?
Carter, please.
Please.
Please, what?
Where's your camera?
I guess I took it off.
I guess you did.
You saved me.
I just returned a favor.
You're going to be okay, right?
Don't you worry.
There ain't no quitting me.
Subtitle created by - Aorion -
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6tctc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles