Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
- USS Kelvin, go for Starfleet base.
- Starfleet Base.
We sent you a transmission.
Did you receive it?
Kelvin, can you double-check those readings?
Our gravitational sensors are going crazy
here. You should see this.
It looks like a lightning storm.
What you've sent us doesn't seem possible.
Yes mam, I understand.
That's why we sent it.
- Report.
- Still out of visual range. 20 seconds.
Alert captain Robau that Starfleet
advised to proceed with caution ...
Polarize the view screen.
- Whatever this is... Klingon origin?
- Captain, we have visual.
- Repeat. Could this be Klingon?
- Negative, lieutenant.
You're 75 000 kilometers
from the Klingon border.
Captain, are you seeing this?
My God.
I have a reading.
They've locked weapons on us!
Red alert!
Torpedo locked on us at 320°- 2!
Arm weapons!
Evasive pattern delta 5!
We're being cut like grass.
Fire all phasers!
Damage report.
Warp drive's been knocked out.
Never seen anything like this.
Weapons offline.
Main power at 38%.
- They're firing another!
- All power to forward shields!
Help me ...
... maneuver has been lost.
Are shields even on?
... decks 17 and 13, we have
confirmed casualties.
11% and dropping. 10%.
Shields at 9%.
All remaining power to forward shields.
Prepare shuttles for evacuation.
Hello.
My commander requests the presence of
your captain
in order to negotiate a ceasefire.
You will come aboard our ship via shuttlecraft.
Your refusal would be unwise.
Walk with me.
If I don't report in 15 minutes
evacuate the crew.
- Sir, we could ...
- There is no outpost out here.
Use autopilot and get off this ship.
Aye captain.
You're captain now, Mr. Kirk.
His heart rate is elevated.
Look at the ship.
- Are you familiar with this craft?
- Who is your commander?
- Is that him?
- I will speak for captain Nero.
Then ask captain Nero:
What gives him the right to attack a Federation vessel.
Do you know the location of
ambassador Spock?
I'm unfamiliar with
ambassador Spock.
- What is the current star date?
- Star date?
2233.04.
Where are you from?
Terminated.
- Sir, they have a lock on our signal.
- They're launching again.
Bravo 6 maneuver fire, full spread!
I'm initiating general order 13,
we're evacuating!
Sir.
All decks, this is the captain speaking,
evacuate the ship immediately.
Get your ... to the shuttlecraft.
Begin evacuating ...
- That's George's voice. What's happening?
- We'll deliver it in the shuttle. Go!
- George.
- You're OK, thank God.
I have medical shuttle 37 standing by.
Get to it now. Can you do that?
- Yes.
- Everything's gonna be OK.
- Do exactly as I say, shuttle 37.
- George, it's coming.
- Our baby. It's coming now.
- I'm on my way.
Autopilot function has been destroyed.
Manual operation only.
Clear those decks now! Get to the shuttles!
Move! Move! Move!
- That was a big one!
- Just keep breathing. You'll be fine.
- And the baby too, right?
- And the baby too.
Right here.
Captain to shuttle 37.
Is my wife on board?
- Yes sir, she is.
- I need you to go now. Do you hear me?
- We're waiting on you sir.
- No, just go, take off immediately.
- That's an order.
- Yes sir.
Wait. We're not going yet.
Please stop.
George, the shuttle's leaving.
Where are you?
Sweetheart, listen to me.
I'm not gonna be there.
- No.
- This is the only way you'll survive.
Please don't stay on the ship.
Come to me here.
The shuttles will never make it
if I don't fight them off.
George, I can't do this without you.
OK, I need you to push now!
SYSTEMS FAILING
COLLISION COURSE
ENGAGED
- What is it?
- It's a boy.
A boy?
- Tell me about him.
- He's beautiful.
George, you should be here.
Impact alert.
- What are we gonna call him?
- We can name him after your father.
Tiberius, you kiddin' me?
No, that's the worst.
Let's name him after your dad.
Let's call him Jim.
Jim. OK. Jim it is.
- Sweetheart can you hear me?
- I can hear...
I love you so much.
I love you!
STAR TREK
Hey, are you out of your mind?
That car is an antique.
You think you can get away with this
just because your mother's off planet.
You get your ass back home now! You live in my
house buddy. You live in my house and that's my car.
You get one scratch on that car
and I'm gonna whip your ass ...
Hey Johnny!
Citizen, pull over.
Noooo...!
Is there a problem officer?
Citizen, what is your name?
My name is James Tiberius Kirk.
- What is the formula for the volume of a sphere?
- 4/3 PI times the radius cubed ...
1.26 ...
- What is the dimensionality ...
- Dimensionality equals the logarithm of n divided by ...
... non-excludability and non-rivalry ...
... 4/3 PI times the radius ...
... is morally praiseworthy
but not morally obligatory.
Spock.
I presume you've prepared new insults for today?
Affirmative.
This is your 35th attempt to illicit
an emotional response from me.
You're neither Human nor Vulcan and
therefore have no place in this universe.
Look, his Human eyes.
They look sad. Don't they.
Perhaps an emotional response
requires physical stimulae.
He's a traitor you know? Your father.
For marrying her. That Human whore.
They called you a traitor.
Emotions run deep within our race.
In many ways more deeply than in humans.
Logic offers a serenity humans
seldom experience.
The control of feelings ...
so that they do not control you.
You suggest that I should
be completely Vulcan?
And yet you married a Human.
As ambassador to Earth it is my duty to
observe
and understand Human behavior.
Marrying your mother was ... logical.
Spock.
You are fully capable of deciding
your own destiny.
The question you face is:
Which path will you choose?
This is something only you can decide.
Spock. Come here, let me see you.
- No.
- Spock.
There's no need to be anxious.
You'll do fine.
I am hardly anxious, mother.
And fine has variable definitions,
fine is unacceptable.
- OK.
- May I ask a personal query?
- Anything.
Should I choose to complete the Vulcan
discipline of Kolinahr.
and purge all emotion?
I trust you will not feel it reflects
judgment upon you.
Oh Spock.
As always, whatever you choose to be,
you will have a proud mother.
You have surpassed the expectations of
your instructors.
Your final record is flawless.
With one exception.
I see that you have applied to
Starfleet as well.
It was logical to cultivate more options.
Logical, but unnecessary. You are hereby
accepted to the Vulcan Science Academy.
It is truly remarkable Spock that you have
achieved so much
despite your disadvantage.
All rise.
If you would clarify, minister? To what
disadvantage are you referring?
Your Human mother.
Council, ministers, I must decline.
No Vulcan has ever declined
admission to this Academy.
But as I am half-human, your
record remains untarnished.
Spock, you have made a commitment
to honor the Vulcan way.
Why did you come before this
council today?
Was it to satisfy your emotional need
to rebel?
The only emotion I wish to convey
is gratitude.
Thank you, ministers,
for your consideration.
Live long and prosper.
- Hi.
- Hey there.
Hi. I'd like a Clabmin fire tea ...
3 Budweiser Classics,
2 Cardassian sunrises and ...
- Try the Slusho, it's good.
- A Slusho mix, thank you.
That's a lot of drinks for a woman.
- And a shot of Jack, straight up.
- Make that two. Her shot's on me.
Her shot's on her.
Thanks, but no thanks.
Don't you at least wanna know my name
before you completely reject me?
I'm fine without it.
You are fine without it. It's Jim, Jim Kirk.
If you don't tell me your name,
I'm gonna have to make one up.
- It's Uhura.
- Uhura? No way.
That's the name I was gonna make
up for you.
- Uhura what?
- Just Uhura.
- They don't have last names in your world?
- Uhura is my last name.
Well then you have ... your first name's Human?
- Excuse me buddy. - So, you're a cadet,
your studying. What's your focus?
Xenolinguistics.
You have no idea what that means.
The study of alien languages.
Morphology, phonology, syntax.
Means you've got a talented tongue.
I'm impressed.
For a moment there, I thought you were just
a dumb-hair colonial
who has sex with farm animals.
Well, not only.
This townie isn't bothering you, right?
Oh, beyond belief.
But it's nothing I can't handle.
You could've handled me.
That's an invitation.
- Hey. You better mind your manners.
- Oh relax cupcake, it was a joke.
Hey farm boy, maybe you can't count.
There are 4 of us and 1 of you.
So get some more guys and then it'll
be an even fight.
Guys. Stop it.
Stop it!
Enough!
Guys, he's had enough.
Outside. All of you.
- Now.
- Yes, sir.
- What ...
- I just bought a drink.
- You all right, son?
- You can whistle really loud, you know that?
You know I couldn't believe it when the
bartender told me who you are.
- Who the hell am I, captain Pike?
- Your father's son.
Can I get another one?
For my dissertation I was assigned USS Kelvin.
Something I admired about your dad, he didn't
believe in no-win scenarios.
- Sure learned his lesson.
- Well that depends on how you define winning.
You're here, aren't you?
- Thanks.
You know that instinct to leap without looking,
that was his nature too
and in my opinion something Starfleet's lost.
Why are you talking to me man?
Because I looked up your file while
you were drooling on the floor.
Your aptitude tests are off the charts, so
what is it?
You like being the only genius level
repeat-offender in the mid-west?
Maybe I love it.
So your dad dies, you can saddle for
less than an ordinary life.
Or do you feel that you were meant for
something better? Something special?
- Enlist in Starfleet.
- Enlist?
You guys must be way down on your
recruiting quarter for the month.
If you're half the man your father was
Jim,
Starfleet could use you.
You can be an officer in 4 years,
you can have your own ship in 8.
You understand what the Federation is,
don't you? It's important,
It's a peacekeeping and humanitarian
armada.
We done?
I'm done.
Riverside shipyard. Shuttle for new
recruits leaves tomorrow - 08:00.
Your father was captain of a starship
for 12 minutes.
He saved 800 lives, including your
mother's and yours.
I dare you to do better.
Nice ride man.
It's yours.
4 years? I'll do it in 3.
At ease gentlemen.
Never did get that first name.
- You need a doctor.
- I told you people,
I don't need a doctor,
damn it. I am a doctor.
- You need to get back to your seat.
- I had one, in the bathroom with no windows.
I suffer from aviofobia. That means fear
of dying in something that flies.
Sir, for your own safety, sit down or
else I'll make you sit down!
- Fine.
- Thank you.
This is captain Pike, we've been cleared
for takeoff.
I may throw up on you.
- I think these things are pretty safe.
- Don't pander with me kid.
One tiny crack in the hull and our blood
boils in 13 seconds.
A solar flare might crop up,
cook us in our seats.
And while you’re sitting pretty with a case
of Andorian shingles,
see if you're still so relaxed when your
eyeballs are bleeding.
Space is disease and danger, wrapped
in darkness and silence.
Well I hate to break this to you, but
Starfleet operates in space.
Yeah, well... I've got nowhere else to go, the ex
wife took the whole damn planet in the divorce.
All I've got left is my bones.
- Jim Kirk.
- McCoy. Leonard McCoy.
Three years later.
Captain Nero. You've been
requested on the bridge, sir.
Ayel says it's time.
Sir, we've arrived at the
coordinates we calculated.
There's nothing here. What
are your orders?
We wait.
We wait for the one who allowed
our home to be destroyed.
As we've been doing for 25 years.
- And once we've killed him?
- Kill him?
I'm not gonna kill him.
I gonna make him watch.
Capture that ship.
Welcome back, Spock.
- Why are you so happy?
- I do not know what you're talking about.
- No, I don't suppose you do.
- Hello ladies.
- I'm taking the test again.
- You've got to be kidding.
Yeah, tomorrow morning.
And I want you there.
You know I've got better things to do than
watch you embarrass yourself for the 3rd time.
I am a doctor, Jim. I'm busy.
Bones, it doesn't bother you that no one’s
ever passed the test.
Jim, it's Kobayashi Maru.
Nobody passes the test.
And no one goes back for seconds,
let alone thirds.
I've gotta study.
Study, my ass.
Jim, I think I love you.
- That is so weird.
- Lights.
- Did you just say that is so weird.
- Yeah, I did, but I ...
You don't love me too?
- Oh, no, my roommate.
- I thought you said she was gone for the night.
Obviously she's not. Quick, you've got ...
just get under the bed.
- Under ... ? - Look, just get under
the bed. She can't see you.
- Why not? - Because I promised her
I'd stop bringing guys back to the dorm.
- Well how... How many guys have you ...?
- Just d... just down.
- Hey.
- Hey. How are you?
- Good. - Strangest thing...
I was in the long range sensor lab.
Yeah, I thought all night...
I was tracking solar systems and I picked
up an emergency transmission.
- Really?
- Yeah.
From a Klingon prison planet.
- No.
- Yeah.
A Klingon armada was destroyed,
47 ships.
So, you're not going back to the
lab tonight?
- Gaila, who is he?
- Who's who?
The mouth-breather hiding under
your bed.
- You could hear me breathing?
- You.
- Big day tomorrow.
- You're gonna fail.
- Gail, see you around.
- Get out.
- If I pass will you tell me your first name?
- No. Good night.
I think the fact that you picked up
a transmission is very impress...
We're receiving a distress signal from
the USS Kobayashi Maru.
The ship has lost power and is
stranded.
Starfleet command has ordered
us to rescue them.
us to rescue them ... captain.
Two Klingon vessels have entered the neutral
zone and are locking weapons on us.
- That's OK.
- That's OK?
Yeah, don't worry about it.
- Did he say don't worry about it?
- Is he not taking the simulation seriously?
Three more Klingon war birds decloaking
and targeting our ship.
- I don't suppose this is a problem either?
- They're firing, captain.
Alert medical bay to prepare to receive
all crew members from the damaged ship
And how do you expect us to rescue them
when we're surrounded by Klingons, captain?
Alert medical.
- Our ship is being hit. Shields at 60%.
- I understand.
Should we, I don't know, fight back?
- No.
- Of course not.
What is this? What's going on?
Hm. Arm photons. Prepare to fire
on the Klingon war birds.
- Yes, sir.
- Jim, their shields are still up.
Are they?
- No, they're not.
- Fire on all enemy ships.
One photon each should do
let's not waste ammunition.
Target locked an acquired on all war birds.
Firing.
All ships destroyed, captain.
Begin rescue of the stranded crew.
So, we've managed to eliminate all
enemy ships,
no one on board was injured,
and the successful rescue of the
Kobayashi Maru crew is under way.
How the hell did that kid beat your test?
I do not know.
This session has been called to resolve a
troubling matter.
James T. Kirk, step forward.
Cadet Kirk, evidence has been submitted
to this council,
suggesting that you violated the
ethical code of conduct
pursuing to regulation 17.43
of the Starfleet code.
Is there anything you care to say
before we begin, sir?
Yes. I believe I have the right
to face my accuser directly?
Step forward please.
This is commander Spock. He is one
of our most distinguished graduates.
He's programmed the Kobayashi Maru
exam for the last 4 years.
Commander.
Cadet Kirk, you somehow managed to install
and activate a subroutine
in the programming code, thereby changing the
conditions of the test.
- Your point being?
- In academic vernacular - you cheated.
Let me ask you something I think we all
know the answer to.
The test itself is a cheat, isn't it?
You programmed it to be unwinnable.
Your argument precludes the ability
of a no-win scenario?
I don't believe in no-win scenarios.
Then not only did you violate the rules, you
also failed to understand the principle lesson.
Please, enlighten me.
You of all people should know, cadet
Kirk, a captain cannot cheat death.
- I of all people?
- Your father,
lt. George Kirk assumed command of his vessel
before being killed in action, did he not?
- I don't think you like the fact that I beat your test.
- Further more you have failed to define the purpose of the test
- Enlighten me again.
- The purpose to experience fear.
Fear in the face of certain death.
To accept that fear
and maintain control of oneself
and one's crew.
This is a quality expected in
every Starfleet captain.
Excuse me, sir.
We've received a distress
call from Vulcan.
With our primary fleet engaged
in the Laurentian system,
I hereby order all cadets to report
to hangar 1 immediately.
Dismissed.
- Who was that pointy-eared bastard?
- I do not know.
But I like him.
Bracer, USS Farragut.
McCoy, USS Enterprise.
McGrath, USS Walcott.
Spader, USS Hood.
Welcome to Starfleet.
Godspeed.
He didn't call my name.
Commander, sir, you didn't call
my name, Kirk, James T.
Kirk, you're on academic suspension,
that means you're grounded
until the academy board rules.
Jim, the board will rule in your favor.
Most likely.
Look Jim, I've gotta go.
Yeah. Yeah, go. Be safe.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah. Yeah. Sorry.
Damn it.
Come with me.
Uhura, USS Farragut.
Petrovsky, USS Antares.
Go to your stations and good luck.
- Bones, where are we going?
- You'll see.
- Commander, a word?
- Yes, lieutenant?
- Was I not one of your top students?
- Indeed you were.
And did I not on multiple occasions
demonstrate an exceptional oral sensitivity
and I quote "an unparalleled ability
to identify sonic anomalies
in subspace transmission tests"?
Consistently, yes.
And while you were well aware that I'm qualified
and desire to serve on the USS Enterprise,
I'm assigned to the Farragut?
It was an attempt to avoid
the appearance of favoritism.
No. I'm assigned to the Enterprise.
- Yes, I believe you are.
- Thank you.
- What are you doing?
- I'm doing you a favor.
I couldn’t just leave you there
looking all pathetic. Take a seat.
Let me give you a vaccine
against viral infection
from the Ovaran mud flies.
- What for?
- To give you the symptoms.
- What are you talking about? - You're
gonna start to lose vision in your left eye.
Yeah, I already have.
Oh, and you're gonna get a really bad
headache and flop sweat.
- You call this a favor?
- Yeah, you owe me one.
Kirk, James T. He is not cleared
for duty aboard the Enterprise.
Medical code states the treatment and
transport of a patient is to be determined
at the discretion of his attending physician.
Which is me. S I'm taking Mr. Kirk aboard.
Or you would you like to explain to
captain Pike
why Enterprise warped into a crisis
without one of its senior medical officers?
- As you were.
- As you were. Come on.
I might throw up on you.
Jim, you've gotta look at this.
- Jim, look.
- What?
We need to get you changed.
I don't feel right. I feel like I'm leaking.
Damn, it's that pointy-eared bastard.
- Mr. Spock.
- Captain.
- Engineering reports ready for launch.
- Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen, the maiden
voyage of our newest flagship
deserves more pompon circumstance
that we can afford today.
The christening will just have to
be our reward for a safe return.
Carry on.
All decks, this is Captain Pike.
Prepare for immediate departure.
Helm, thrusters.
??? retracted, captain, dock
control reports ready.
Thrusters fired.
Separating from space dock.
The fleet's cleared space dock, captain.
All ships ready for warp.
- Set course for Vulcan.
- Aye-aye, captain.
Course laid in.
Maximum warp. Punch it.
- Lieutenant, where's helmsmen McKenna?
- He has lung worms sir.
He couldn't report to his post.
- I'm Hikaru Sulu.
- And you are a pilot, right?
Very much so, sir. I'm ...
I'm not sure what's wrong here.
Is the parking brake on?
No.
I figured it out, I'm just...
Have you disengaged the external
inertial dampener?
- Ready for warp, sir.
- Let's punch it.
- Where are we?
- Medical bay.
- This isn't worth it.
- A little suffering's good for the soul.
Hi, how are you?
- My mouth is itchy. Is that normal?
- Well, those symptoms won't last long.
- I'm going to give you a mild sedative.
- Oh, I wish I didn't know you.
Don't be such an infant.
How long is it supposed to...
Unbelievable.
Engines at maximum warp captain.
Russian whiz kid, what's your name?
Cheikov? Chirpov?
- Ensign Chekov, Pavel Andrejevic, sir.
- Fine.
Chekov, Pavel Andrejevic,
begin ship wide mission broadcast.
Yes, sir. Happy to.
Ensign authorization code
95 Wictor Wictor 2.
Authorization not recognized.
Ensign authorization code
95 Victor Victor 2.
Access granted.
May I have your attention please.
At 22:00, telemetry detected an anomaly
in the neutral zone.
What appeared to be a lightning
storm in space.
Soon after, Starfleet received a distress
signal from the Vulcan high command
that their planet was experiencing
seismic activity.
Our mission is to assess the
condition of Vulcan
and assist in evacuations
if necessary.
We should be arriving at Vulcan within
3 minutes. Thank you for your time.
Lightning storm.
Aah Jim, you're awake. How do you feel?
- Good God, man!
- What? Aah!
- What the hell's this?
- A reaction to the vaccine. Damn it.
Nurse Chapel, I need 50cc
of cortisone.
Yes, sir.
May I ... Appeared to be
a lightning storm in space.
We've gotta stop the ship.
Jim. I'm not kidding. You need
to keep your heart rate down.
Computer, locate crew member Uhura.
I haven't seen a reaction this
severe since medical school.
- We're flying into a trap!
- Damn it, Jim! Stand still.
Stop it!
- Uhura.
- Kirk. What are you doing here?
Transmission from the Klingon prison
planet, what exactly did it say?
- Oh my God, what's wrong with your hands?
- Who is responsible for the Klingon attack?
- Was the ship Romu...?
- Was the ship what?
- What's happening to my mouth?
- You got numb tongue?
- Numb tongue?!
- I can fix that.
- Was the ship what?
- Romulan.
- What?
- Romulan? - Yeah.
- Yes. - Yeah!
Prod Nero seven Federation
ships are on their way.
- Jim!
- What's going on?
- Jim, come back.
- Captain!
Captain Pike, sir, we have to stop the ship.
Kirk, how the hell did you get
on board the Enterprise?
- Captain, this man is under the influence of a
severe reaction to a vaccine. - Bones, plea...
... He's completely delusional ...
Vulcan is not a experiencing a natural disaster,
it's being attacked by Romulans.
Romulans? Cadet Kirk, I think you've
had enough attention for one day
McCoy, take him back to medical.
We'll have words later.
- Aye captain.
- Sir, that same anomaly ...
Mr. Kirk is not cleared to be
aboard this vessel, captain...
Look, I get it, you're a great ...
I'd love to do it again with you soon ...
- I can remove the cadet ...
- Try it!
This cadet is trying to save the bridge!
By recommending a full stop mid-warp
doing a rescue mission?
It's not a rescue mission.
Listen to me. It's an attack.
Based on what facts?
That same anomaly,
a lightning storm in space
that we saw today, also occurred
on the day of my birth.
Before a Romulan ship attacked
the USS Kelvin.
You know that, sir.
I've read your dissertation.
That ship, which had formidable and
advanced weaponry
was never seen or heard from again.
The Kelvin attacked a place on
the edge of Klingon space.
And at 23:00 last night
there was an attack.
47 Klingon war birds destroyed
by Romulans, sir.
And it was reported that the Romulans
were in one ship, one massive ship.
And you know of this Klingon attack how?
Sir, I intercepted and translated
the message myself.
- Kirk's report is accurate.
- We're warping into a trap, sir.
The Romulans are waiting for us.
I promise you that.
The cadet's logic is sound.
And lt. Uhura's is unmatched in xenolinguistics.
We would be wise to accept her conclusion.
Scan Vulcan space. Check for
any transmissions in Romulan.
Sir, I'm not sure I can distinguish the
Romulan language from Vulcan.
What about you?
Do you speak Romulan, cadet?
Uhura. All 3 dialects, sir.
- Uhura, relieve the lieutenant.
- Yes, sir.
Hannity, hail the USS Truman.
All the other ships are out of warp
sir and have arrived at Vulcan,
but we seem to have lost all contact.
Sir, I pick up no Romulan transmission
or transmission of any kind in the area.
It's because they're being attacked.
Shields up. Red alert.
Arrival at Vulcan
in 5 seconds.
4 ... 3 .... 2 ...
- Emergency evasives.
- Running, sir.
- Damage report.
- Deflector shields are holding.
All stations.
Engineering, Olson, report.
Full reverse. Come about starboard, 90°.
Drop us down underneath them, Sulu.
- Sir, there's another Federation ship.
- Destroy it too.
Fire torpedoes.
Captain, they're locking torpedoes.
Divert auxiliary power from port
nossel to forward shields.
- Sulu, status report.
- Shields at 32%.
Their weapons are powerful, sir.
We can't take another hit like that.
- Get me Starfleet command.
- Captain.
The Romulan ship has lowered some
kind of high energy pulse device
into the Vulcan atmosphere.
It's signal appears to be blocking our
communications and transporter abilities.
All power to forward shields.
Prepare to fire all weapons.
Weapons ready.
Wait!
- Gohol, magnify!
- Yes, sir.
Captain, we're being hailed.
Hello.
I am the captain Christopher Pike.
To whom am I speaking?
Hi Christopher. I am Nero.
You've declared war against the Federation.
Withdraw
and I'll agree to arrange a conference with
Romulan leadership at a neutral location.
I do not speak for the Empire.
We stand apart.
As does your Vulcan crew member.
Isn't that right, Spock?
Pardon me, I do not believe that
you and I are acquainted.
No, we're not.
Not yet.
Spock, there's something I
would like you to see.
Captain Pike, your transporter
has been disabled.
As you can see, by the rest of
the armada, you have no choice.
You will man a shuttle. Come aboard
the Narada for negotiations.
That is all.
- They’ll kill you, you know that.
- Your survival is unlikely.
Captain, we gain nothing
by diplomacy.
Going over to that ship is a mistake.
- I too agree. You should rethink your strategy.
- I understand that.
I need officers who've been trained in
advanced hand to hand combat.
I have training, sir.
Come with me.
Kirk, you too. You're not supposed
to be here anyway.
- Chekov, you have the con.
- Aye, Captain.
Prepare the red matter.
Yes, sir.
Without transporters we can't beam off the ship.
We can't assist Vulcan.
We can't do our job.
Mr. Kirk, Mr. Sulu and engineer Olson
will space-jump from the shuttle.
You will land on that machine
they've lowered into the atmosphere
that's scrambling our gear. You'll get
inside, you'll disable it
then you'll beam back to the ship.
Mr. Spock, I'm leaving you in
command of the Enterprise.
Once we have transport capability
and communication back up
you'll contact Starfleet and report
what the hell's going on here.
And if all else fails, fall back
and rendezvous with the fleet
in the Laurentian system.
Kirk, I'm promoting you to first officer.
- What?
- Captain?
Please, I apologize. The complexities
of Human pranks escape me.
It's not a prank, Spock.
And I am not the captain, you are.
Let's go.
Sir, after we knock out that drill,
what happens to you?
I guess you have to come and get me.
Careful with the ship, Spock.
She's brand new.
- Dr. Puri, report.
- It's McCoy.
Doctor Puri was on deck 6.
He's dead.
Then you have just inherited his
responsibility as chief medical officer.
Yeah, tell me something I don't know.
Shuttle 89, USS Enterprise, you are clear ...
- You've got the charges, right?
- Oh yeah.
Can't wait to kick some Romulan ass.
- Yeah.
- Oh yeah.
So what kind of combat training do you have?
Fencing.
Pre-jump.
Shuttle commander, you are clear
from USS Enterprise ...
Gentlemen, we're approaching the drop zone.
You have one shot
to land on that platform.
They may have defenses, so pull your chute
as late as possible.
3 ... 2 ... 1.
Remember, the Enterprise won't be able to
beam you back until you've turned off that drill.
Good luck.
Away team is entering the atmosphere, sir.
20 000 m.
Approaching the platform
at 5 800 m.
Kirk to Enterprise.
Distance to target 5 000 m.
4 600 m from the platform.
4 100 m to target.
4 000 m.
3 000 m.
2 000 m.
Pull the chute.
- 2 000 m.
- Pull your chute, Olson.
No, not yet. Not yet.
- 1 500 m.
- Open the chute!
- Olson, pull your chute!
- 1 000 m.
Olson!
Olson is gone, sir.
Kirk has landed, sir.
Gimme your hand.
Olson had the charges.
I know.
- What do we do?
- This.
The jamming signal's gone. Transport
abilities are reestablished.
Transporter control is reengaged sir.
Check all gravitational sensors. I wanna
know what they were doing to the planet.
Aye, Commander. Captain. Sorry, captain.
The drill's been sabotaged sir but
we have reached the planet's core.
Launch red matter.
Kirk to Enterprise. They just launched something
at the planet through the hole they just drilled.
- Do you copy Enterprise?
- Yes, sir.
Captain, gravitational sensors
are off the scale.
If my calculations are correct,
they're creating a singularity
... that will consume the planet.
They're creating a black hole
at the center of Vulcan?
Yes.
How long does the planet have?
Minutes, sir. Minutes.
Alert Vulcan command center to
signal a planet wide evacuation
all channels, all frequencies.
-Wait. - Maintain standard orbit.
Yes, sir.
Where are you going?
To evacuate the Vulcan High Council.
Their task is to protect our cultural history,
- My parents will be among them.
- Can't you beam them out?
That is impossible. They will
be in the Katric ark.
I must get them myself.
- Chekov, you have the con.
- Aye.
Kirk to Enterprise.
Beam us out of here.
Stand by, locking on your signal.
- Retract the drill. Let's move out
- Yes, sir.
Fold up.
I can't lock on to them. Don't move.
Don't move!
Sulu.
Hold on.
I've gotcha.
Now pull my chute.
Kirk to Enterprise!
We're falling without a chute!
- Beam us up!
- I'm sorry I can't lock on to your signal.
- You're moving too fast.
I can do that. I can do that!
- Take the con.
- Aye, sir.
The black hole's expanding. We won't reach
minimum safe distance if we don't leave immediately.
Move. Move... I can do that.
I can do that. Move. Move...
Give me manual control, I can lock on.
Beam us up!
- Enterprise, where are you?
- Hold on. Hold on! Hold on!
Now! Now! Now! Do it now!
Now! Now! Now!
Hold on. Hold on. Compensating
gravitational pull. Aaand...
Gotcha.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Clear the pad. I'm beaming to
the surface.
The surface of what?
What, you're going down there?
Are you nuts?
- Spock, you can't do that.
- Energize.
- Spock? - The planet has only
seconds left. We must evacuate.
Mother, now.
Spock to Enterprise.
Get us out now.
Locking on to you. Don't move.
Stay right where you are.
Transport in 5 ... 4 ... 3 ... 2 ...
- Mother!
- I'm losing her! I'm losing her! ...
I've lost her! I've lost her.
Acting captain's log, star date 2258.42.
We have had no word from captain Pike.
I have therefore classified him a hostage
of the war criminal known as Nero
Nero, who has destroyed my home planet
and most of its 6 billion inhabitants.
While the essence of our culture has been saved
in the elders who now reside upon this ship ...
I estimate no more than
10 000 have survived.
I am now a member of
an endangered species.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What do you need.
Tell me. Tell me.
I need everyone ...
- ... to continue performing admirably.
- OK.
You must have a lot of questions for me.
I only have one for you.
I need the subspace frequencies of
Starfleet's border protection grids.
Specifically those surrounding Earth.
Christopher, answer my question.
No, you answer for the genocide you just
committed against a peaceful planet.
No, I prevented genocide.
In my time, where I come from,
this is a simple mining vessel.
I chose a life of honest labor.
to provide for myself and the wife
who was expecting my child.
I was off planet doing my job
while your Federation did nothing.
And allowed my people to burn
while their planet broke in half.
And Spock, he didn't help us.
He betrayed us.
No, no... you're confused. You're misinformed.
Romulus hasn't been destroyed.
It's out there right now. You're blaming the
Federation for something that hasn't happened...
It has happened! I watched it happen!
I saw it happen!
Don't tell me it didn't happen!
And when I lost her.
I promised myself retribution.
And for 25 years I planned my
revenge against the Federation.
And forgot what it was like to
live a normal life.
I did not forget the pain.
It's a pain that every surviving
Vulcan now shares.
My purpose, Christopher,
is to not simply avoid the destruction
of the home that I love
but to create a Romulus that
exists free of the Federation.
You see only then will she be truly saved.
That is why I will destroy all the
remaining Federation planets.
Starting with yours.
Then we have nothing left to discuss.
You will give me the frequencies to
disable Earth's defenses.
Centaurian slugs. They latch
on to your brain stem...
and release a toxin that will
force you to answer.
Frequencies please, sir.
Christopher Pike, captain of
the USS Enterprise ...
As you wish.
Have you confirmed that Nero
is heading for Earth?
Their trajectory suggests no
other destination, captain.
Thank you, lt.
Earth may be his next stop, but
we have to assume
every Federation planet's a target
Out of the chair.
Well, if the Federation is the target,
why didn't they destroy us?
Why would they? Why waste a weapon?
We obviously weren't a threat.
That is not it. He said he wanted me to see
something. The destruction of my home planet.
How the hell did they do that, by the way?
And where did the Romulans get
that kind of weaponry?
The engineering comprehension necessary
to artificially create a black hole
may suggest an answer.
Such technology could theoretically
be manipulated
to create a tunnel through space-time.
Damn it man, I am a doctor, not physicist.
Are you actually suggesting
they're from the future?
If you eliminate the impossible, what ever
remains, however improbable
must be the truth.
How poetic.
Then what would an angry future
Romulan want with captain Pike?
As captain he does know details
of Starfleet's defenses.
What we need to do is catch
up to that ship,
disable it, take it over and get Pike back.
We are technologically outmatched in every
way. A rescue attempt would be illogical.
Nero's ship would have to drop
out of warp for us to overtake it.
Then what about assigning engineering
crews to try and boost our warp yield?
Remaining power and crew are being
used to repair radiation leaks
on the lower decks. The damage ...
- OK. All right. All right. - ...communications.
Without it... - There's got to be some way.
- ...we cannot contact Starfleet. We
must gather with the rest of Starfleet.
To balance the terms of the next engagement,
- There won't be a next engagement.
By the time we gather it'll be too late.
Look, you say he's from the future and
knows what's gonna happen
then the logical thing is to be unpredictable.
You're assuming that Nero knows
how event's are predicted to unfold.
The contrary. Nero's very presence
has altered the flow of history
beginning with the attack on the USS Kelvin,
culminating with the events of today,
thereby creating an entire new chain of incidents
that cannot be anticipated by either party.
An alternate reality.
Precisely.
Whatever our lives might have been
if the time continuum was disrupted
our destinies have changed.
Mr. Sulu, plot a course for the
Laurentian system. Warp factor 3.
Spock, don't do that.
Running back to the rest of the fleet for
a con fab is a massive waste of time...
These orders were issued by
captain Pike when he left.
He also ordered us to go back and get him.
- Spock, you are captain now. You have...
- I am aware of my responsibilities ...
Every second we waste Nero's
getting closer to his next target.
That is correct and why I'm instructing
you to accept the fact that I'm...
I will not allow us to go backwards...
... instead of hunting Nero down.
Security, escort him out.
- No.
- Jim!
Get him off this ship.
Computer, where am I?
Location: Delta Vega.
Class M planet. Unsafe.
There is a Starfleet outpost 14km
to the northwest.
- Remain in your pod ...
- Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
Star date 2258.42.
... for ... for ... Whatever.
Acting captain Spock has
marooned me on Delta Vega.
What I believe to be a violation
of security protocol 49.09
governing the treatment of prisoners
aboard a starship.
James T. Kirk.
- Excuse me?
- How did you find me?
How do you know my name?
I have been and always shall be your friend.
Look, I don't know you.
I am Spock.
Bullshit.
It is remarkably pleasing to see
you again old friend.
Especially after the events today.
Sir, I appreciate what you did for me today
but if you were Spock, you'd know
we're not friends at all.
You hate me. You marooned
me here for mutiny.
- Mutiny?
- Yes.
You are not the captain?
No, no... You're the captain.
Pike was taken hostage.
By Nero?
What do you know about him?
He is a particularly troubled Romulan.
Please. Allow me.
It will be easier.
- Whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
- Our minds, one and together.
129 years from now, a star will explode
and threaten to destroy the galaxy.
That is where I'm from Jim.
The future.
A star went supernova.
Consuming everything in its path.
I promised the Romulans that I
will save their planet.
We outfitted our fastest ship.
Using red matter I would create a black hole
which would absorb the exploding star.
I was on root when the unthinkable happened.
The supernova destroyed Romulus.
I had little time.
I had to extract the red matter
and shoot it into the supernova.
As I began my return trip I was intercepted.
- He called himself Nero,
- ... collapse of Romulan Empire.
In my attempt to escape, both of
us were pulled into the black hole.
Nero went through first.
He was the first to arrive.
Nero spent the next 25 years
awaiting my arrival.
But what was years for Nero
was only seconds for me.
I went through the black hole.
Nero was waiting for me.
He held me responsible for the
loss of his world.
He captured my vessel and spared my life.
For one reason. So that
I would know his pain.
He beamed me here so that
I can observe his vengeance.
As he was helpless to save his planet
I would be helpless to save mine.
Billions of lives lost because of me, Jim.
Because I failed.
Forgive me. Emotional transference
is an effect of the mind meld.
- So you do feel.
- Yes.
Going back in time you changed all our lives.
Jim! We must go.
There is a Starfleet outpost not far from here.
Wait.
Where you came from ...
... did I know my father?
Yes.
You often spoke of him as being
your inspiration for joining Starfleet.
He proudly lived to see you become
captain of the Enterprise.
Captain?
A ship we must return you to
as soon as possible.
- Warp 3, sir.
- Course 151-3.
- Laurentian system, sir.
- Thank you gentlemen.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes. Doctor.
I am aware that James Kirk is a friend of yours.
I recognize that supporting me
as you did must have been difficult.
Is that thank you?
- I am simply acknowledging your difficulties.
- Permission to speak freely, sir.
- I welcome it.
- Do you?
Ok then. Are you out of your Vulcan mind?
Are you making a logical choice sending
Kirk away? Probably. But the right one?
Back home we've got a saying. If you're
gonna ride in the Kentucky derby
you don't leave your prize stallion in the stable
A curious metaphor, Doctor,
as a stallion must first be broken
before it can reach its potential.
My God man. You could at least
act like it was a hard decision.
I intend to insist in the effort to reestablish
communication with Starfleet.
However, if crew moral is better served
by my roaming the halls weeping
I would gladly defer to your medical expertise.
Excuse me.
Green blooded little goblin.
What?
You realize how unacceptable this is?
- Fascinating.
- What?
I am sure you're just doing your job, but
could you not come a wee bit sooner?
Six months I've been here. Living off Starfleet
botty nips and a promise of a good meal.
And I know exactly what's going on here.
Ok? Punishment, isn't it? Ongoing. For
something that was clearly an accident.
- You are Montgomery Scott.
- You know him?
Yeah, it's me. You're in the right place.
Unless there’s another hard working
equally starved Starfleet officer around.
- Me.
- Getup, shut up.
You aren't doing anything. You can
eat, like, a bean and you're done.
I'm talking about food, real food.
But you're here now. So, thank you.
Where is it?
You are in fact a Mr. Scott who postulated
the theory of transwarp beaming?
That's what I'm talking about.
How'd ya think I wound up here?
I had a little debate with my instructor
on the issue of relativistic physics and
how it pertains to subspace travel.
He seemed to think that the range of
transporting something like a grapefruit
was limited to about a 100 miles.
I told him that I could not only beam a
grapefruit from one planet to the adjacent planet
in the same system, which is easy by the way
I could do it with a life form.
So, I tested it on admiral Archer's prize beagle.
I know that dog. What happened to it?
I'll tell you when it reappears. I don't
know. I do feel guilty about that.
What if I told you that your transwarp theory was correct?
That it is indeed possible to beam onto
a ship that is travelling at warp speed?
I think that if that equation had been
discovered I'd have heard about it.
The reason you haven't
heard of it, Mr. Scott,
is because you haven't discovered it yet.
- Are you from the future?
- He is. I'm not.
Well that's brilliant. Do they still
have sandwiches there?
Well, she's a wee bit dodgy.
Shield emitters are totally bum jacked
as well as a few other things.
In you go.
So, the Enterprise has had it's
maiden voyage, has it?
She is one well endowed lady.
I'd like to get my hands on her ample nossels,
if you'd pardon the engineering parlance.
Except, the thing is, even if I believed you.
Where you're from, what I've done...
Which I don't, by the way. We're still
talking about beaming aboard the Enterprise
while she's travelling faster than light
without a proper receiving pad.
Get off there. It's not a climbing frame.
The notion of transwarp beaming
is like trying to hit a bullet with a smaller bullet
whilst wearing a blindfold, riding a horse.
What's that?
Your equation for achieving transwarp beaming.
You're out of it...
Imagine that. It never occurred to me to
think of space as the thing that was moving
You're coming with us, right?
No, Jim. That is not my destiny.
Your destiny ...
He. The other Spock is not gonna believe me.
Only you can explain what the hell has happened.
Under no circumstances can he be made aware
of my existence. You must promise me that.
So you're telling me I can't tell you that I'm following
you're own orders. Why not? What happens?
Jim, this is one rule you cannot break.
To stop Nero, you alone must
take command of your ship.
How? Over your dead body?
Preferably, not.
However, there is Starfleet regulation 619.
619 states that any command officer who is
emotionally compromised by the mission at hand
must resign command.
So, you're saying that I have to
emotionally compromise you... guys?
Jim, I just lost my planet.
I can tell you, I am emotionally compromised.
What you must do is get me to show it.
Aye then lady. Live or die.
Let's get this over with.
You cannot come with me. Go on.
Coming back in time, changing history,
that's cheating.
A trick I learned from an old friend.
Live long and prosper.
Mr. Scott?
Mr. Scott, can you hear me?
Hold on a second.
No. No!
RELEASE VALVE.
Purifier release valve activated.
You all right? You all right?
My head's buzzing and I'm soaked,
but otherwise I'm fine.
Captain Spock, detecting unauthorized
access to water turbine control board
Bring up the video.
Security, seal the engineering deck.
We have intruders in turbine section 3.
Set phasers to stun.
Halt!
Come with me
cupcake!
Who are you?
- I am with him.
- He's with me.
We are travelling at warp speed. How
did you manage to beam aboard this ship?
You're the genius, you figure it out.
As acting captain of this vessel
I order you to answer the question.
Well I'm not telling, acting captain.
What now? That doesn't frustrate you, does it? My
lack of cooperation, that doesn't make you angry?
- Are you a member of Starfleet?
- Yes. Can I get a towel?
Under penalty of court martial I order
you to explain to me how you were able
to beam aboard the ship while moving at warp
- Well.
- Don't answer him.
You will answer me.
- I'd rather not take sides.
- What is it with you, Spock?
Your planet was just destroyed, your
mother murdered, and you're not even upset.
If you are presuming that these
experiences in any way impede
my ability to command this ship
you are mistaking.
And yet you were the one who said
fear was necessary for command.
I mean, did you his ship?
Did you see what he did?
- Yes, of course I did.
- So are you afraid or aren't you?
I will not allow you to lecture me
about the merits of emotion.
- Then why don't you stop me?
- Step away from me Mr. Kirk.
What is it like not to feel anger?
Or heartbreak?
Or the need to stop at nothing to avenge the
death of the woman who gave birth to you.
- Back away from me.
- You feel nothing!
It must not even compute for you.
You never loved her!
Spock.
Doctor, I am no longer fit for duty.
I relinquish my command based on the fact
that I have been emotionally compromised.
Please note the time and
date in the ship's log.
I like this ship.
You know it's exciting.
Well congratulations, Jim. Now we've got
no captain and no God damn first officer
to replace him.
Yeah we do.
- What?
- Pike made him first officer.
- You've gotta be kidding me.
- Thanks for the support.
I sure hope you know what you're
doing, captain.
So do I.
Attention, crew of the Enterprise,
this is James Kirk.
Mr. Spock has resigned commission
and advanced me to acting captain.
I know you're all expecting a regroup with the fleet,
but I'm ordering a pursuit course
of the enemy ship to Earth.
I want all departments at battle
stations and ready in 10 minutes.
Either we're going down or they are.
Kirk out.
Speak your mind Spock.
That would be unwise.
What is necessary is never unwise.
I am as conflicted as I once was as a child.
You will always be a child of two worlds.
I am grateful for this.
And for you.
I feel anger for the one who took mother's life.
An anger I cannot control.
I believe, as she would say ...
... do not try to.
You asked me once why I married your mother.
I married her because I loved her.
Whatever the case we need to
get aboard Nero's ship undetected.
Just can't just go in there guns blazing, Jim.
I'm telling you to ...
- Captain Kirk. Captain Kirk.
- Yes, Chekov. What is it?
Based on the Nerada’s course
from Vulcan
I have projected that Nero will
travel pass Saturn.
Like you said we need to stay
invisible to Nero or he'll destroy us.
If Mr. Scott can get us to warp factor 4
and if we drop out of warp behind one
of Saturn's moons, say Titan.
The magnetic distortion from
the planet's rings
will make us invisible to Nero's sensors.
From there, as long as the drill
is not activated
we can beam aboard the enemy ship.
Aye, that might work.
- Wait a minute kid, how old are you?
- 17, sir.
Oh good, he's 17.
Doctor.
Mr. Chekov is correct. I can
confirm his telemetry.
If Mr. Sulu is able to maneuver us into position
I can beam aboard Nero's ship,
steal back the black hole device
and if possible bring back captain Pike.
I won't allow you to do that Mr. Spock.
Romulans and Vulcans
share a common ancestry.
Our cultural similarities will make it easier
for me to access the ship's computer
and locate the device.
Also my mother was human. Which
makes Earth the only home I have left.
I'm coming with you.
I would cite regulation, but
I know you will simply ignore it.
See? We are getting to know each other.
Prepare the drill.
All stop in 3 ... 2 ... 1.
Gimme 1/4 impulse burst for 5 seconds.
I'll do the rest with thrusters.
On my mark.
Aye.
Fire.
Transporter room. We are in
position above Titan.
Really? Fine job Mr. Sulu, well done.
- How are we Scotty?
- Unbelievably sir. The ship is in position.
Whatever happens Mr. Sulu, if you
think you have the tactical advantage
you fire on that ship even if we're still
on board. That's an order.
Yes, sir.
Otherwise we'll contact the Enterprise
when we're ready to be beamed back.
Good luck.
- I will be back.
- You better be.
- I'll be monitoring your frequency.
- Thank you, Nyota.
- So her first name's Nyota?
- I have no comment on the matter.
Oky doky then. If there’s any common
sense in the design of the enemy's ship
I should be putting you somewhere in the
cargo bay, shouldn't be a soul in site.
Energize.
Captain, we have Starfleet officers
aboard the ship.
- One of them is Vulcan.
- No.
Ayel!
- I'll cover ya.
- Are you certain?
Yeah, I've gotcha.
Do you know where it is?
The black hole device?
And captain Pike.
Move.
They have activated the drill.
Communication and transportation are inoperative.
Sulu, please tell me you have them.
Otherwise we won't be
able to beam them back.
Kirk and Spock are on their own now.
I foresee a complication. The design of this ship
is far more advanced than I have anticipated.
Voice print and face recognition
analysis enabled.
Welcome back ambassador Spock.
That's weird.
Computer, what is your manufacturing origin?
Star date 2387. Commissioned by the
Vulcan Science Academy.
It appears that you have been keeping
important information from me.
You'll be able to fly this thing, right?
Something tells me I already have.
- Good luck.
- Jim.
The statistical likelihood that our
plan will succeed is less than 4,3%.
I will work.
In the event that I don't return
please tell lt. Uhura ...
Spock, it'll work.
Fascinating.
Startup sequence initiated.
Nero, order your men to disable
the drill or I will ...
I know your face from Earth's history.
James T. Kirk was considered
to be a great man.
He went on to captain the USS
Enterprise. But that was another life.
A life I will deprive you of just like
I did your father.
Captain Nero. The Vulcan ship's been
taken. The drill has been destroyed.
Spock! Spock!
- Open a channel.
- Yes, sir.
Spock, I knew I should have
killed you when I had the chance.
I hereby confiscate this illegally
obtained ship
and order you to surrender your
vessel. No terms.
That ship ... take it out.
- Sir, if you ignite the red matter..
- I want the Spock dead now!
- He went to warp.
- Go after him.
Yes, sir.
Your species is even weaker
than I expected.
You can't even speak.
What?
I got your gun.
What's he doing?
Ambassador Spock, you are
on a collision course.
Fire everything.
Incoming missiles. If the ship is hit,
the red matter will be ignited.
Understood.
Captain, I've picked up another ship.
- What are you doing here?
- Following orders.
Enterprise now!
Nice timing Scotty.
I've never beamed three people
from two targets
onto one pad before.
- Jim. - Bones.
-I've got him.
That was pretty good.
Captain, the enemy ship is loosing
power. They're shields are down.
- Hail them now.
- Aye.
This is captain James T. Kirk
of the USS Enterprise.
Your ship is compromised. You're
too close to the singularity
to survive without assistance
which we are willing to provide.
Captain, what are you doing?
Showing them compassion may be the only way
to make peace with Romulus, Spock.
It's logical, Spock.
Thought you'd like that.
No, not really. Not this time.
I would rather suffer the end of
Romulus a thousand times,
I would rather die in agony than
accept assistance from you.
You've got it.
Arm phasers. Fire everything we've got.
Yes, sir.
- Sulu, let's go home.
- Yes, sir.
- Why aren't we at warp?
- We are, sir.
Kirk to engineering.
Get us out of here, Scotty.
You bet your ass captain.
Captain, we're caught in
the gravity well. It's got us.
Go to maximum warp. Push it!
I'm giving it all she's got captain.
All she's got isn't good enough.
What else you got?
Ok, if we eject the core and detonate
the blast could be enough to push us away.
I can't promise anything though.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
- Clear the area. Go!
- Yes, sir.
Father?
I am not our father.
There are so few Vulcans left we
cannot afford to ignore each other.
Then why did you send Kirk aboard when
you alone could have explained the truth?
Because you needed each other.
I could not deprive you of the revelation
of all that you can accomplish together.
Of a friendship that will define you both.
In ways you cannot yet realize.
How'd you persuade him to
keep your secret?
He inferred that universe
ending paradoxes would ensue
should he break his promise.
You lied?
- Oh. I implied.
- A gamble?
An act of faith.
One I hope you will repeat in
the future in Starfleet.
In the face of extinction it is only
logical I resign my Starfleet commission
and help rebuild our race.
And yet you can be in two places at once.
I urge you to remain in Starfleet.
I've already located a suitable planet
on which to establish a Vulcan colony.
Spock, in this case do yourself a favor
put aside logic, do what feels right.
Since my customary farewell
would appear awfully self serving
I shall simply say good luck.
This assembly calls captain
James Tiberius Kirk.
Your inspirational valor and supreme
dedication to your comrades
is in keeping with the highest
traditions of service.
And reflect at most credit to yourself,
your crew and the Federation.
It is my honor to award you
with this commendation.
By Starfleet order 28455, you are
hereby directed to report to admiral Pike
USS Enterprise, for duty as his relief.
I relieve you, sir.
I am relieved.
- Thank you, sir.
- Congratulations, captain.
Your father would be proud of you.
Thrusters on full.
Firing thrusters and impulse
engines at your command, sir.
Weapon systems and shields on standby.
Dock control reports ready, captain.
Bones.
Buckle up.
Scotty, how we doin'?
Dilithium chambers at maximum captain.
Get down!
Mr. Sulu, prepare to engage thrusters.
Permission to come aboard, captain.
Permission granted.
As you have yet to select a first officer,
respectfully I would like to submit
my candidacy.
Should you desire I can provide
character references.
It would be my honor commander.
Maneuvering thrusters Mr. Sulu.
- Thrusters on standby.
- Take us out.
Aye aye, captain.
SPACE, THE FINAL FRONTIER
THESE ARE THE VOYAGES OF
THE STARSHIP ENTERPRISE
HER ONGOING MISSION: TO
EXPLORE STRANGE NEW WORLDS,
TO SEEK OUT NEW LIFE FORMS
AND NEW CIVILISATIONS
TO BOLDLY GO WHERE NOONE
HAS GONE BEFORE.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org