Ladies and gentlemen,
Christopher Wilde!
Every girl, every boy
They got your posters on their walls
Photographs, autographs
Soon as you step out the door
You will meet the applause
Yeah!
Paparazzis hiding in the bushes
Trying to make a dollar
Wanna be you, when they see you
They scream out loud
Starstruck, camera flashes
Cover of magazines
Starstruck, designer sunglasses
Living the dream as a teen
Driving fancy cars
Hollywood Boulevard
Hear the crowd
calling your name, yeah!
Starstruck!
Prepare to get...
All right!
Yeah!
Starstruck
Yeah! Yay-yeah!
As soon as you move
They gonna talk about it
In the paper, the news
'Cause you're on the A-list
You better believe it
You better believe it, yeah...
I just love Christopher Wilde.
'Cause you're in the top spot
And nothing can stop ya
Jessica!
Oh, I'm sorry, Sara.
Am I blocking your view
of what's his name?
Move it or lose it, sister.
Sara, Jessica. Suitcases.
Come pick out your clothes
and get packed.
We're leaving for the airport
right after school tomorrow.
In less than 2 4 hours,
I'll be in Los Angeles
where Christopher lives.
What if he picks me up at the airport?
Why would he do that?
I'm an original member of his fan club.
I follow his minute-by-minute
blog posts,
and I text him every day.
Trust me, he wants to meet me.
ls it too late for me to be an only child?
-Yes.
-Then can I please stay home?
-No.
-Why not?
Because your grandmother
hasn't seen you in two years.
Plus, you're a minor and it's illegal.
Everybody...
There's more about Christopher.
The fabulous Christopher Wilde
picked up six
Music Association Awards last night,
just in time for his new CD,
Real Wilde,
to drop, wow, double platinum.
I caught up with our favourite pop star
on the red carpet.
Well, first I'd love to say
thank you so much
for buying the records
and coming to my concerts.
You're the reason I love what I do.
You guys are the best fans
in the world. Thank you.
He is such an amazing person.
He's definitely not amazing.
He is amazing.
And if you knew him like I know him,
you wouldn't say that.
Hello? We live in Michigan.
You don't know him.
But I do.
I know everything about him.
I know where he works,
eats,
shops,
surfs,
and parties.
-You ready to party?
-Absolutely.
Well, let's do it!
You know, out of all of your cars,
Angelina's my favourite.
-Angelina?
-Yeah. I mean, look at her.
Hey, does that new valet
look a little shifty to you?
-No. Not really.
-He looks a little shifty to me.
Come on, Stubby.
Let's find you a real girl.
That is a real girl.
Oh, wow. Look who it is.
Christopher Wilde's girlfriend,
the fantabulous,
fabulous Alexis Bender!
-Hi, sweetie.
-Hi.
-Stubby.
-Yeah.
You look beautiful tonight.
I know. Wait until you see
what I'm wearing tomorrow.
-Tomorrow?
My birthday?
Baby, you promised
you were gonna sing.
Right. Hey, I'll be there. Absolutely.
Okay. Wait.
-Something's wrong.
-Yeah, you're here.
What? lt's guys' night out!
Where are the paparazzi?
Oh, you did not blog again, did you?
There he is. Let's run.
That's so weird. Hi.
-Look right here.
-Just like that.
All right, back-back up, guys. Back...
Back up! Back up!
Okay, back up, back up,
back up, back up, back up!
-Come on.
-What? Calm down.
You're not invited.
Everybody's invited, Sara.
lt's an all-school dance.
The operative word being ''dance.''
Embarrassing.
Don't worry. I'm just going there
to cover it for the school paper.
Are you bringing your camera
with you to California?
AJ, of course I am.
Because we still need pics
of Christopher Wilde!
Talking, walking, singing, dancing,
moving, breathing.
Why are you both
so hung up on this guy?
''This guy''?
-Now you see what I live with?
-Poor you.
Little sister, when we go to California,
you can play shuffleboard
with Grandma,
but I'm going to meet
Christopher Wilde.
And just how
are you planning to do that?
Well, we've mapped out
his every move for the past 1 8 months.
I know when and where he's likely to be
every second of every day.
About the time we leave
for Los Angeles,
he'll be having his daily meeting
with his managers.
-He's late.
-He'll be here.
You need to manage him better.
Hello, we both manage him.
He needs to know opportunities
like this don't come every day.
He knows. He's not a kid.
Yo. What's up?
-You're late.
-Sorry, Mom.
How you doing, Son?
Great, great. Excited.
Oh, honey, honey, honey.
You could have cleaned up a little bit.
What? I'm... I'm totally clean.
He looks like a street kid,
not a movie star.
He looks fine.
Just be yourself, Christopher.
All right.
He's here.
All right. This is it, bud.
Your chance
at what we've always wanted.
-Alan, please come in.
-Sherry. Daniel!
-Great place you got here.
-Actually it's Christopher's.
We just kind of work here.
-All right. Christopher Wilde.
-Hey, Mr Smith.
-My daughters are big fans of yours.
-Oh, great.
-Wow! This is great.
-Please.
I love this. I love this.
Rock and roll! Hello, Cleveland!
Awesome. Got this album at the house.
Girls love this.
Something Wilde.
All right, now let's get right to the point.
Let's get right to it.
l've been watching you
and I like what I see.
You are a talented, talented kid.
He's a talented kid.
You sing, you dance.
I hope you can act.
Because I like you for this movie.
Thank you, sir.
I mean, coming from you,
this would be such an honour to...
I mean, to work with someone...
But my people don't necessarily
agree with me.
See, all they see is a spoiled punk
who likes to tangle with the paparazzi.
Alan, you know how the tabloids are.
They manipulate those photos to...
Daniel, I get it. I get it.
Look, all I'm saying, kid,
is a chance like this
comes along once in a lifetime,
and I want to give you a shot,
but you have to prove that
you're a serious and committed actor.
How do I do that?
On Monday,
I'm gonna meet with my people,
try and sell them on you.
In the meantime,
you keep your face out of the tabloids.
No press, good or bad. Okay?
-l can do that.
-In fact, stay home.
-All right.
-Thank you, sir. I appreciate it.
You're such a dork.
You brought homework?
No. lt's called reading.
You should try it sometime.
What? I read.
This? lt's all pictures.
Don't touch that!
Gladly.
What's taking them so long?
Just get me a car already
so I can go meet Christopher Wilde.
Sara. You can't drive.
Yes, I can. Licence.
No, you can't. Sign.
''You must be at least
25-years-old to drive
''or rent a car from
Los Angeles Car Rental''?
What?
How am I supposed to do
what I wanna do?
And what would that be?
Take Jessica sightseeing.
Well, I think your grandma's
got a car you can borrow.
Sweet.
See what I mean? Mom, be careful!
Here comes the cavalry.
You could fall and break a hip.
Oh, now, Barbara. Calm down.
Howard had my back. Hi.
We take care of each other.
Okay then.
-Grandma!
-Jessica!
Oh, I'm so happy to see you.
-l've missed you so much.
-Ditto.
Sara. You can take her
for a spin if you want to.
Just gave her a tune-up.
She runs like a top.
Yeah, a super-ugly top
you'd never want to be seen in.
Does that mean
you'll be joining us for shuffleboard?
Sara out!
Grandma says stop pacing.
You're creating a draught.
I just got a call from AJ.
She just had a chat about a text
quoting a blog
about Christopher Wilde.
He's singing tonight
at Alexis Bender's birthday party.
I have to go!
Good luck
convincing Mom and Dad of that.
-Go with me.
-No.
They'll let me go if you go, too.
How many times do I have to say this?
I'm not interested in meeting
a stupid celebrity.
I mean, I am sick and tired
of Christopher Wilde.
-He's all you talk about.
-I'll shut up.
-What?
-lf you go with me,
and I meet Christopher Wilde,
I'll stop talking about him
for the rest of the trip.
How about the rest of your life?
Please?
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
What are you doing?
This is a no-parking zone.
When one person stays in the car,
it's not parking. lt's waiting.
We'll get a ticket.
Just get behind the wheel!
-Do it!
-Okay!
Every boy, every girl
They got your posters
on their wall, yeah!
I don't know about this, man.
-Nah, it'll be fine.
-We shouldn't even be here.
I mean, we should be at home,
chilling at that party
your parents are throwing.
Since when do you want
to party with my parents?
Are you kidding?
The caterer's from Argentina.
There's gonna be steak for dessert.
Tempting, but I promised Alexis
l'd sing at her birthday.
-I'm not going to let her down.
-You and your stupid friendship rules!
Yeah, they work for you, don't they?
Stay at my house for free,
eat my food, drive my cars...
Okay, okay.
And in return, you get to hang out
with myself, Albert J. Stubbins.
Best friend since fourth grade.
Yeah. Works for me, too, Stubs.
Let's do this.
He's here.
Just stay here.
Alexis! Baby! Happy Birthday.
-Where's Christopher?
-He couldn't make it.
-He's at home eating steak.
-Alexis, where's your boyfriend?
Come on. Let's go have some fun.
-Stubby!
-What?
I'm so sorry I'm late! Come on!
-Do you know her?
-Not yet.
Great. I'm gonna be here forever.
Thanks.
Looks like we pulled it off.
What would you do without me?
Our birthday girl in the VIP section,
Alexis Bender,
has a special guest tonight.
Christopher Wilde.
I knew it.
Excuse me.
No, you can't see me
No, you can't be me
You know I'm on my game
That's when I'm in my shades
See the cameras flashing
In the party and it's time for action
You're the main attraction
Hey, in my shades
Pull up to the spot looking hot
Everybody knows
Don't got no stress
and my haircut's fresh
So fly in my fancy clothes, yeah
They wanna take my picture
Watch out, those lights'll get ya
And they calling your name
That's when I'm putting on my frames
I tell 'em watch me now
Little mama, how ya like me now?
On the dance floor we can work it out
And bring this whole place down
Better stand up, hands up
B boy in my stance like and what?
So get on the floor
Show 'em what you came here for!
No, you can't see me
No, you can't be me
You know I'm on my game
That's when I'm in my shades
See the cameras flashing
In the party and it's time for action
You're the main attraction
Hey, in my shades
You wanna watch me, watch this
And when you watch TV, watch Chris
'Bout to have the whole place jumpin'
Cameras flash
and you know the bass bumpin'
Shades on like a rock star
And I'm bustin' out
the best moves so far
Feel the air from the speakers
So, so fresh from my hair
to my sneakers
Turn the beat up on the radio
I'm-a keep my frames on
till I'm ready go, go
Going gone I is
You ain't never
ever heard a song like this
If you ain't know, better get some ideas
Baby, you should holla
at ya boy right here
And if the girl wanna get crazed
You can find me in my shades
No, you can't see me
No, you can't be me
You know I'm on my game
That's when I'm in my shades
See the cameras flashing
In the party and it's time for action
You're the main attraction
Hey, in my shades
And as we're rolling up
on the midnight hour,
get ready for 55 minutes
of your favourite music.
And for those of you that haven't won
anything from us recently, stay tuned.
We got tickets to give away,
we got T-shirts, we got concerts.
Up next, some of your favourite music.
Happy birthday, Alexis.
Good night, everybody.
Excuse me. Move!
No. Oh, no!
Did I just hit you?
No, the door hit me by itself.
-This is not good.
-For you or for me?
'Cause right now
it feels a lot worse for me.
-This is really not good.
-Wait.
You're Chris...
I will give you front-row tickets
to my next concert
-if you don't scream my name.
-l don't want to see your stupid concert.
Okay. I need to get you to a doctor.
Come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
No, get this hand. This hand.
There we go. Come on. Just...
-What about Sara?
-Who's Sara?
My sister. She's up in the club.
-What happened?
-Look, help now. Questions later.
-Okay.
-Just get her in the car.
-Who is this?
-Seat belt.
-What is your name?
-Jessica.
Well, it's nice to meet you, Jessica.
I can think of nicer ways.
I'm not feeling too hot.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Do not hurl in Britney, okay?
-l just got her detailed.
-Okay.
Oh, no, those are my favourite shoes!
I'll buy you new ones. Door.
Keys. Just make sure
her sister Sara gets home okay.
Just don't tell anyone about this.
I got to get some new shoes!
Follow the light with your eyes.
Well, l've done a thorough exam,
and the CT scan was normal.
Everything looks good.
-So she's okay?
-Out.
There's no sign of head trauma,
and I'm absolutely certain
you don't have a concussion.
How come I threw up?
Maybe it was something you ate.
Or maybe it was a reaction
to meeting that doofus.
lt's a curtain, Sanjay. I can hear you.
No, no, you can't.
-You two know each other?
-Yeah. He's my sister's husband.
So I can go now?
Yes, but I want you to put an ice pack
on that bump until you get home.
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
-You gonna answer that?
-Oh, right. Just...
Hello, Mom? What?
Who?
Where?
Now?
Yes! Right now!
We thought he wasn't coming,
but he just showed up
with your two biggest fans.
Look, you promised him you were
gonna stay home this weekend.
lt's up to you to fix this, Christopher.
Okay. Just stall them.
I will be right there.
-Sherry!
-Alan!
Where is he?
-That might be a problem.
-Why?
My waiting room is filled with big guys
with big cameras.
You... The paparazzi found me?
Okay, Sanjay,
what kind of car you driving?
Nothing you'd be interested in.
I'm still paying off six years
of medical school.
-Perfect. How about a trade?
-No.
Only happens once.
Okay.
Are you sure this is safe?
I'm pretty sure.
-I'm pretty sure it's not!
-Just calm down, okay?
I don't wanna calm down!
I wanna go home! Okay?
-What is wrong with you?
-What's wrong with me?
Nothing. Nothing. I'm looking forward
to being grounded until I'm 30!
Oh, is that why you're so crabby?
-I'm not crabby!
-Not crabby. Defensive.
-l am not defensive.
-See?
You disagree with everything I say.
-Do not!
-Do, too!
-Just take me home!
-l will!
First we need to make one
teeny-tiny little stop.
You've got to be kidding.
-You live here?
-Yeah, why?
-Go, go. Let's go.
-What are you doing?
Got to go upstairs. Got to go.
-Stop pulling me!
-I'm sorry. I just...
Where are we going? Christopher!
-I'm sorry. I just don't know...
-Don't know where to hide me?
No, I'm not hiding you.
lt's just that I don't want these
particular people to see you right now.
And because I'm not a movie star.
No! Okay, because I don't want anyone
asking questions and neither do you.
Who is she? Where did you meet her?
Are you two dating?
-Dating?
-Yeah, they make stuff up. Come on.
The guestroom. Be my guest.
-Do I have a choice?
-Not really. I'll be right back.
Just stay.
Woof.
Good to see you.
I'm glad you came. Thanks for coming.
Hey! Hey, how are you?
So nice to see you.
Looking good, buddy.
-Hey. lt's about time.
-Hey, Mom.
-How you doing, bud?
-Good to see you.
-Christopher, my daughters.
-Oh, yeah. What's up?
I think they wanted to
ask you something.
-Yeah.
-Can you sing us a song?
Of course, absolutely.
l've got something new I'm working on.
-Can you grab me a stool?
-Sure, Chris.
-You know where your guitar is?
-Yeah. Of course.
You're gonna love this.
Hey, everybody.
This is a little something
I'm working on for my next album.
I hope you like it.
I'm no superman
I can't take your hand
And fly you anywhere
you wanna go, yeah
I can't read your mind
Like a billboard sign
And tell you everything
you want to hear
But I'll be your hero
'Cause I, I can be everything you need
If you're the one for me
Like gravity, I'll be unstoppable
I, yeah, I believe in destiny
I may be an ordinary guy
with heart and soul
But if you're the one for me
Then I'll be your hero
Oh, I'll be your hero, yeah
I'll be your hero
So incredible
Some kind of miracle
That when it's meant to be
I'll become a hero, oh
So I'll wait, wait, wait, wait for you
Yeah, I'll be a hero, yeah
'Cause I, I can be everything you need
If you're the one for me
Like gravity, I'll be unstoppable
I, yeah, I believe in destiny
I may be an ordinary guy
with heart and soul
But if you're the one for me
I'll be your hero
Yeah, yeah, I'll be your hero
Yeah, I'll be your hero
Hero
Great. Great.
So, girls, am I the greatest Dad
in the world or what?
Hey! Where you going?
Anywhere but here.
What did I do now?
You said you'd take me home. When?
Just pick a car. I'll take you home.
-No!
-Fine, we'll walk.
-Where does Grandma live again?
-Hollywood.
Oh, that's great.
We'll get there on Tuesday.
-Okay.
-Okay?
But here are the rules.
You drive me straight there,
drop me off,
and then you come back
to your fabulous life.
What's the purpose of that?
I don't get it.
Why does she do this?
There's something about
the sunshine, baby
I'm seeing you in a whole new light
Really?
What? I thought you'd like it.
Let me guess.
You thought l'd be dying to ride
in a car with Christopher Wilde
as he sings to one of his big hits.
A fan's dream come true!
There's just one problem.
-Which is?
-I'm not your fan.
You don't... You don't like my music?
No, I like your music.
I'm just not crazy about you.
-But you don't even know me.
-Precisely.
You know, I think if you...
I think if you did know me,
-you'd really like me.
-Turn here.
-Thanks for the ride.
-Hey, look, Jessica.
Look, I just wanna say I'm sorry.
Noted. Are we done now?
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I guess we're done.
-Good.
Okay, bye.
Oh, great.
Go away.
Look, I'll give you $5,000
if you do me this favour.
lt's not a favour if you pay for it.
So is that a yes?
You know, you can help a little.
No, this car wouldn't be moving
if I wasn't pushing it.
You'll be out of here before morning,
right?
Yes. Hopefully no one will ever know
I was here.
I'll know.
-Thank you. Thanks a lot.
-Yeah.
Hey, is there anything up there
that I can wear
so when I do leave,
the paparazzi won't recognise me?
You can look in those.
So, is all this really necessary?
Yes. Clearly you don't understand.
They're everywhere.
Paranoid.
You know what? Just forget it.
Love to.
Well?
That was my grandpa's hat.
He used to wear it
when he took me fishing.
Oh, wow. I'm sorry. Here.
No. You keep it.
lt looks kind of good on you.
Thanks.
Anything else?
No. No, I'm cool.
Yeah.
So cool you're sleeping in your car.
Jessica.
-Stop doing that!
-What am I doing?
Oh, you know exactly
what you're doing.
In fact, I bet you do it all the time.
You give girls that look
and expect them to fall for you.
Well, it's not working with me,
so get over it!
Eat up. We're helping Grandma
with some yard work today.
-Morning, sunshine.
-Hey.
-Syrup, please.
-l didn't see any.
-Mom, got any more syrup?
-Oh, sure. On the shelf in the garage.
I'll get it.
No. I'll get it.
-How was your little cab ride?
-What cab ride?
What cab ride? I am this close
to meeting Christopher Wilde,
and I have to leave because Stubby
tells me that you decided
to take a cab home.
Oh, that cab.
Where did you go? Wait. Don't tell me.
I don't wanna be that bored.
I'll make it up to you.
I'll help you find him.
How are you going to do that?
Let's go... Let's go inside and research.
Mom and Dad don't even need to know.
Mom and Dad
don't need to know what?
-Nothing.
I don't understand you girls.
-Oh, that's wonderful.
-Yeah, great.
Oh, Sara.
They're doing a story on television
about that boy you like so much.
In there.
Yeah.
-No!
-What is with you?
I don't...
Alexis Bender arrived
at her birthday party last night
without her leading man.
Although no one saw him arrive
at the fabulous Club Under 2 1,
witnesses confirm that
Christopher Wilde did indeed
make a secret appearance to sing
for the packed house of well-wishers.
Partygoers say the pop star
left the club immediately
following his performance,
only to magically reappear
at his Beverly Hills mansion
several hours later with a different girl.
My sources tell me this mystery girl
might be stealing the heart
of our favourite pop star.
Stop! I wanna see that!
Why? lt's all lies. Technically, slander.
Why do you care?
You don't even like him.
I care about the truth.
And I'm pretty sure that's not it.
-Girls, knock it off.
-l know what.
lt's a beautiful day. Here.
Take the keys to my car,
and go to the beach.
Really? Thanks, Grandma.
Take Jessica with you.
Go.
I thought we were going to Venice.
Why are we in Malibu?
Because Christopher Wilde
surfs in Malibu.
Today's the day. I can feel it.
He's here somewhere.
I doubt that.
I just hope
he's not with Alexis Bender, who,
lMHO, is totally not cute enough
for him.
I wonder what his eyes look like.
Up close.
Blue. Really blue.
Excuse me. ls this seat taken?
No? Okay.
What a beautiful day.
lsn't it a beautiful day?
Oh, I'm sorry. You were sleeping.
Did I wake you?
No? Oh, then you're awake. Good.
Would you put some
sunscreen on my back?
-How did you know it was me?
-The hat.
Does kind of smell like fish.
No, I'm pretty sure that's you.
Now, what are you doing here?
What are you doing here? Go home.
-l tried.
-And?
Nah, you wouldn't understand.
So you think you're so special
that a nobody like me
couldn't possibly understand
how hard it is to be you?
Okay.
There were about 1 0 paparazzi parked
outside my house with their cameras.
Yeah, that is tough.
Not.
See, you don't understand.
I just need to get home in a car
the paparazzi won't recognise.
So what are you driving?
Oh, you'd love it. lt's a classic.
Really vintage.
Perfect. I could pay you.
-l know that's kind of...
-Stop that!
-Stop what?
-Throwing your money around.
I mean, you still owe me five grand
for staying at Garage de la Grandma.
-Just give me your keys.
-Why?
Well, if you're taking our car,
you can't leave us here without one.
Keys.
Come on.
Okay, look, she's a...
She's a 300 and...
Three hundred
and thirty-five horsepower,
first generation '69 Tudor
with original paint.
Look, I love Cher, okay?
Cher?
You name your cars?
Christopher, meet Petunia.
You've got to be kidding me.
She runs like a top.
Have her back here in an hour.
Down. Get down.
I can't believe it.
How do they know where to find me?
My sister knows where to find you,
and she's from Kalamazoo.
All right, here. Put these on.
He's probably under an umbrella.
Look under an umbrella.
-Now!
-Okay.
All right. Get in the car.
He's got to be around here, all right.
Okay, you really need
to stop hitting me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Just get in. Get in. Get in!
Quick, buckle up. Put your head down.
-Put your head down. Head down.
-lt's down.
-What are you doing?
-I'm looking for something.
Here, put this on.
-What... Why?
-Do it now!
-Come on.
-Okay.
You know what?
You drive like my grandpa.
And you look like my grandma.
-Okay.
-l need my sunglasses back.
I don't know. I kind of like them.
-I'll give them to you. Later.
-For reals?
Because my friends just won't believe
that l, Jessica Olson,
have an actual pair
of Christopher Wilde sunglasses
worn by Christopher Wilde himself.
Will you autograph them for me?
-Very funny.
-What?
No, but seriously.
I really want these glasses.
Give them. Come on.
So, how long do I have to
drive around with you this time?
Only until the paparazzi
leave the beach.
-Hey, let's go do something.
-Like what?
Anything. What have you seen
since you've been here?
Nothing. l've been too busy
following you around.
-Really?
-With my sister.
She idolises you.
I mean, l, on the other hand,
couldn't care less about you
or your city.
Well, I know you don't like me,
but don't take it out on Los Angeles.
This is one of the greatest cities
in the world.
-Really?
-In fact, I'll be your tour guide.
I thought you needed to get home.
Nah. Take the long way.
Wake up to the blue sky
Grab your shades
and let's go for a ride
Breakfast by the ocean
We'll do lunch at Sunset and Vine
-Every day's a dream in California
-Every night the stars come out to play
-Wish that I could always
-Feel this way
-There's something about
-the sunshine, baby
-I'm seeing you in a whole new light
-Outta this world for the first time, baby
-Oh, it's so right
-There's something about the sunshine
In Hollywood, we're rockin'
In Malibu, we hang out and chill
It's all about the shopping
From Melrose to Beverly Hills
-Everywhere's a scene
-and now we're in it
-I don't want to paint this town alone
-When I see you smile
-I always feel at home
-There's something about
-the sunshine, baby
-I'm seeing you in a whole new light
-LA 's a breeze
-with the palm trees swayin'
-Oh, it's so right
Now that you're here
It's suddenly clear
-The sun's coming through
-I never knew
-Whatever I do
-It's better with you
It's better with you
Yeah, yeah
There's something about
the sunshine, baby
There's something about it
-I'm seeing you in a whole new light
-Whole new light
-Outta this world for the first time, baby
-Baby
-Oh, it's so right
So right
-Something about the sunshine, baby
-I'm seeing you in a whole new light
-Outta this world for the first time, baby
-Oh, it's so right
There's something about
the sunshine, baby
I'm seeing you in a whole new light
-LA 's a breeze
-with the palm trees swayin'
What a perfect day.
Not any more.
Man. I need to lose these vans.
Okay. Take your next left.
-You're sure?
-Yes.
Okay, if you take your next left,
the road loops back to the highway.
Or maybe not.
This isn't even a road any more.
This is a firebreak, it has to be.
Just... Just keep driving.
That last sign said ''Deer crossing.''
There are no deer.
You know,
you complain more than my sister.
Are we on the right road or not?
-Not?
-Show it to me.
No! Keep your eyes on the road.
I'm the navigator.
ls that what you call it?
-What's that supposed to mean?
-lt means you're such a know-it-all.
-A what?
-A know-it-all!
God, you are the queen
of snap judgements.
''Turn here! This is the right road!
I'm sure of it!''
-l was sure of it.
-You're sure.
You're so sure of things
you couldn't possibly be sure about.
-l am not.
-And you're defensive.
Move the car! We're not moving.
Great.
We'll have to get out and push.
-Wait, wait, wait. Look, I'll help you.
-Don't touch me.
-Why are you so mad?
-l don't know. This.
Look, turning onto this road
was not my idea.
-You're blaming me?
-Yeah, you're a terrible navigator!
-You're a terrible driver!
-Hey, I'm a great driver.
Right.
-Jess, we're gonna have to jump.
-I'm not jumping.
-You got a better idea?
-Use the branch as a bridge.
-lt does not look stable.
-lt looks fine.
All right.
Here goes. All right.
lt's sinking and making noises.
-Go faster.
-Okay!
This is my grandma's car!
I understand that.
Just give me your hand.
You okay? Grab the branch!
Grab the branch!
-Excuse you.
-You killed Petunia!
Well... Yeah.
My backpack! Don't just stand there.
Help me!
Here. Here. Give me your hand.
Give me your hand.
-Come on.
-I'm dead. I'm dead.
I'm gonna die,
that's what's gonna happen,
'cause my parents are gonna kill me.
Why did I have to get in that stupid car
with you?
-Answer your phone!
-Okay. Sorry.
-Dad?
-Yeah... Son? Can you hear me?
-Hello?
-We are a little worried over here and...
Can you hear me?
Dad? There's no signal.
Christopher, come home, honey, okay?
Or call us.
Do you... Hello?
Hello?
Look at this!
When we get out of here,
you're paying for a new one.
I'm paying for it right now.
-Jess.
-What?
Where are you going?
To the beach where my sister
is probably freaking out right now.
-Jess?
-What?
Beach is that way.
Please.
Christopher John Wilde.
Come on. Am I being Punk'd?
-Hey, how you doing? You okay?
-Now you're concerned?
You know, l've always been concerned.
-Maybe you should stop.
-Why are you so grumpy?
I'm not grumpy or cranky or crabby!
I just wanna get home to my family,
explain why I disappeared,
and suffer the consequences.
You want to know what I want?
I wanna have fun.
Okay, for the first time in years,
there's no reporters,
there's no interviews,
there's no crowds.
I'm having a great time. I want you
to stop complaining so I can enjoy it!
Wow, so that's what it's like with you?
You don't get what you want so you
throw a big ol' tantrum and walk away?
You know, I'll bet your friends
chase after you when you do that.
Christopher, I'm so sorry
I hurt your delicate little feelings.
Christopher, forgive me
for not treating you
like the big enormous star
you think you are.
What a brat.
I'm a brat? I'm a brat?
What about you, huh?
-Me?
-Yeah.
Over the last two days,
l've done nothing but think about you.
Really? So when you hit me
with a door twice,
hid me in your house,
wrecked my grandma's car
and dropped me in mud,
you were just being thoughtful?
-l pity your friends.
-You wish you were one.
l'd rather go down with Petunia.
You know what,
I'm confused about something.
What?
Okay, when we were
on our little photography tour,
-l thought you liked me.
-You thought wrong.
But everyone likes me.
Why is it that you don't like me?
Maybe because you think
everybody likes you.
-lt's 'cause I'm likeable.
-No, because you're a star.
-What does that mean?
-You don't even see it, do you?
Your life isn't real.
You park in no-parking zones,
you never have to wait in line,
you buy anything you want, anytime.
Your house is like a hotel.
You have so many people
working for you,
and I'll bet
you don't even know their names.
-Do, too.
-Name one.
-Bob.
-You just made that up.
Well, okay, Stubby knows everybody.
That's his job.
See, that's not normal.
Okay, your best friend is your driver,
your parents are on your payroll,
and your girlfriend...
I mean, real people date someone
because they want to be with them.
Why are you with Alexis?
That's all I'm saying.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Hold on.
Wait. Stop. What...
Are you saying I'm not a real person?
Because I am.
I stand corrected.
Well, all right. Well, what if I told you
something about me
that no one else knew?
You collect your toenails
in a peanut butter jar?
-No. What... No.
-Then what?
Well, from the first day I met you,
I just... Whoa!
Christopher!
-l can't swim.
-No.
-Gotcha!
-What? You're evil.
-You deserved it.
-You're so evil.
-You're gonna get it.
-You can try.
Get over here. No. Come on.
-Got you.
-I'm gonna get you.
-This is nice, isn't it?
-Man.
I wish I could just stay here
where no one can find me.
Why?
'Cause they all want something
from me.
A performance, or an interview,
or a photograph.
-Even your parents?
-That's complicated.
You know, sometimes I feel like
they only care about the business
-of ''Christopher Wilde.''
-I'm sure that's not true.
I don't know. I feel like all we talk
about right now is this movie deal.
They think
it's my next big career move, so...
Well, what do you think?
Think if I get the offer, I have to take it.
-What about your tour?
-What about it?
Well, 30 countries, 1 2 weeks.
One million screaming fans.
I mean, I'm not an expert or anything,
but it seems like a lot,
the tour and the movie
at the same time.
I don't have a choice.
Everyone has a choice.
What do you wanna do?
Well, I know what I don't wanna do.
I don't wanna disappoint anybody.
Especially my fans.
I wouldn't be where I am
without them, so...
I just never say no. To anything.
Maybe I don't understand.
-What?
-Your life.
I mean, it's so different from mine.
Everything you do and say
is so big and public.
Not everything.
Right now, here with you,
I feel like I can just be myself.
Not Christopher Wilde. Not famous.
Just... You know, just me.
-How do you like it?
-l like it a lot.
Me, too.
So tell me something about you.
-What do you wanna know?
-Everything.
That could take a while.
I live a very exciting life.
You're doing it again.
-Doing what?
-That thing with your eyes.
You mean this?
Okay, so comedy?
Not your next big career move.
What? No, I'm funny.
-Funny-looking.
-You like me.
You wish.
We should go.
Yeah. Come on.
Stubby?
Whoa. Sara?
What are you doing here?
That's not good.
-We made it.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Look, I had a really great time today.
-Me, too.
You're so different from any other girl
l've ever known.
-Different weird, different annoying?
-Different surprising.
In the best way.
I mean, you say things to me
everyone else is afraid to say,
and you make me see things
about myself that I can't see.
-You're pretty surprising, too.
-Really? How?
Well, for one thing,
you're a terrible driver,
which is strange for a guy with six cars.
I'm wounded.
Do you really think I'm bossy?
No. I think you're amazing.
I think you're amazing, too.
What are you doing?
That was close.
Okay. Back to the real world.
You know what happens next, right?
-No.
-This ends here.
-What does?
-This. Us.
You can't tell anybody
about what happened today.
Not even your parents.
Why? They're not gonna go post it
on their blog or anything.
Look, if we go down there, if we get
photographed together, it'll get crazy.
-And I won't get this movie deal.
-Why does it have to get crazy?
Because I'm Christopher Wilde.
You're just an ordinary girl.
I have to go now.
Wait, Jess! Jess! Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. What just happened?
You tell me. One second I'm amazing
and the next you're embarrassed
to be seen with me?
-Jess, I'm not embarrassed...
-Really?
lf I was Alexis Bender,
you'd rush right down there
and make sure
somebody took our picture.
-But, no, I'm just an ordinary girl!
-That is not what I meant.
Look, I meant you're normal.
I want you to stay that way.
Right. Just leave me alone.
Jess. Stop. Please.
What?
The pictures you took. Of us.
I should probably keep them.
-You want my camera?
-Just in case.
I wouldn't want the pictures to,
you know, get out.
Fine. You want my pictures? Here.
There's nothing
l'd wanna remember anyway.
I need cab fare to get home.
-I'm going to Hollywood, not Hawaii.
-Just keep it.
I still owe you for my stay
at Garage de la Grandma.
Jess, wait.
I don't wanna say goodbye like this.
Okay, how about this?
How about we both forget
this whole day ever happened?
You won't talk about me
and I promise I won't talk about you.
Go ahead and judge me, okay,
but you don't know what it'll be like.
The paparazzi never go away.
And once they have you in their sights,
they won't quit
until they get what they want.
And when they finally get it,
they'll turn it into something ugly.
They'll ruin everything.
They don't have to. You already did.
I'm no superman
I can't take your hand
And fly you anywhere
you wanna go, yeah
I can't read your mind
Like a billboard sign
And tell you everything
you wanna hear
But I'll be your hero
'Cause I, I can be everything you need
If you're the one for me
Like gravity, I'll be unstoppable
I, yeah, I believe in destiny
I may be an ordinary guy
with heart and soul
But if you're the one for me
Then I'll be your hero
Could you be the one
Could you be the one for me?
Then I'll be your hero
Could you be the one
Could you be the one for me?
Then I'll be your hero
Searching high and low
Trying every road
But if I see your face
how will I know, yeah
I'll put my trust in fate
That you will come my way
And if it's right, it's undeniable, yeah
I'll be your hero
I, I can be everything you need
If you're the one for me
Like gravity, I'll be unstoppable
I, yeah, I believe in destiny
I may be an ordinary guy
with heart and soul
But if you're the one for me
Then I'll be your hero
Could you be the one
Could you be the one for me?
I'll be your hero
Could you be the one
Could you be the one for me?
I'll be your hero
So incredible
Some kind of miracle
That when it's meant to be
I'll become a hero, oh
So I'll wait, wait, wait, wait for you
Yeah, I'll be your hero
I, I could be everything you need
If you're the one for me
Like gravity, I'll be unstoppable
I, yeah, I believe in destiny
I may be an ordinary guy
with heart and soul
But if you're the one for me
Then I'll be your hero
Could you be the one
Could you be the one for me?
Then I'll be your hero
Could you be the one
Could you be the one for me?
Then I'll be your hero
That was great, Chris. Take five.
Thanks, guys. That was great.
Let's take a break.
All right, man.
-Good job, guys. Yeah.
-Hey, wait up.
Yo. You okay?
Yeah. Yeah,
I just can't get her out of my mind.
Yeah, me neither.
She cacked all over my shoes.
I mean, she's real, you know?
She's annoyingly honest, she's smart,
she's cool, she's funny, she's beautiful.
Yeah.
Hello, boys.
Talking about me?
Dude.
-Look, Alexis, I can explain...
-l don't want to know who she is.
ls she an actress?
ls she more famous than me?
No. No, she's not an actress.
She's not famous at all.
Then I really don't understand
why you would pick her.
I didn't pick her.
lt just kind of happened.
Silly. That kind of stuff
only happens in the movies.
This is the real world.
I have a date with Zac. I have to go.
Whoa. Are you breaking up with me?
Okay.
-Friends?
-Sure.
-Bye, Grandma. I love you.
-Goodbye, Sara. I love you more.
-You sure you're gonna be okay, Mom?
-Yes, Barbara.
And you mustn't believe
what you read about old folks.
-Howard and I are gonna be just fine.
-l can see that.
-Love you.
-Love you. Love you.
And how about you, Jess?
Are you gonna be all right?
Sweetheart. I know it hurts right now,
but things are not always
what they seem in the moment.
Given some time, life has a way
of working itself out for the better.
-Really, Grandma?
-Yup. I mean, look at me.
l've been trying to get rid of that ugly
old car since your grandpa died.
-Honey.
-l love you, Grandma.
I love you, sweetheart.
-Bye, Howard.
-Take care, sweetheart.
You, too.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
Bye, everybody!
Jessica Olson.
-Such a nice name for a nice girl.
-Where'd you get that?
Where do you think I got it,
Christopher?
Libby Lam has had a whole fleet
of photographers on you
-for the past two days.
-l know, but I was so careful.
Now, this is exactly the kind of thing
I was afraid of with you, kid.
I mean, you're obviously not serious
about doing this movie.
I don't know,
maybe you're just too young.
No, sir. Look, I made a mistake.
Come on, Alan.
Give us a chance to fix this.
All right, all right.
Make the story go away.
-How do we do that?
-You call Libby Lam.
You offer her an exclusive.
You say you don't know this girl.
You say she's just some fan
who was following you around all day.
-You want me to lie?
-Christopher!
This is the tabloid press, dude.
This is not the Supreme Court.
Say whatever you have to say,
because I promise you, either this girl
goes away or the movie does. Okay?
Goodbye.
So we're talking about this girl,
Jessica Olson.
-Yeah, she looks kind of familiar.
-Come on, Christopher.
We know you were at the beach
with her.
Look, lots of fans come to Malibu
to watch me surf,
and I try to say hi to everybody
that comes up to me, but...
Please.
Maybe I signed an autograph for her
or something.
Excuse us. lt's okay.
According to our sources,
she came all the way from Kalamazoo,
Michigan, just to see you.
-Coming through. Enough of that.
-Wow, really?
I'm sorry
I didn't get the chance to meet her.
Going inside.
You have to talk to us, Jess.
What happened out there in California?
Nothing bad, I promise.
I can't talk about it.
Please, please, just trust me.
Christopher Wilde
is talking about you on Starstruck!
So you're saying
that you don't know this girl.
Yeah. I mean, I don't know
what she's saying about me,
but I don't know anybody
named Jessica Olson.
Sorry, Libby,
there's nothing more to tell.
Okay. You heard it here first.
I'm Libby Lam. This is Starstruck News.
I can't believe they're still out there.
Why don't they just go home?
Because they haven't got
what they came for yet.
You know,
you should just go talk to them.
I mean,
you're already all over the lnternet.
-l am?
-Yeah!
There's like a whole website devoted
to what people think about Chrissica.
''Chrissica''?
Wow.
You really shouldn't read any of these.
Wait, wait, here's a good one.
''That Jessica Olson chick
is a real nut, dude.
''She just wants to be famous.
She should get a life because she...''
Guys, stop. Just stop.
Maybe it's the phrasing or the tempo.
Something's not right.
-Yo, what's up with you, man?
-l don't know.
You want to know what I think?
Sure you do.
I think you're still torn up about Jessica.
No. I'm good. I'm over her.
All my life people telling me
just who I am
They don't wanna know
They don't really understand
Too many people trying to tell me
to be practical
Only think that I am one-dimensional
But I can feel it
There's a fire raging underneath
Burning through the pages
here I am coming clean
I'm sick of lying to myself
Gotta live the truth
Now I gotta do what I gotta do
This is where I should be
There ain't no other place, yeah
Where my soul really speaks
There ain't no other way
I can feel it
save me, move me, shake me
Gotta go where the music takes me
Let it set me free
You got to believe
Is it a crime to just be who I wanna be?
I need some space
so that I can chase all my dreams
'Cause when I hit the stage
anything is possible
I get lost in the song
and that is magical
So crank it up, feel the rush
then just turn me loose
I wanna feel the inspiration
that is coming through
And there's no other place
where I feel so alive
When I start to sing you just can't deny
This is where I should be
There ain't no other place, yeah
Where my soul really speaks
There ain't no other way
I can feel it
save me, move me, shake me
Gotta go where the music takes me
Let it set me free
You got to believe
When everybody's gone
And I'm here all alone
I don't gotta hide
I don't have to try
You got to understand
That this is who I am
And it's where I shine
And it's where I shine, I know
This is where I should be
There ain't no other place, yeah
Where my soul really speaks
There ain't no other way
I can feel it
save me, move me, shake me
Gotta go where the music takes me
Let it set me free
You got to believe
This is where I should be
There ain't no other place, yeah
Where my soul really speaks
There ain't no other way
I can feel it move me
Gotta go where the music takes me
Let it set me free
You got to believe
You are definitely not over her.
-Okay, they need to go now.
-l thought you liked being on TV.
Yeah, but I need to buy a dress for
the dance, and they're blocking my car.
Christopher said this would happen.
He said it would get crazy.
Celebrities might have to
put up with this, but I don't.
Jessica! Jessica.
Tell us about your weekend
with Christopher Wilde.
We only want the truth.
You don't want the truth.
You want a story.
You take a good, normal person
and turn him into
your own little reality show.
You build him up into a big celebrity
just so you can tear him down
in public.
Just so you can sell magazines
and TV shows?
That's really sick.
And Christopher Wilde's
just one example.
He's talented and successful.
He has all the stuff
lots of kids dream of having.
But thanks to you, he's had to give up
some of the best things in life.
Freedom. Privacy.
Honesty.
So, congratulations,
you've created a celebrity.
But you have wrecked
the human being inside.
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
Did you get that?
Jessica. Jessica,
just one more question.
In your opinion,
who is Christopher Wilde, really?
Who is he? I don't know.
The Christopher Wilde
you're all so obsessed with,
I promise you, I never met him,
and I wouldn't want to.
Didn't you say you liked her
because she was so honest?
-Yeah.
-Wow.
Congratulations, Chris. You did it.
You got her to lie for you.
I didn't have a choice, okay?
All right.
-Where are you going?
-To find my best friend,
'cause he's not the guy
sitting here now.
-Dude, what are you talking about?
-''l didn't have a choice.''
Lately that's been your answer
to everything, man.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Your life, your choice, man.
What do you want?
Cut!
Guys, you nailed it. Perfect, guys.
That was the one. That was perfect.
Let's go one more time.
Circle. Great take. Great... Christopher!
Buddy. Great news. You're in.
Rehearsals start on Monday.
-Actually, I'm not available.
-Not a problem. We'll change the date.
No. I came to say, you know,
thanks for the offer,
but if I have to lie to be
in your little club, think I'll pass.
Wow. Kid's got edge. Fire. I like that.
And cue the rain!
Okay. He's got two weeks
between Oslo and London.
We could make him available
for the movie then.
That's tight.
You know, he needs some downtime.
Okay. All right. How about after Tokyo,
but before Melbourne?
-What's going on?
-Hi, honey.
Hey.
We're working the movie
into your tour schedule.
I don't want to do the movie any more.
Sweetie, don't be silly.
Of course you do.
We're about to make the deal, bud.
Well, it's too late. l've already passed.
Honey, that's not your decision.
Yes, it is.
I'm 1 7 years old.
I just want to have fun and make music.
Okay, okay. Hey. No worries.
No worries. We'll handle it.
No. No. lt's time that I started
managing my own life. So...
You know what? You're fired.
Wow.
l'd really like for you
to just be my parents from now on.
Right.
Okay, come here.
Turn.
lt's just not girly enough.
But imagine it on me. Girlier, right?
-Maybe.
-Why don't you just try it on yourself?
Stop whining. Here.
We have three hours before the dance.
Go change.
Kids!
So what was it like
to have reporters on your lawn?
Exciting. But I need my privacy, too.
We all watched your sister on TV,
and she looked wacko.
-Really?
-Yeah!
lt was so weird
the way she made up that story
about meeting Christopher Wilde.
She is so pathetic.
Do you think she heard that?
-AJ. You're an idiot.
-What?
-Get out.
-But...
Go!
-Jessica.
-Go away.
No. I actually live here.
What?
Go with me to the dance.
I thought I was pathetic
and embarrassing.
Only if you actually dance. So don't.
Come on. Come on.
Let's make you pretty enough
to be my sister.
You look good. Don't slouch.
You know, Sara, in a weird way,
you're a good sister.
Pretend you don't know me.
Lame.
Oh, my God!
Jessica Olson?
There's some things I forgot to say
to you back in California.
Can't blame you
For thinking
That you never really knew me at all
I tried to
Deny you
But nothing ever
made me feel so wrong
I thought I was protecting you
from everything that I go through
But I know that we got lost
along the way
Here I am
With all my heart
I hope you understand
I know I let you down
But I'm never gonna make
that mistake again
You brought me closer
to who I really am
So come take my hand
I want the world to see
What you mean to me
What did you think?
That you could just come here
and sing to me
and everything would be fine?
Yes. No? No. No.
Well, which is it?
I just came to tell you
I was wrong about everything,
especially about you.
-Don't you think you're a little late?
-Come on.
Everyone here thinks I was lying.
But I'm the one who lied.
I lied about knowing Jessica Olson.
'Cause the truth is
I know Jessica Olson.
Jessica Olson's a terrible navigator
and a know-it-all,
but she's honest.
When she makes a promise,
she keeps it.
She understands me
like no one else does.
And I'm crazy about her.
Jessica, I'm so sorry.
I know that I hurt you
and I will never do
anything like that again.
Just, please, forgive me.
-Go away. Now.
-Okay. Get out of here. Move it.
Christopher, this is my sister, Sara.
Sara, this is Christopher Wilde.
Sara. Do you wanna dance with me?
I think I got this one, Chrissy.
You didn't have to come
all the way to Michigan for this.
Yeah, I did.
lt's not cool
to ask a girl out on the phone.
So, will you go out with me?
On a real date.
-Do I have to wear a disguise?
-No.
-Do you?
Then, yeah. l'd really like that.
I almost forgot. For you.
You remembered. How do I look?
Like a superstar.
Party up
Put your hands in the sky now, yeah
If you wanna get fly
We can do it all night now, yeah
Turn the beat up high
One time for the ladies, yeah
And the fellas come on
We gonna go crazy
Till the lights come on
All night, here we go now
Come on and get right on the floor now
Nah, nah, baby girl, don't slow down
'Cause me and you gonna have
a showdown
Little mama get lowdown
And I'm-a rock it out like this
We movin' and groovin' smooth
Can't lose with a flow that is so swift
So maybe when you wake up
and your face still got that grin
You can smile all day in a flygirl way
and say, ''Yeah, I'm that chick''
And maybe we can get the deejay
to play this track all night
And when I ask how you feel out there
Everybody say...
-All right!
Put your hands in the sky now, yeah
If you wanna get fly
We can do it all night now, yeah
Turn the beat up high
Party up
One time for the ladies, yeah
And the fellas come on
We gonna go crazy
Till the lights come on
Party up
Put your hands in the sky now, yeah
If you wanna get fly
We can do it all night now, yeah
Turn the beat up high
One time for the ladies, yeah
And the fellas come on
We gonna go crazy
Till the lights come on
Party up
Download GOM Player to experience
the highest video and audio quality!