Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(CHATTERING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(GRUNTING)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(PANTING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(CAL SINGING) Oh, the night
that Paddy Murphy died
Is a night I'll never forget
Some of the boys
got loaded drunk
And they ain't got sober yet
As long as
a bottle was passed around
Every man was feeling gay
O'Leary came
with the bagpipes
Some music for to play
That's how they
showed their respect
for Paddy Murphy
That's how they showed
their honor and their pride
They said it was
a sin and shame
And they winked
at one another
And every drink in
the place was full
The night Pat Murphy died
As Mrs. Murphy sat
in the corner
Pouring out her grief
Kelly and his gang came
tearing down the street
They went into an empty room
And a bottle of whiskey stole
They put the bottle
with the corpse
To keep that whiskey cold
That's how they showed
their respect for...
They took the white
kid to the hospital.
He's in a coma.
Officer, you should
check in with the family.
Whatever you're selling,
I ain't buying.
Okay, guys, take off.
Yes, sir.
Coffee's free for
friends of the press.
I heard Metro ballistics
was just here.
Who told you that?
You just did.
You got the names of
the victims for me?
You gotta be kidding me.
You know I'm gonna
find out anyway.
Not from me.
Okay. You want to play
a little confirm or deny?
I'm not playing this
game with you, Cal.
Look, Don, I got
a living to make,
all right?
I got mouths to feed,
goldfish.
(CHUCKLING)
No names,
no quotes,
all right?
Okay.
Two victims,
one shooter?
Confirm.
One dead,
one in the hospital?
Confirm.
Drug related?
Confirm,
but deny later
if I have to.
Good morning.
WOMAN: Good morning, sir.
Okay, I'm late. I know.
I don't need to
be reminded of it.
I've been over
the briefing notes
1,000 times.
Stephen.
Yes?
Metro Police just called.
What?
Sonia Baker was
killed in an accident
on the Metro this morning.
They identified her
by her staff badge.
Horrible news
for all of us.
But, Stephen,
we're scheduled
to start now.
What do you want to do?
WOMAN: Morning, Pittsburgh.
Yinzer.
Cal.
Morning.
Talk to me
about this shooting.
You know,
one guy's still alive.
Deshaun Stagg?
No, he's dead.
The other guy on the bike,
Vernon Sando.
Hey, Gene, did you read
the guinea pig piece I filed?
Yeah, I'll get
to it, Ferris.
Because it's a great
human interest story.
Yeah, human interest.
So what's the deal?
Stagg's drug deal goes wrong,
and this guy just rides by?
Yeah, something like that,
I think.
That's a remarkable
feat of survival.
Well, at least it's
got a little bit of
a zip code to it.
Georgetown's the angle,
right?
No, no, the angle is
that this guy Vernon Sando
has got an MBA from Duke.
What's he doing on a bike?
He's buying
a pizza franchise.
You know,
they make you ride the bike
for the first six months,
learn the ropes.
He's got a wife,
two kids, mortgage,
total citizen.
What's his condition?
Critical, non-reactive.
Paragraph three.
He's in a coma.
Okay, let me know.
I will.
(CLEARING THROAT)
Good morning.
ALL: Good morning.
Welcome to our hearings
with private security
contractor PointCorp,
part of the inquiry
into the Defense Department's
privatization and
outsourcing practices.
Before we begin,
I've just received
some terrible news.
Sonia Baker,
who was the lead researcher
for this committee
and a valued
member of my staff,
died this morning.
(CROWD MURMURING)
The circumstances
of her death
are not yet clear.
Well, I'd like to
send my condolences
to her family.
(SIGHS)
(EXHALING)
Oh, my God,
are those tears?
50 bucks says
he's balling her.
50 bucks?
Wait, you owe me 50 bucks.
Bad Congressman! Bad.
What a scumball!
GENE: Somebody get me
a picture of the girl.
Let's hope she's not
5'2" and 300 pounds.
Gene, Gene, what is your
obsession with fat girls?
If you want to
have sex with Pete,
you should just say it.
Not tonight,
I got a headache.
HANK: Say it.
Say it, Gene.
Say it.
GENE: Picture! Picture!
REPORTER: Reaction to
the tragic death was
initially,
and understandably,
one of shock,
yet questions immediately
began to surface
as soon as Ms. Baker's death
was announced.
Hey, Joe, Cal
McAffrey over
at the Globe.
Just calling
about that shooting
in Georgetown last night.
I heard the dead kid
had a couple of priors
as a purse snatcher.
Got any more details for me?
Call me back?
Yeah, yeah. You, too.
Hey, I got
a question for you.
Stephen Collins.
He's an old friend of yours,
is that right?
Yeah.
I'm Della. Della Frye.
I write
the Capitol Hill blog.
All right.
Online side.
I'm a big fan of your work.
So, I'm writing this piece
on personal relationships
in the political sphere,
"single girl in
the corridors of power"
kind of thing,
and as you probably know,
there was this
incident this morning
on the Hill,
at your friend's hearing.
Is there a question
on the horizon?
Yeah. Have you spoken
to him today?
Are you trying to make me
part of your story?
No. I'm trying to get
a little context.
Context, re: Dirt?
Well, do you think
he was having
an affair with that girl?
Gee, Della.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'd have to read
a couple of blogs
before I could
form an opinion.
Okay. Thanks for your help.
Anytime!
ANCHORWOMAN 1: Capitol Hill
may be rocked with
another bombshell.
Speculation is rife
that Stephen Collins
may have been
romantically linked
with the young
aide found dead
this morning.
His spokesmen call this
another political cloud...
ANCHORMAN: The timing couldn't
be worse for Collins.
He needs all the political
leverage he can get
as he begins looking
into the Defense Department's
outsourcing practices.
ANCHORWOMAN 2: Called
mercenaries by some and
saviors by others,
PointCorp, the controversial
private military contractor,
is said to be
the biggest beneficiary
in the Defense
Department's outsourcing
in Iraq and Afghanistan.
Collins, who'd been
married for 10 years
to his college sweetheart,
is thought to have
refused to leave his wife
for Miss Baker.
GEORGE: Brass tacks.
Were you having
a relationship
with this girl?
Yes,
and I can't tell
you how sorry I am
about all of this.
Okay.
I've asked Andrew
here to help us
handle things from
a media point of view.
If anyone can steer us
through this, he can.
Well, the next 72 hours
are gonna be brutal.
You ought to brace
yourself for that.
For a while,
you're gonna be everything
that's wrong with politics.
You're still a star, Steve.
The party takes
care of its stars.
You just have to
lay low for a while.
How low?
Low.
Nothing that would
bring any undue
attention to yourself.
At the hearings,
for instance.
We're not finished
with PointCorp.
No, but you are.
If you open up fire on
those guys right now,
that's not gonna look
like good governance,
just a calculated
distraction.
Is your wife
speaking to you?
No, not right now.
Then that's job one,
isn't it?
Yinzer! She knows you
got the message,
and she knows
you're in the building.
Yes.
Morning.
So, where are we?
Was he knobbing her or not?
Morning, Cam.
It's funny about you.
Every time your friend
runs for reelection
or conducts a hearing,
you drop his name to me
until we give
him some coverage.
But he finally
does something
that actually might
sell some newspapers,
you're rendered mute.
It's incongruous.
No, it is not.
It's inconsistent.
(SCOFFS)
Don't be an ass.
What do you think?
Those are the ideas
for our facelift.
I know. I know.
It's crap.
Our new owners
have this odd idea
that we ought to
be turning a profit.
Yeah, well,
I hear our online
side is doing great.
I mean,
not like I'm the kind of guy
who would notice
that sort of thing,
but I've been here,
what, 15 years?
I use a 16-year-old computer.
She's been here 15 minutes,
and she could launch
a Russian satellite
with the gear she's got.
Yeah, she told me
you behaved like a pig.
That's too strong.
Well, piggish.
I showed her
a little snout.
Well, I happen to like
Ms. Della Frye.
And, yes,
I did send her down there
to winkle
something out of you.
She's hungry, she's cheap,
and she churns
out copy every hour.
Yeah, I know. I'm overfed,
I'm too expensive,
and I take way too long.
Yes, you do.
I was Stephen Collins'
roommate in college.
I don't live with him now.
Well, that's a shame,
isn't it?
Yeah, 'cause that could sell
some newspapers.
ANCHORMAN 1: Miss Baker
died this morning in an
apparent accident
on the D.C. Metro.
Suicide has not
been ruled out.
(CHATTERING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
It appears to be a suicide.
People close to the case say
that Congressman Collins,
quote, "took advantage"
of this young girl,
resulting in today's suicide.
ANCHORMAN 2: Suicide.
ANCHORMAN 3: Suicide.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
So, I know you're thinking,
"This guy's gotta
be pretty desperate
to show up here."
No, I was thinking I can
finally give you back
that Roxy Music CD
you left in my car.
Is that where that one went?
I was looking for that.
I got three dozen reporters
camped in front of my place.
I'd go somewhere else,
but I don't have
anywhere else to go.
Come in.
Thanks.
I see you redecorated.
Yeah. I moved that
couch a couple of feet.
Looks good.
Aren't you gonna ask me
how I could be so stupid?
In a minute.
Okay.
You know,
I co-sponsored two bills
in the last three years.
I'm in
the middle of co-authoring
another one,
and this is
what I'm gonna be
remembered for.
I'm gonna get
more coverage on this
than anything else I do
for the rest of my life.
The nature of the beast,
public office.
Okay.
Look, Cal,
I know the last
time I saw you,
I said a few things.
Hey.
I deserved it, all of it.
Annie and I were
having problems
in the marriage, obviously.
You're the only
real friend I got.
I'm in trouble, man.
You know?
This whole thing with Sonia,
what happened,
it just snuck up on me.
She was an amazing woman,
beautiful and
really funny, smart,
and she, you know,
she adored me.
That was nice,
you know, for a change.
Have you called the parents?
(SIGHS) No, I haven't
called the parents.
You should.
Tomorrow,
you're gonna make
a condolence call.
The first thing
the attack dogs will
pick up on, you know,
"He never so much
as called after our
daughter's suicide."
She didn't kill herself.
How do you know that?
Hey, baby, I just want
to wish you good luck.
I want you to give them hell,
and I can't wait
for this weekend.
I love you. Bye.
That's this morning.
Look like someone
who's about to go out
and commit suicide?
No.
You show this to anybody?
Well, I thought
about firing it up
on YouTube.
Hey, you know what?
This is
the moment where I ask you
how stupid could you be.
This changes everything.
It'll bring it
all back your way.
How are you gonna do that?
Because we're
gonna fight back
with our own facts.
All we have to do is,
we have to build
a plausible
alternative story,
all right?
Now, look.
"Unfortunately,
it appears that Sonia Baker
"has met with
a tragic accident
on a subway platform.
"So questions
have to be asked
about transit safety."
Okay?
Cal.
Now, Stephen,
you gotta be
proactive, okay?
If you're not,
then you're just letting
the bloodsuckers
and the bloggers
have another
free shot at you.
The bloodsuckers
and the bloggers.
Have you seen
the Globe's website
tonight?
No.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Miss Capitol Hill Blog?
It's Cal McAffrey.
Do you have a pen?
What?
Sonia Baker, right?
I have a source,
and you need to talk to him.
Well, why?
Do you have a pen?
Yeah.
Lieutenant Leon Comey.
Pen, pen, pen.
Write that down. C-O-M-E-Y.
C-O-M-E-Y.
202-555-0167.
He's gonna show you
an off-the-record preview
of the security camera tapes
from the Metro station.
What, you mean...
Do you mean, like, now?
Yeah, like now.
Sorry. Who am I calling?
I was trying to get
Della Frye the reporter.
Gee, I'm sorry.
I thought that I was
talking to the guy
who wouldn't give me
the time of day this morning.
Look,
I am just trying to help you
get a few facts in the mix
next time you decide
to upchuck online.
What?
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
I'm not doing it. I'm not.
DELLA: Wake up.
Does anybody know
where Room 514 is?
514A or 514B?
It doesn't say.
Is there a big
difference?
Big enough. You looking
for Uniform Squad
or Investigation?
I don't know.
Cal McAffrey sent me.
Why didn't you say so?
You Cal's new assistant?
No, I'm not.
Hey, can I see that?
Yeah, it's right
down the hallway here.
Thank you.
Like a police escort?
No, I'm okay.
Thank you.
Hey, no trouble.
I'm just grabbing
some dinner here real quick.
So, how long have
you known Cal?
Too long.
What's your title?
Okay, Sergeant,
I can file
a public records request
and get
the information anyway.
You got nothing?
No.
They've got 56 cameras
covering the track platforms.
There are three blind spots
in the entire system,
and Sonia Baker went
down in one of them.
You got copy for me, Cal?
The shooting delivery guy,
what are we doing?
I'm on it.
Well, I got Marty lined up
to take some
pictures of the family.
If you'd like,
I can send somebody
out there with him.
He can do the crying,
you can do
the nuts and bolts.
No. No need. I'm on it.
You'll have it tonight.
You're on it.
(EXHALING) Okay.
You know what you gotta do?
Call Leon, all right?
Just sort of push
him for the details.
Ask him a few more questions.
You know...
Nine suicides in 20 years.
There were five
accidental deaths,
three from people
trying to get their stuff
off the tracks
before the train came
and two of
the psycho-on-stranger
pushing attacks.
Did Collins sleep at
your place last night?
What?
Hmm?
I was just trying to
get my facts straight.
(PHONE RINGING)
Excuse me. Della here.
Yeah, just a sec.
He's right here.
Hang on, hang on, hang on.
It's Anne Collins.
Hey, I'm not at my
desk at the moment.
Can I call you back?
Yeah.
You know, look into
the two psycho-on-stranger
cases,
see if anything correlates
or anything connects.
Mmm-hmm.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
CAL: Hey.
You okay?
No.
There are
paparazzi on my lawn,
so I guess that entitles me
to half off on Us Weekly.
I've been trying
to call you.
I had my phone off.
You talk to Stephen yet?
No.
They want me to come down
for a press conference.
Well, you know if you don't,
they're gonna toss
him on the bonfire.
You know,
I'm not that hurt.
I'm not even that surprised.
It's just so humiliating,
you know.
(SIGHING)
Tell me you
didn't know about her.
I didn't.
I did not know
about her, okay?
I'll take the train down.
Will you buy me
a drink after?
Of course. Hey,
just call him,
all right?
Just call Stephen.
Thanks.
CAL: Deshaun Stagg.
Be nice if they could
spell his name right.
No one's even come
to get his stuff yet.
It's appalling.
Never happen
to a white man.
Skip it.
I'm not in the mood.
What, no love,
no politics?
What are we gonna talk about?
We're not.
You gotta get out of here
before we both
get into trouble.
They're saying it
was only one shooter.
What do you think?
No idea.
What about drugs?
It's a good bet.
Come on, Cal,
leave that shit alone.
Close your eyes.
I'm just checking
out his cell phone.
(SIGHING) Watch, this will be
the moment they decide
to come and pick
all this shit up.
Then what are you gonna do?
Write some articles,
get me my job back?
You know I will.
Cal?
Cal, for Christ's sakes,
what do I tell Jack
if he walks in?
Nothing, 'cause I'm done.
I'll give you a hug
next time, all right?
Bye.
Buy me a soda?
Not diet.
Thanks.
(PHONE RINGING)
Yo, yo, if you want to leave
a message for Kippy,
make sure you leave
your number, all right?
That way I can call you back.
Later for you.
AUTOMATED OPERATOR:
We're sorry.
Your call cannot be...
(PHONE RINGING)
MAN: Yo, who this?
It's me, man. Who that?
Me who? Bitch, you the one
got your number blocked!
Don't be fronting me, man.
It's Deshaun. Come on.
No.
Where you at?
Who the hell gave
you my number, fool?
I was just talking to Kippy.
Skippy?
Kippy, man.
This shit ain't funny, trick.
Hi. You've reached
Sonia Baker.
I can't take
your call right now,
but if you leave
your name, number,
and the time you called,
I'll be sure to get
back to you. Thanks.
Hi. You've reached
Sonia Baker.
I can't take
your call right now,
but if you leave
your name, number,
and the time you called,
I'll be sure to get
back to you. Thanks.
Excuse me.
Sonia Baker.
We got any kind of
drug angle on her?
She ever arrested or rehabbed
or anything like that?
Who's asking?
Me.
You're not on the story.
I gave you
the Metro tapes idea, right?
Yeah.
So are you trying to ruin
what's left of
her reputation?
Are you doing
this for Collins?
A little context on Sonia?
You gotta be kidding.
Hey, Maurice.
Hey, Cal,
you getting your regular?
Yeah.
Sure. Hey, Jay!
I need a chili cheeseburger,
a chili cheese fry,
and a chili half-smoke.
I got the burger on!
Anybody get you yet?
All right.
You're a hungry man, eh?
Yeah.
How's it going, Happy?
That's a long way to
go for another soda.
You want to buy something
from the last bag
Deshaun ever stole?
I need 500 bucks.
Did you get the train okay?
What?
Did you get on
the train all right?
Get through.
Everything okay?
You're gonna
make small talk?
(CLEARING THROAT) I will go
check on the arrangements.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't have to be
a detailed statement.
Short and dignified,
and we'll be out of here.
Dignified. Got it.
MAN: Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for
joining us here today.
Mr. And Mrs. Collins
would like to give you
a brief statement.
GIRL: Deshaun boosted
this metal briefcase
from some guy
outside of Starbucks.
That's what we did,
you know?
Grab a guy's bag and
sell it back to him.
Usually we just got,
like, people's business
papers and shit.
This one?
This one was different.
GIRL: There was a gun
in there, too,
and a little bag of these
weird-looking bullets.
Did you see the guy
that owned the bag?
No.
I told Deshaun
we shouldn't
sell this bag back.
I mean, you know,
what about the girl?
But he needed
a fix real bad,
and he and this
guy figured out
a time and place.
And that was it.
My boy never came back.
You took these out of
the briefcase first,
and then you called her
from Deshaun's phone.
Her number was there, too.
I figured someone
had to warn her
that this psycho was
following her around.
She just didn't pick up.
Mr. Collins moved to
staunch a growing tide
of hostility towards him
this afternoon
when he appeared
together with his...
...the long line of
politicians' wives.
We've had triumphs
and disappointments,
and we've both made mistakes
that have caused...
MAN: Apologize for
his affair and offer an
apology to his constituents.
Can you believe this?
We're on six channels
simultaneously.
CAL: Who might have
wanted Sonia dead?
What?
Is there something
in her history,
you know, something you
haven't told me about?
Some connections
that might have
got her in trouble?
No. No, no. Wait, who...
Am I talking to
my friend now,
or am I talking
to a reporter?
I gotta be both.
You ever heard of a guy
called Deshaun Stagg?
No.
Was a kid. Minor criminal.
Drug addict.
Got shot and killed
the night before Sonia died.
Cal,
Sonia didn't have anything
to do with drugs.
Look, Stephen,
I'm telling you things
that I haven't even
discussed with the paper.
Okay, you gotta
think about this.
Who might have
wanted Sonia dead?
CHRIS: Who is this man here
in all the photographs
where she's crying?
CAL: We don't know that yet.
And what was her background
before she started
working with Collins?
DELLA: Well, she has some
very random moments
in her résumé.
She was...
She waitressed
a couple times.
She had
a string of bad debts.
Shoplifting conviction
two years ago.
Don't they do
background checks
on the Hill?
DELLA: She wrote position
papers for Collins
about bank regulations
and the SEC.
I mean,
a lot of people thought
she was a star.
She was also
the lead researcher
on the PointCorp hearings.
CAMERON: So?
Stephen represents
the loss of a lot of
money for those guys.
Look, what if all of
this is just an attempt
to marginalize
Stephen Collins?
CAMERON: You've gotta love him
for it, haven't you?
I mean,
you give him 24 hours,
body in the alley,
and this geezer
will turn it into
a full-blown
corporate conspiracy.
You don't see
any connection?
No.
All right.
Let's go through
what we know, okay?
The guy that was
stalking Sonia Baker,
he shot Deshaun Stagg
and Vernon Sando.
Deshaun Stagg,
of no fixed abode,
he boosts a briefcase.
Now, in that briefcase
are these photographs,
and according to our source,
a little baggie
of weird bullets.
Metro PD ballistics tell me
the casings at
the crime scene were reloads,
untraceable.
The slugs were hand cast
at twice the weight of
store-bought bullets,
X'ed for expansion.
So that means
that the shooter
intended to kill.
Stagg and Sando were
both double-tapped,
one bullet in the spine,
one in the head.
That is the mark of a pro,
or at the very least,
somebody with
a military background,
perhaps even Special Forces.
PointCorp founded by,
staffed by 100% ex-military.
I think that's
a connection
we can't ignore.
Chris, how long before
we have to hand these over?
CHRIS: Time to verify,
consult relevant case files,
outside counsel,
48 hours, tops.
But if this is evidence,
don't they need
to see it now?
How's he doing?
Hey, you gonna let me know
if I gotta call
the ID team, right?
NURSE: I'll let you know.
Walter Schroyer,
Army buddy of your
libidinous friend,
gives his moving tribute
to Stephen Collins
in that asswipe
excuse of a paper
and not to us. Why?
CAL: Platitudes,
padding and fluff.
I'm a journalist.
I'm not a publicist.
CAMERON: I want to bring
some more people in
to work with
you on this, Cal,
on the political side,
people with real experience.
I'm thinking Ted Moody.
I mean,
Ted's perfect for this.
Are you taking me
off the story?
No, no.
Not off, just off point.
If this is as big as he
says it is, a big "if,"
then it's gonna
be good for you.
How? How is that good?
Well, watching
seasoned reporters
that work on
a big story, you know,
being a part of it all,
you'll learn a lot.
So, Ted Moody,
what do you think?
Don't let her do it.
And, Cal, if you're on this,
I want this to be
clean through and through.
Tell her to forget it.
It's your gig.
You got it. Get loud now.
Excuse me.
You're defending her now?
She's fine.
I can work with her.
But, Cal,
she's inexperienced.
Inexperience isn't fatal.
I'm not giving up the story!
I just... Sorry. I just...
If I could just have
a few more days with it,
I promise you I'm not
gonna let you down.
For Christ's sake.
Don't throw those
dewy cub reporter
eyes at me.
It's nauseating.
And fuck you very much.
Pleasure.
This is Nurse
Leif and myself...
The lab work's back.
It's the panel 13 you ordered?
Yeah, well, we called for
a neurologist a half hour ago.
You can't use
that phone here, sir.
Hey. What's up, Carnes?
How you doing?
Yeah. Yeah.
Looks like that
Sando guy's waking up.
You sending anyone over?
You ever been
to D.C. Hospital?
No.
Don't worry about it.
It's easy.
CAL: All right,
there's a uniformed officer
on the third floor ICU.
Okay.
Write it down. Got a pen?
Yes.
Here.
I have a pen.
Okay.
The uniformed officer's
name is Brown.
Okay.
Brown.
Third floor ICU.
Tell him that
Detective Bynes,
B-Y-N-E-S, Joe Bynes...
Okay.
All right,
he cleared you for access.
Access for what?
Vernon Sando, the pizza guy,
looks like he's coming around.
That's your side
of the story.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
You want me to go
and sit around
in some hospital,
waiting for a guy
who looks like he might be
coming out of a coma,
while you clean up
the rest of the story?
I mean, is that what
that was all about in there?
Look, this is a real story.
It's not open
for interpretation.
It does not require opinion.
We got two dead bodies,
and we got a guy in a coma,
and we got us with a lead
that nobody else has got.
So you gotta make
a decision,
because I have to follow
another lead tonight,
and I cannot be in
two places at one time.
So, are you gonna
be okay slumming it
to find out if Vernon Sando's
coming around or not?
Good.
If we're gonna work together,
we gotta work together.
Yeah? Deal?
All right, see you later.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
Excuse me.
Don't tell me
you're still lost.
Hey, what are you
doing here?
Working.
You're Officer Brown?
You're who I'm looking for.
(CHUCKLING) I knew
you'd come around.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
How about Sando?
Is he coming around?
Yeah, yeah,
it looks that way.
They're sending
a detective over
right now.
Maybe get an ID.
Really?
I gotta take this.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah, Officer Brown.
No, sir.
You okay?
My dad did warn me
about politicians.
The only people
he hated more was
journalists.
Smart man.
I'm making you nervous.
You always did.
Well, they say
sex is the best way
to ruin a friendship.
They do, do they?
And who's they?
What, Cosmopolitan magazine?
Teen Beat?
Come on.
Tell me, please,
it didn't ruin ours.
It hasn't ruined anything.
NURSE: Pulse is 82.
BP is 105 over 79,
O2 sats 94.
He seems stable.
DOCTOR: Okay, let's do another
blood work-up, CBCs...
Miss, you cannot be in here.
I'd just like to
ask him
a couple of questions.
DOCTOR: Miss, please!
No, I'm sorry.
Come on. Look.
You know you're not
supposed to be in here.
I know. I just...
(SCREAMING)
Get on the ground!
OFFICER BROWN:
Stand back! Stay down.
(MONITOR BEEPING RAPIDLY)
That's a colleague of mine.
I'm gonna have to go.
I'm really sorry.
I'll see you soon.
Okay.
(SIRENS WAILING)
OFFICER: Let him through.
Blockade, let him through.
Hey, Ricky!
Let him through.
Della!
You okay? You all right?
Della, tell me
that's not yours, right?
What is it?
It's just
a little bit of blood.
It's all right.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's okay.
(WHIMPERING)
(CRYING)
It's all right. It's
all right. It's all right.
Oh, my God, Cal,
we could have stopped this!
What, by being psychic?
No. We should have given
the police that file.
What if there
were fingerprints
on the photographs?
God, Cal, we can't just let
people get hurt like that.
Look, it's over.
It's all right.
It's okay.
We can't just keep
letting people get killed.
No, it's not okay.
It's okay.
It's over. It's over.
It's over.
All right? It's okay.
CHRIS: You're sitting
on evidence in an
execution homicide.
How do you think
that's gonna play
with the family of the guy
that just got
shot last night?
Chris, let's be productive.
Hold on,
I'm actually not done.
Our reporter made
a full statement last night.
CHRIS: What,
you had these when?
Cam, don't answer that!
When did you have these?
You want subpoenas?
I'll get on
the phone right now.
We called you! We called you
before we called
outside counsel.
A little late.
It's a little late.
Give me a break.
How you doing, Don?
I'm hanging in, Cal. You?
Good. Good.
This source have anything else
I might need to do my job?
Wait a minute.
Nothing, all right?
This was it,
and we've kept it
for less than a day.
Detective, until last night,
we didn't actually
know what we had here.
Bullshit.
DONALD: Who do you think I am,
Bambi's baby brother?
No, sir.
You knew exactly
what you had.
You just decided
that your need was
greater than ours,
and now you have
blood on your hands.
CAL: Hold on.
CAMERON: Detective, look.
The thesis that
we are pursuing
involves a certain company
that Congressman
Collins is investigating.
DONALD: What, this is
corporate conspiracies
that threaten
the highest levels?
All my years on the job,
I've only ever seen that
on TV.
All the years I've known you,
you've only ever
watched sports on TV.
CAMERON: So, Detective,
in exchange for
our cooperation,
can we be assured
that you will open
your books to us?
Quid pro quo?
If we decide to go
public with this,
we'll give you six hours,
but that's the end of it.
This is an open
homicide investigation.
You slow us down,
endanger the public
any more than
you already have,
it won't be pretty.
For the record,
I'm still not happy
the way you presented
the evidence.
I'm just gonna
put that out there.
CAMERON: Police gossip
being what it is,
I'm guessing that even
Entertainment Tonight
will know as much as we do
within 48 hours.
So we've gotta have
something solid today.
That means no assumptions,
no unnamed sources.
Not fast and loose.
I want this thing wrung out.
Damned if we can't
do a better job of it
than those cops.
Della, how are you?
I'm good.
Yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
Good, okay.
Well, you take
Sonia Baker, okay?
I want to know everything
that we can about her,
who she knew, who she blew,
the color of her knickers.
Got it.
PointCorp?
Okay. Hank and Pete,
you work with Cal.
Cool.
The rule on this
one is discretion.
This is not a good
subject for gossip over
drinks at the Monocle,
or spliffs in
the stationery
cupboard, you.
I'm offended, truly.
CAMERON: Well, be offended.
Go downstairs,
get your stuff,
bring it in here,
because this is
your new home.
Go on!
Okay! Yes, yes, yes.
Speed of light.
Cal? Any conflict
of interest here?
No.
SLATOFF: Perhaps this is
a good opportunity
to address another issue
that's been discussed
during these hearings,
your price structure.
Surely,
and I thank you
for giving me
an opportunity to
touch on that today.
Our price structure follows
the Defense Department model
as established in
the first Gulf War,
adjusted, of course,
for inflation.
Happily,
what's costing us so much
this time around
are some incredible advances
in on-field medical care.
But, simply,
we're now keeping more...
Sir, I'm sorry. Just...
When you were in the military,
did you see any combat duty?
No, sir, I did not.
No.
Do you think if you had,
you might see
things differently?
MAN: We're all aware
of your war record,
Congressman.
STEPHEN: I'm not talking
about my record.
I'm talking about the numerous
allegations of atrocities
committed by PointCorp
and its subsidiary
contractors
against
the civilian population
in Iraq and Afghanistan.
MAN: Those are
unsubstantiated allegations.
Okay.
This is straightforward.
Since a war on
terror was declared,
has your personal
net worth gone up
by more than $250 million?
Straightforward question.
Excuse me,
I was told that
personal financial data
would not be addressed
in open session.
Adapt.
Isn't that your slogan?
"Adapt and Achieve?"
It's on the brochure here.
"Commoda et Confice."
You have it in Latin.
MAN: Your point being?
Putting war in
the hands of mercenaries
and those who
consider it a business
is a contradiction in
terms in any language.
May I remind you,
sir, that the wars
this country fought,
that defined it,
were fought
despite what they cost,
not because of it.
I didn't come here for
a lesson in morality,
Congressman.
No, I expect you didn't.
Well, especially from you.
The men who work
for PointCorp,
the men you dishonor by
calling them mercenaries
are, by and large,
retired American
military personnel.
It's a great system,
isn't it?
We pay to train these men,
and you get rich
by killing them.
(CROWD MURMURING)
PETE: PointCorp,
well, they're on a roll.
They just bought 60,000 acres
to expand their facility.
60,000 acres.
Yeah.
Where?
In Conway, North Carolina.
The locals call
it Little Baghdad.
Not so little.
HANK: They've also got
some interesting real
estate locally.
Offices at
the Watergate building.
Check that out.
"Medal of Freedom Initiative."
What's that?
PETE: It's a lobbying
interest.
HANK: Yeah,
according to the website,
MOFI,
Medal of Freedom Initiative,
is an umbrella
group for a bunch
of these private
defense contractors.
You know,
they lobby a little,
party a little, kill things.
PETE: MOFI!
(WHOOPING)
Hello?
PETE: We went down there.
The place is totally empty...
Like they're just
waiting for all their
new recruits.
Did they outsource to Mumbai
or something?
Or are they
just getting ready
for an expansion?
CAL: Hello?
This is Della Frye.
I'm a reporter
over at the Globe.
You were Sonia
Baker's attorney
on her
shoplifting case,
correct?
MAN: Did Dominic
give you my number?
Yes, how do you
know Dominic?
Well, I'm sorry. This
really isn't appropriate.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
I...
Hey, Michael,
I need someone
to help me dig
a little deeper
into PointCorp.
I need somebody
on the inside,
somebody who knows
the way they operate.
WOMAN: She owed
everybody money.
Oh, God,
that's how she always
walked around,
in her underwear.
Yeah!
You moved.
You can't move.
Hi! Hi, yes, yes.
Who is this?
He looks familiar.
WOMAN: Dominic Foy.
He's a friend of Sonia's.
Dominic.
Hey, Michael, it's Cal.
So what did you find out?
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
DELLA: Hi. Mr. Statler?
STATLER: Yes?
Yes, I'm from the Globe.
I'm writing
an article on the death
of Sonia Baker,
and I just wanted to...
And he was, like,
high up in PointCorp?
Hi. Della Frye from
the Washington Globe.
I... Could I speak to you?
Please don't...
Yes, I'm still holding
'cause that's what I do.
That's what I like to do.
Sonia Baker's ex-roommate,
Rhonda Silver.
Nobody's got her yet.
She changed her
name a couple times
in the past year.
How'd you get it?
I had to agree
to go on not one,
but two dates with
a sweaty guy named Vic.
Don't even ask me.
Hey, Bob, it's Cal.
Want to run a Social
Security number for me?
(EXCLAIMS)
Rhonda Silver's number.
Did we just break the law?
Nope, that's what you call
damn fine reporting.
Your pen.
Keep it.
You're welcome!
Thank you!
Hi. Is Rhonda there, please?
I'm actually an old
friend of Rhonda's
from school.
I'm in town for the day,
and I thought maybe
I'd stop by and see her.
Do you think I could
show up at her work?
Would that be all right?
Actually, sir,
can I call you back?
That page and the next page.
HANK: This guy, Jerry Symes,
local politician,
he campaigns
against the expansion,
and then he dies in
a freak car accident.
CAL: All right,
what does "freak
car accident" mean?
Middle of the day...
He's driving on the
open road...
No witnesses.
...30 miles an hour...
Perfect weather,
no skid marks.
...car turns over.
And the police think
it might be sleep apnea.
Cal. Sorry,
I really need to talk to you.
What do you got?
So, I was looking
for images of Sonia
in the Metro security
footage, right?
And 20 seconds after
she went into the blind spot,
this guy appears.
Okay?
I think that I
saw him last night
at the hospital.
Are you sure?
Michael, it's Cal.
Your PointCorp insider,
I need to meet him, now.
I want you to know something.
I love my country.
I love the military.
My aim here is to save them.
You understand my terms?
I will not give you my name.
I will not give you
my rank in the PointCorp
military structure,
or the in and out
dates of my service.
Understand.
CAL: I'm looking for
a guy that PointCorp
are using on
a covert operation.
Total deniability.
Our mutual friend
at DOD thought
you might be able
to help us find him.
I don't know.
I'll check it out.
So, what's your understanding
of the PointCorp MO?
Their MO?
They do whatever
the hell they want.
These soldiers are
answerable to no one.
They're loyal to nothing
but a paycheck.
It's the Muslim
terror gold rush.
You've been watching
these hearings?
Yeah.
So, the head of
the committee there,
Stephen Collins...
He's finished.
They'll just keep
knocking him down
until he goes away.
Do you have any idea
what he's threatening here?
This is $30 or $40
billion annually.
That's wrath of God money.
The hearings
are saying 3 or 4.
Overseas. The real
money is what PointCorp
stands to make in its
domestic operations.
I wasn't aware
that they had any.
Who was sent in
for crowd control
after Hurricane Katrina? Us.
Private security
contractors deputized
to shoot at
American citizens.
Who's training
Chicago police on new
interrogation techniques?
Soon, PointCorp will
take over from the NSA
on phone taps,
terrorist databases,
all of it.
It's a fundamental
restructuring
of domestic
intelligence policy.
It is the privatization
of Homeland Security.
Billions and
billions of dollars.
Now you really think
they're gonna
forfeit all that
because some hero
from the seventh district
of Pennsylvania thinks
that they should?
Hey.
CAL: I just got told
by a former
PointCorp employee
that they have a plan
to monopolize
domestic security
that's worth about
$40 billion a year.
Is that true?
STEPHEN: Yes.
CAL: How?
You cannot connect anything
that I tell you back to me.
You understand?
Of course.
Okay.
Last year, 47 companies
bid on major Homeland
Security contracts.
Of those,
16 companies were
granted the bids.
Of those,
I could make connections
between 14 companies,
and I'm not
just talking about someone
leaving one company
and go work for another.
I'm talking about
shared banking practices.
collusive behavior.
Now, my belief is,
when all's said and done
and when
the veil is pulled away,
you will not see 14
individual companies.
You will see one company.
You understand?
And you've been
digging around
trying to make
those connections clear.
Yeah. That's right.
And Sonia was
working on that?
She was my lead researcher.
She was involved in
everything we did.
They're gonna
get you, Stephen,
one way or another.
They got 40
billion good reasons to want
you out of the way.
You gotta go on the record.
Swing the spotlight
back on them.
You gotta
protect yourself, man.
You go out there
and find me evidence
linking Sonia's
death to PointCorp.
I will go on the record.
I will shout this thing
from the rooftops.
I can do that.
All right.
I gotta get back.
I'll be in touch.
Stephen.
Yeah?
Just watch your back.
You, too.
Hi. Is Rhonda here?
Yeah, she's just
right over there.
(SINGING) Whoa
I'm walking on sunshine
Whoa
And don't it feel good
Yeah!
DELLA: Cal, you're not gonna
believe what Sonia's old
roommate just told me.
You're right.
I don't believe
a word of it.
You got no corroboration,
no independent witness,
and she obviously has
a financial motivation.
We've got Sonia
Baker's roommate claiming
she had a threesome
with Stephen Collins,
and you want to ignore that?
I am not saying ignore it.
I am saying consider it.
Consider how it impacts
everything else we have,
and consider that
she is full of shit!
Yeah, but, Cal,
she's also saying
that Stephen paid off
Sonia's $40,000
credit card debt.
That is a story.
Somebody's gonna put that
on the front page.
Okay, is that
the right thing to do?
Look, it's your half
of the story.
It's your scoop.
Your decision.
Do whatever you want.
ANNE: But I do know
that Stephen and I
have been through
far too much together
to make this one moment
the thing that
defines us forever.
REPORTER: The political
future...
I tried to call.
I mean, I actually
did call about 12 times,
but I hung up every time.
Well, you know,
I'm glad you dropped by,
'cause I've been
wanting to talk to you.
Remember you
brought that girl
from Humboldt?
Soleil,
or whatever her name was.
Luna.
Luna. That's right.
And you two were
stoned the whole time.
Yep.
You managed to flip the boat,
and we lost everything.
We had to walk
the rest of the way...
We flipped the boat?
You did.
It was an adventure.
That's what you kept saying.
Irish wine.
Whiskey?
Cheers.
Sláinte.
So...
I've been...
I wanted to ask...
Sorry.
You first.
I was wondering,
do you think Stephen
could have pulled together
$40,000 without you knowing?
What?
Well, it's a story
that might break
that basically
accuses Stephen
of doing something
that would require
his having access
to a large amount of cash.
I was just wondering,
could he do that?
A story that might break?
You mean something that
you're involved in?
Indirectly.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to help Stephen.
I'm trying to protect you.
Bullshit!
(SIGHS)
You always do this.
Sometimes I feel like
we all made this deal,
and it works out
great for you and Stephen,
and not for me.
And instead of us
just figuring it out,
you guys are just
fine walking around
as if nothing ever happened.
Okay.
Okay, let's start over.
I come here to tell you
that I'm thinking
about walking away
from my marriage,
and you say what?
I say it's too late.
We're way past this.
You made your choice.
Because you
wouldn't step up.
(STAMMERING)
What do you mean?
Not then, not now,
not in college.
I'm saying that
you're asking me
for something
that's not real.
That's what I'm saying.
(SIGHS)
Annie...
We have two mortgages.
We have the place
in Virginia.
We've got
the apartment here.
Basically, we spend
everything we make,
so there's no way
Stephen could have
given anyone $40,000
without me
knowing about it.
Annie...
It's okay.
Now I'm just a source,
so the pressure's off.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
MAN ON PHONE: Who's the
great-Iooking blonde, Cal?
Who's this?
Across the street.
I like your style, man.
I got something for you.
And you couldn't
just ring the doorbell?
Precautions.
The guy in the photo,
I asked around.
He's definitely a grunt.
Buddy of mine used to see him
at security trade shows.
Never knew his name,
but he worked
for an old-timer
called Fred Summers.
Does alarm installations,
shit like that.
Here's Fred's address.
Crystal City.
Thanks.
Mr. Summers?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hey.
Who you looking for?
Fred. Fred Summers.
Do you know him?
Fred's not here.
Oh, yeah? Uh-huh.
You live here.
You're his roommate.
Sorry. Okay.
Do you know
where he might be?
He's overseas.
He shipped out last week.
Overseas like...
Look, I don't really know
what Fred's into, okay?
He ships out,
and he comes back.
(STAMMERING) Okay.
Could you pass a message?
Take it easy.
All right. Okay.
Hey, Joey? Cal McAffrey.
(WHISPERING)
Yeah, yeah, shut up.
Listen! Listen!
Tell Bill he's gotta
send some cops to 566...
(RUSTLING)
(GASPS)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(CHATTERING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(CAR ENGINE STARTING)
(YELLING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(WINCES)
DELLA: So?
DONALD: No sign of the guy.
Did you get a name?
How about the apartment?
You find something?
Nothing?
Place belongs to a guy
named Fred Summers,
except Fred passed away
last March.
Neighbors say that
his nephew stays there
from time to time
while the probate
is being worked out.
Except he doesn't
have a nephew.
You're catching on fast.
Cal, I thought we had
an understanding.
You were supposed to share
your information with us.
Do you remember that?
Don, I went there
to talk to a guy named
Fred Summers, right,
who I now find
out is deceased.
Do you think
I would've gone there
if I knew what I was
gonna be walking into?
Just happened to
be there, huh?
Yeah.
Now, do you mind
if I get back
on with my story?
It's not a story.
It's a case!
And... And just so you know,
a girl by the name
of Mandi Brokaw,
16, junkie,
turned up dead tonight.
Probable homicide.
She look familiar?
We got her fingerprints
off of those
surveillance photos
you so kindly gave us.
Hello, I'm Rhonda Silver.
Like I said,
that's what he called
"being in committee."
I know you got shot
at last night,
and I know I should be making
you a nice cup of cocoa,
but I'm just so bloody angry!
I mean, the decision,
I'm assuming, was that
this was not news.
We... Look, we didn't...
We were worried that...
It was my call, Cam.
All right?
I didn't, and I don't
believe her.
(SCOFFS)
She's not credible.
She was just trying
to sell us her sexy
scrapbook photos of
her friend, Sonia Baker.
Her dead friend.
Yeah, well,
why the hell couldn't
we have printed that?
A waitress comes forward
with a claim about
a sex scandal.
Great, that's an A-1 story.
Then he denies it.
There's another story.
And then... And then
one of them cracks,
and there's another story.
Meantime, people are
reading about it,
and they're
reading us about it,
because we had it first!
Except we didn't, did we?
No, no, no, 'cause some wanker
decided it was beneath us.
Look at her, come on!
Look at her!
She's a sideshow!
It's a smear campaign.
It's exactly what
these companies do
to destroy people
who get in their way.
The true story here,
the real story here,
is PointCorp.
The real story is the sinking
of this bloody newspaper!
Christ!
(SIGHS)
We have new management
to answer to now, Cal,
and they are
interested in sales,
not discretion.
And how am... How am I
gonna tell them that we are
now behind a story
we were once in front of?
Well, we're running with
what we've got today.
No! No.
You can't do that.
Why not?
We've got more than
enough to go with.
You run with it,
and you're gonna
frighten off the wildlife.
And we haven't got
the rest of the story.
I do not give a shit
about the rest of the story!
We are going to
press tonight.
You've got eight hours.
WOMAN: You look tired.
Want some coffee?
Yeah, that's nice.
Can you hold on
for one second?
George, a word with you
for a minute?
Sure, Steve.
Thanks.
Listen, I just wanted
you to know
my speaking up
in the hearings
the other day
was not meant
in any way as a gesture
of disrespect to you
or a lack of gratitude
for the support that you've
shown me.
No, no. Not at all.
It was a very
impressive performance.
You have your passions,
I understand that.
All right, good. Well,
that's a relief to know.
You have your show horses,
and you have your work horses.
I'm sure we can all
find a way to get along.
There's no way.
There is no way we
can meet that deadline.
Yes, we can.
All right, guys, we're
getting our balls busted.
What do you got?
All right, the guy
you had us check out,
Dominic Foy,
turns out he's a gold mine.
CAL: Dominic?
Foy.
Right.
He's a guy
I keep hearing about.
A friend of Sonia's in all
the surveillance
photos where she's crying.
And he's in
Rhonda's cell phone shots.
CAL: Mmm-hmm.
Okay, so,
is this Halloween,
or is he
some kind of freak?
PETE: Freak.
He runs a legitimate
PR business.
Handful of corporate clients.
Just likes to party
on the weekends.
PETE: Special parties.
Tell him the good part.
Yeah,
mostly works out
of the Daily Grill,
but guess where his
registered office is?
Where?
Guess.
HANK: The Watergate.
Oh.
PETE: Not only that,
Suite 413.
Same suite as the Medal
of Freedom Initiative,
which is...
The lobbying
subsidiary of PointCorp.
Let's get him on tape.
PETE: You want me to
call Rodney and get the gear?
Yeah, same place.
What... I'm sorry.
You want to
put him on tape?
Yeah.
What are we, cops now?
That's totally illegal.
If Dominic Foy can
connect Sonia Baker
to PointCorp,
he's gonna be
under a lot of pressure
to recant anything
he might tell us,
all right?
So we put him on tape.
That's our insurance.
And why do you think
he's even gonna talk to you?
Because he's scared.
How do you know?
Because I'm gonna scare him.
Hey, is that your
Cadillac out there?
Yeah.
V-8 XLR, 320 horsepower,
adaptive cruise control,
heads-up display?
That's the one.
That's a hell of
an impressive car.
Yes, I know.
What do you got
in your gay-rage?
Excuse me?
Your gay-rage.
Your garage.
Right.
You drive
the same thing?
No, I don't.
I have a 1990 Saab.
Oh.
Yeah. I got velour seats.
The passenger side
one's ripped,
but it gets me
from A to B, you know.
Sorry to hear that.
If only I could get
a job in PR, right?
Who the hell are you?
Do you read
the newspapers,
Dominic?
Sometimes.
Okay.
I got something I want
to run by you, all right?
It ain't finished.
I'm still working it up.
Let's see how
you feel about this.
"Dominic Foy, a D.C.
Public relations figure
"with known ties
to defense contractor
PointCorp
"was yesterday
linked to the death
"of Capitol Hill
staffer Sonia Baker."
Come on.
Are you a reporter?
This is not cool.
This is definitely not cool.
Very unprofessional.
I'm just sitting here...
Cal McAffrey from the Globe.
Congratulations. Keep it.
That's gonna run
tomorrow unless
you can tell me what
I need to know today.
I don't think so.
I got a car out the back.
I got a nice, safe place
where you and I can talk.
Hey, hey, Saab.
I don't know anything about
anything, all right?
I'm a PR guy. Got it?
Be that as it may,
there's two ways
this article
can run, Dominic.
Without your name
or with your name,
and maybe even
a photo from your website.
Now, who knows who
that's gonna piss off
and how badly?
I'm trying to be
your friend, Dominic,
all right?
I'd hate to see you
end up under a train
like Sonia Baker.
And you promised never
to use my name, right?
Yes, I did.
This place is nice?
It's classy?
I'm gonna be
comfortable?
Uh-huh.
DOMINIC: What kind
of dump is this?
Where have you brought me?
No booze in the mini-bar.
There's no
On Demand on the TV.
What kind of hotel is this?
Little bit more of a motel,
I'd say, isn't it?
CAL: Nobody's gonna find
you here, Dominic.
DOMINIC:
How are your beer-getting
skills, sweet pea?
You want to go get
Uncle Foy a nice frosty?
I'll time you.
Christ.
So, let's start
from the beginning.
Where did you
meet Sonia Baker?
Why don't we start
with a little compensation?
This guy's
stoned off his face,
and now he wants a beer.
Can I have one?
Yeah.
What's he
taking exactly?
Dude, downers.
This guy's losing his shit.
For what? For what?
Me helping you out.
Me losing my business. Me...
This bed's disgusting.
Compensate me, okay?
Okay, so you want to be paid
to help solve Sonia's murder?
(SIGHS) Save it, all right?
I'm in PR.
I know a little bit
about phrasing questions.
Why don't you try
phrasing it like this?
Would I like to be paid
for helping you
get a book deal?
Nobody's here
for a book deal.
Really?
Everybody wants a book deal.
And I'd like my cut, okay?
That's just fair.
When did you meet Sonia?
Compensation,
compensation.
You came here
to talk, Dominic.
You know, mouse,
I'm the talent and I
don't like the vibe.
So why don't you
change that up, okay?
It's a non-smoking room.
It's under your name.
He's a douche.
I love this guy.
I want to call my lawyer.
I think you should
think that through.
Can we get a signal
in this rat hole?
Why don't you
think it through? Hmm?
Dominic, let me just lay this
out for you one more time,
because I don't
think you're getting it!
So I'll lay it out
for you! Okay?
Relax.
I'll lay it out for
you nice and clear!
The newspaper can slant this
any which way they want to,
and they can make you
the one and only
principal source.
How do you think
that's gonna go down
with your friends
at PointCorp?
Not great.
And anybody else
you're connected to?
Don't do that.
Please don't do that.
The more you talk,
the more you give us,
the more protected you are.
That's the way we work.
And your compensation
is your anonymity,
and that is all you're
gonna get from us.
Okay?
Yeah.
Great.
DELLA: Okay, how's
it going in here?
Sounds frigging great.
We're just about ready.
Let's do it.
DELLA: Great. Good.
Come on.
I'm not gonna do it.
I'm gonna open the door,
and I'm gonna
let you say it.
You have to talk to her.
Cal is asking us to
push the deadline.
We really can't
afford to keep doing
this type of thing.
Where the hell are they?
(EXCLAIMS) You saying that
as if I should know?
Yeah, well, you just
spoke to him.
Yeah, well,
they didn't tell
me where they were.
$20,000 an hour.
Yeah... All right!
Bugger off!
Shit.
It was just this guy, okay,
that I knew from
the clubs, all right?
And he worked
for a PR firm,
a very big one.
Name?
And... No, I'm not gonna
give you his name.
He's a friend, okay?
He had this, uh...
He had this...
Well, the company
that he worked
for had a client,
a very special client.
Name?
I'll give you that one.
PointCorp.
And they wanted
a special employee.
They needed a girl.
I thought of Sonia.
You got that?
I'm sorry, are you saying
that Sonia was working
for PointCorp?
Like a steel trap,
this one.
Don't lose her
to another paper.
Yeah, that's
what I'm saying.
Turn it up, turn it up.
DOMINIC:
She was a perfect fit.
She had balls.
She was smart.
She was in debt.
And she was
in debt, exactly. Yeah.
They paid her
$26,000 a month.
Whole hell of a lot
more than they gave me.
They paid me
a flat 20.
It's big.
Did they tell you
what the job was?
No, they did not.
She told me what
it was, though.
She told me about Collins.
She told me
about spying on him.
And did they want Sonia
to sleep with Collins?
No. She got on her
back all by herself
and screwed
everything up,
didn't she?
How did they get her
onto Collins' staff?
That I'm not gonna tell you.
You can forget it.
You can kidnap and torture
someone else for that toughie.
We have a deal.
Yeah.
I've done my work.
Nobody's here
to screw you,
but we need to know
who was working
this on the Hill.
Mmm-hmm.
From the Hill, huh?
Well, from the Hill,
they found a guy to fix it.
Name?
No.
Who?
Leave it.
Come on.
What, are you
not hearing me?
Forget it. I'd be
afraid to start that
sweet ass Caddy
every morning.
I mean, keep in mind
if I was driving
that wheelbarrow
Saab of yours,
I'd probably blow it up
myself with me in it.
You seen that thing?
It's like a lawnmower.
I'm gonna get you
another beer.
Hey.
Oi.
Are you sleeping
with that guy?
I mean, what are
you doing here?
Are you sleeping
with him? Hmm?
Or you got a guy.
You got a guy, right?
DOMINIC: Donna?
DELLA: Della.
DOMINIC: Della.
I got a guy.
Got a girl, too.
Right? I don't want
to leave anybody out.
Hey, Stephen.
How did you find Sonia?
STEPHEN: What?
How did she come to
work in your office?
Was somebody...
Did somebody recommend her?
What are you talking about?
I think you've been played.
Really?
Who gave you her name?
What is this about?
Don't dick around about this,
Stephen, all right?
Two questions.
How the hell did she come
to work in your office,
and the name of
the individual
who recommended her?
Fergus. George Fergus.
Said she was the daughter
of an old family friend.
Doug Sponder's
bachelor party.
You remember that hotel,
the Americana?
Yes.
Get here now, alone.
I'm in Room 408.
I'll meet you
at the office.
Stephen, we're
late already.
I'll call in.
Stephen, we are
late already.
I'll call in.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
Don't check
your voicemail.
Cameron's going
on a rampage
about this deadline.
So, did you cue it
where I asked?
HANK: Close enough.
Okay. So, guys,
I'm gonna need you
to clear the room.
That means you, too.
What?
CAL: I got Stephen Collins
coming in here.
It's gonna be a lot
more comfortable for him
if you're not here,
all right?
Tell me you're kidding.
DELLA: Since when does
the subject of an
investigation
get his own private
preview of another
subject's interview?
That's crazy!
You're polluting the story!
Special circumstance.
What? What?
Is it that he's a congressman,
or that he's your friend,
or that you have
a crush on his wife?
Could you
fill me in here?
All of the above.
DELLA: Oh, my God,
you're such a hypocrite!
This is my story, too,
and you are about
to kill it forever
by letting him
come in here.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
I'm gonna
bring him in.
I'm gonna sit him down,
show him this.
I'm gonna get him
on the record,
then we've got both
sides of the story.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
CAL: Stephen Collins,
Della Frye.
Congressman.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You know this guy?
No.
You don't
recognize him at all?
I don't know. Maybe.
Is this in here?
No, no, it's next door.
He's sleeping it off.
Sit down.
Okay.
CAL: PointCorp wanted to plant
someone on your staff.
This guy, Dominic Foy,
he finds Sonia.
He takes a fee.
George Fergus does the rest.
No. That's not possible.
They paid off her debt,
and they paid her
monthly to report back
every single thing
that you were doing.
And when she went dry,
they killed her for it.
How do you know this?
DOMINIC: And so I get a call,
I gotta go down
to a street corner.
I gotta buy a magazine.
I gotta meet some new guy.
This guy, you know,
he's some hardcore,
thick-neck, corn-fed,
Navy-SEAL-Iooking guy,
you know?
And he's all up in my face,
scaring the hell out of me
because he's
pissed off and...
When was this?
DOMINIC: This is
like a month ago.
You know,
he's pissed off because
Sonia's not giving
him anything anymore.
And what did he want
you to do about it?
He wants me to fix it.
He wants me to fix it,
like one of my hair dryers.
And did you?
I tried.
I tried. I called.
She wouldn't take my call.
I go over there.
I try to talk to her.
She's crying.
DELLA: Why is she crying?
She's scared somebody's
after her?
DOMINIC: No, she's crying
because of Collins.
She was in love with him,
and she was pregnant,
and she didn't tell him.
She didn't tell him,
and, you know,
she was petrified
that he's gonna find
out what she did,
and then he's
not gonna want her,
and he's not
gonna want the baby...
She got so wrecked
about it that she burned
thousands of dollars
worth of paychecks.
Who does that?
(SOBBING) And I tried
to get her to just relax
and to think
about the publicity,
or think about an abortion,
or think about,
you know, her word.
"Just keep your word.
And what about how
"your decisions
are gonna affect me?"
And then she's dead,
you know? I hear
it's a murder,
and so I don't
want anything more
to do with this thing,
you know?
I'm just terrified,
and I want to go
someplace warm,
and I want to come
back to a clean slate.
And you guys write
your article and just get
them off me.
I'm nothing.
I'm nothing to those guys.
So you were right, man. Okay?
And now we can prove it.
I get you on the record.
We can nail these
mothers to the wall!
Sliberty?
We can nail them to the wall,
all right? We win!
Yeah. Just...
All right?
(STEPHEN COUGHS)
Just... Will you just
give me a minute?
Okay.
He just needs
a minute.
Shit!
Get off... Get off of me!
You fucking...
Help!
Stephen!
Get up!
What are you doing?
Hey, stop!
No!
CAL: Come on, man!
Hey! Hey!
Get off!
What the hell are
you doing to him?
CAL: Stephen!
Stephen! Stephen! Stephen!
Hey, I'm trying to
help you, man. Yeah.
She was pregnant, Cal.
Did I need
to hear that?
Yeah.
Huh? You couldn't
tell me yourself?
You had to do it like that?
Was that important to you...
I thought you'd want
to hear the truth.
That's right.
You were just seeking
the truth, that's all.
You're just...
You're a truth seeker.
That's all.
You can't help it.
It's who you are.
You're such a hypocrite.
You're not
interested in me.
Me coming here
was all about you
and getting your story.
I trusted you.
You're my friend!
You were supposed
to be my friend
when you were
screwing my wife!
You're my friend, Cal.
I never would've
done this to you!
I'm sorry, Stephen, okay?
I'm sorry
about all of it.
Please, look,
I've been an asshole,
and I can understand
why you hate me for it.
You've just gotta put aside
how you feel about me
and stay with this.
We're so close.
Every single part of this,
I have put myself on the line.
Stephen.
Stephen!
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(GROWLS)
(DRAMATIC INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
I need a minute with
Congressman Fergus.
Tell him it's Cal McAffrey
from the Globe,
and I'm on a deadline.
(INAUDIBLE WHISPERING)
Fuck him.
Asshole.
It's all right. I saw that.
Just give him this card
and tell him it's an issue
that directly concerns him.
Sir? He asked me
to give you this.
Excuse me.
Congressman.
That Cal McAffrey.
What's up?
How'd you find me?
I followed the trail
of crumbs, Congressman.
I need
a confirmation from you
for an article that
we're running tomorrow.
I have been told
that you recommended
to Greer Thornton
to hire Sonia Baker,
is that correct?
So?
So if it turns out
that Sonia Baker was,
in fact,
gathering information
on Stephen Collins'
committee findings
and passing that
information back
to the very company
that was being investigated
and that company is
complicit in her murder,
well, Jesus Christ,
it's not gonna look
too good for you,
is it, Congressman?
One, never use
the Lord's name
in vain with me.
Two, how could you
even assume
that a bright, naive,
25-year-old girl
was what, a double agent?
Mr. McAffrey, I went
to bat for a young girl
whose family I met
and respected,
a family that
seemed like
the wholesome ideal
upon which this
country was founded.
And Sonia Baker's
mother's first name is?
Pardon me?
You heard me,
family friend.
Do you really think
that your new owners,
these responsible
corporate citizens,
are going to allow
you to publish this
speculative drivel?
You are gonna be
out of a job before
the devil can even
say your name, son.
Janine.
Sonia's mother's
first name is Janine.
CAL: You're missing the point.
You didn't see his face.
I saw his face. Fergus is
at the heart of this story.
CAMERON:
This story is dead, Cal.
One way or another,
PointCorp pushed
Sonia Baker in
front of that train.
Really? The trouble is,
our new corporate owners
won't let me print any of this
unless I have one
of the major players
on the record.
On the record, Cal!
And the only person
who could do that won't.
Would you like
to tell me why?
Or is it just that
you shagged his wife?
Maybe you'd like to
explain to me how, when
and why MediaCorp
chopped off your balls.
This is as big and as
connected as it gets.
You follow
any fissure of this,
it's a massive story.
You got Fergus,
you got PointCorp,
and now you got MediaCorp,
all connected,
all in collusion,
all playing for
the same country club.
I didn't realize you'd
taken up the game.
Oh. Oh, Cal, if there's
any corruption involved here,
it's coming from you.
You have injected
yourself in this story
right from the beginning,
and we all know why.
It's over, Cal,
as far as you're concerned.
I can't protect you anymore.
And right now,
I'm not too sure
I'd want to.
You want the story?
Yeah. Come on.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I was first introduced
to Sonia Baker
in April of 2007.
She was hired
as a research assistant
on my staff.
She was recommended
by the Majority Whip,
Congressman from
West Virginia,
George Fergus.
Three months into
her time there,
Sonia and I began
a romantic relationship.
STEPHEN: I have e-mailed
copies of documents to you,
which show beyond doubt
the corruption between
members of my own party.
I now know
that she had been placed
in my office as a spy.
PointCorp's tentacles reach
into every corner
of the ever-growing
private security industry,
both at home and abroad.
Not only does
this pose a great...
But it is
a violation of our laws.
A monopolistic business...
...obstruct and
otherwise destroy
my investigation
into PointCorp.
Sonia was paid
to make regular reports
to PointCorp...
Left unchecked, I believe
that within five years,
PointCorp will have
its own standing army
on US soil.
...into their
fraudulent practices...
It will control our
intelligence-gathering
apparatus...
What happened in committee...
She had access to
everything we were doing
and effectively crippled
our investigation.
It is a frightening vision
and one which must be stopped.
However, when
my relationship with her grew,
she ceased her spying
on their behalf,
and I believe
they killed her for it.
STEPHEN: For people like this,
who I've spent
the last year and a half
of my life investigating...
Innocent civilians are
really little more than
disposable lives,
thought of as
collateral damage.
And I believe it was
simply the public nature
of my position that
saved me
from a similar fate.
So, as political suicides go,
how was that?
CAMERON:
Thank you, Congressman.
You okay?
Yeah.
He was set up.
She was sleeping with him
for $26,000 a month. I mean...
Sliberty.
Cal.
You all set?
Okay.
Mmm-Hmm.
Let's go.
(SIGHS)
You still here?
Yeah.
I thought you would've been
down at your desk
blasting it online.
Well, you know,
a piece this big,
people should
probably have newsprint
on their hands
when they read it,
don't you think?
I'll do Collins,
Fergus, PointCorp,
and corporate and
government malfeasance.
Okay.
You do Sonia Baker...
The murder, Mandi,
Rhonda Silver.
And the Dominic Foy
connection, all right?
Yeah.
Retire to the
neutral corner.
Okay.
Gentle. Thank you.
Sir, it's Robert Bingham.
I'm sorry to
call you directly.
I want to assure you
that I'm ready to finish
what we started.
Goodbye.
(GARBAGE DISPOSAL GRINDING)
I won't be
more than an hour.
Hey, guys.
Evening, sir.
How you doing?
(TAPPING)
Hello.
CAL: Is it a night for it?
Yeah, yeah,
I think it is.
So, how old are you?
Actually, don't tell me.
It would just
make me sick.
You never ask
a girl her age.
Well, see, I look at you,
and I don't see a girl.
I just see a reporter.
(SIGHS) At last.
Anyway, back to the story.
Yes.
So I had this, uh, English
teacher in high school.
Mmm-hmm.
He was a kind of a longhaired
hippie kind of guy.
Mmm-hmm.
He had
a pen problem. Yeah.
Oh.
He solved it by
having a piece
of leather string
around his neck,
and that's where
he'd keep his pen.
Smart.
So I started thinking,
"My friend Della's
got a pen problem.
(EXCLAIMS)
"How do I solve it?"
And I came up
with this.
What is it?
I call it the "Della
Frye Nubian Princess,
"'I'm never without a pen"'
celebratory necklace.
Oh, it's beautiful!
I always wanted one
of these.
Cheers.
You know, I wanted
to tell you something
about Anne Collins.
Okay.
I was just talking to her.
How does Anne
Collins know that
Sonia Baker was
earning $26,000 a month?
What?
How does she know
how much Sonia Baker
was earning?
We know that.
Yeah.
How does Anne
Collins know that?
Well, I mean, Stephen
must have heard it
in the Foy interview.
We played him
a specific part
of that tape,
and that figure
is never mentioned.
Cal. Wait,
what are you doing?
DELLA: What are
you doing? Cal?
You gonna fill me in?
Just tell Cameron,
"Hold the story."
What? Cal? Cal!
Shit.
Who's Robert Bingham,
Stephen?
Who is Robert Bingham?
(SIGHS)
Are the police outside?
No.
I saved Robert Bingham's
life in Kuwait in '91.
He was a 17-year-old kid.
He was a good soldier.
He was proud
of what we did.
The Army was his life,
and he had problems
when he got discharged.
So you had a guy that
you knew to be unstable
do what, exactly?
Scare her?
Maybe beat her up
a little?
No, Cal.
I had him follow her.
Why?
Because I knew
she was hiding
something from me.
Because when I'd...
I'd be at her house
and a fax would come in,
she'd get nervous.
Because there were
phone calls late at night.
I was suspicious.
I asked Bingham
to observe her
and report back to me.
That's all.
You're a liar, Stephen.
He was more upset
about what she was
doing than I was.
You have to understand
what the military
means to Bingham.
He hates PointCorp
for what they're
trying to do to it.
In his mind,
she just had to stop.
But she did stop,
right?
She tore up her paychecks,
and she put her life
at risk for you.
Yes, but I didn't
know that.
I didn't know that
he was gonna kill her.
I didn't know
he had killed her.
When I found out,
my thought was just
the same as yours.
I thought PointCorp
had done it.
And when you did
find out?
What was
I supposed to do?
Tell someone.
I tried.
When?
When I came
to your house,
and I wanted to
talk to you about it,
and all you cared
about was the story.
No, Stephen,
I cared about helping you.
Bullshit. Bullshit.
All you cared about was
clearing your conscience
over this little soap opera
you have with Annie.
So you used me.
No, Cal.
The same way
as you used Bingham.
I was suspicious of her.
I brought him in.
That's all it was!
It was a mistake!
It's my responsibility.
I should never
have done that.
But I never asked
him to kill her.
He owed you his life!
That's why
you called him.
You called him,
and you used him,
like you've been
trying to use me.
One to kill,
and one to cover it up.
If PointCorp and
Fergus hadn't hired her,
none of this
would've happened!
No. This is not about Bingham
and PointCorp
and Fergus, man!
It's about you
and the decisions
that you have made
that have led to four
people being killed.
One of them was
delivering a pizza,
Stephen.
Cal. What are
you gonna do?
You know
what I'm gonna do.
You know, it's laughable,
your sense of
your own self-worth.
Why is that?
'Cause nobody reads
the papers anymore?
Is that it?
It's just another story,
a couple days of shitstorm,
and it's wrapping paper?
You know, in the middle
of all this gossip
and speculation
that permeates
people's lives,
I still think
they know the difference
between real news
and bullshit.
And they're glad that
someone cares enough
to get things on the record
and print the truth.
Cal. Please,
Cal, don't do this.
Please.
I'm asking you
as your friend.
You got about three minutes
before the cops get here.
I thought you said
you didn't call them.
I lied.
(KEYS RATTLING)
(GUN COCKING)
A good soldier fights
for his country
and his friends.
(SIRENS WAILING)
But these guys,
they want to make it
all about the money.
You want to live
in a world like that?
DONALD: Drop the weapon!
The story about
Stephen comes out,
whether I write it or not.
COP 1: Drop your weapon!
COP 2: Drop it!
I'd rather be nothing.
COP 1: I repeat,
drop your weapon!
(GUNS FIRING)
(SIGHS)
CAMERON: Well, aren't
you gonna send it?
I've only been holding
the front page
for four hours, after all.
You send it.
Good night, everybody.
See you tomorrow.
Yinzer.
(LONG AS I CAN SEE
THE LIGHT PLAYING)
(MAN SINGING)
Put a candle in the window
'Cause I feel I've got to move
Though I'm going, going
I'll be coming home soon
Long as I can see the light
Pack my bag
and let's get movin'
'Cause I'm bound
to drift a while
When I'm gone, gone
You don't have to worry long
Long as I can see the light
Guess I've got
that old travlin' bone
'Cause this feelin'
won't leave me alone
But I won't, won't
Be losing my way, no, no
Long as I can see the light
Yeah
Oh, yeah
Put a candle in the window
'Cause I feel I've got to move
Though I'm going, going
I'll be coming home soon
Long as I can see the light
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org