Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
-You ready?
-Yeah. Boot it.
-That's it.
-Okay, that's it.
-I'm recording!
-Good, good.
Are you crazy?
Wait till l get this down!
You trying to l.D. me?
-Fucking retard!
-What's the problem?
-Don't be a pussy.
-Fuck you.
Fuck you, don't call me a pussy.
I'll fucking l.D. you!
-Take the gun.
-I get this piece of shit?
I can't believe it.
Is it even loaded?
I want the auto.
I never get the auto!
I fucked your shit, man!
Don't fucking shoot at me!
Don't fucking touch me.
Right there. Turn right.
Okay, okay, okay! Just relax.
Here we go, here we go.
There it is, there it is.
Easy, easy, easy.
Okay, one, two, three.
-Go!
-Yeah, go!
Crush that punk!
Go, go, go, go!
Get on the ground, you motherfucker!
Hands in the air! Hands in the air!
No, no, no. Where you going, bitch?
Over here! Over here!
-Get the fucking money!
-You, open the register. Now!
You want to fucking die,
you little fuck?
Get the fuck out of the way!
That's it? That's it?
-Where's the fucking money?
-Here we go.
-Don't shoot us!
-Come on. This way, this way.
Go, man!
Run! Run, man, run!
You want to die? Run, man!
Go! Don't look at me,
you fucking Chink!
-Get in there!
-Get him inside.
Get inside! Get inside!
-You get the money?
-Yes!
-What are you doing?
-Come on, man. We gotta go!
You get the money or not?
How much? How much?
-It's the police!
-Oh, fuck!
I'm going! l'm going!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Come on! Follow me.
Stop!
The fucking doors are locked!
Where are the cops?
What are you doing, man?
Just go, man, go!
Shit. Shit!
Drop your goddamn weapon!
Come on. Come on.
Go, man, go!
Come on, jump! Don't look!
This is insane, man!
Hey! You stop, asshole!
-Oh, no!
-Grab my hand!
I'm gonna fucking die!
l'm gonna die!
Goddamn it!
You know l don't deal in snuff.
-Don't have a coronary.
-You could've warned me.
I hate the zap when they die.
It just brings down your whole day.
-Jesus, Tick.
-Sorry.
How did you get it?
Why isn't it in evidence?
With all the blood,
they didn't see the rig.
-It was under a wig.
-How did you get it?
I got ways, Lenny, l got ways.
I got a deal with some paramedics.
My guy pages me,
l pick it up at the morgue.
This clip has got to be worth
at least a grand, right?
Tick, not to dash your hopes. . .
. . .but you know l don't deal
this kind of product.
I'll pay four since l have to cut off
the end and my customers want uncut.
Fuck, the last part is the best.
You dry-dive six stories and blammo!
You jack into the Big Black.
I don't deal black-jack clips!
It's policy. I got ethics here.
Yeah? When did that start?
This is what people want to see.
You know it.
Give it to somebody else.
Lenny, l got expenses.
I gotta fix my rig.
There's blood all over the heads.
-Put it away.
-Give me six at least.
This is a good clip, man.
It gets you pumping.
Well, the first part's okay.
Better than the usual soaps
you bring me.
That's cold.
I always bring you choice.
Sure, like this low-grade shit here.
A girl fighting with her boyfriend.
It's a test pattern.
Nothing happens. I'm snoring.
You're always telling me
bring you street life.
Bring you real life. That one man's
mundane and desperate existence. . .
-. . .is another man's Technicolor.
-I said that?
-It's a direct quote.
-I'll take it for five.
You'll make out okay.
It's pure cream.
No cut to the wearer.
Yeah, that's for sure.
-Okay.
-What else you got?
Calls are a little kooky tonight.
It's a little after 2 a.m.,
December 30th, 1999.
-Second to last day of the century.
-Hello, Jer?
I'll drop the money by tomorrow,
next day latest.
It's a little crazed now.
Would l lie? Never to you.
Never to you. You're not wrong.
You're not wrong.
Prick.
Dan, you looking forward to 2000?
Not really.
I mean, what's the point?
Nothing changes New Year's Day.
The economy sucks.
Gas is over 3 bucks a gallon.
Fifth-grade kids are shooting
each other at recess.
The whole thing sucks.
What the hell are we celebrating?
Shoot the clip.
Get it to me by Monday.
Client wants a guy and two girls.
The guy wears.
He's trying to be original.
And the girls have to be young, okay?
So don't use your mother
like you usually do.
Yeah, you too, asshole.
Caller, you're on the air.
I'm DeWayne. I got a
New Year's resolution for the police.
Hey, yo, 5-0,
better get down with the 2K.
2K, DeWayne? What is that?
2K, you know? The big 2000.
Tomorrow night.
Out with the old, in with the new.
See, for the Man,
no news is good news.
He'd like to keep it the way it is,
but we're gonna make it our own.
History gonna start right here,
you know? Right now.
I want to give a shout out to Boo.
You're on, Lori.
Read the Bible, Mark.
There won 't be another 1000 years.
We're in the Last Days as told in--
The Last Days? You mean the coming
of the Apocalypse, the Rapture?
Look at the signs.
Wars, and rumors of wars--
Just so the rest of us know
how much time is left...
... when is the Rapture
supposed to hit, exactly?
Is it midnight, New Year's Eve?
That's right.
Is that midnight L.A. time
or Eastern Standard Time, or what?
-What time zone is God in anyway?
-I pray for you all.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Okay, yeah, l can use this.
Listen, it's not bad. . .
. . .but move your eyes slower
next time.
Much slower, like you're making love
with your eyes. Okay?
Let me get this straight.
You're gonna pay me $200 to put on
a hairnet and bang some babe.
I gotta think about this.
Let's get you wired up.
I hope the axle grease in your hair
doesn't harm the SQUID receptors.
What is all this "squid" shit?
Superconducting Quantum
lnterference Device. SQUID.
The receptor rig on your head
sends a signal to the recorder.
We call it being "wired. "
But there's no wire.
Keep the recorder close.
Five, six feet away max.
In your jacket pocket, by the bed,
or wherever you close escrow.
-Got it?
-Yeah.
You got a half-hour of tape,
so give a lead-in to the main event.
But l don't want to leave for popcorn.
-Don't worry.
-You got it?
-No problem.
-You look great. You look beautiful.
10- 17, do you request back up?
That's a negative.
Suspect is a black male. 35 to 40.
We're handling it.
-Freeze!
-Freeze, you bitch!
You fucking bitch!
Fuck!
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
God!
Hi, it's Lenny.
Just what do you have in mind?
Lenny.
Goddamn it, you gotta be there!
You gotta help me.
Please pick up the phone.
Come on, pick up.
Come on, Lenny.
Fucking pick up the phone!
Okay, l'll call you back.
You okay?
You're doing good, honey.
You look so good.
-Hey, come back.
-You all right?
You need help?
Sweetie, you're doing good.
I'm sorry.
-Hold my hand.
-I'm sorry, baby. Are you okay?
How do you feel?
Lucky.
Dry me.
You want to watch or you gonna do?
Watch and see.
Oh, wow.
You look so beautiful.
I love your eyes, Lenny.
I love the way they see.
New Year's Eve, 1999.
It's called the party of the century,
but it may be the biggest party ever.
No one's seen preparations like this.
But preparations require care...
...and insurance.
And the LAPD is one insurance company
that doesn 't want accidents.
The two bodies found today
under the Hollywood freeway...
...have been l.D. 'd as rap star Jeriko
One and band member James Polton...
...known to fans as "Replay. "
Both were shot repeatedly...
...in what police characterized
as execution-style.
An unidentified woman
was found with them...
...also shot numerous times.
Police said that the killings
appear to be gang-related.
With his band, Prophets of Light,
Jeriko One's political stance...
...and violent lyrics have stirred
nationwide controversy.
Keith.
Keith?
-Yeah.
-Lenny.
Lenny Nero.
We spoke on the phone. Hi.
Not to be rude, Keith,
but l gotta ask. Are you a cop?
-I understand. No, l'm not.
-You understand?
Attorney, right?
Attorney?
-Right?
-That's right.
Tasseled shoes.
Entertainment law would be my guess.
Relax. It's my job to know people
and what they want. . .
. . .what's behind their eyes.
Okay, so tell me.
Have you ever jacked in?
Have you ever wire tripped?
No.
A virgin brain! Good.
We're gonna start you off right.
Just save us some time.
Tell me what you know.
Just what l've read.
The technology was developed for
the feds to replace the body wire.
And now it's gone black market.
That's right. So this conversation
is not taking place, okay?
-You're damn right it's not.
-Good. Good.
-So do l get the deck from you?
-I'll get you a deck at my cost. . .
-. . .since my thing is the software.
-Clips, right?
Clips. Right.
Now, listen, l want you to know
what we're talking about here.
This is not like TV, only better.
This is life.
It's a piece of somebody's life.
Pure and uncut,
straight from the cerebral cortex.
You're there.
You're doing it, you're seeing it. . .
. . .you're hearing it,
you're feeling it.
What kind of things, exactly?
Anything. Whatever you want.
Whoever you want to be.
You can go skiing
without leaving your den.
But l'm assuming a guy like you. . .
. . .you want to ski, you fly to Aspen.
That's not what
you're interested in here.
It's the stuff you can't have.
The forbidden fruit.
Like running into a store
with a .357 Magnum. . .
. . .feeling the adrenalin pumping
through your veins. Or. . .
. . .see that guy with the drop-dead
Filipino girlfriend?
Wouldn't you like to be him
for 20 minutes?
The right 20 minutes.
I can make it happen.
You won't even tarnish
your wedding ring.
-Sounds good.
-See, l can get you what you want.
I can. You just have to talk to me.
You have to trust me.
Because l'm your priest.
I'm your shrink.
I am your main connection
to the switchboard of souls.
I'm the Magic Man.
The Santa Claus of the subconscious.
You say it, you think it,
you can have it.
You want a girl?
You want two girls?
I don't know what your thing is,
what you're curious about.
You want a guy?
Maybe you want to be a girl.
Think of that. Be a girl,
see what that feels like.
Maybe you want a nun to tie you up?
lt's all doable.
Talk to me about costs.
Before we get into numbers,
l want you to try a taste.
-I got a deck with me.
-Right here?
Step into my office.
You were just an 1 8-year-old
girl taking a shower.
Are you beginning to see
the possibilities here?
Hey.
Where is he?
In the back, making a deal.
Can we meet someplace less public?
The cops have more to worry about
than the SQUID trade--
Don't move!
Assume the position,
you techno-perv puke.
Beat it, fuckwad!
-Gotcha.
-Jesus, Max, l was with a client!
You think that's funny? Prick.
You see the look on that
preppie puke's face?
-Pissed on his Top-Siders!
-It was funny.
But it cost me a lot of money.
Amigo, the world's full of marks.
No one works them like you do, pal.
You could sell a rat's asshole
for a wedding ring.
Yeah, l could.
-Let me buy you a drink. Bobby!
-Bobby!
Tequila. Double shots.
Make it a Tres Generaciones.
Nothing but the best
for my good friend.
Finest cop to ever
get thrown off vice.
Fuck you.
-Nice tie.
-Thanks, Max.
-You always gotta dress like a pimp?
-The tie cost more than your wardrobe.
-That's not saying much.
-It stands between me and the jungle.
To the jungle!
Where some shitbird can cap you in the
back of the head and ruin your day.
-You were lucky, Max.
-Yep.
So darn lucky, l wake up with
a .22 short floating in my brainpan. . .
. . .and a cop pension
l can't live off of.
It's a good thing
l wasn't any luckier.
Bobby. Hit me again.
You seen Faith lately?
She won't call me.
Just as well, Lenny.
Faith was the most outstanding woman
a guy like you could ever hope to get.
And it's deeply humiliating
that she's gone.
But you gotta face
that it's over, compadre.
I'm touched by your concern.
I just hate to see
you pining away, okay?
You're my friend.
It makes me want to vomit.
-Hey, lris. You okay?
-I gotta talk to you. It's serious.
What happened, honey?
Some john get rough on you?
No, l mean talk private. Please?
I'm in trouble.
So is Faith.
-There it is, the magic fucking word.
-Can we go to your car?
-There's something you have to see.
-What's going on?
-It's a bad situation.
-What?
If they get me. . .
-. . .I know they'll--
-Who?
Oh, shit!
Hang on, that's my car!
Not anymore. Belongs to the bank.
Hey, wait a second.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Great!
Two million years of evolution,
that's the best idea you come up with.
What do you get to repo a car?
200? 250?
I'll pay you 350 right now.
-You got cash?
-I was gonna write a check--
-See you.
-Okay, l totally respect that call.
I would want cash.
They'll take my check inside.
You're pressed for time.
Just give me two minutes.
Here, you can keep my watch
for collateral.
It's a Rolex.
Be right back. Two minutes.
Two minutes.
Son of a bitch!
What happened to your car this time?
See, Lenny, if you packed your piece,
you could make the guy see sense.
Bobby, turn it up.
I want to watch this shit.
You know how l feel?
Are you asking how l feel?
We felt Jeriko! We listened to him!
The LAPD is a military force...
... turned against its own people.
We live in a police state!
-The mayor...
-Hey, Macey.
...and councilmen sit in their offices
with their social programs...
... that don 't work.
They're rearranging deck chairs
on the Titanic.
But a new day is coming!
2K is coming!
The day of reckoning is upon us.
History...
...ends and begins again...
...right here!
Right now!
Right on!
To the end of all things!
You know how l know it's the end?
No, tell me.
Because everything's
already been done.
Every kind of music's been tried,
every government's been tried. . .
. . .every fucking hairstyle,
fucking bubble gum flavors. . .
. . .breakfast cereal, every type of
fucking-- What are we gonna do?
How we gonna make it
another 1 000 years?
I'm telling you, man, it's over.
We used it all up.
-What's this week's sad story?
-They jerked my wheels.
It's outrageous, the errors
the banks are making lately.
-You noticed?
-No, l haven't. . .
. . .because l make my payments.
Max Peltier, how's the PI business?
Sucks. But as soon as l get
this new logo--
Shut up, l want to hear
this scumbag.
You have any leads?
Why wasn 't security provided?
We always had
adequate security available.
He chose not to have
those encumbrances in his life.
-Why's he a scumbag?
-You-know-who left Lenny for him.
-Faith left Lenny for him?
-Don't say "Faith. "
Use the F-word around him,
it triggers a maudlin display.
The LAPD said it's
a gang-related incident.
I only know l've lost a friend
and a man of great courage...
... which is more than l can say
for most of us.
-If you're riding, let's--
-Okay, let's go.
"Driving Mr. Lenny. "
It's gonna be a big night.
Can't you feel the energy?
There's money to be made.
There's dreams to sell.
Sleaze to peddle.
See, that is so unenlightened.
I sell experiences.
I see it as performing
a humanitarian service.
I probably save lives.
I want to hear this part.
Everybody needs to walk to the
dark end sometimes. It's what we are.
The risks are out of line.
The streets are a war zone.
Sex can kill you.
So slip on the 'trodes,
get what you need.
Almost as good as the real thing.
A lot safer.
Porno. Face it, you sell porno
to wireheads.
Harsh! Harsh and untrue.
My clients are professionals.
Some of them are even celebrities.
-Yeah? What celebrities?
-The guy from the news.
He does the weather.
Well, that counts.
Hey, you passed La Cienega.
-I'm not taking La Cienega.
-It's the quickest way to the club.
I gotta get to the club.
I got business there.
You're my friend. I need you.
Plus l'll give you 25%
of what l make tonight.
This may be a hard concept for you. . .
. . .but friends
don't have to pay friends.
-Faith is singing there tonight.
-I should have known.
Look, l pulled 1 2 hours.
I gotta get some sleep.
I got one last pickup
at the St. James's Club.
There's a taxi stand.
Catch a cab to where you want to go.
A taxi?
Well, someone might see me.
Damn it, you made me late.
-What's his name? l'll find him.
-Fumitsu.
Fumitsu. Fumitsu.
Oh, fuck.
-Nero.
-Strickland.
-Commissioner.
-Whatever.
Since you canned me,
l don't even have to say "sir. "
One of life's pleasures.
You're peddling a little far
from your gutter.
I was invited here by a close friend,
Mr. Fumitsu. He's right over there.
I don't like disappointments, Nero.
Do you know what disappoints me?
Your sex life? Excuse me.
Mr. Fumitsu.
Leonard Nero,
BLS Limousine and Security Service.
One of our finest drivers,
Lornette Mason, will take care of you.
She's a security specialist
trained in defensive combat.
Of course, the car is bulletproof
and fully armored.
I'm coming along for a routine
periodic driver evaluation. . .
. . .with your permission.
We do it to ensure our VIP clients
are always treated as honored guests.
Good evening, Mr. Fumitsu.
Sir, please watch your head.
Excuse me, Mr. Nero.
Excuse me, sir!
-What the fuck are you doing?
-Coming with you.
You will not live to see the morning.
Drive on.
-Are you a cop?
-No.
No? Good.
Have you ever been wired?
Wired?
The latest technology.
That is so beautiful.
You gotta take a look at this, okay?
-You're gonna love it.
-You have more?
-I have more.
-You do?
-Believe me, l have more.
-Okay.
Hey, hey! Careful on the jacket.
It's Armani.
-Hey, you angry?
-I said, no wirehead shit in my car.
-You're on foot.
-In L.A.? Are you crazy?
Can l come in?
I'm having a hard time
hearing the stereo.
I need my case.
It's still in the back.
Hey, can we talk a little bit here,
like two rational adults?
That would be no.
You got my attention. It's cutting
off the circulation to my head.
Do you mind?
Mace.
It's cool. Two seconds.
This is uncharacteristic of you,
Miss lce-Water-ln-Her-Veins.
You pushed me too far.
I lost it in front of a client.
I could get fired.
-Are we still friends?
-I don't know.
Friendship is more than one person
doing favors for another.
-I know--
-I don't hustle friends.
-Hey--
-You suck people along. . .
. . .with your schemes, scams
and slick act.
-Buddies?
-Don't use the time l'm talking. . .
. . .to think about what to say next.
-You listening?
-Yeah.
Your ass is always broke.
You go from one score to the next.
You're getting strung out.
You don't even see it.
It's your brain, so you do whatever
the hell you want with it.
But not on my watch.
You understand me?
I got a child, l got rent,
and an ex-husband doing hard time.
He doesn't send me a dime of support.
I'm just trying to hold on here.
I know you wouldn't be saying all this
if you didn't care.
-Thanks.
-You get out with Fumitsu.
And that's the end.
I'll get you there in 1 0 minutes, sir.
I'm sorry.
I'm changing my plans.
Your supervisor has recommended an
excellent club, the Retinal Fetish.
I believe it's on La Cienega.
Yes, sir.
Enjoy your evening.
Hey, Mace, l really appreciate it.
Thank you.
Excuse us.
-Hi, Lenny.
-This is Mr. Fumitsu.
Take care of him.
Show him a good time.
John, can you take care
of this gentleman?
Hey. Bye.
How you doing?
Who's the side of beef
in Gant's posse?
Oh, that's Wade Beemer.
He was a running back
for the Rams in '96 and '97.
Hit like a freight train.
-Rams, that's football, right?
-No, it's Ping-Pong.
Hey, lris was looking for you.
Hello, Lenny.
It's okay, Wade, he's an old friend
of mine. Lenny Nero.
Come to peddle clips
for old time's sake. . .
. . .or making extra bucks
for the holidays?
You're not a client. I wouldn't sell
you the sweat off a dog's balls.
I already got everything l need
from you, thanks.
Cut it out, Philo.
Too bad about Jeriko. Tough break.
You've lost your golden goose.
Try showing some respect.
He was an important artist.
Important for your label,
which is why you're in mourning.
His records will sell out
now he's dead. You'll make out.
Always do.
Faith, can l talk to you
for one second?
It's not a good idea right now, Lenny.
I gotta talk to you for one second.
-About what?
-That would be between me and Faith.
Funny, l don't feel anything
between you and her.
You see, that's your problem, Lenny.
You assume there's something
where there's nothing.
You assume that you have a life.
In fact, you're just peddling
pieces of other people's lives. . .
. . .and the broken parts of your own.
Faith.
-Wade, get him to his car.
-Call me. Faith, call me, okay?
Faith! Call me!
Lenny the Loser.
-Leave him alone, Philo, okay?
-You shouldn't be talking to him.
You shouldn't talk to anybody.
Not with all that's going on.
You are too goddamned paranoid,
you know that?
Paranoia's just reality
on a finer scale.
Thank you.
-What up, Tex?
-What's up, my brother?
Those rascals still
haven't grown back?
No. Any day now.
I just know it.
I got something for you.
It's a present.
Something l had custom made.
Happy Millennium.
I got something for you too.
It just showed up tonight.
I don't know who from.
"Fan mail from some flounder?"
-Hi.
Hi, baby.
I missed you.
Lenny, you have to leave.
I mean it.
Iris said you're in trouble.
What did she mean?
-You talked to lris? When?
-Tonight.
I haven't seen her in months.
What the fuck would she know?
-Who knows what's in her head?
-She used to be your best friend.
What, lris?
You're really running out
of excuses to come around.
I know you, Faith.
You're afraid of something.
-What's going on?
-Let it alone, Lenny.
-It'll take care of itself.
-It's Gant.
This guy is poison. Listen to me.
He's got you walled in.
He uses the wire too much.
He gets off on tape, not on you.
That's a good one, coming from you.
-Why don't you just split?
-I don't want to.
What, you love him?
I don't think so.
To him, you're just a possession.
You're like a Ferrari,
just something to show the other guys.
Yeah? He has his uses too, you know.
What?
-He gonna record you on his label?
-He might.
You never know, right?
Listen to me. I've watched you
create yourself out of nothing.
You're like a goddamn cruise missile
targeted on making it.
And you will.
I know l will.
It's you up on that stage.
It's not him. You don't need him.
You have to get out.
If Philo catches you, he'll hurt you.
-I'm already hurting.
-I'm serious.
He's acting crazy.
He's doing way too much playback.
He's gotten completely paranoid.
He's such a control freak, he's even
paying Max to follow me around.
Max? You're kidding!
Yeah, for about a month now.
Jesus.
Look, Lenny,
just stay away from Philo.
And stay away from me.
Stop trying to rescue me.
Those days are over.
I'm a big girl now. I've changed.
Stop trying to save me. I don't
need saving. Just give up on me!
I just wanted to make sure
you were all right.
You know one of the ways that movies
are still better than playback?
Because the music comes up,
there's credits. . .
. . .and you always know when it's over.
It's over!
You were great.
Hey, man, l know what you're thinking.
You should have told me.
I was gonna. It's just a job.
-I feel like shit about it.
-You should.
I do feel like shit.
You introduced me to that prick Gant.
I introduced him to Faith too.
Not a good move.
Questionable move, definitely,
given the historical perspective.
I take the prick's money--
You wouldn't believe what l charge--
--and l make sure that Faith
is okay at the same time.
I keep an eye on her for you, okay?
Which you can't do without getting
your fingers bent the wrong way back.
I need the money.
This way, it does us both some good.
Fairly twisted logic, Max.
Even for you.
-Hey, you got a job.
-I got a job.
Okay, l'm sorry.
You got a job. That's great!
Listen, you've gotta stay on her.
-Watch her for me, please.
-I'm on her.
-Okay.
-Be cool. Take care.
-Take it easy.
-You too.
Here, chicky, chicky, chicky. . . .
Hey, wait a minute!
I recognize you.
You're Wade Beemer, right?
Running back for the Rams, '96, '97.
Am l right?
Yeah, that's right.
I saw you play, man.
You were good. Really good.
I mean, like a fucking freight train.
So, what happened? lnjuries or what?
-Bullshit politics.
-It's always politics.
Like this thing here.
He's paying you to tune me up.
I could pay you more not to.
-I could write you a check right now--
-I gotta go.
Okay, cash! Cash!
Here's everything l have on me.
Oh, look! What do you say?
How about a Rolex?
I got a real one.
It won't hurt too bad.
-It's nothing personal, all right?
-Just one second, please.
It's my jacket.
It's really expensive.
Just not the eyes.
You're bleeding.
Some jerk puked on the stairs
and l slipped.
I should sue. You came back for me.
I came back to pick up my client.
No, you came back for me.
I gotta lie down, Macey.
Please, in the back?
You're some piece of work, Lenny Nero.
You calmly backstroke along
in the big toilet bowl. . .
. . .and somehow you never
let it touch you.
Between working vice and your
current so-called occupation. . .
. . .you must've seen
every kind of perversion.
But you're just like some Teflon Man.
You still come out
this goofball romantic.
It's my sword and my shield, Macey.
All right, a little B&E action.
-What did you say?
-Oh, nothing.
Shit.
Please. Please.
Please, you can let me go.
Please. I haven't seen your face.
Let me go. Let me go, please!
Oh, my. . . .
Lenny.
Lenny!
Go to the Sunset Regent right now.
Go! Go!
He's jacking it into his own output.
She's seeing what he's seeing.
She's seeing herself.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Lenny. What is it?
Black-jack.
Black-jack?
Snuff clip.
It was lris.
-Sick fucker killed her.
-Are you sure it's real?
Oh, shit.
Well, l've lost my appetite.
For about a year.
-Want to take a look?
-Hell, no. I don't fool with that.
-You all right?
-Yeah.
-You okay?
-No, not really.
All right.
Let's work it.
No, l can't.
Come on, Lenny.
You used to be good at this shit.
-Play it down. What's the perp doing?
-I can't.
You used to be a fucking cop.
That's a fucking murder.
-What's he doing?
-Okay. He stalks her.
He rapes her. And he does her.
He records it. It's a thrill kill.
He wants to see it again.
He records himself raping
and killing her.
-And he sends the signal to her.
-So she feels what he feels. . .
. . .while he's inside her.
The thrill while he's killing her
is sent to her. . .
. . .heightening her fear,
which heightens the turn-on for him.
-I've seen a lot.
-So have l. Too much.
It's a bad one. It's a bad one.
He makes her see her own death,
feeds off the reaction.
He records it all. Everything.
And gives it to you.
Yeah, he wants to share.
Of course he wants to share, man.
That's his deal.
He needs an audience.
This is a sick puppy.
-Why me?
-Because you're the Magic Man, Lenny.
You make dreams happen, don't you?
If it has to do with the wire,
eventually it washes up on your beach.
I've never dealt in black-jacks.
Never. Everybody knows that.
He's skull-fucking you.
He wants to get a reaction out of you.
He wants to make you do something
you do not want to do.
Maybe he just figures Lenny
will appreciate what he's created.
It's the dark end of the street.
You like it?
Jesus, Mace. Back off.
This guy is one of your
squid-head contacts.
-He's somebody that you know.
-Problem with that is. . .
. . .Lenny knows everybody.
Take it to the cops.
No.
They'll crucify me.
I see, so this wire-freak
gets to keep running around, huh?
He's right.
They'll think he's the perp.
Or they'll go through his
client list and ruin his life. . .
. . .such as it is.
I'll call my buds in Homicide, say she
was a friend. They'll keep me posted.
I'll get me the forensics
and all that shit, okay?
I'll call you when l get something.
Relax.
Keep moving, man. Somebody's thinking
about you a whole lot.
Leave me alone.
Don't come to my house.
Are you trying to ruin my life?
Iris is dead. She was murdered.
-Who did it?
-I don't know, but he's damaged.
Iris said you were in danger.
I'm not in danger.
No more games.
Whatever you're hiding. . .
. . .you have to get out of here now.
Come with me now.
Then what? Will you protect me?
Big tough guy.
You're a fucking talker.
You don't even own a gun.
I do. It's under my bed.
-You don't know what's happening.
-Tell me.
Tell him, Faith.
Go on.
Listen, listen. Lenny just stopped
by to give me some bad news.
An old friend of mine was murdered.
Remember lris?
How did you get up here?
Charm.
Tell you what, Lenny. . .
. . .just for you, make you a deal.
Why don't you just take her?
If she's so unhappy and wants to,
she can go.
I'll let her decide.
Faith always knows what she wants.
Don't you, Faith?
Hands off.
Tell you something else.
I'll tell you this, you fuck:
If she says she stays, you go.
You crawl back in your cockroach hole
and never cross my vision again.
Come on.
I've made my choice, Lenny.
Get him out.
Fucking crazy, Faith!
You're fucking crazy!
I don't love you anymore.
Do you understand that?
You mean nothing to me.
Leave me alone, Lenny, please.
You said you were gonna
get lris out of this.
Now you understand
the danger we're in.
So sweet what you said out there.
So touching, l almost believed it.
I don't think he even understands
that you did it for him, right?
He doesn't know what's going on.
Leave him alone!
I'd love to, if he'd stop coming
around and you'd stop talking to him.
The only time a whore should open
her mouth is when she's giving head.
This is your floor.
Just go.
-Guess who's going to the hospital?
-Can we be smart here?
I could make it worth your while.
I'm not saying you don't land
a couple shots, just go light.
Here, look. Take my Rolex.
Nice watch.
-Is this impact-resistant?
-Sure.
You stupid piece of shit.
You stupid fuck, get up!
Come on, get up!
We tried to find a smaller girl
to beat you. . .
. . .but it was short notice.
It was short notice.
That one had to hurt.
Safety's on.
Come on. Let's go.
Hey, wait!
That's fucked up.
I need a drink.
-I want you to get some rest.
-Cops know they'll never nail him.
The second they walk in the room,
what do they see?
A dead hooker, handcuffs,
penetration. . . .
Cops are lazy, and they know
nobody cares about a dead hooker.
They're road kill. They'll come in. . .
. . .take some pictures, make jokes. . .
. . .shrug it off
like it's a random kill.
The kind you never solve.
-That doesn't add, does it?
-No, it doesn't.
Iris knew somebody was after her.
That's not random.
If they get me, l know. . . .
She said "they. " "lf they get me. "
Which means this whole random
sex-killer thing is bullshit.
They whacked her for a reason.
So the guy's not a psycho?
He's a psycho. To do what's on that
tape, he's not a well-adjusted human.
I gotta get some sleep.
Put that down.
I'll check on you tomorrow.
You want to rub my neck?
Shoulder's real sore.
-Right here?
-Yeah.
Don't stop.
How's Zander?
He's fine.
I miss him.
He misses you too.
I'm real sorry about being so hard
on you earlier.
It's just that l see you getting
sucked in deeper and deeper. . . .
Mace, come on.
I know you still love me.
How do you do this in front of
a child? Get away!
-In front of your own son!
-Hold up.
In front of your own son!
--a child loves you for a long time.
Not just to play with, loves you.
Hi, Mommy.
-This is Lenny.
-Hi.
It's Lenny.
Just what did you have in mind?
Last day of the world,
you spend it in bed?
-What's up, Max?
-Not a whole hell of a lot.
They've been saying words over Jeriko.
Tensions running pretty high
down here.
-Faith okay?
-Yeah.
She's leaving with Gant.
I'll be fast.
Iris checked into the Sheraton last
night under a false name. Paid cash.
Looks like she was hiding out.
I heard you dropped in on Gant.
Slick Lenny move.
He's in this somehow.
I don't know how.
Just stay close to Faith, okay?
No worries, bro. I gotta jam.
What up, Lenny?
-Where are we going?
-Anywhere.
You're acting strange.
What's going on? What?
We'll talk in the car.
Hand me that box of tapes.
Oh, shit.
-What?
-This tie doesn't go with blue.
Lenny, would you relax?
We're not being followed.
-Stop being paranoid.
-The guy had a knife. . .
. . .to my throat. . .
. . .in my living room.
Relaxing might be out, okay?
That is one unbelievable
piece of eye-fuck.
Skip the art criticism.
What can you tell me about the wearer?
-The guy's fucked up.
-We know that.
No. He's got some kind of distortion
in his visual cortex.
The color and gray-scale values
are all messed up. . .
. . .Iike color blindness.
Could be some kind of tumor or brain
lesion or something, some trauma.
-They're using a box to split signals--
-You ever make a box like that?
A few, but l can't see the gear
well enough.
I don't like this.
-This isn't good.
-What?
It's cutting awfully close to me.
She was just here, man.
-Who was just here?
-Iris.
Iris was here?
She came by, shaking like a junkie,
wanted me to make a copy of some clip.
What clip?
I don't know.
She wouldn't let me see it.
She was gonna give it to you.
Like insurance.
-She never gave me a tape.
-Think about what she said.
She came into the bar crying.
She wanted to go to my car.
Can we go to your car?
There's something you must see.
-Something about my car.
-In your car.
That's a handy little
attitude adjuster.
Damn. I'm boxed in.
What's it say?
Nothing.
Let's go play this back.
Give us the tape right now.
What tape?
l'm trying to get my car--
Shut the fuck up.
Give them the tape.
It's in my case.
I'm gonna open my case.
Facing us so we can see it.
Take it and turn her loose, okay?
Yeah. Absolutely.
"No, we're not being followed, Lenny. "
"Don't be so paranoid, Lenny. "
The glass is bullet-resistant.
Whatever happened to bulletproof?
Calm down, baby. This is what l do.
Hang on!
Oh, Christ.
Goddamn it, 91 1 is busy!
It's all right.
They'd never make it in time, anyway.
Oh, you're crazy.
This is bad.
The gas tank will go any second.
Hold on.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
The fire's out, isn't it?
Get in here, Lenny.
Come on, move it. Move!
Get ready to hold your breath.
Just kick out hard
and follow me, okay?
Let's get out of here.
I can't believe you had to give
them the damn tape.
Yeah, me neither.
It was one of my favorites:
Me and Faith in a hot tub
on my birthday.
Are we impressed yet?
Yeah, pretty impressed.
Well, you got me missing the party
of the century.
Like l ain't
got better to do.
-Hey, Curtis? Just drive.
-This shit is whack.
Those two were cops.
-You sure?
-It's the walk.
Anyway, they'll run your plates and get
your address. We gotta keep moving.
What you doing all wet?
Lornette, what's up?
We'll watch fireworks
from Aunt Cecile's.
-Aw, Mom!
-Come on, boy. Chop-chop. Come on.
Come on, Zander.
We're going for a ride.
-What's up?
-Get in the car.
-What's going on, Nette?
-Now!
Yo, what's up?
Yo, Mace! What's up?
-You don't come around here no more.
-I'm working, brother.
-This is Lenny. He's with me.
-What's up?
-Watch the fireworks.
-How you doing?
Tell me.
I can't tell you.
You've gotta see it.
I'm not doing it.
I know what you think
about the wire. . .
. . .but you gotta see it.
It's that important.
I'm sorry this has to be
your first playback.
It's all right. Keep your eyes
closed or you'll see double.
-Baby, yes.
-I'm gonna take you home.
Thank you, Jeriko.
Oh, l'll take you home.
You owe me two, you bastard.
-That's right.
-Oh, you do?
-I'll take you home.
-That's right.
-Me, baby.
-I'll work them all night.
Lights, damn. Look at this, man.
Oh, goddamn, man.
Just be cool, Jeriko.
-Slow down.
-We don't need no problems.
-I'm not speeding.
-Stop the fucking car.
What's the matter, black man
can't own a Jeep?
Go all the way
to the foot of the ramp.
-No problems at all.
-Is this against the law in L.A.?
If we be cool, they gonna be cool.
I can't afford no trouble.
-A man can't do shit in this town.
-I ain't going back.
-Shut up. Quiet.
-I don't give a fuck. I don't care.
Driver, step out of the car.
Get down on your knees;
put your hands on your head. Now!
Everyone else, out of the car.
Goddamn, man. What the hell
you pull me over for?
If l was going any slower,
l'd have been parked.
Get down on your knees and put
your hands behind your head.
Put your hands on the hood.
Don't move. You two, don't!
You stopped us because you had
suspects of our description.
Is that what you'll say?
What was the description?
Two black males in a car?
-I heard that one before.
-What the fuck?
Well, you stopped the wrong black male
tonight, officer-- What is it?
Steckler. Officer Steckler.
I'm that 800-pound gorilla
in your mist, fucker.
I make more in a day than you make
in a year, and my lawyer. . .
. . .Ioves to spend my money dragging
Aryan robocops like you into court.
Get a man down on the ground
with no probable cause.
Shut the fuck up!
-We weren't--
-Shut up and get back!
-You all right?
-Motherfucker kicked me.
-It's that rap bastard.
-You're that rapper puke?
Jeriko One?
You're the one getting all
the gangbangers going downtown. . .
. . .forming citizen groups. . .
. . .trying to rake the LAPD
over a cheesegrater?
That's right, and you're gonna be
in my next song.
It's gonna be called "Robo-Steckler. "
It's all about a cop who met
his worst nightmare:
A nigga with enough political juice
to squash his ass like a stink bug.
You're gonna be famous, fucker.
I don't think so.
Stop that bitch!
Get her!
Oh, God!
Hang on. Hang on, Max.
You see?
You had to see it.
I see the world opening up
and swallowing us all.
Yeah, l know.
Max, are you there?
Meet me at Tick's in a half-hour.
And, Lenny. . .
. . .don't get pulled over.
You know what this tape could do
if it gets out?
Yeah, l've got a pretty good idea.
People finding out. . .
. . .seeing. . .
. . .that the LAPD just flat out
executed Jeriko One.
Jesus.
Maybe they ought to see.
Maybe.
But tonight is probably not
the best night.
Come on.
We're rolling.
Those cops didn't do lris. Whoever
lris was wearing for killed her.
Why?
To break the trail.
If those cops had gotten hold of her,
they'd know who she was wearing for. . .
. . .and then gone after them too.
Our killer is running as scared
as we are.
Which makes him really dangerous,
judging by how scared l am.
Sounds like Tick's already
celebrating.
You seem a little overdressed
for this party.
I want to look nice for you, Lenny.
Tick, l gotta talk to you.
Shit.
He's been cooked-off.
-Is he dead?
-No, but his frontal lobes. . .
. . .are like runny eggs.
They put an amplifier in-line
to boost the signal. . .
. . .and fried his brain.
It's Lenny.
Tick, come on!
Come on!
Come on, Tick, come on!
He's totally cut off from
the outside world.
How long does it last?
Forever.
Those two psycho cops are on
a slash-and-burn. . .
. . .to find the tape and cover
their tracks.
They want to find out what Tick knows.
If there are copies, who wired lris.
It won't get investigated
as a homicide. . .
. . .since he's technically alive.
That's right. He's technically alive.
Seems sophisticated for them.
They're not subtle.
There's more to this than you think.
What do you mean?
All l'm saying is, you don't know how
high up the food chain this goes.
-I've heard stuff.
-What stuff?
You know, l heard stuff. Smoke.
Rumors. I've heard stuff.
I've heard stuff about a death squad.
A group of guys, cops, loyal
to the hard-line school.
Guys that've had too many years
of city hall. . .
. . .review boards and the media
pissing down their necks. . .
. . .suspending cops right and left,
tying their hands. . .
. . .while out of the other side of
their mouths, these people. . .
. . .are squealing, "Save us!
Do something, you fucking morons. . .
. . .crime is totally out of control. "
Bullshit. It's conspiracy paranoia.
The issue isn't whether
you're paranoid.
The issue is whether you're
paranoid enough.
Christ!
Exactly. Get religion, man.
I love you like my own blood. . .
. . .but don't walk near me
in public, okay?
The only card we got to play
is the tape.
Get it to the media.
Yeah, right, blow it open.
No disrespect, but if it's
the 1 1 :00 news, by midnight. . .
. . .you got the biggest riot
in history.
So you're saying we just pretend
it didn't happen?
I didn't say that.
The LAPD executed one of the
most important black men in America.
Who the fuck are you to bury it?
Trying to rake the LAPD over
a cheesegrater?
Fine. Do you want blood running
waist-deep in the storm drains?
Gangbangers'll spread like a wave
and burn this city to the ground.
When the fires start, the cops will
cap off anything that moves.
It'll be all-out war and you know it.
I don't think so.
Well, maybe it's time for a war!
You really want that on your head?
Really?
Whoever did lris did Tick.
It's the same sick wirehead shit.
Same reason, to burn the trail.
If Faith knows anything about this,
and she does. . . .
Somebody's gonna kill Faith?
Jesus! You scared the fuck out of me.
What do you want?
We know about Jeriko.
Iris made me a copy of the tape.
Goddamn it. I was trying to
keep you out of this.
I know. How did it happen?
What was lris doing riding around
with Jeriko, wearing a wire?
Faith, listen. Look at me!
You gotta trust us, we're here
to help you.
All right, l'll talk to you alone.
-Mace is in this.
-Tell us.
Philo's gotten obsessed with playback.
He's a total wiretrip junkie.
He's such a control freak,
he's having people followed.
He's recording his business
partners' calls.
He's wiring up people left and right.
Philo and Jeriko didn't get along.
He thought Jeriko might dump him. . .
. . .but he wasn't sure, so he started
with the surveillance.
A couple nights ago, he wires up lris.
He sends her and the other girl,
Diamanda, over to Jeriko's table.
Hi, baby. My name's lris.
I've got a present for you.
You're so beautiful.
So that night, lris calls up crying.
She's freaking out.
She comes over and plays the tape.
Philo loses it.
He can't believe what
a disaster it is.
He's afraid the cops will beat it out
of her who she's been working for. . .
. . .and come looking for him.
Why not go public and save himself?
If it got out that he had his own
artists under surveillance. . .
. . .he'd lose all his other acts and
it'd be over for him.
So he gave lris some money. . .
. . .and tells her to check into
a hotel under an assumed name. . .
. . .so he can figure out what to do.
He figured out what to do all right.
You think he killed her?
The killer knew where she was.
What a nightmare.
I don't know where the fuck she is,
but we're late. Let's go.
Listen, how do you want me
to work tonight?
At the Bonaventure, you want me
at the party or the suite?
Leave here with me, right now.
Come on.
-We talk later.
-I need to know.
Upstairs, downstairs,
where will you be?
Go get her, go!
I just say things once, baby, so. . .
. . .we'll talk about that later.
Okay, man. I'm cool, l'm sorry.
Wait. Go for a pass, bro.
Shit!
Go! Out of my fucking way!
Come on!
Go! Go!
Pardon me! Sorry, sorry!
Get out of my fucking way!
Move it!
Move!
You're finished!
Let's go, darling, walk with me.
Happy New Year!
Get out of the way!
Excuse me!
Out of my fucking way!
Not now, baby.
Not here.
Well, l'm certainly in the mood
for a party.
-Wait. I'll take her up to the suite.
-No problem.
You'll have a glass of champagne. . .
. . .or six.
I'll be up in a bit to help you
ring in the New Year.
I live for the moment.
Pussy-whipped,
sorry-ass motherfucker.
Take it easy.
So where are they now?
He's got her up in the room,
under guard.
And he's still working the party. . .
. . .acting smooth like
nothing's nothing.
So, buddy, l say we work a trade.
-What do you mean?
-Give him the clip.
It's brilliant. The tape for Faith.
He'll go for it, l can set it up.
This is what we laughingly refer
to as a plan, right?
Just get your butt down here.
If l'm not at the party downstairs, go
to the room. It's 2203. You writing?
2-2-0-3.
If he gives us any shit,
we kill them all.
What do you say?
Release him to the pigeons.
Okay, we got to get over there.
-Can you borrow a dress from Cecile?
-I'm not going.
We're going! Gant'll do her--
Shut up.
Park your mouth and listen.
It's a setup. Think about it!
Why send you the tapes?
Get you to rush in without thinking?
Put a bullet in you, one in her,
put the gun in your hand?
That sounds right.
I'm going.
You'll get yourself killed for this?
For this toxic-waste bitch!
What the fuck are you doing?!
This is your life!
Right here, right now.
This is real time, you hear me?
Real time!
Time to get real. No playback.
You understand me?
She doesn't love you anymore.
Maybe she did once, l don't know,
but she doesn't now.
These are used emotions.
It's time to trade them in.
Lenny, memories were meant to fade.
They're designed that way
for a reason.
Have you ever been in love with. . .
. . .someone who didn't return
that love?
Yeah, Lenny.
I have.
It didn't stop you from loving them,
right?
Or being able to understand them,
or forgive them?
I guess.
Didn't stop you from wanting
to protect them.
Did it?
When l met Faith she was just
another. . .
. . .another runaway. . .
. . .giving $20 blowjobs
to buy crank.
Another lost soul.
And she had this voice.
It was scary.
Like she could take all the hurt
and rage of the entire world. . .
. . .and lift it up to heaven
in one voice.
I helped her.
And l promised her that l'd always
just be there. . .
. . .to protect her.
It's not about what's in her head.
It's what's in mine.
I can't let go of the promise.
It's like, it's all l have left.
No, it's not.
Come on.
Let's go to a party.
Shit!
Let's bail.
You look great in that dress.
Better than l would.
Thank you. I think.
Come on, let's go!
How do we get into
the biggest party in history?
Relax, Mace, this is what l do.
You see Gant?
Shit.
Come on, Max. Come on, buddy.
Your call is unavailable or
has traveled....
I still got one ace to play.
Gant's got what l want
and l've got what he wants.
That's the original.
There are no copies.
That's why it's a makeable deal.
Look, this tape is
a lightning bolt from God.
It's worth more than you,
more than me. . .
. . .and more than Faith.
You understand?
It can change things.
Things that need changing before
we all go off the road.
And you do not have the right
to use it for currency.
So if you go, you go alone.
I care about you, Lenny.
A lot more than you know. . .
. . .which makes us both pretty stupid.
But if you pawn this tape. . .
. . .you mean nothing to me.
Excuse me.
See that guy over there?
That's Deputy Commissioner
Palmer Strickland.
The prick who busted me out.
His ass is so tight, when he farts
only dogs hear it.
If there's one cop who's not dirty,
it's him. Take it to him.
You want me to trust a cop?!
No. Trust me. Here.
What if you're wrong?
Go.
Excuse me.
Commissioner?
There's a clip in here you need
to see right now.
If it wasn't New Year's Eve, l'd
arrest you for illegal equipment.
Just look at the clip.
You want to know who killed Jeriko?
Go in the stall and hit "play. "
Sir, is there a problem here?
Damn it. I knew it.
Let go of me!
Wade, can we talk here,
like two human beings--
It's nothing personal.
Remember me, you fucking bitch?
Come on, come on!
What are you looking at?
Goddamn it!
Enjoy the party.
Fuck!
I didn't hear you come in.
No!
Okay?
Did l hurt you?
I love you, Max.
You're so pretty, Faith.
Come here! Come here!
Fuck you. You want to fucking die?!
You want to fucking die?!
This piece of puke hired me to kill
you, baby. Can you believe that?
-Isn't that right, Gant?
-Oh, my God. I don't believe this.
Believe it. Now bring me the 'trodes.
Come on, quick.
Come here, big shot. Suck on this.
Want to suck on some, suck on this!
What are you going to do?
You can't just kill him.
Give me that. I won't kill him.
Just a little poach job.
You shut the fuck up! Shut up!
Shut up!
I'm going to pull this fucking
trigger!
Fuck!
Here's how much l love you, baby.
God, Max!
Hope you enjoy the show, Philo.
Fuck.
-Take it, you prick!
-No, Max, don't!
Take it!
Take it, take it!
Don't make any assumptions about
our friendship, Lenny.
I didn't know you were colorblind,
Max.
Only way l could stand your ties.
Glock 23.
Nice.
Where's Faith?
I sent her to the party.
I figured l'd wait up here
until you killed Gant.
Why would l kill Gant?
You just did.
Jesus.
Statistically, that's the word
people use just before they die.
Shit being number one.
I killed Gant and you ran in,
and being on his payroll. . .
. . .you shot me.
That's about the way it happened.
Wait, now l remember.
I killed lris too, didn't l?
That's right. They'll find the
original snuff clip in your apartment.
The one l gave you at the club
was a copy.
Was l busy? Did l do Tick too?
You bet. Like it?
Why, Max?
Why did you have to do lris?
I feel l have to share this with
someone because it's too perfect.
Don't worry, l won't say anything.
Oh, l know.
So l'm working for this puke, right?
He says he'll pay me large
to do the hooker. . .
. . .but l also have to do his bitch
girlfriend because she knows the score.
Only he doesn't know
about me and Faith.
I say to myself, "lf l turn him
down, he'll get someone else.
And l lose Faith. "
To coin a phrase.
So to buy some time,
l do the skank. . .
. . .but l still gotta deal with Gant.
It's him or me.
But l can't just cap him without
some chump. . .
. . .to take the fall.
And who better. . .
. . .than his girlfriend's loser
ex-boyfriend.
A known criminal who's been seen
hassling him in public.
Who is, regrettably, also your
best-fucking-friend.
No plan is perfect, Lenny.
Cheer up. World's ending
in 1 0 minutes anyway.
You must be so pleased.
I followed your jellybean trail right
here, just like a good little chump.
You got ahead of me a couple times.
Remember the death squad?
I had to keep
you from going to the cops.
--stuff about a death squad.
The issue is not whether you're
paranoid, Lenny.
It's whether you're paranoid enough.
-So there wasn't a death squad?
-No.
Just two loose-cannon cops
covering their butts?
Pretty zany, huh? All this
caused by a random traffic stop.
Nothing means nothing.
You know that.
Look around.
The whole planet's in chaos.
The day of reckoning is upon us.
Get what you can, while you can. . .
. . .because some shit can put a .22
in the back of your head. . .
. . .any second.
How'd you hook up with Faith?
This fuck hires me a month ago
to eyeball her, only. . .
. . .Faith knows me from you.
So she says to me,
"Max, why are you following me?"
And l say, "l'll buy you
a drink and l'll explain. "
-Then she says, "So--"
-Do you enjoy watching me?
You're supposed to go downstairs.
Go downstairs.
I know. I don't always do what
l'm told, you know that.
So l said, "Do you enjoy watching me?
Come on, Max. Play with me. "
And then what did you say?
I said, "Yeah, l'd even
do it for free. "
I said, "That's good, because l like
the feeling of being watched.
I acquired the taste from Lenny. "
And then she said:
"Since we're going to be spending
so much time together--"
"Why don't we make the best of it?"
The very best.
You know all about that,
don't you, Lenny?
Faith and me found a place you
could never reach, Max.
Never.
Faith, l know it's gone. . .
. . .but, Max, you can't
fucking touch it.
Enjoy it.
Wait!
Fucking bitch!
Shit!
Motherfucker, you're going down!
Come here!
Come here. Come here, Lenny!
I'm taking you with me, motherfucker.
Come here!
Come with me! Come here!
Fuck!
There she is!
Freeze!
I said, fucking freeze!
Down! All the way down!
Right now!
Now, pay attention, motherfucker.
Stay down.
Down, down, down!
Roll, now!
Son of a bitch.
You ain't going anywhere.
Shut up and move!
Put that gun down!
Get on the ground now!
Hold on.
Let me tell you what's going
on here, okay?
Let me tell you.
Get on the ground now!
Now!
Let me tell you what happened.
Get these fucking things off me!
-No! Don't do it!
-Shut up!
Get down!
Wait! You don't know
what happened!
Commissioner Strickland.
That is the cause of all this!
Right-fucking-there!
These two are under arrest
for murder.
Read them their rights.
Move it!
Get this woman some medical attention.
-Are you okay?
-I got them.
Get the fuck out of here!
Everybody!
Get the fuck out!
Drop your weapon!
Drop it now!
Put that gun down!
-Drop your weapon!
-Put the gun down!
Drop your weapon!
-Put it down!
-Drop your weapon!
Shoot!
You fucking nigger bitch!
Yeah? What?
-Are we under arrest?
-No, they'll just ask us questions. . .
. . .for about six hours.
Okay, where are you hurt, sir?
Ma'am, you okay? Ma'am?
Take off the coat.
You hurt anywhere else?
Ten, nine. . .
. . .eight, seven, six. . .
. . .five, four, three, two, one!
You need an ambulance, sir.
This way.
This way, sir.
Lenny, we made it.
Yeah, we did.
You should get going.
Yeah. See you downtown.
See you there.
Ripped by thewildbunch22
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/356nc
Help other users to choose the best subtitles