Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(Helicopter blades whirring)
Johnny:  Talk to me, Ray.
Low on gas and almost
out of ammo, Johnny.
Johnny:  God damn it.
This isn't supposed
to be happening in this area.
Soldier 1: Retreat! Let's go!
Soldier 2: Move it! Move it!
Soldier 3: To RP Tango.
(Gunfire)
Charlie company overrun.
Requesting firepower.
Gotta go home and refuel,
come back for them.
If we go, there'll be no one
left to come back for.
-Soldier 1: Move it!
Move! Move!
-Soldier 2: Retreat! Retreat!
(Indistinct shouting)
Ray: We're hit!
Johnny:  Mayday! Mayday!
Dragonfly 2 going down!
(Bullets whizzing)
Johnny: Come on, Ray.
Let's go. Come on, Ray.
(Bullets ricocheting)
Come on, Ray, let's go!
(Indistinct shouting)
(Gunfire)
(Shouting continues)
Soldier: Move! Move!
On your knees.
(Typing)
(Line connecting)
(Speaking local dialect)
(Computer chimes)
Johnny: What's going on?
Hey, you will not.
No, you can't. No!
-Ray: No!
-You're all right, Ray.
Just stay cool.
- You're all right.
- Johnny, help me.
No! Ray!
Sniper: Here come
the visa crew.
Log 'em in.
Range finder: Murdock, Alvin.
Purvell, Robert.
Su, Joyce.
Rosenbaum, Naomi.
- (Engine revving)
- What the hell is that?
Sniper: That is Kate abbott.
The new security officer.
Vip request.
We need to process it.
Okay.
- Sorry, Sally.
- What's the rush, Sam?
Security breach.
Everybody in the
conference room in 10.
Nero Franks, Maltese National.
Over the weekend,
he tried to board
an oceanic airlines flight
from Heathrow to Chicago.
Alarms went off when Franks
presented his passport.
It didn't have
the new digital watermark.
Franks tried to run.
MI5 thought he was
a suicide bomber
and took him out. Take a look.
Abbott: Nero Franks was
a scientist with no priors,
working for
a German chemical outfit.
His specialty
was combustible gas munitions.
The brits and the Germans
are still looking
for a possible
terrorist connection,
but no joy so far.
So here's the issue
for us, people.
Now our enemies know
they can't forge Visas.
That means they'll be looking
for ways to get real ones,
the kind you hand out
every day.
We're working with all
the British security agencies,
but they're stretched
really thin.
Budget cuts, plus they have
homegrown terrorists
to worry about.
We're not saying that you
have to give everyone
the third degree.
90% of our applicants
are straightforward.
It's the remaining 10%
that I lose sleep over.
Any application that tweaks
you the wrong way,
take it straight to Kate.
She excelled at this work
in Washington.
What Sam really means is
you'll need someone to blame
if the wrong guy gets
through, so use me.
What I'm really interested in
is anyone
with scientific expertise,
specialists in chemicals
or gases.
Any questions?
All right, gang. Back to work.
(Sighs)
That's fine, madam.
Your visa will be ready
tomorrow.
She's never seen the ball drop
in Times Square
on New Year's Eve.
Have a good stay
in the United States, sister.
Thank you, sir.
So do you promise to watch me
when I'm on  American Idol?
Oh, absolutely.
What?
- Have a good stay.
- Thank you very much. Bye-bye.
(Computer chimes)
Dr. Balan, good afternoon.
I was told my paperwork
is in order.
This won't take long.
Romanian citizen.
You have listed
a medical conference
as the reason for visiting
the United States.
Yes.
This conference is
for pediatricians.
You're a general practitioner.
I work in a clinic
for newly arrived immigrants.
Many of my patients
are children.
Dr. Balan, it also says
that you consult
for Vicker's pharmaceuticals.
I'm curious why we don't have
a letter from them.
I've only been there
a few months.
- Is there a problem?
- I certainly hope not.
Let me see this file.
I'm not done with my review.
A word.
You don't think it's strange
that a GP,
who also happens
to be a researcher,
wants to attend
a pediatrics conference?
There's nothing odd
about moonlighting
as a consultant
to make a few extra bucks.
Besides, Naomi already did
the background check.
- Balan's fine.
- I'll be the judge of that.
Look, I know you were
a high-flyer in D.C.
I am not here on vacation.
Even when it's slow,
we're not processing people
fast enough.
We're seriously understaffed.
So when paperwork
gets held up by security,
people start missing flights,
and I'm the one that has to
deal with their complaints.
Unless you wanna suffer
the ambassador's wrath.
I'm doing my job, Bill.
We all are.
We have a problem.
A new security expert.
From Washington.
Her name is Kate Abbott.
She knows about Vicker's.
So no visa?
She's trouble,
I'm telling you.
I'll take care of her.
(Buzzer rings)
(Door unlocking)
Woman: This way, please.
Sweet of you to stop in.
There's something
you need to see.
I'll have it done tomorrow.
(Door closes)
(Computer chimes)
(Alarm ringing)
Abbott: Lisa.
- Hey.
- I'm so sorry.
It's okay. I saved us
a bottle of bubbles.
Oh! You're the best.
So how did it go?
Would you believe
I sold every damn one?
- No.
- (Laughs) Yes.
But I saved those for you.
I know you have a thing
for the underworld.
Thank you.
Oh, wow.
So all work and no play, huh?
(Sighs)
It's complicated.
Is everything a state secret
with you?
(Exclaims)
It's so beautiful.
(Computer beeps)
- Naomi:  Hello?
- Hi, Naomi. It's Kate.
I'm so sorry it's so late.
It's okay.
Is something wrong?
You remember a guy
you processed a while ago,
Sri Lankan researcher
by the name of Fazli Sameer?
Uh, yeah,
I was checking him out
when Bill pulled the file.
He said I had too much
on my plate,
and he'd handle it.
Okay, all right.
Thanks so much.
Bye.
(Typing)
(Clock ticking)
(Sighs)
Actually, Dr. Balan
did ask me for a reference.
Request slipped
through the cracks.
I'll get my secretary
to draft one today.
Oh, would it be possible
to see Dr. Balan's
security clearance?
What's this really about?
-I just thought
since I was here, it'd be...
-About that.
If you were even
remotely familiar
with the British
defense ministry's
standards on secrecy...
We're on the same side here.
You need to present
a proper written authorization
from the home office
to even inquire
about security clearances.
- Dr. Perry, I...
- It's time for you to leave.
(Sighs)
Get inspector Anderson
for me, please.
(Doorbell ringing)
(Motorcycle revving)
(Beeping)
- Hey, Howie.
- Hey, sweetie. What's up?
Listen, I need the list
of this month's visa files.
Yeah.
There's no authorization.
Oh, Parker probably
forgot to call.
Could you remind him?
- Yes. Oh.
- (Cellphone rings)
- Bye.
- Bye. Bye-bye.
- You wanted to see me?
- Miss Abbott.
I believe you know
inspector Paul Anderson
from counter terrorism
command?
Good morning.
Why are you making inquiries
into the security status
of a British resident,
Dr. Emil Balan?
He applied for a visa
to come to the United States.
So you took it upon yourself
to go to his workplace
and interrogate his superior
rather than contacting
my office?
Dr. Balan needs
his visa today.
I just thought
it would be faster.
Not to go through
proper channels?
What's this about, Paul?
The director, Perry,
contacted me personally
to complain that Ms. Abbott
had been making
unauthorized inquiries.
Then he called his friend,
the home secretary,
who asked me
if you have issued the visa.
- No, I haven't.
- (Knock on door)
Is there a problem?
Ambassador Crane.
Inspector. Sorry I'm late.
I didn't know
you were joining us.
I didn't either.
The home secretary
just called.
So what's the problem?
I can't discuss the details
of an ongoing investigation.
We're talking about
a medical professional
with serious
political connections.
Is this really a matter
of national security?
Sam?
It's her call.
I'm standing by it.
I'll inform the home secretary
accordingly.
But let me tell you
something about Balan
that you probably don't know.
A few years ago,
his wife applied for a visa
for emergency
medical treatment
in the United States.
She died
because some bureaucrat
kept asking
for one more piece of paper.
Under the circumstances,
you might consider
showing her widower
a little compassion,
Ms. Abbott.
Ambassador.
Congratulations.
You're already making enemies
in high places.
Keep it up.
Sam, get control
of this situation.
Ugh.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thanks for backing me up.
You have great instincts,
Kate.
(Sighs)
(Indistinct chatter)
Bill.
- Can I talk to you for a sec?
- Sure.
Sorry, Kate,
I'll have to take this.
I'll meet you guys
at the restaurant.
Man 1: All right,
see you there.
Man 2: Okay. Gaston's, right?
See you there.
Man (On phone):
You need to do it now.
Bill: Okay, I understand.
Thanks, mate.
Man: After you.
Woman: Thanks.
Woman: I think
this is our table.
Classy. Look at that bar.
Woman: Naomi, have you ever...
Abbott:
This place is really nice.
Woman: That bar looks amazing.
Bill's crazy about this place.
What you told me last night
about Bill pulling
that file...
Kate, it's the guy's
birthday party.
We're supposed
to be having fun.
Oh, um, he Pre-ordered
the pressed duck
for all of us.
- Okay.
- Um, we're six, please.
Wait. Did anyone
remember to pick up
the present for Bill?
- What? That was you.
- I'm pretty sure...
Not playing a part of this.
- Don't look at me.
- All right, guys, pony up.
Naomi: Is this enough?
Joyce: I know.
It's like we're here
for the free food.
Hi. I'm here
to pick up a gift.
- That's beautiful.
- Yes. It's a great choice.
- I'll wrap it up for you.
- Thank you.
What's taking bill so long?
All right, here comes
the good part.
What do you mean?
Is that what we're eating?
That's disgusting.
Thank you.
(Cellphone beeping)
(Car alarms blaring)
Man: Help.
Abbott: Naomi.
Alvin!
Joyce!
(Grunting and panting)
Help.
There's someone hurt.
- (Gas hissing)
- (Canister explodes)
(Sirens blaring)
Abbott's still alive.
Where?
Following the embassy
survivor protocol.
That's what they're
trained to do.
Make sure she doesn't survive.
-Parker: What are you
hearing, Sally?
-A restaurant blew.
The place looks
like a killing zone.
According to first responders'
radio chatter, it was a bomb.
I'm working on getting
security video feeds.
- Where was the hit?
- Just a few blocks away.
Do we have anyone
in the area?
The visa crew took Bill
to lunch at gaston's.
Christ. Waring Lane.
Oh, God.
Parker: American embassy.
Officer: Right, sir.
Anderson: How long
until this is fully out?
Man: Hours.
Parker: How many?
Four of yours, two waiters,
saleswoman from
the glassware shop,
and five passersby.
And more than a dozen wounded.
The blast originated
where your people were seated.
Has anyone claimed
responsibility?
No.
The bomb took out most of
the security cameras
near the restaurant.
Don't know how much of
the feed we'll recover.
Is that all of 'em?
We found this in the shop.
Abbott must have been in there
when the bomb went off.
Do you think she's dead?
We can't find her.
(Breath trembling)
Joyce, Robert, Alvin, Naomi,
they're all dead.
Sally:  Oh, my God.
Bill Talbot was supposed to be
at that restaurant.
He stayed behind
to take a secure link call.
He should be somewhere
between the embassy
and the restaurant.
Get a lock on the trackers
on bill and Kate's ids
right now.
Okay. That was
the search team.
There's still
no sign of Abbott.
So what do we know about her?
Only child,
born and raised in Montana,
parents are deceased.
Stanford university.
Then a two-year scholarship
for graduate studies
at the university of London.
She applied
to the state department,
scored high enough to get into
the bureau
of diplomatic security.
She single-handedly
unraveled a plot
to bomb
the American embassy in...
Okay, so she knows the city
and she's good at her job.
Tell me something
I don't know.
Well, she's better than good.
London's considered
a senior posting.
She speaks four languages,
three of them being
Russian, Arabic, and Mandarin.
- Wait. She's CIA?
- We don't know.
Okay, until proven otherwise,
we assume abbott is alive.
That makes her
a material witness
and quite possibly a suspect.
Get her details out to
the police, MI5, the media.
Woman: If she's
wandering around injured,
surely a security camera
will pick her up.
Anderson: No,
she'll know better than that.
But put her friends,
especially that photographer,
Lisa Carr,
under surveillance.
Abbott might reach out to her.
I had a lock
on Kate's locator,
Kate knows we're tracking
her embassy ID.
She's following protocol,
heading for the safe zone
in the park.
- Talbot's already there.
- I'll be there in two minutes.
(Tires screeching)
(Distant sirens wailing)
(Indistinct)
- Kate.
- Bill.
-Thank God you're
all right. Okay?
-Okay.
- Bill, they're all dead.
- I know, I know.
- All right, come here.
- Bill, I tried to save them.
- There's nothing left.
- Let's walk here.
- I tried to save them.
- I know. Relax.
There was a man
with a gun outside.
He almost...
Why couldn't you
have left things alone, Kate?
Now I have no choice.
(Gunshot)
- (Gunshot)
- (Abbott gasps)
(Bill groans)
Kate...
(Shuddering) Bill.
Look, look. Over there, see?
Woman: Danny! Come here!
(Crowd murmuring)
Man 1: Get away!
She's got a gun!
It was an accident.
- He tried...
- Man 2: Someone call the police!
(Clicks)
Woman: Somebody help him!
Someone call the police!
(Panting)
Yeah, yeah, Lancaster gate.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Damn it.
(Women laughing)
Anderson: Witnesses saw
Abbott holding a gun
and Talbot staggering
toward the fountain.
And this time,
we have video evidence.
(Sighs)
Please, Paul,
give me a chance to find her.
I'm sorry, Sam.
I have my orders.
Look, I know
that you track your people
using GPS chips in their IDs.
It's how you knew that
Talbot and abbott were here.
Hang on a second.
- Where's bill's ID?
- I'm sure we'll find it.
My point is this.
Assuming abbott still has
her ID, you can find her,
and it's best I'm there
when you do.
(Parker sighs)
The kid's video went viral.
The home secretary saw it,
got on to the foreign office.
Now she's wanted
for deadly assault
and questioning
in a terrorist incident.
Kate has diplomatic immunity.
You can't touch her.
You know we won't take chances
with people like that, Sam.
(Knock on door)
Come in.
Who are you?
Trevor. I work with Fred.
I only work with Fred.
Shut the door.
He's ill.
Do you want my help or not?
(Sighs)
The signal is active.
You'd better hurry.
What's happening
with those trackers, Sally?
Sally: Someone must have
taken Bill Talbot's.
It's moved away from the park.
At the moment, it's stationary
off Russell square.
There's still
a problem with Kate's.
The tracker must have got
damaged in the explosion.
Parker:
What's the last location
we have for her?
Lamb's market
off curzon street.
And you're sure
no one else can track her?
Absolutely. Only you and me.
I need to get to her, Sally.
That's exactly what Anderson
is expecting you to do,
and he'll be right behind you
with an SAS team.
Kate knows what to do, Sam.
It's more important
we find Talbot's tracker.
Whoever has it might be able
to tell us
what really happened
in that park.
The fireworks in Dubai.
That was you, right?
(Beeping)
Now you can follow
whoever has one of these.
And the second item?
Straight from the lab
used by the security services.
Dials you into
their field agent
communication system...
(Chokes)
(Grunts)
You shouldn't have asked
about Dubai.
- (Squelching)
- (Trevor groans)
(Exhales)
On the north side
of Kensington Gardens,
where a short time ago...
(Cellphone ringing)
The met has issued a warrant
for Kate's arrest.
Reporter: (On TV)
...Horrific explosion
earlier today
at a popular restaurant
not far from here.
Parker: (On phone)
This is Sam Parker.
Leave a message.
(Sighs)
God damn it.
Sally:  And Bill Talbot's
tracker fell off the grid
five minutes ago.
(Line ringing)
Reporter: (On TV)
...Taken by a witness here.
-We can show you
these images now.
-(Indistinct chatter)
There is a woman seen running
from the scene...
- Sally:  Section 5.
- Sally, it's me.
I've been monitoring you,
but your tracker
keeps shorting out.
You have to give me
your location, Kate.
Kate?
(Speaking mandarin)
Damn.
Sally: Sam, what's going on?
Did you find Talbot's tracker?
- No, just a dead guy.
- What?
Talk to me about Kate.
She called in two minutes ago,
hung up before
I could get a location.
Sam, you need
to get back here.
The ambassador's
on the warpath.
He must have missed abbott.
Tell the pickup teams
to stand down.
Let's see what's so
interesting about that hotel.
Abbott: What do I have
to do to convince you?
Oh, come on, please,
give me a break.
Just one phone call.
Look, it was a present.
It's Sterling, okay? Please.
(Sirens wailing)
- Local call only.
- Okay.
(Cellphone ringing)
Hello.
Lisa, please,
I need clothes and money.
All right,
I'll go to your place.
No, no, no.
It's not safe, um...
Can you just come meet me
and bring me
some of your things?
-Where?
-Somewhere where
there's a lot of people.
St. Pancras Station
by the Christmas market.
Two hours.
What's the composition
of the gas?
A precise mixture of hydrogen,
methane, and fluorine.
The volume in New York will be
four times greater.
So will the results.
Made to the exact
specifications necessary
to trigger this device.
I'm curious. Why not use
a detonator in New York?
At major events,
the police carry beeper-size
radiation detectors.
There's bomb-sniffing dogs,
Hazmat units.
(Metal clacking)
If there's any sign
of an alert,
even a false alarm,
the first thing
the authorities do
is kill all communications,
jam radio frequencies,
shut down
all cell phone towers.
Then we have
the counter snipers
placed in a 500-meter radius.
However, I shall be firing
outside their perimeter.
- (Cocking rifle)
- (Man sighs)
(Explosions continue)
Soon, my friend.
So now there's only the girl.
Just make sure my shipment
gets to New York,
that's all I ask.
(Explosions continue)
Reporter:  The large
gas explosion ripped
through the housing estate
- in tower hamlets.
- Thanks.
Man: What have you got for me,
Maureen?
The president is
demanding answers.
I just spoke with
the British home secretary.
They don't have her. Do we?
Abbott's tracker
was damaged in the blast.
We lost her signal
for the moment,
but even if we get it back,
the brits have snatch teams
ready to go.
If I try to make
a move on Abbott
and happen to get lucky
on her location,
I lead her right to Anderson.
Sam, she's a liability.
Kate had nothing to do
with Bill's murder.
- Go ahead.
- (Clears throat)
This morning Kate took
the monthly visa list.
The flash drive contains
all of the background checks
and references
on the applicants.
If we find there's been
a possible terrorist breach,
that's usually
the first place we look.
- She said you'd okayed it.
- Did you?
No.
What about the backup systems?
Five files were permanently
deleted earlier today.
The entry log shows
that it was Abbott's ID.
It gets worse.
We checked the security log.
Abbott has been working
a lot of nights
when there's no one around.
It's possible
that she created documents
to get somebody
into the country,
and then erased the records
to cover herself.
May I remind you
that just five weeks ago,
you sent her over here
with glowing recommendations
because we needed the best.
If I recall correctly,
she was one of your protegees,
although I'm sure
you'll deny that now.
I was skeptical at first,
but it turns out
you were right.
- She's an extraordinary asset.
- Yeah, just not for us.
That's complete bullshit,
and deep in
your scared little souls
you all know it.
And we damn sure
don't sell them out
at the first sign of trouble.
But most of all,
we don't forget motivation,
She lost some
of her best friends on 9/11.
Then why is she still running?
(Engine revving)
She's on the move.
(Cellphone chimes)
Parker: Where's Kate?
The last time we got a signal?
Leicester square,
and that was 10 minutes ago.
It was barely registering.
Jesus, you look how I feel.
How are you holding up?
We're monitoring
Anderson's communications.
His people are looking hard,
but in all the wrong places.
How did it go upstairs?
They want me to try
to bring in Kate,
use Anderson if I have to.
From Anderson's forensic lab.
Don't ask how I got it.
The bomb has
traces of chromium.
- We haven't seen that since...
- Paris, two years ago.
The watchmaker.
Sally: Or whatever he calls
himself these days.
Whoever wanted
the visa crew dead
paid for the best operator
in the business.
Parker: He's had so much
reconstructive surgery,
no one knows
what the hell he looks like.
(Beeping)
She's in St. Pancras station.
I'll have to take the chance.
And where's Abbott's friend?
Man:  She just turned
off the euston road
into St. Pancras station.
All right, stay with her.
I'm on my way.
Announcer: (On PA)
Please allow passengers
off the train first.
For your safety and security,
CCTV is in operation
in every station.
(Sirens blaring)
(Indistinct chatter on PA)
Code Lucifer.
Repeat, code Lucifer.
Abbott: Lisa.
Suspected suicide bomber
at northeast entrance.
Man: Okay, move.
Move, move, move, move!
(Alarms blaring)
What's the matter?
Did you bring the money?
Did you bring it?
Kate, you've got
to tell me something.
Stay here. Don't move
until someone tells you to.
What?
Kate. Kate!
Anderson: Move! Move!
Move, move, move! Abbott!
(Abbott grunts)
(Panting)
You had your chance
to help me, Sam.
Make sure he doesn't
follow us.
(Beeping)
(Panting)
-(Gasping)
-There's no way out, Abbott.
It's a dead end.
(Door banging)
(Grunts)
Man: This way, sir.
Anderson: Damn it.
It's this way.
Anderson: Abbott!
Abbott, stop!
(Gunshot)
(Glass shattering)
- (Abbott gasps)
- Man: Stop!
(Door slamming)
Stop!
(Gunshot)
Follow her!
Anderson: (Faint) Abbott!
No, this way!
-Man: I think she went
this way.
-Shit. Shit.
Shit!
We can seal them off
from the street.
What, you think she's
gonna take an officially
marked tourist exit?
There are hundreds
of other ways out of here!
She could be anywhere.
(Rats squeaking)
(Panting)
(Beeping)
- Abbott: What?
- (Beeping rapidly)
(Exploding)
(Groans)
(Gasping)
(Groaning)
Jesus.
(Faint sirens wailing)
(Cellphone beeping)
Fucking technology.
Bitch.
(Door rattling)
- (Door rattling)
- (Abbott sighs)
(Glass shatters)
(Gasps)
Oh, come on. You know
I didn't do any of this.
(Beeping)
Gotcha.
You sure it was the same guy
you saw after
the restaurant explosion?
Yes, and he was in the park
after Bill tried to kill me.
So he could have
followed you here.
We don't need anybody else
tracking you.
Abbott: You think he's
tracked me all this time?
Sam, who is he?
His code name
is the Watchmaker.
He's one of the most wanted
assassins in the world.
You doing okay?
How did you know
I would come here?
I didn't.
I just came looking
for answers.
(Sighs)
What are we doing
with our lives?
I put everything into this.
And what am I now?
A suspect? A target?
Maybe both.
(Sighs)
(Exhales)
We're doing this
because we believe
in that old-fashioned idea
of country, right?
Or at least protecting
our fellow citizens.
Our friends.
Right now, I'm doing it
to protect my own hide.
That's good thinking.
What's that?
It's the flash drive
I got from Howie.
Last month we processed
over 600 visa applications,
and Bill personally intervened
in five of those cases,
including Balan's.
Now for each applicant
he used a different member
of the visa team,
and when I started
asking questions,
he ignored me,
slammed them through.
So what's the connection
between the applicants?
I don't know yet.
But we do know balan is an
expert in combustible gases.
Maybe bill had the answer.
Bill said something strange
in the park.
"Now I have no choice."
He must have kept
some information
about the people he let in.
A little leverage,
in case he needed it.
Who puts a padlock
on a bedroom door?
(Gun cocking)
(Gunshot)
Hello, my lovely.
Abbott: God.
- Is this Bill's son?
- Yeah.
Johnny died in Afghanistan.
Something about this
just doesn't add up.
It's like bill was expecting
him to walk through the door
at any minute.
(Sighs)
Take it apart.
Everything.
Parker: Look at this.
Johnny: (On TV)
Hi, dad. I'm doing okay.
Hope you are, too.
It'll be Christmas soon.
Wish we could be together.
Johnny's been alive
all this time.
Do you think
there's a chance?
I doubt it. Look at his eyes.
He's swimming in dope.
Someone kept him alive
for as long as possible
to get this footage.
But how did they know
it was Bill's son,
or who Bill was?
They must have someone
with access to army records.
Doesn't have to be
a major player.
A guy inputting data
could be enough.
Once they knew it was Bill,
they threatened
to kill his son
if he didn't give them
what they wanted.
Which makes Bill's actions
understandable.
But not excusable,
because once Bill got
his people into the states,
it was only a matter of time
before he eliminated
everyone who handled
the paperwork.
Then he got the bastard
who murdered them
to come after me.
The watchmaker would
never deal with
low-level guys like Bill.
His business is with
whoever had Bill's son.
You said there were
four others besides Balan?
Yeah, and every single one
of them is in America.
(Cellphone beeps)
(Line ringing)
We need to move now.
I'll get Archer to meet us
out front.
(Ringing)
- (Line ringing)
- (Exhales)
Come on, come on, come on.
What's wrong?
Let's get the hell
out of here.
- Sam?
- (Groaning)
(Footsteps approaching)
Watchmaker: Kate.
Kate.
(Gasping)
(Siren wailing)
(Bell dings)
- (Siren wailing)
- (Line ringing)
(Ringing)
- Sally.
- Kate?
- Is Sam still alive?
- Barely.
He's pretty badly hurt, Kate.
Hold on.
Anderson's on the scene.
He's coming on the line
with Crane.
Madam ambassador,
I'm at Bill Talbot's
apartment.
Sam Parker's been
critically injured.
Jesus.
Witnesses saw abbott
running from the scene,
and we found her embassy ID.
Crane: Where is she now?
Anderson:  We don't know.
If you get her in your sights,
do not hesitate.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
The longer she lives,
the more people die.
Kate.
- I'm here.
- I'm so sorry.
They think you tried
to kill him.
What?
That's insane.
I need to get into
the embassy. To the vault.
The building's
on total lockdown.
- There's no other way.
- Kate, listen to me.
The place is crawling
with marines.
You know I'm innocent.
And I know I'm right
about this plot.
You have to get me in, Sally.
(Indistinct radio chatter)
(Keypad beeping)
(Buzzer ringing)
-Abbott:  I'm at the north
roll-up door.
-I'm buzzing you in now.
I'm shutting down the cameras
in the stairwell
and the vault.
In and out,
as fast as you can.
(Buzzer ringing)
(Grunts)
(Electricity crackling)
(Alarm blaring)
Man: (On PA)  Attention.
Security breach
at basement level.
(Men shouting)
(Door slams)
Oh, God. No.
(Alarm continues)
Abbott: There's a terrorist
headed for the states.
Emil Balan. He's traveling
on a Romanian passport.
Oceanic Airlines, flight 428,
out of Heathrow to JFK.
They have to stop him, Sally.
(Indistinct radio chatter)
She got herself
a new passport, and then
wasted the hard drive.
The name she used,
the passport number,
they're gone.
She could be anyone.
Get Abbott's picture
to security
at all London airports
and train stations.
Yes, yes, yes, what is it?
The purpose of your visit,
doctor?
Medical conference.
There's still time
to stop Balan,
Madam Ambassador,
if you act now.
No. Don't you see
what Abbott's doing?
She is trying to get us
to chase a shadow
instead of her.
(Sighs)
(Indistinct chatter on pa)
You're supposed to have left
for New York.
I'm not sure I'm going.
What the hell are you
talking about?
I found your reaction
to that little explosion
quite instructive.
The way your eyes lit up,
the greed I saw in them.
Fortunes are made when
there's blood on the streets,
and very soon there's gonna be
a great deal of blood
on the streets of New York,
won't there?
Just as there was after 9/11.
However, when the New York
exchanges reopened,
people who bet against
the market
made a fortune.
This isn't an act of terror
or a bold political statement.
Balan may wish to avenge
his wife's death,
but for you,
it's just about making money.
$100 billion is in play.
I would say the word "just"
doesn't quite fit.
If I stay home,
you won't make a penny.
- What do you want?
- Half.
Half of your
short-selling profits
on the New York exchanges
the day they reopen for trade.
Simple.
Is the girl dead?
Very.
(Indistinct radio chatter)
Announcer: (On PA)
For security reasons,
please do not leave
baggage unattended.
Baggage left unattended
will be removed
and may be destroyed.
- I'll grab these, too.
- Yeah, got it.
(Beeps)
(Receipt whirring)
- There you go. Thanks.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Your flight boards
in 15 minutes,
Miss Harrison.
Thank you.
- Good morning.
- Hi.
(Typing)
- Just one way, Miss Harrison?
- Yes.
Is everything all right,
ma'am?
Death in the family.
- Safe travels.
- Thank you.
(Typing)
Now this is taking too long.
I'm doing the best I can,
Madam Ambassador.
Excuse me, ma'am.
You'll have to shut that down
for landing.
Okay.
- Ma'am.
- I'm shutting it down.
(Exhales deeply)
(Computer chimes)
(Whispers)
Gonna get us both killed.
It doesn't make sense.
Why Paris?
Abbott has no history there,
no friends to help her.
And why risk flying? It's
safer to take the Eurostar.
(Beeping)
She's going to New York.
- Welcome home.
- Thank you.
Abbott is a security officer
and a serious threat.
- Find her.
- Understood, madam ambassador.
- Hey, listen up.
- Man: Ma'am.
- We got a red flag. Red flag.
- Man: Let's go.
Us passport number 212683550.
Suspect is traveling
as Harrison, Amy,
coming off USS827.
Real name, Katherine Abbott.
Photo's on the way.
Jamieson, let's get
the details to immigration.
-Miller, let's alert customs
and NYPD.
-Yes, ma'am.
Woman:  As soon
as her picture comes in,
I want you to get it out
to every taxi and bus driver
and the rental car agencies.
Stay alert, people.
Officer: Careful, ma'am.
You're in New York now.
Taxi, madam?
You're a gypsy, right?
Madam,
I'm an independent contractor
with 14 years' experience.
Okay. No medallion?
No radio either?
Please, I want no trouble
with the police.
That makes two of us.
500 bucks for the night.
In cash, plus gas.
- It's new year's Eve.
- Okay. Let's go.
I have an address
in lower Manhattan.
Balan: Red, increase 3%.
Green, maintain present level.
Yellow, reduce 1%.
Bit too slow,
but maintain levels.
(Beeping rapidly)
(Alarm ringing)
And stop.
Lock the cylinders.
Don't worry about
the tanks or equipment,
but make sure you pack up
everything else.
I'm going to look after
the loading.
Take the BQE
to the Brooklyn bridge.
Very good.
You like TV? We have TV.
(Flicks switch)
Reporter: (On TV)
This is a live shot
of preparations
for tonight's new year's Eve
celebrations in Times Square.
As you can see, the famous
New Year's Eve ball,
which is displayed year round,
is not in place.
It has been taken down
for some last-minute checks
on the new led lights.
Balan: Wait.
(Engine starting)
Reporter: It has almost
3,000 waterproof crystals,
ranging between
four and five inches each,
and will be illuminated
by over 32,000 leds.
To prevent the ball
from overheating,
a coolant gas
is piped into the ball
just before it is attached
to the pole.
Abbott: Change of plan.
Take me to Times Square.
(Crowd cheering)
Paperwork?
All right. You're good to go.
- Thank you. Happy new year.
- You too, sir.
Abbott:
Can't you go any faster?
(Engine revving)
Go.
(Crowd cheering wildly)
(Fireworks popping)
Sorry, ma'am.
This whole area is closed off.
Great. I'm just gonna
get out here.
(Gas hissing)
Thanks.
Oh, my God.
(Abbott grunting)
Man: Ahh!
(Man screams)
(Gun cocking)
(Car honking)
Abbott: No. No.
(Buzzer ringing)
Hurry.
Come on.
Can I help you, ma'am?
The guys that just came in,
where'd they go?
Uh, 1501.
Man: Help! I need the cops.
Someone call 911.
We have to go. We have
less than five minutes.
(Gunshots)
(Distant crowd cheering)
(Exhales)
(Faint cheering)
You just had to be here.
I've been waiting 10 years
for this moment,
to see the Americans pay
for what they have done.
How far will
the explosion travel?
Not this far.
Good.
(Door opens)
- (Groans)
- (Gunshot)
- (Bullet ricochets)
- (Explosion)
- (Whizzing)
- Ahh!
No.
Bitch! Come on.
Come on.
(Both grunting)
Fuck you.
Kate...
Crowd: (Chanting)
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three, two, one.
Abbott: Time's up.
- (Screaming)
- Crowd: Happy new year!
(Fireworks exploding)
(Crowd cheering wildly)
- Freeze!
- Don't move!
Man: Abbott.
Abbott, it's for you.
Hello?
-I always liked
your instincts.
-Oh, Sam.
You're alive.
Yeah. You, too,
from what I hear.
(Laughs)
Mostly.
So I guess this is what
we're doing with our lives.
Yeah, it is.
Kate, there were
over a million people
out there tonight,
and you saved them all.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org