Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
-Miss Quinn.
-Justice Lowell.
-I hope you haven't been waiting long.
-Oh, no, sir.
Please come in.
-Do you have plans for the holidays?
-I'm staying in the city...
...spending Christmas with some friends.
I never know what to get people.
My wife would buy our gifts.
She always seemed to get
just the right thing.
I hope this is appropriate. Use it well.
Thank you, Mr. Justice. I will.
-Have a good Christmas.
-And you, too.
-Would you like your car brought around?
-Not just yet. I want to clear my desk.
You know, Abraham Lincoln used
to hunt wild turkey down our roads.
You can still bag one there
for Christmas dinner.
Okay, polar bears! Let's go!
Come on, Mike. It's not that cold.
Bill, we've got something here.
Hey! Up here!
And now, back to our main story.
Justice Lowell is said to have been
despondent over failing health.
This morning at a memorial service
at Washington Cathedral...
...the President called the Justice
''one of our finest jurists.
''A man dedicated to law
and devoted to truth.''
Funeral services will be held
this afternoon at Arlington Cemetery.
That was my mother's!
What is she doing?
Out of the way, man!
From Your Honor's lockup list, number 15...
...the United States versus Daniel Adams.
Mr. Adams, you are being charged with....
-Hi, Jack.
-Hi, Kath.
-Did you get my message?
-Yeah. You okay?
I'm fine.
Get him to take a recess for a few weeks.
We'll blow smoke up his judicial ass.
Did I miss anything?
Your assault with intent skipped.
What a surprise. He promised he wouldn't.
I have a feeling we might see him in March
with a nice Florida tan.
Here's today's top 40.
Busy night.
A hundred and two felony arrests.
Some kind of a record for a Monday.
I don't know what it is.
It's like something in the air.
The Christmas spirit.
Get Carl Wayne Anderson.
Next on Your Honor's lockup list
is number 17...
...United States versus
Carl Wayne Anderson.
Is Mr. Anderson's attorney present?
Your Honor, Mr. Anderson has refused
to speak with an attorney.
He has refused to speak with anyone at all.
You are accused of first-degree murder.
Do you understand that, Mr. Anderson?
Do you know where you are,
Mr. Anderson?
As I am unable to determine
whether Mr. Anderson is competent...
...I will postpone presentment
pending psychiatric evaluation.
Does Mr. Anderson have means of support?
He's indigent, Your Honor.
The court, then, will appoint new counsel.
Let the record show that Miss Riley...
...with the public defender's office
will represent Mr. Anderson.
Your Honor, I'm due for a vacation.
I haven't had one in a year.
Miss Riley, please accompany
Mr. Anderson and interview him.
Yes, Your Honor.
We'll pass this case. What's next?
Mr. Anderson, I am Kathleen Riley
from the public defender's office.
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
You're being charged with murder.
Could you tell me where you were
around midnight, December 18?
Mr. Anderson, where were you at midnight,
December 18?
I'm your lawyer.
Anything you tell me is confidential.
If you don't talk to me, I can't help you.
I guess this is a waste of time.
Do you understand
what's happening to you?
Jim, you want to let me out of here?
Can't they read?
Don't you own a watch?
We're in trouble.
We're in deep shit.
Support's drying up
quicker than an old whore.
-It's too close to call.
-Did Comisky declare?
She's on the fence.
They're waiting to see where she falls.
-Did she go in?
-Yeah.
Congressman Newton! Good to see you.
And the whip?
He said he'd keep his people in line.
He said he'd never turn his back
on the American farmer.
What else is new? He got a sudden
backache. He's sitting out the vote.
He told his side of the aisle
to vote their conscience.
That'd be a first.
What do you think, Grace?
I can't help you, Eddie.
I just wanted to see
which way the wind was blowing.
That's it?
I respect you, Grace.
I'm not going to insult you...
...with a promise out of left field.
You have to vote your conscience.
When you get humble, I get nervous.
I feel like I'm being set up.
Nothin' up my sleeve.
You did what you could.
I'm in a tight spot.
My district's blue collar.
They don't like government subsidies.
I'm on their side, Grace.
I come from a farm family myself,
of dirty collars.
But everyone wants milk on the table.
If the price isn't right...
...the dairy farmers will dump it
in the river. It's a terrible waste.
Grace?
When you were in trouble...
...and needed the crop states' support
on the car company bailout...
...I ran up the flag for you.
I pulled a lot of votes.
That's life, Eddie.
No, Grace, that's politics. Life's
what everybody else does, remember?
Your district has a big
inner-city lunch program, right?
Yes.
What if we donated
a year's worth of free milk.
No point in it going down the river.
I don't believe that you're trying
to bribe me with milk for babies.
It's a good bill. Just give me some time
to shore up some support.
Have the vote postponed
till after the holidays.
Why did you wait so long to come to me?
It slipped my mind.
Nothing slips your mind.
''Life's what everybody else does.''
You're dangerous.
I'll get it postponed, but that squares us.
Don't ask me for my vote. It's not for sale.
-What happened?
-He hit an officer last night.
I'd like to put his eye out. That's the
third time it's happened in two months.
Keep goin' like this he goin' to wake up
one mornin' and find hisself hung.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear that.
Did a doctor see him?
Yeah. He came and went.
He wouldn't let him touch him.
Take the cuffs off.
Chief told me not to.
Just take the cuffs off. I'll be responsible.
All right. You wearin' the suit.
-They put animals to sleep, you know.
-They miss some sometimes, don't they?
Are you trying to commit suicide?
Just tell me if you are...
...because if you are,
I've got better things to do with my time.
Oh, Jesus.
Get a doctor.
I couldn't read your writing in some places.
I got most of it but I have to ask you
some more questions.
Carl?
Carl!
Have you told me everything?
A piece of cake.
Maybe it won't bother a jury that
your fingerprints were all over her body.
Possibly, they won't mind
that you carried a big knife.
They'll probably understand.
She was dead anyway.
What the hell? Why not rob her?
And maybe I'll play quarterback
for the Redskins next season.
Tell me that you did it.
I'll go to the judge and ask for mercy.
It'll save us both a lot of headache.
''Michael was there...
''...before me.''
Michael? Michael who?
And eyes.
What color were his eyes?
Brown.
And his hair? His hair.
Dark hair.
And how tall was Michael?
Medium.
He had a tattoo on his hand?
Is there anything more?
Is there anything more about Michael?
Can you remember anything more?
The doctor's here. Come on.
-Good evening, Louis, Ansel.
-Matthew.
I hear you're up for an appointment
to the D.C. Circuit Court of Appeals.
-I've heard those rumors.
-Don't bullshit a bullshitter.
They're more than rumors.
When's the announcement?
The President should make
his choice known by the end of the month.
That reminds me.
I'm scheduled to hear the Winslow trial.
It's got to drag on into spring.
I was wondering if you'd consider
making a change.
I'd like to clear my docket
in case the appointment comes through.
You're scheduled for...
...''United States versus Anderson.''
It looks pro forma.
Two weeks at the outside.
It'd make my life a lot simpler.
As a lifelong Democrat, I should do
all that I can to delay your appointment.
But in the spirit of bipartisanship
and future considerations...
...I'm okay with a change.
Excuse me, gentlemen, my prostate's shot.
Sitting on my ass too many years.
Want a ride?
No, thanks.
Morty?
I need some investigative help.
I can't do this one all by myself.
We're short right now.
The interns have their finals.
I know, but I've got to find
a material witness.
Is this witness hard
or a figment of your client's imagination?
I don't know.
-You want a beer?
-Yeah, please.
Can you live without him?
I can live without him fine. My client can't.
I'll see if I can find you
a private investigator somewhere.
-What if your witness doesn't materialize?
-Then it's your basic dog-and-pony show.
Circumstantial evidence. Reasonable
doubt. We'll be dead in a week.
-Who's prosecuting?
-Some guy named Charlie Stella.
He just came on.
He's real hot shit in Baltimore.
He wants to be a senator
after he's president.
Listen, Kath. Prosecution owes me a few.
How about going to the table
with this one?
Maybe plea-bargaining
and cutting your losses.
My client has nothing to lose.
''Motion to dismiss
for failure to Mirandize...
''...for illegal search and seizure,
and for insufficient evidence.''
It's a waste of paper.
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
I don't have a life.
The last movie I went to was a year ago.
The only time I listen to music is in my car.
I don't date.
I'd like to have a child but I don't even
have a boyfriend. How can I have a child?
I spend all my time
with murderers and rapists.
What's really crazy is that I like them.
It grows on you.
I don't think I can do it anymore. I'm tired.
I'm really tired.
I'm even thinking about
going into private practice.
If I'm gonna go crazy,
I might as well get paid for it.
You have stayed around
a lot longer than most.
Why do you stay?
I don't know.
Same thing as you, I guess.
For the sake of the one poor bastard
who didn't do it.
-Plus, I look a bit fat in a three-piece suit.
-You? Never.
-You coming?
-No, I have to finish.
All righty. Thanks for the beer.
Excuse me.
Where do I report for jury duty?
Third floor.
-I need to be excused. Who do I talk to?
-Jurors' Excuse Officer.
Everybody's got a title.
What's a good excuse?
-You ever been called before?
-Yeah, last year. I was too busy.
The second time you're called,
you gotta serve. It's the law.
I'm sure something can be worked out.
I don't like your chances.
Dennis Kirkham?
Here.
Kathryn Conrad?
Miss? Attorney.
I'm Everett Bennett, private investigator.
You're looking for someone?
You.
Either be seated in the gallery
or leave now.
This isn't a bus station, Miss Riley.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
Lee Ron Davis?
Here.
Shelley Boylen?
Doris McCloud?
Here.
Ladies and gentlemen. As the defendant
has a hearing and speech impairment...
...and is unable to read signing, the court
has provided him with assistance.
If you are seated as a juror, you'll be asked
to disregard this disability...
...unless it is shown to have
a direct bearing on the case.
Mr. Stella, whenever you're ready.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Good morning.
I'm Charlie Stella,
an assistant United States attorney.
I'll be asking questions
about your backgrounds and experiences...
...which may reflect on your ability
to sit as fair and impartial jurors.
Mr. Davis, as a loan officer...
...is it one of your responsibilities
to handle foreclosures?
It's part of my job.
How do you feel about that part
of your job?
It must be difficult
putting people out of their homes.
It doesn't trouble me. A person should
be responsible for his debts.
Thank you very much for coming,
Mr. Davis. You're excused.
And what are your feelings
about capital punishment, Mr. Sanger?
Objection, Your Honor.
Mr. Stella knows capital punishment
isn't an option in the District of Columbia.
I'm sure Mr. Sanger has
a thoughtful opinion, but it isn't germane.
I'll determine what's germane, Miss Riley.
It's misleading, Your Honor.
My client is not facing the death penalty,
nor has he been convicted of any crime.
We resent the implication.
Don't bring a rope
unless you intend to use it, Counselor.
Would Your Honor please instruct
the prospective jurors?
The death penalty is not an option
in the District of Columbia...
...although some of us feel it should be.
We thank Your Honor for his consideration.
Will you please answer, Mr. Sanger?
I think the punishment should fit the crime.
Thank you, Mr. Sanger.
Good morning, Mr. Sanger.
Mr. Sanger, you've stated
that you are a congressional advisor.
Is that another word for lobbyist?
I don't know. That's sort of like
calling a lawyer a mouthpiece, isn't it?
Who are you congressional advisor for?
Agribusiness, mostly.
The United Milk Producers.
Now, the lobbyists that I've known
are very persuasive people.
They could sell you just about anything.
It's sort of un-American not to like milk.
I'm allergic to milk.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Sanger, are you from Washington?
No. Wisconsin.
And what brought you here?
I was a legislative aide
for my home senator, Gaylord Nelson.
-I was 21, anything was possible.
-Thank you.
-You learn quickly....
-Thank you, Mr. Sanger.
Do you have faith
in the American justice system?
It seems to work.
Do you believe that a man is innocent
until proven guilty?
Absolutely.
You've stated the punishment
should fit the crime.
Yes.
Would you turn around, Mr. Sanger?
Excuse me?
Just turn around and face
the back of the courtroom, please.
Mr. Sanger,
could you tell me what color my hair is?
Brown.
Does my hair look brown to you?
You asked me what color your hair was.
I thought you wanted the real color.
You're very observant.
But appearances can be deceiving.
Sometimes circumstances make the truth
almost impossible to find.
As jurors you will be asked
to keep an open mind...
...to put aside your assumptions...
...and to look for and find that truth.
What if I'd said ''black''?
I ask the questions here.
-How many challenges do I have left?
-One.
Thank you for coming, Mr. Sanger.
-Does that mean I'm excused?
-No, it doesn't.
What are you, an immigrant?
Nobody has jury duty.
Next you're gonna tell me you vote.
Good evening, Mr. Sanger, Mr. Everett.
Well, hello, Marilyn.
How are things?
I haven't seen you around.
Something to drink?
Stolichnaya vodka martini,
straight up, three olives.
-You working?
-Justice.
Third girl
in the Deputy Attorney GeneraI's office.
Paul Gray?
Type much?
The job doesn't require much typing.
Anyway, it's temporary.
Paul says he wants to groom me
for management.
I wish I had a dollar for every promise.
Just once, I wish an ''I can't help you out.''
Let's go.
-The boy wonder.
-Hi, Paul. How are you?
-Let's catch up sometime.
-Yeah.
Come on.
Congressman.
-How's it look, Eddie?
-Oh, it's down to the wire, sir.
-Call me if I can do anything.
-Thank you very much.
Fuck him. I called him three different
times. He never returns my calls.
There's Comisky.
Maybe you should take another run at her.
Grace.
Hello, Eddie.
Are you alone?
I stayed in the office late, and just
stopped in to catch my breath. I'm beat.
I'm out on my feet. I've been
up and down the Hill all day for votes.
Do you mind?
-Do you want a drink?
-No, it wouldn't have any effect anymore.
I've been nursing drinks and listening
to the sound of my own voice since 5:00.
I know the feeling. There's a vote
coming up on a bill that I cosponsored.
It gives me a knot in my stomach
like a fist.
Closer the vote, tighter the fist.
Grabs me a little lower.
How close is the vote?
Well, let's see, if everything falls right,
we're still a handful short.
I never noticed your eyes.
Sometimes they're blue,
sometimes they're green.
You're still a handful short.
-I told you, my vote's not for sale.
-I can't help myself, Grace.
It's a lovely thought anyway. Nobody's
mentioned my eyes in a long time.
-There's another stop.
-How much do I owe you?
$7.50.
Here, keep the change.
Michael, you are served.
His face was completely rearranged.
He spent half the night in surgery.
By the time the police arrived,
the assailant had fled.
That's why I need a continuance...
...until Michael John Guthridge
can be apprehended.
I don't see any need for a continuance.
The subject was served a subpoena.
He's required to appear
or be in contempt of process.
You've got to be joking.
There's not a chance in hell that this man
is going to voluntarily appear.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
I sympathize with you.
I was a trial attorney for a number
of years, at the mercy of witnesses.
If we had to wait for every supposed
witness, we would grind to a halt.
It could take months to locate this man.
With no guarantee that he'll testify,
or that he'll have anything to testify about.
ln all fairness to my client,
I cannot present a complete defense...
...without this witness.
I'm sorry.
Your request for a continuance is denied.
Miss Riley?
Don't try to contaminate the process...
...with any backdoor comments
about this witness in open court.
How can I possibly
contaminate this process?
Opening statements, Mr. Stella.
Elizabeth Rose Quinn.
She was 24.
A clerk/typist at the Justice Department.
She made $17,000 a year. She was single.
She liked to play tennis. She was a
member of the Baptist Church in Arlington.
She wasn't very important.
Especially in a city
that's full of so many important people.
She was just a decent,
hardworking citizen.
On the night of December 18...
...a week before Christmas...
...Carl Wayne Anderson, in cold blood...
...cut her throat.
I've prosecuted 43 murder cases.
It's always a horror. It's always senseless.
Of all the murder cases I have prosecuted...
...this is the most horrible,
the most senseless...
...the most indefensible.
For $9.00.
$9.00.
$9.00, that's all she had.
Is this what we've become?
Is the value of human life so cheap?
Elizabeth worked late that night.
It was cold.
She was tired and anxious to get home.
She took the bus to the parking lot
on K Street where her car was.
That's as far as she got.
We will show that Carl Wayne Anderson
had been in there...
...trying to break into cars.
He had been sleeping in Elizabeth's car...
...and a parking lot attendant
had chased him away.
But he had come back.
And when he saw Elizabeth
alone and defenseless...
...he beat her, dragged her down
to the river, slit her throat and killed her.
This isn't the 11:00 news.
We can't just shake our heads,
go to bed and forget about it.
We have a responsibility
to Elizabeth Rose Quinn.
She is, after all...
...too important.
Miss Riley?
Carl Wayne Anderson is not a decent,
hardworking citizen.
He is not a shining example
of the American dream.
Carl Anderson is the American nightmare.
He's one of the nameless,
faceless derelicts that...
...wander aimlessly through the streets
of our country every day by the thousands.
We step over them in doorways.
We cross the street...
...in order to avoid having to come
into contact with one of them.
We look at them with a mixture of pity
and contempt and fear.
And we choose not to see
that under their ragged blankets...
...and their filthy clothes is a frightened,
lost human being...
...just like you and me.
Carl Wayne Anderson
was a soldier in Vietnam...
...not a hero, just a dog soldier...
...who believed in
and fought for his country.
When he tried to regain his identity...
...and his self-respect
in a veterans hospital...
...he contracted spinal meningitis,
became deaf...
...and suffered a traumatic speech loss.
We will show that Carl Anderson
lived in a world where $9.00...
...could mean the difference
between eating and starving to death.
What's going on?
The vote's supposed to be next week.
They were getting ready to adjourn.
The leadership called for the vote.
What's the count?
We're on the button.
The right ''yes'' puts us over the top.
No comment.
Eddie, you lucked out. Her committee
chairman must have persuaded Comisky...
...to vote yes.
That must have been it, Congressman.
Give me a call.
Nice job, Eddie.
Could you describe what you found?
She'd been attacked from behind.
Her throat cut laterally across the larynx
and the carotid artery...
...from left to right.
And what kind of instrument caused this?
A very thin, straight blade.
A razor, a knife.
I'm showing you what's been marked as
Government Exhibit 1 for identification.
Have you seen this knife before?
Yes. I was asked to do
a forensic examination of it.
And what were your conclusions?
The width of the blade and its sharpness...
...were consistent
with the deceased's wound.
I move Government Exhibit 1 in evidence.
Without objection.
Your witness.
Before Miss Riley cross-examines
we'll take a 15-minute recess.
You're excused, Doctor.
Excuse me, Your Honor, may I have
another look at that photograph?
Objection, Your Honor.
This has become ghoulish beyond purpose.
The juror is entitled to a thorough
examination of the evidence. Overruled.
Thank you.
I'll remind the jury, you are not to discuss
this case with anyone.
Okay, let's go.
Miss Riley? There was a call for you.
He wouldn't give me his name.
He left a number.
Okay, thanks.
-Hello?
-Hi, this is Kathleen Riley.
Yes. Do you know if your client
is right or left-handed?
Excuse me?
Do you know if Carl is right or left-handed?
Who is this?
I noticed something.
I was wondering if you did.
Who is this?
Dr. Koleena, you examined
Carl Anderson's knife, didn't you?
-Yes, I did.
-And what did you find?
Some rust, a partial hair follicle
and microscopic traces of human tissue.
And did you compare the tissue...
...taken off of his knife
with Elizabeth Quinn's?
Yes.
And would you tell the jury
what your findings were?
They were inconclusive.
Excuse me, Dr. Koleena,
could you please speak up?
They weren't conclusive.
So what you're saying is that...
...you have no direct evidence
that this knife, Carl Anderson's knife...
...was the weapon used
to murder Elizabeth Rose Quinn.
No bone fragments...
...no tissue samples,
no traces of her blood.
I don't know what we would have found.
The knife had been cleaned.
Excuse me, didn't you say a moment ago
that you found rust and a hair follicle...
...and some sort of tissue on this knife?
So was it wiped clean
or wasn't it wiped clean?
It's more complicated than that.
There's a wide--
No, it's not more complicated.
It's either simple yes or no.
It was cleaned or it wasn't.
Objection!
Forensic pathology is an exact science.
Miss Riley is making this sound
like a cooking class.
Excuse me?
Objection sustained. And dispense
with your characterizations, Mr. Stella.
My apologies to the court and to counsel.
Thank you, but I don't want the jury left...
...with the impression that Mr. Anderson
cleaned off his knife...
...to hide any incriminating evidence.
Objection sustained.
Miss Riley,
are you through with the witness?
Yes, I am.
Doctor, you're excused.
Your Honor, one more question.
Make up your mind, Miss Riley.
You've said
that the wound was left to right.
That's correct.
The entry wound was left of median...
...and the exit wound right of median.
-Entrance here, exit here.
-That's correct.
Could you step down for a moment?
Objection. What is the point?
I need to make a clarification.
I'll overrule the objection.
Doctor, will you please step down?
Now, Dr. Koleena, I'm right-handed,
so could I assume that it would be...
...a natural motion for me
to cut you this way?
Yes.
And if I were left-handed,
that would be an unnatural motion?
Yes. You would cut right to left.
Thank you very much.
I have no further questions.
You're excused, Doctor.
Carl?
Objection, Your Honor--
One more stunt like that and I'll slap you...
...with a contempt citation so fast,
you won't know what hit you.
Mr. Sanger, don't ever do that again.
Hey! Wait a minute!
I'm not allowed to talk to you, Mr. Sanger.
The least you could do is thank me.
Thank you! I should go to the judge
and have you thrown off this panel.
Nobody twisted your arm to use it.
I was just trying to help.
I didn't ask for help.
-Hi, Kathleen.
-Hi.
You're not the one on trial, Miss Riley.
I thought the idea was to find the truth.
-I guess I got the wrong idea about justice.
-Don't hustle me!
You can save that bullshit
for your friends up on Capitol Hill.
We all know that you're just
brimming over with integrity, Miss Riley.
Who the fuck are you
to preach to me about mine?
If you really want to be helpful,
leave me alone.
Jury tampering is a felony.
Well, you haven't tampered with me...yet.
And I don't intend to.
Well, you want to win, don't you?
Look, this is not a game.
A man's life is at stake here.
Of course, I want to win.
But I draw the line at certain things.
Obviously, you never draw the line.
I change it all the time.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were allergic to milk.
I lied.
Did he kill her?
That's your problem.
We got to write 'em down every two hours
to see how long they been here.
It's surprising the number of those
trying to beat you out of some bucks...
...telling you they lost their ticket.
That's a ''9''.
You wrote an ''8''. See, it's a ''9''.
I mix 'em up sometimes
when I'm in a hurry, all right?
You say you got somethin'
to do with the trial?
A friend of the court.
Yeah, I got me a subpoena.
I'm supposed to testify.
You ain't no lawyer?
No.
They should send a shitload
of 'em back to Beantown.
-It was slow that night.
-KBG 622.
There couldn't have been more than 10,
15 cars on the lot.
She was parked down on the end.
The white Honda.
The city's supposed to pick it up,
but you know...
...they take their sweet-ass time.
-So the bearded mother, the bum?
-Yeah.
He been hangin' around off and on most
of the night. Let me tell you somethin'.
I got a case of trouble with them people.
He's roamin' around...
...looking for an unlocked car. He crawled
into that woman's car and went to sleep.
I ran his ratty ass outta there.
The bus dropped her off
a little after midnight...
...and I saw him hanging around again.
But it was too fuckin' cold to go out
and mess with him.
I remember thinkin', ''It's kinda strange
she didn't just drive right out.''
Then my girl called and we got into it,
you know, and I just forgot about her.
The bum iced her right around then.
Did you see anybody else?
No. Nobody to speak of.
Man, we get cars in and out of here
all the time.
And I slept some.
They don't pay me enough...
...to freeze my jones off
and stay awake, too.
-You know what I'm saying?
-Yeah.
That list...
with the license plate numbers on it?
-Yeah.
-The one from that night, do you have it?
Yeah, I got a copy if you want it.
Might as well keep it, man.
I don't know
what they save this bull for anyway.
Oh, shit.
How long you gonna be?
Thanks.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Where did you get that?
Over there.
-Could I ask you when you found it?
-For Christmas.
Would you sell it?
It isn't for sale.
I'll trade for it.
What do you want?
Your shoes.
My shoes.
And your socks.
Thank you.
Hello?
I have to talk to you.
-I can't hear you.
-I have to talk to you.
-I'll meet you at the Federal Station.
-Who is this?
I'll meet you in five minutes. Be there.
Mr. Sanger,
I told you to stay away from me.
Michael?
What do you think you're doing here?
If I had said it was me,
you wouldn't have come.
-You're right.
-Wait a minute.
Wait just a minute, all right?
A bag lady found this down by the river
where Elizabeth was killed.
What are you, a detective now?
I'm an amateur, but look at it.
The presidential seaI's on it.
It's got his signature on--
So what?
You can buy this at any gift store?
No, not one of these, you can't.
It's solid gold.
The President gives them out
as special gifts.
Senators, cabinet members, big donors...
...some lobbyists.
Look, the river is filled with garbage, okay?
Half the city washes up there.
What does it prove?
That's your problem, Counselor.
Get some sleep, okay? You look tired.
God is angry with the wicked.
-Why did you send the black devil for me?
-Because Carl--
Carl has already been judged.
The mighty hand
struck him deaf and dumb.
Only the Lord Jesus can take a soul.
I saw the angel of death.
I watched her die.
I saw her spirit leave her body. She gave
me a message from the Almighty.
A key to the kingdom.
The innocent
shall know the glory of heaven.
Stop it, asshole.
This is probably gonna burn.
Okay. All right.
God! Let me sit down.
If you feel you're gonna faint,
put your head between your knees.
-You think it'll leave a scar?
-I don't know. Could you sit still?
-It hurts, damn it.
-Well, I'm sorry.
It shouldn't hurt that much.
-Oh, yeah? Well, it--
-Hold on, hold on.
You got a piece right here.
I know. I know.
It hurts, damn it!
You're such a baby.
He got me, didn't he?
You know, you're lucky that you had
your jacket and your sweater on.
Yeah, I feel real lucky.
All right.
Maybe you're not as big an asshole
as I thought you were.
All right, it's a little better.
Good night.
You know,
I know that people have no values today.
Psychiatrists sleep with their patients,
lawyers sleep with their clients...
...professors sleep with their students.
I'm no angel...
...but I'm having a hard time...
...just pretending
like it's business as usual.
-Don't make a scene.
-All right.
-Are you trying to get me disbarred?
-Just listen to me a minute.
The President gave away
30 pairs of cuff links for Christmas.
They went out on the 15th.
He gave a set to Deputy Attorney General,
Paul Gray.
I know a girl who works in his office.
She told me that he brought up a couple
of girls from clerical, working nights.
And one of them was Elizabeth Quinn.
So what are you saying? Because she
happened to work for him, he killed her?
I need the cuff link.
Fuck the cuff link.
What you're asking me to do
is absolutely illegal.
You're gonna let your client fry
because you want to play by the rules?
No, I would do anything for my client.
I'm the only chance he has.
-But I'm not gonna break the law.
-All right.
If he did it, I'm gonna vote guilty.
But if he's innocent,
I don't want that on my conscience.
Miss Riley?
I want to see you in my chambers.
Now?
Now.
Have a seat, Miss Riley.
I saw you the other day.
I had the impression
you were talking with one of the jurors.
Have you had contact
with a juror on this trial?
No.
I'll have to take you at your word.
I'm very disappointed in you, Miss Riley.
I had heard good things about you.
But your cross has been weak.
Your behavior in this courtroom
has been unprofessional.
Well, I'm frustrated, Your Honor, because
I have no character witnesses and...
...I have no one
to corroborate my client's story.
Now I have no material witness, so l...
...I desperately need a continuance.
Come on, we've been through this.
You know how I feel about that.
Your Honor, last night Michael John
Guthridge contacted me and said things...
...that convinced me that if he isn't
the real suspect, then he saw who is.
And you think he can identify the killer?
Yes, I do.
Why is it whenever defense is in trouble,
there always seems to be a ''reaI'' suspect?
I'd genuinely like to help,
but it would be imprudent of me...
...to grant a continuance
because your case is weak.
Your dedication is commendable.
Don't be tempted
to sacrifice your integrity.
I warn you, Miss Riley,
if I find any evidence of collusion...
...you'll be disbarred
and charged with jury tampering.
Thank you all very much for coming.
Thank you.
Have you a minute, sir?
What's this ''sir'' shit, Eddie?
You never respected me
when I was on the Hill.
Well, you weren't a ''sir'' then.
Good afternoon, Mr. Gray.
From where I sit,
you have to be very discreet.
Come on, Paul,
discretion was never your best position.
I hear you've taken up my slack.
Well, you know what they say.
You can't measure a live snake.
A friend of mine was at a party
the other night.
He runs down by the Potomac.
He's a jogger. He found this.
I remember you wearing
a pair at the reception.
It's not something you want to lose.
I thought maybe
you weren't discreet enough.
I didn't want it to come back to haunt you.
I haven't lost one that I know of,
but I appreciate your concern.
Whoever did lose it
might not want it to be found.
Asking people about it
isn't such a bright idea.
It's a good way to make enemies.
And this is a bad place to have enemies.
Paul, you were the one who told me
that everybody's your enemy.
It just isn't very smart
to go looking for them.
Maybe you're right.
Oh, Eddie? Let's see that again.
I'll take a look at home. Maybe it is mine.
You don't need it for anything, do you?
What'll I do with it?
Detective Purcell,
you stated earlier in your testimony...
...that homicides are usually committed
by the most obvious suspect.
That's the way it usually falls.
And we will agree
with your logical assumption...
...that Mr. Anderson
was the most obvious suspect.
With the evidence and my experience...
...it was more than just an assumption,
Counselor.
Your experience is impressive indeed,
Detective Purcell.
But isn't it true,
in the American justice system...
...that the police do not determine
the guilt or the innocence of a man?
Yes, that's true.
Did you know from
the Justice Department's own research...
...343 innocent people
were convicted of capital crimes?
Objection.
Twenty-five were executed
and later found innocent.
-Objection.
-They were the most obvious suspects.
Miss Riley, that's enough.
This is a cross-examination of a witness...
...not an indictment of the justice system.
I'm trying to show that the police
aren't infallible. None of us are.
Counselor, approach the bench. Mr. Stella.
The jury should deal with the facts
and not with the defense's rhetoric.
Sir, would you step down, please?
Either you'll argue the merits of this case
or I'll excuse the witness.
You understand?
What was that about a rope, Counselor?
Detective Purcell...
...would you say we have an abnormally
large population of homeless?
Yes, I would.
I see them across the street
from the White House in Lafayette Square.
We've cleared most of them out of there.
It just doesn't look good.
Anywhere else?
Yes, Union Station.
-We've got a real problem down there.
-Objection.
This is all fascinating,
but where's the defense going with this?
I'll allow her to continue, Counselor.
I'm interested to see
where she's going with this.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Now, you said Union Station.
I take the train occasionally
and I've never seen homeless people there.
Well, Counselor, you really have to look.
We've cleared most of them out.
So now they use
the old Railway Express building.
Hello.
I'm looking for somebody.
Man, who do you want?
I'm looking for a man....
He's got a tattoo on his hand.
It's a cross. It says ''Jesus the Savior.''
Do you know who I'm talking about?
What's the matter?
I've asked for a delay in the start
of the proceedings this morning.
A man found murdered
at Union Station this morning...
...has been identified
as Michael John Guthridge.
Your Honor,
I'd like to ask for a continuance...
...until the police can ascertain
if his murder is related to this case.
I'm inclined to agree with you. Counselor?
A decision shouldn't be made
on a continuance...
...until more information is made available.
I would propose we press on.
I want to give this proper consideration.
We'll continue with the proceedings...
...and I'll make my decision known
by the end of the court day.
All right.
Bring in the defendant. Call the jury.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
This won't happen again.
The defendant will have his hands cuffed
during the proceedings.
Please don't do this to me.
Your client has done it for you, Counselor.
Call your first witness.
Your Honor,
we call Dr. Alan Alpert to the stand.
Call Dr. Alan Alpert.
Raise your right hand, please.
Do you swear to tell the truth...
...the whole truth,
nothing but the truth, so help you God?
-I do.
-You may be seated.
Dr. Alpert, you are a professor
of sociology at Maryland University.
-Is that correct?
-Yes.
-And what is your field of expertise?
-Transient behavior.
Excuse me. The President has announced
his nomination for D.C. Circuit Court.
I've been asked
to come to the White House.
This court will stand adjourned
until tomorrow morning at 9:30.
Your Honor, what about my continuance?
A juror must have left this glove.
This is where she worked.
My friend said Elizabeth Quinn's section
was putting everything on computer disks.
All the case transcripts.
Okay.
What are you doing on this floor?
Fourteenth is secure.
I thought I could help.
I was the last officer. I already done it.
Get up to the 16th floor
where you're supposed to be.
Eddie.
Shit.
What did you expect?
Something was in there,
and Elizabeth Quinn found it.
I'll find it...
...if I have to read every goddamn
transcript from every case in 1968.
-How many cases?
-Over 100.
You know, Paul Gray started out
as a federal prosecutor.
-He ever work here?
-I don't know.
All right, just hold on.
Morty said that Paul Gray prosecuted here
in the late 60s.
Bingo.
What we do is, tomorrow we go
through the cases he prosecuted first.
-Can you get home from here?
-Yeah, I just take the metro.
-I'm the other way.
-All right.
What?
Never mind.
I've read eight cases
that Paul Gray prosecuted.
There's nothing unusual about any of them.
Supreme Court Justice Lowell
was a presiding judge on two of the cases.
When did he kill himself?
December, before Christmas.
What's the connection?
See if you can find me 287.
-What are you doing here?
-I had no place to go.
A friend checked those license numbers...
...to see if any names came up.
Nothing, just names.
413 927: Spencer Lewis.
CAN 412: Andrea Duncan.
That's a Maryland plate.
-I know them all by heart.
-I don't care.
-What do you mean?
I'm tired and I don't care. Good night.
Well, fuck you, too. Good night.
I don't deserve this.
Look, I don't owe you anything.
I don't owe anybody anything.
I'm working for some creep
who's probably guilty.
-Guilty?
-Yeah, that's right, guilty.
It's not complicated.
He was hungry, he needed money,
he saw a woman and killed her.
-And Michael, with his throat slit?
-A sick bastard.
-What about the files?
-It's all bullshit.
-You don't believe that!
-I'm tired, okay? I want you to go. Now.
Good night.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...it is my responsibility
to insure that these proceedings...
...maintain the highest standards
of integrity.
It came to my attention
there's the possibility...
...of these standards being compromised.
To insure this doesn't happen...
...I'll sequester the jury
for the rest of this trial.
I remind you of your solemn oath
to remain impartial...
...to weigh the evidence and independently
render a verdict of your conscience.
You'll be made as comfortable as possible,
under the circumstances.
I thank you for your perseverance.
Counsel, I expect you
to be the models of propriety...
...for the remainder of this proceeding.
Your Honor,
the defense calls Carl Wayne Anderson.
The marshal may remove
Mr. Anderson's handcuffs.
His hands can be free while he testifies...
...so long as he doesn't abuse the privilege.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Please raise your right hand.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth, nothing but the truth...
...so help you God?
For the record,
the witness indicated his assent.
You may be seated.
Please state your full name and address.
Your address?
''None.''
We need a home address, Your Honor.
Make it in care of me,
the public defender's office.
Without objection.
Mr. Anderson, have you ever killed anyone?
''Yes.''
Why?
''I'm not sure.''
You killed someone
and you're not sure why?
''I was in Vietnam. I was 19.''
So you were a soldier.
It was your job to kill. You did your job.
You didn't need a reason.
Carl, do you think you needed a reason?
''Yes.''
The fact is, it upset you so much
that you had a breakdown.
You were discharged
for psychiatric reasons...
...and spent six years
in a veterans hospital.
All because you were a good soldier
who thought he needed a reason to kill.
What were your dreams?
Your dreams. When you were young,
what did you want to be?
''A carpenter...
''...and build my own house.''
And were you ever in love?
''I loved Caroline.''
Who was Caroline?
''My wife.''
Did you and Caroline plan to have children?
''We talked about it.''
And what happened?
''We were divorced.''
Why?
''After the sickness...
''...I had nothing left...
''...to offer her.''
It's been rough.
You've had your share of problems.
You've been kicked around pretty good.
Are we supposed to feel sorry for you?
Plenty of people have problems.
Plenty of people get kicked around.
You know the difference
between you and them?
They still have their dignity.
They don't sleep in the gutter.
They don't eat out of garbage cans.
They don't urinate on people's lawns.
They take showers, change their clothes.
They don't feel sorry for themselves.
They get married, they have children.
They take responsibility for their life.
They don't sleep in other people's cars.
They don't steal $9.00 from anyone!
Did you kill Elizabeth Rose Quinn?
Your witness.
That was a wonderful performance.
The man shouldn't be on trial,
he should be given a medal.
You were discharged from the army
for psychiatric reasons, is that right?
''Yes.''
Did you beat your superior officer
with a shovel...
...because he asked you to dig a trench?
Was that one of the reasons?
''Yes.''
Violence seems to follow you
wherever you go.
-Objection, Your Honor.
-Sustained.
Were you arrested in 1978...
...for assaulting a congressional aide
on Constitution Avenue?
''Yes.''
And were you in the District of Columbia
jail for six months for beating a man?
''He stole my shoe.''
Did you punch your own attorney
in the face when she--
Objection, Your Honor. That's privileged.
I'll withdraw the question.
You were in the parking lot on K Street
the night of December 18?
''Yes.''
And you did break into
Elizabeth Quinn's car?
-''It was cold.''
-Just yes or no, please.
Your counsel has given us
enough explanation.
Objection, Your Honor.
Could we proceed?
Did the parking lot attendant
throw you off the lot?
''Yes.''
But you came back, just before midnight?
You attacked Elizabeth Quinn there
and dragged her down to the river?
''No.''
You were at the Potomac River
after midnight, weren't you?
''I was looking for wood--''
Just yes or no, please.
''Yes.''
Elizabeth was there. You were there.
Her purse was stolen. You had her purse.
Her throat was cut! You had a knife!
Those are the naked facts!
Objection, Your Honor.
Perhaps Mr. Stella would wait till the end
to make his closing argument.
Sustained.
Ms. Riley has the gift of speech.
I'll let the facts speak for themselves.
How did you expect us to believe
you didn't kill her?
No further questions at this time,
Your Honor.
-Hey, lady, what do you think you're doing?
-I was her friend.
I'm sorry to bother you at home.
That's all right,
although this is highly irregular.
I have evidence that will,
if not prove my client innocent...
...at least necessitate a mistrial.
Excuse me, Matthew.
May I use your phone?
Deputy Attorney General Paul Gray,
Miss Kathleen Riley.
Miss Riley is the public defender
in the Elizabeth Quinn trial.
Miss Quinn worked in my department.
I've followed the trial with great interest.
Miss Riley feels she has evidence
which will exculpate her client.
-The phone?
-There's one in the study.
No, don't bother, Matthew.
Nice to meet you, Miss Riley.
Yes, what is this evidence?
Your Honor, I feel that I've behaved rashly.
I should present the evidence properly
tomorrow in court.
This is somewhat erratic, isn't it?
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
I've been under tremendous strain lately.
This behavior is bordering
on professional misconduct, Miss Riley.
Mathew? I'm sorry,
there's a problem I have to take care of.
My regards to your wife.
Thanks for the evening.
-Let me show you out.
-Don't bother.
This is Justice Charles F. Lowell.
For 20 years I've lived with this burden,
always expecting exposure...
...from a law student,
a legal scholar, or a colleague.
Elizabeth Rose Quinn,
a clerk at the Justice Department...
...unfamiliar with the law,
recognized the injustice of the decision...
...in United States vs. Cook
and came to me.
More than the fear of exposure,
I've had to live with myself.
It's a terrible price to pay for ambition.
In 1968...
...while I was the presiding judge
on the case of United States vs. Cook...
...in the Federal Court,
Washington District...
...I conspired to fix the case.
I accepted a bribe.
In exchange for an appointment...
...to a seat
on the United States Circuit Court.
I dismissed all charges of vote fraud
against a politically influential defendant.
Miss Quinn has contacted the others
that were involved.
I leave them to their consciences.
I will make my peace somewhere else.
I have asked Elizabeth Quinn
to make this public after my death.
This is my last small measure of justice.
To fix a case, you've got to have a judge
who's willing to go along.
You've got to have
a very influential defendant...
...a politic defense attorney,
and a corrupt prosecutor.
United States vs. Cook.
That must be one of the cases
I didn't get to.
I'm willing to bet you
Paul Gray was the prosecuting attorney.
You realize you're accusing...
...the Deputy Attorney General
of the United States of murder.
I had the federal supplement here.
I must have left it at the courthouse.
I'll see you.
Hey, what's going on?
Sounds like a fire alarm.
Is this for real or what?
Is this for real?
Madam, close the door, please.
Please. Stay together.
It's just a fire alarm.
-Is this the public defender's office?
-Yes.
Is Kathleen Riley there?
She's gone over to the courthouse.
She'll be back shortly.
Could I take a message?
Would you--
Never mind, thank you.
Kathleen!
It's all right.
All rise. The court for
the District of Columbia is now in session.
The Honorable
Judge Matthew Bishop Helms presiding.
Please be seated and come to order.
The court calls forward the matter...
...of the United States
vs. Carl Wayne Anderson.
-We were going to begin redirect.
-The defense has no redirect.
-Mr. Gray?
-Defense called me to appear, Your Honor.
I wasn't aware of any subpoena.
I've come under advisement of counsel
on my own volition. To hear charges.
We would like to thank the Deputy
Attorney General for his compliance.
Approach the bench.
Why wasn't I informed of this?
The defense has the prerogative
to call vital witnesses.
-Don't lecture me on the law, Miss Riley.
-I'm sorry.
-Do you have other witnesses?
-Yes, I do.
-Are they present?
-Yes.
-You may call your first witness.
-Thank you.
Your Honor,
we call Your Honor to the stand.
What's the meaning of this?
I can't be called to the stand.
You have knowledge
that is vital to our case.
Counsel, approach the bench.
I'll have a subpoena issued
to compel you to testify.
Approach the bench
or you'll be in contempt of court.
-I can't be compelled to testify.
-You're not above the law.
If you persist,
I'll be forced to call a mistrial.
Mr. Helms, were you the federal prosecutor
on the United States vs. Cook trial 1968?
This trial is a mistrial.
Did you conspire with
District Court Judge Charles F. Lowell...
...to dismiss that case
for his appointment to a higher court...
-...and an appointment to your seat?
-You're in contempt of court.
Did you wait 17 years
while lesser men passed you by?
Watching lesser men
get appointments to a higher court.
I'll have you disbarred!
An appointment to the Circuit Court...
...a step away from the Supreme Court...
...did your past haunt you?
Did you strike it and kill it?
Remove her from the court!
Did you willfully plan
and murder Elizabeth Quinn...
...when she approached you
with your past?
Remove Miss Riley from this court.
Miss Riley, you're in contempt of court.
I'll have you disbarred.
Remove Miss Riley from this court.
-Was your car, license number...
-Remove Miss Riley!
...6F9 587, in the parking lot on K Street
on the night of December 18?
Did you wait, and when Elizabeth Quinn
arrived at her car, did you beat her...
...drag her down to the river
and savagely cut her throat?
I've filed charges
with the D.C. Police Department...
...for the arrest of Matthew Bishop Helms
for murder in the first degree.
-Congratulations, Kathleen.
-Thanks.
All of a sudden I have nothing to do.
I have to be in court in an hour.
A guy on the jury was a jeweler.
I had him check out that cuff link.
It turned out to be gold-plated.
Just garbage.
I know. I told you so.
Yeah, I thought you would say that.
-What can we do for an hour?
-Leave the door open.
Let go.
Download GOM Player to experience
the highest video and audio quality!