Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Renacimiento... renacimiento.
We're clear.
Renacimiento...
That's all he's been saying.
It means rebirth.
Renacimiento renacimiento.
Rebirth of what?
Renacimiento...
You said he was blind.
Yes... he was.
Can you show me where
it landed?
We're too late.
This place is changing.
Everyone in town's nervous...
But, like you say, nothing
bad ever lasts, right?
Annie's coming to visit.
I was hoping we could take
a road trip.
You'd be so proud of her,
you know.
So proud.
Radio announcer
headlining news this morning,
protests continue around...
The nation following approval
of the president's draft
bill...
Pledging over 100,000
additional troops
to operation terminus...
The ongoing occupation of Iran.
Russian and Chinese foreign
ministers have intensified
warnings...
Against the United States
as the president maintains
resolve.
Last week it was braces.
Yesterday, ritalin.
Trading stocks, man, that's my
game.
You assholes gonna do
any work today?
Oh, yeah, we're
over-friggin-whelmed here.
Hey. J.C.'S trans-am needs
a transmission overhaul.
New exhaust...
Nitrogen in the tires.
It's a long shot.
Yeah.
Three days to order the
parts. Two days bank shuts
us down.
22 years I've been helping
this town run on wheels.
Doesn't have to end like
this, ned.
You kidding me?
I'll be paying this shit-storm
off for the next 22 years,
if I don't file chapter 7 now.
We ain't asking
for a handout.
Boys'll put in the work,
you know that, but fuck, ned, we
need our jobs.
David, it's over. Done.
Well, I'll see if Ramon 's got
any exhausts lying around.
Fix j.C.'S trans-am, maybe
that keeps the doors open
another couple days.
Yeah. Do what you want.
She's something.
Yeah, she's a crying shame.
You the boss around here?
If you're looking for a job,
you're in the wrong place.
Tony, let's go.
I did three years as a field
engineer with the ninth.
Yep.
I just need a chance.
We all do.
Reporter
general corazon estimates
casualty rates to drop...
Once draft reinforcements
complete training.
Jesus, dad!
I'm cutting you off.
Just go home.
No...
Come on, Mickey.
You can ride with me.
Come on.
No.
You too, Mr. Chamberlain.
Come on. Last one.
As you can see, the
occupation relies...
On strategic strong-holds along
the Afghan-iranian border.
A swathe of Russian-endorsed
guerilla fighters continued
across the hindu kush...
From Pakistan to conduct raids
on us bases.
H2o... on the rocks.
Hey. Bourbon, double.
Reporter
the daily casualty rate
has risen to 23.
So when'd the U.S. army become
target practice for arabs...
And Cannon fodder for Jews?
Should send me over.
I'll teach 'em how to fight.
Bunch of goddamned pussies.
Used to have standards.
Now they'll take anyone.
Queers, Mexicans. Mexican
queers.
No wonder we're losing.
What the fuck would you
know about it? Huh?
You should sign up. They'd
love you.
Okay, Princess... let's go.
Goddamn Tyson.
Here we go again.
Hey!
Come on, guys, leave him alone!
You son of a--
what the hell?
He's got a goddamn fake leg!
He's a goddamn cripple.
Shit!
Ah, man. Screw this.
Let's get out of here.
Here.
Hey.
Get in.
Come on.
What did you think was gonna
happen back there?
How long were you over there?
You know what your problem is?
You're like every other hick
in this town.
Full of opinions on things
you know nothing about.
Scared shitless of losing
what you think you have.
And what's that?
A future.
A future?
Yeah.
I'm not the one picking fights
i know I can't win.
Asshole.
Pull in here.
Shit.
Guess you forgot.
What happened?
Accident. Looks worse
than it is.
When'd you get in?
This afternoon,
like we talked about.
I'll clean you up.
Lot of luggage for one week.
I'm staying.
How long?
You quit... why?
I don't want to talk about it,
not while you're like this.
Like what? Disappointed?
What happened? Some boy
break your heart?
No.
Well, I didn't send you out
there to quit, Annabelle.
I've been busting my ass
every damn day in that shop
so you can have a future.
I didn't quit.
Your last two payments
didn't go through.
Shit. So my-- I'm sorry.
I just need another week.
I'll call them, fix it.
Forget it.
No, I'll take care of it.
No. Stop, i--
I don't want you working
yourself to the bone...
Not again.
You think she would've
wanted this?
Don't tell me
what she wanted.
Happy birthday.
He didn't come home last night.
He's not answering his cell.
Sheriff, please. There's
something seriously wrong.
He wouldn't--
24 hours?
Ned?
I'm looking for my dad.
He hasn't come home.
Neither has my wife.
She took the Camaro.
Drove the boy to Canada.
She's afraid he'll get drafted.
Have you seen David?
Your dad's a good man.
Guys like him, they run
on hope.
But... you can't eat hope.
Hey.
We haven't got the chance
to tell you.
Real sorry about your mom.
She was a good one.
Dad?
David.
Annabelle.
I don't mean to be
insensitive...
But I was kind of hoping you
could answer a question for me.
Your mother underwent a
kidney transplant at St. Luke's.
Your father is listed
as the donor.
Her body rejected the
transplant.
See, what I'm trying
to understand is...
There must have been some
kind of mistake.
The x-rays--
your father has two perfectly
functioning kidneys
of his own.
We've just reached the point
of no return.
Ultimatum from Russia and China
changes everything.
Not hungry?
And with no sign of the U.S.
or Israel backing down.
In the hospital, you kept
calling her...
Talking to her like
she was right there.
Commentator
thermo-nuclear war and
at the very least...
A conflict that will just
overshadow absolutely anything
that's going on.
I know it's been tough,
but we're only going to make it
if we work at this together.
Okay?
Yeah.
Commentator
there's a great deal of secrecy
surrounding...
The general's next move.
But there are rumors that
ground forces are making
their way...
Across the border into Tehran
in the coming days.
Air raids have already
intensified...
And we have word
that special forces troops...
Have infiltrated several
critical outposts closer in...
Paving the way for
aggressive ground attacks.
The first wave of us draft
troops have arrived from
training in Afghanistan...
Despite stern warnings from
Russian, Chinese and French
leaders.
David.
Jane?
I miss you.
I know.
What's happening to me?
You remember the night
i told you I was pregnant?
You said you didn't want to
bring a child into this place...
But as long as we were together
there was always hope.
You have to create it.
There isn't much time...
For Annie.
Commentator
the president has assured us
that the disarmament of Iran...
Will insure a sense of security
for generations to come...
But what we're dealing with
is the complete and utter...
Destabilization
of an entire region.
We've caused the displacement
of thousands of families into
refugee camps.
These families are suffering
from starvation due
to overcrowding.
The question we've got
to ask ourselves is...
When will the bloodshed
come to an end?
I wasn't expecting you to
come all the way out here.
I came so you could explain to
me in person why, in the middle
of a war...
Are you still chasing
space rocks?
I'm sure you can understand
why we haven't been able
to leave.
The data is undeniable.
You were ordered to shut down.
I can't... not yet.
We're too close.
You were army intelligence
before you joined us...
Four years in Pakistan, yet you
chose an assignment completely
unbefitting your skill set.
I felt I could make a
difference this time.
This war needs men like you
on the front line.
Men with scars like yours,
win wars.
What we are about to find here,
it could change everything.
You wouldn't need war.
The country is dying.
People are starving.
Desperate for opportunity...
Hope.
War gives them a reason...
Purpose.
Now, we don't need to end
this war, not yet.
But as is the case with any
conflict, we do need a strategic
advantage.
Although the specimen we have
hasn't survived...
But there may be a living sample
somewhere.
It seems to require
temperate climates.
It's unsustainable above 80
degrees.
What's the status of our
patient?
Dr. Wilkins advises that
Mr. Gutierrez may not
survive the procedure.
We're at 23 casualties
a day in Iran... 23.
Open him up.
I want to know everything
about it.
Hey. What are we telling
the wife?
You can tell her that
Mr. Gutierrez suffered
cardiac arrest...
In the attempt to
save him from a lethal virus.
That his sacrifice has spared
the country from a deadly
epidemic.
David
oh, messy, messy face.
Okay... silly me.
Now push her on the swing.
Look out.
Whoo! Daddy will catch you.
Touching the camera.
There we go. I'm gonna
tickle your feet.
Okay. Want me to push
you on the swing?
Oh, you're a good girl...
Good girl.
Hi, daddy.
Look at the camera.
I want a round.
What are you doing?
Writing a letter
to general corazon.
What for?
The age of advanced
technological warfare...
And we're sending draftees
to die in the desert.
And here I am unemployed
and impotent.
Fuck draftees.
I can still hold a gun.
Yeah?
I'd rather starve
to death here.
Beats the pity stares and
those 11:00am support groups.
Nothing worse than being
surrounded by a bunch of guys...
Claiming that the silver lining
of the colostomy bag...
Is that you don't have to wait
to the commercial to piss.
You don't want to go back.
See pain, I can deal
with that.
It's the inactivity that sucks.
World's going to hell anyway.
We're just reaping what
we've sown.
Hey, you know what
acrotomophilia is, right?
Anima-- what?
It's perverts getting
turned on by stumps.
No joke.
Why would you bring that up?
You got one on your six.
Give me a second.
I get ten percent.
What do you want?
Still looking for a job?
Run the winch.
What are we haulin'?
Bring it up!
What the hell is that?
Help me here.
Come on.
Get in.
Commentator
what we're seeing now
are the arrival...
Of half a dozen Chinese and
Russian warships into the
persian Gulf...
What the president is calling a
futile show of intimidation...
Against the coalition forces
currently occupying Iran.
What's this?
I'm putting half
in the barn.
The other half is going
to goodwill.
Fresh start for both of us,
right?
This your mom's stuff?
Yeah, well, you haven't been
around much...
So I figure that this place
could use a little bit
of a spring clean.
This is one of her favorites.
That ski-hike... we did
in Vermont that winter...
And the blizzard rolled
in right over the top of us.
You were so scared, but your
mom held you so tight.
You remember what she said?
Nothing bad will ever last.
You don't need to pretend she
was never here to move on.
You're due for an upgrade, man.
Christ, Zach,
this one works fine.
Ooh!
What's the matter?
You all right?
Yeah. Leg's playing up.
Phantoms... I get 'em
all the time.
It's different if you see
your limbs come off.
You get closure.
How much did that perv pay you?
$40.
That all?
Well, it's something.
One minute it's a job, next he's
got his cock in your mouth.
Makes sense to me.
What else are we good for?
They think you'll charge half
the price for just one knee pad?
Why don't you put that
in your letter? Hm?
What's that supposed to mean?
Okay. You ready to do this?
For all the good it's gonna do.
We don't want your fascist war!
We don't need your draft no
more!
We don't we want
your fascist war!
We don't we need your draft
no more!
All right, all right, come on,
people. Let's wrap this up.
We don't we want
your fascist war!
We don't we need--
what the--
come on.
Hey, sir? Hey, you look
like a smart guy.
Sign this and you won't
have to worry about your kids
getting blown up.
How 'bout it?
Traitor.
Say it again! Say it again!
Hey! Hey!
Say it again! I'll kill you!
Get off me!
That's it, people!
Enjoy the freak show! Huh?
Want to spend a night
in a jail cell?
Oh, Jesus, you got to get
that leg checked out, man.
Go.
Just go.
What the hell is that?
What the hell did
you do to me?
Dad?
Get some water.
Now, Annie!
Breathe, breathe.
He needs to go to the hospital.
No hospitals.
Are you crazy?
He'll bleed to death.
No, he won't.
It's healing him.
What is that?
I need you to stay here
and watch him.
Keep your eyes on him.
I'll be back.
So what's the plan?
Our movement orders came in.
We report to Philly at 0800.
I'm sorry to disappoint,
gentlemen, but we're not going
to Philadelphia.
What?
Give me three samples.
Now what do you mean?
We just had another one land...
North-east.
But our intel is thin at best.
How do we explain this
to deputy ep--
deputy Epstein will
come around.
I'm sure he'll be grateful
for every dead soldier
we don't need to bury.
A blind man can see...
What the fuck else do you need?
We're going north-east.
Medic!
Hey.
Are you okay? Stay calm.
Just rest.
You're okay?
You're gonna start bleeding
again.
It'll be okay.
Just rest. Okay?
It's okay. It'll be okay.
What the hell is going
on here?
We need to move him.
Grab the door.
Grab the door!
Oh, hold him.
What is that?
It's dying from the heat.
We gotta get him closer.
Bring that over.
What's it doing?
You'll see. Just watch.
Hey... it's okay.
Look. See?
Hey.
It's okay... he'll be here.
You okay?
It's real. I'm not dreaming.
I hope not.
What's it like?
Strange.
Where is he?
Dad?
You gotta see this.
What's it for?
Protection.
Protection? From what?
Something we can't prevent.
Look, I know it sounds crazy,
but you've seen what it can do.
You've felt it.
This-- this is a gift.
You have no idea what this
thing is or what else it's
capable of.
You have to trust me
with this, Annie.
Everything'll be fine...
I promise.
We're gonna need a ton of steel.
Ramon 's got me on inventory.
Shit job, but who's complaining,
right?
Guy's got his hands in so many
pies, still bitches.
Half the shit I don't even ask
about. How you doing?
You know.
You should hook up with Mickey,
trade some stocks.
Yeah, that'd be great.
That old metal works, though,
that's where it's at.
Swear to god if I had the money,
I'd re-open it myself.
Come on, that place's nothing
but a graveyard.
Hey, you could be my foreman.
Thanks.
So this is the shit
you wanted?
Yeah. I owe you.
How's Annie holding up?
She's worried. Who wouldn't be?
No, I mean since Jane.
I don't know. She's fine.
Maybe better than I am.
You know, I always wanted
to kill you.
Scoring the one girl on the
drill team that turned me down.
I was strong side linebacker.
You always were a lucky son-
of-a-bitch though, huh?
Hey, thanks.
Hey, how old are you now?
Keep dreaming.
Bottoms up.
We should go to a titty bar.
Yeah.
There you go.
Yep. Got em.
Come on, let's go.
This is it.
You sure?
Yeah. No one's set foot
in here in years.
Let's bring in that
cement mixer.
Should I be concerned
about any of this business?
Oh, not at all, sheriff.
It's just protocol.
Appears to be stable.
Where's the rest of it?
You're supposed to tell me.
Do you believe in
coincidences, agent stipe?
In my experience, there are
no coincidences, sheriff.
You might want to talk
to David Chamberlain.
Local guy, crashed his car
near here the other night.
Strangest thing, too.
Not a scratch on him.
It's unprecedented.
At first we couldn't understand
what we were seeing.
Fluorescence in-situ
hybridization identified
the presence...
Of hundreds of different alleles
for each gene.
But this genetic information
isn't organized into chromosomes
as we understand them.
So far, we've isolated multiple
sequences resembling various
plant and animal strands.
Some of these strands even
appear to be human.
What we're dealing with here
is a living sample
of a biogenesis.
Evolution?
No, no. This precedes
evolution. It's creation.
Who'd have thought...
That's an amoeba.
I don't know what to do.
You always said that he'd
do things in his own way.
The fact is that without
you he--
he did his best
and... I hate him for it.
I don't want to hate him.
I never could quite understand
how you... kept loving him.
No matter how many times
he let you down.
I miss you so much, mom.
This'll work.
You're standing too close.
What?
Unless you're planning
on setting yourself alight.
You must be Annabelle.
Special agent Julius stipe...
National science agency.
We'd like to ask your father
some questions.
Is he here?
No.
Oh, no need to be alarmed.
It's just protocol.
What do you want
with my father?
We're looking for something.
We're hoping he might be
able to help us find it.
Got a little drunk
with the boys.
It was my birthday.
I came home to celebrate
with my daughter.
I can't recall seeing anything
but a light in the sky...
And that was when
i lost control.
Not much more I remember
before I blacked out.
You ever been to the
air and space museum in D.C.,
Mr. Chamberlain?
No.
My mother used to drive me
there every summer.
She'd let me wander
the place for hours.
I learned so many things
about the universe and time
and space.
It's really incredible
everything we've accomplished...
But what's even more fascinating
is how little we actually know.
I've always believed that
if we found real evidence...
Of something greater
than ourselves...
Something that inspired
the human race...
Then maybe the world
would have peace.
Now this thing you found,
it just might be the miracle
people are hoping for.
Can't say I believe
in miracles all that much.
You have a kidney in your
body that wasn't there
before, Mr. Chamberlain.
So, please don't lie to me.
The last person to come
in contact with an object
like the one you found...
He thought it had healed
him, too.
That's where I kept it.
Wasn't long before I noticed
it didn't react well to the
humidity in here.
Thing had just ... melted.
Melted?
Things been tough,
Mr. Chamberlain?
Huh?
Since the death of your wife.
Must have been very hard
for you...
Knowing there was nothing
you could do to save her.
Yeah.
Sorry I can't be more
help to you.
No, you've been more
than helpful. Thank you.
Annie?
They know you have it.
They're gonna find it.
What then?
They take you away?
Cut you open like that old man?
No, that won't happen.
Those men were here,
in our house.
It found me for a reason.
She found me.
Who? Who found you?
Your mom, Annie. She showed me
something's gonna happen.
No. This-- this thing is messing
with your head, changing you.
Can't you see that?
No, you're wrong!
She's gone, dad.
You didn't want to see it
when she was lying in that
hospital bed all alone...
But she's gone and you
can't bring her back.
No! No.
I won't let them
take it away.
You know what it showed me?
It showed me everything
i wanted to forget.
Just before she died,
she asked me where you were...
When you were coming
to see her.
But you never came.
Annie?
Hey, Mickey, I need a favor.
He's driving in circles.
Bring him in.
How you doing? Nice suit.
We have a situation.
You lost him.
For now.
The daughter.
U.S. casualties have risen
well above 35 soldiers a day...
As the advancement
into Tehran continues.
Members of congress have met
to persuade the president
and general corazon...
To halt any further movement...
What the hell is that?
In Iran until an agreement
can be reached...
This isn't gonna end well.
...with Russia and China.
They'll shake hands,
exchange pleasantries...
Then go back to killing
children again.
Ramon , you okay?
Explain why some assholes
are moving my scrap.
And a truck that only you
have the keys to.
What?
This some kind of inside job?
Inside job? I don't know
shit about this.
No? It sure looks like your
boy Chamberlain to me.
Dave.
Don't fuck with me, cerillo.
Get my truck back.
Zach?
You okay?
Look at me.
Didn't know where else
to go.
She was sick.
He did everything he could.
Gave her a part of himself...
But she kept getting worse.
All he did was work.
Trying to pay for treatments
we couldn't afford.
I know he thinks
he's doing this for me...
But I can't be the reason.
They'll kill for it.
I won't let that happen.
Okay?
I'll take you to your dad...
But first... I want you
to meet someone.
Jim.
I brought a friend.
This is Annabelle.
You know the t-bones they're
serving here are shipped
in from China?
You believe that?
Where the hell is all our
meat, if we gotta eat cows
from China?
Hey.
I've found a way
to make things better.
The way it was before.
I don't need another one
of your goddamned arms or legs,
Zach. I got nowhere to go.
Hey, listen. Listen to me.
Hey!
It's healed. It's healed.
That's a nice trick.
Come with me.
I can make you better.
Maybe another time.
Celtics are playing
the bulls tonight.
Not many games left.
Who knows if there'll even
be another season, right?
I'm coming back and I'm
gonna get you out of here.
Okay?
Let's go for a ride, corporal.
Don't be a hero.
Tony?
We used to play in here.
You stole Ramon 's truck.
For this?
What the fuck is this?
You couldn't begin
to understand.
Understand?
After all I've done for you?
This is the only way.
This thing is bigger than you.
Bullshit!
I got responsibilities.
Dave, I'm not going down
for you.
You won't go down.
I'm not going down
for you or no one.
I'm telling you.
Yeah, police.
Shit!
Tony?
Dave?
How long since we last
did this?
Thanksgiving... two years ago.
That was the last time
i could move like this.
You're so beautiful.
Where is she, David?
She doesn't trust me.
She wants to.
No.
No, I've done a terrible thing.
I don't deserve this.
I know. It was never
meant for you.
You have to find them.
You're out of time.
This has now been confirmed.
Bagram airbase, the U.S.
military's primary staging
point for operation terminus...
Has been attacked by a long
range wmd of Russian origin.
We have unconfirmed reports
this was in fact a nuclear
missile.
The search for survivors has
been impeded by the danger and
instability of the site.
Says here you were
wounded in combat.
Left leg amputated below
the knee.
In the Pentagon report that we
are now at defcon 1...
Meaning the nuclear retaliation
against Russia--
well, by the looks of it,
things have taken quite
a turn for you.
Think of the good we could
achieve, corporal.
Field casualties would drop
exponentially.
We could actually have a
chance at ending this war.
Don't you see that?
You need to tell me
where it is, Annabelle.
Wherever he's taken it,
you can be sure it's far
from here.
Touching.
Stop!
Tell me where it is!
I gave you a chance...
On your knees.
We got something by the barn.
He's here.
Get him.
Look around back. Go.
Mr. Chamberlain.
We have to go, Annie.
We're not leaving him here.
The key.
Turn around.
Slowly!
What now?
Can you walk?
Yeah.
Come on, Annie. We've got
to get out of here.
Come on.
Get the rifle.
Give me the gun.
Annie!
Come on, let's go!
Stay-- stay with me. Stay, stay.
It's okay. It's okay, Annie.
Okay, dad.
It's okay.
Come on!
All right... they're headed
across town.
This isn't right.
We're on the brink
of nuclear war.
I need you to understand that.
Maybe this thing wasn't
sent to win wars.
Just drive.
You hear me?
Just fucking drive.
She needs you.
She's waiting for you.
Baby, I did this for you.
Come on.
Please, please. Please!
Fuck!
They're here.
Sorry, baby.
She's gone.
David, what are you doing?
Put it down.
You're gonna get us killed.
David, stop.
You don't want to do
anything stupid.
I need you to put that out.
No.
I have to destroy it.
Put it out now.
Dad?
Dad!
Wait! Stop!
Crap!
I won't let you do this.
You stupid fuck.
Dad. Come on, dad.
Stay inside. Annie!
I need you to look
after her for me.
Can you do that?
Get inside, Zach.
Get inside!
Dad.
I'm sorry, Annie.
I'm sorry.
I can't go.
Go where, dad?
I love you.
Dad!
Annie, it's okay... it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
What is that?
David, look at me.
Open it.
I can't... I can't open it.
Annie. It's okay.
Come home, David.
Come home.
My mother once told me...
Nothing bad will ever last.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/6vyjg
Help other users to choose the best subtitles