Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Piedmont, New Mexico. Population 68.
Come on.
I didn't notice them before.
That's crazy. I didn't know buzzards fly at night.
That's what they look like.
Here.
Boy, that's some dead burg.
Buzzards only come when something's dead.
Well, I guess we better go in and have a look.
This is Caper One to Vandal Deca.
Caper One to Vandal Deca. Are you reading? Over.
Yes, I'm reading. Over.
We're about to enter the town of Piedmont and recover the satellite.
Very good, Caper One. Leave your radio open.
Roger.
We're now inside the town.
It's kinda spooky.
I see a church steeple ahead on the left.
It's quiet here.
It's the damndest thing. There's no sign of life.
The signals from the satellite are getting very strong.
Sir! You see that, Lieutenant?
See what, Crane? Over by the fence. It looks like a body.
Easy, Crane. You're imagining things.
Holy! Sir, it's another one.
You're right. It looks dead.
Yes, sir, shall I... No! Stay in the van.
Vandal Deca to Caper One. What's happening?
- We see bodies, lots of them. - Are you certain, Caper One?
Damn it, Comroe, of course we're certain.
Your orders are... proceed to satellite and retrieve.
Roger, Vandal Deca.
Stay at your stations! Hit that security button!
Get me Major Manchek.
Somehow they don't hardly look dead, Lieutenant.
They're all over the place. Must be dozens of them. Damn it, get this call through!
It's sort of like they just dropped in their tracks, sir.
Sir! Good Chri..!
Do you see that thing in white? Yeah, it's coming toward us.
Major, this may sound crazy, but there's something strange going on with Caper One.
Sir, I think we should get out of h...
Hello, Ops, this is Major Manchek, Scoop Control A-12.
We need a flyby over Piedmont, New Mexico.
Infrared. A FLIR scan, all sectors. Film to come direct to Scoop.
Assign Gunner Wilson, if he's not crocked someplace.
Jeez!
I'm declaring a state of emergency.
All personnel restricted to base.
Everything seen and heard in that room is top secret. Yes, sir.
This is a recording. State your name and your message and hang up.
Major Arthur Manchek, Scoop Mission Control A-12.
I recommend calling a Wildfire Alert.
We have evidence here on film of unnatural death caused by Scoop 7 returning to earth.
Time check 0-1-4-7 inclusive.
We'd like to see Dr. Jeremy Stone, please.
Well, I'm Mrs. Stone. We are having a party. May I...
Does that man have a gun?
Ma'am, we must see Dr. Stone.
What is this?
Please call Dr. Stone to the door. Otherwise we'll go get him.
Just a minute.
I'll just wait here, ma'am.
I'll come to Berkeley anytime, Stone.
That $4 million must be your largest federal grant.
May I see you, Jeremy?
The S.D.S. has arrived no doubt.
Jeremy, there are some Army types in the hall and two more outside with guns.
They want to see you. I'll take care of it.
Jeremy! If you knew about this, you might've told...
I didn't. I'll explain later.
I'm Dr. Stone.
Yes. I'm Captain Morton.
There's a fire, sir.
I've got to leave.
For God's sakes, Jeremy! When will you be back?
I'm not sure. The guns, is it...
Mrs. Stone, it's our job to protect your husband.
From now on, nothing must be allowed to happen to him.
I'll be safe as in your arms.
Jeremy? Jeremy!
You tell the senator it's his daughter!
Allison?
Dad, something very peculiar has just happened, even for Jeremy.
A few minutes ago...
Dad, are you there? What's going on?
This communication is being monitored.
The connection has been broken for reasons of national security.
You will be briefed at the appropriate time.
Thank you for your cooperation, Mrs. Stone.
I feel like Onassis.
It was the fastest thing we could arrange, sir.
Thanks.
Yes?
General Sparks here. I just wanted to inform you...
that all members of your team have been cleared and are now being called in.
Except for Professor Kirke. He's in the hospital. Appendectomy.
You'll get complete details on everything when your team is assembled.
You don't make sense. You talk like you've been brainwashed.
You don't understand.
Germ warfare people, Dad? A lab accident? Thank you.
It's different this time. Don't pack, Claire, I won't need anything.
A hippie. He's going to a love-in.
I give up.
One minute you're fed up. You talk about retiring... to Alaska yet!
Now you've turned into a cloak-and-dagger man.
My glasses. Here they are, Dad.
Can't you at least tell me who phoned at this ungodly hour?
Grandpa, there's a car, and they got guns.
Do they now? Well, that's serious.
I'll watch out. Honey, you've been dreaming.
I wish I were!
No. Uh-uh. Get someone else.
Dr. Leavitt, I told you, there's a fire!
My experiment's at the critical stage.
I've been working around the clock. I can't just leave now.
I want that new plate read as soon as it's developed.
Yes, ma'am.
My orders come from Dr. Robertson,
the president's science advisor in Washington.
There's a phone. Pick it up. Call Robbie.
Tell him I burnt my draft card.
Are you sick, ma'am? We have a physician on call.
All Dr. Leavitt needs is rest.
Knock it off, Bess.
If the physician certifies that you are unable to continue...
No!
I'm fine.
Relax.
I'm going with you.
Skin knife.
Hold it, Mark. Sorry to disturb you.
There's just been a call from a Dr. Robertson at the White House.
Your orders are to break scrub.
Orders? I've got a patient all ready.
Kelly will take over for you.
It's all arranged. You're expected in the surgeon's room in 30 seconds.
Are you sure the satellite isn't radioactive?
No. Manchek showed me the telemetry reports.
Presumably, it could be some form of space germ.
Presumably this stuff is nonporous.
Why did you pick me?
You're an M.D., a talented surgeon who knows blood chemistries...
and you're single... the "Odd Man Hypothesis."
What the hell is that?
Didn't you read the Wildfire material I've been sending you?
Very little. I never went in much for science fiction.
Nor do I!
It seems to me, General, Dr. Stone put one over on you.
In fact, he made us all think his Wildfire Lab could handle contamination from outer space.
I disagree with the senator from Vermont.
Dr. Stone, a Nobel Prize winner,
twice president of the National Academy of Sciences, is well known here in Washington.
Is the implication that Dr. Stone deliberately misled us?
Perhaps not deliberately, Senator.
I'm reasonably certain that before the night the Wildfire Team was mobilized,
Dr. Stone didn't know Scoop existed.
- I'm astounded. - Reasons of national security.
Very smart. We've had experiences with scientists before.
Now, let's talk about this famous letter...
Dr. Stone sent to the president some two years ago.
From what you're saying, it was just a shot in the dark?
Perhaps that's a little unfair, Senator.
Dr. Stone and I were consultants with NASA on the Lunar Receiving Lab.
He wasn't completely satisfied. He felt a more advanced lab was required.
You mean more expensive, don't you?
I call that Dr. Stone's $90 million mash note to Uncle Sam.
"In a true biological crisis which our exploration of space could bring about,
"the present Lunar Receiving Laboratory might prove inadequate.
"I therefore urge the establishment of a facility...
"to deal specifically with an extraterrestrial form of life.
"The purpose of this facility would be to limit...
"the dissemination of such an unknown organism from outer space...
"and to provide laboratories for its analysis.
"I recommend that this facility be located...
"in an uninhabited region of the United States,
"that it utilize all known isolation techniques,
"and that it be equipped with a nuclear device for self-destruction...
"in the event of an emergency.
Yours very truly, Jeremy Stone."
Don't encourage the president to think scientists are wizards.
If things get out of control, and they might, even you can't work miracles.
I'd expect to have your help, Charlie.
Piedmont approaching, gentlemen.
Go over and give us a look first, Dempsey.
I was afraid of that.
The birds'll eat the infected flesh, and then fly off and spread the disease.
If it is a disease.
Drop the gas canisters. Someone's supposed to be alive down there!
Somebody did something. That's for sure.
Let's give it a double dose.
That gas will only kill the birds.
Okay, Dempsey, hover over the main street and drop the ladder.
Do not attempt to land. Is that clear?
Roger. Clearer all the time.
When we climb down, lift off to 1,000 feet and hover at a safe distance.
And come back when we signal. If anything happens to us, you have your orders.
Yes, sir. Proceed directly to Wildfire and then...
If we're eliminated, the aircraft and pilot will have to be sterilized.
Wait a minute!
That's not what they told me. Just incinerated.
Coronary? I doubt it.
Hall!
Take a look at this. Are you sure that isn't coronary?
No, coronary's painful. They should grimace.
If it was fast, they wouldn't have time.
Fast? These people were cut down in mid-stride.
Up there! Look.
An Air Force jet.
If we don't make it to Wildfire, he'll see the helicopter does... or shoot it down.
Well, for Dempsey's sake, we better not slip up.
"The Day of Judgment is at hand.
Have mercy on my soul and to hell with all the others. Amen."
Senile. This took time! Regardless of what made her do it, it took time.
There's a chance someone's still alive.
I wouldn't believe you could commit suicide that way.
Most of them died instantly, but a few had time to go quietly nuts.
Let's find the damn satellite.
This injury, there isn't any bleeding.
A cut like this... torn veins, broken capillaries... should bleed like hell.
Yes. Well, there's no blood on any of them.
Even where it's chewed, no bleeding.
Hold it, hold it!
You'd better back up. We gotta go to the... left.
We're damn close. Bear right.
I'll bet they took it to the doctor.
There it is.
The damn fool opened it!
Yeah, every country doctor should run his office like the lunar lab.
The capsule first, Hall.
We've got about 40 minutes of oxygen left.
Have a look at his buttocks.
That's not funny. Not meant to be.
Normally blood in a dead person goes to the lowest points.
There should be marks of lividity. Do you see purplish marks on his butt?
No.
Careful you don't puncture your suit.
Clotted blood!
Powdered!
I'll be damned!
No wonder they didn't bleed. It's clotted throughout the entire system.
Five quarts of blood turned to powder!
In theory, I suppose, a single organism could do it.
But, in fact, there isn't an organism on Earth...
You mean there didn't used to be.
I don't... We heard it all right.
Go away! Go back!
Get back! Get outta here. Go back!
Get away!
This must be the mother.
He's scared, and hungry as hell.
Can't be more than six months. There's probably a formula in the kitchen.
Don't feed it! He hasn't eaten in at least 12 hours!
We don't do anything until we get that kid into a controlled situation.
Maybe feeding is part of the disease process. Maybe those who hadn't eaten lasted longest.
Whatever it is, with our oxygen running out, we can't take a chance.
Wait a minute. This is a major break... a survivor.
Too bad he can't tell us what happened.
Maybe he can... if he lives.
You!
You... you did it!
Give me that knife.
You're not human. Everybody's dead.
What happened?
What is it?
The town is finished, contaminated beyond all...
Careful, sir. This is an open transmission.
I'm aware of that, Manchek. Order up a 7-12. Only the president...
Precisely. Get on it. The town must be neutralized immediately.
Has the president made his decision on Directive 7-12 yet?
He doesn't jump into things, Dr. Robertson.
First I've got to put together a briefing for him.
The president's main concern is the international consequences.
What do you think, Mr. Secretary?
It's against the Moscow Treaty of 1963...
to fire thermonuclear weapons above ground.
The Russians will have to be privately informed we're going to cauterize the area.
Then they'll ask a flock of questions. Some we don't want answered.
That'll take hours.
God knows how far the infection can spread in that time.
Yes, Chief?
Yes, sir.
Yes, Mr. President.
The president's decided to postpone Directive 7-12 for 24 to 48 hours.
Instead he'll call out the National Guard to cordon off the area around Piedmont.
That's your department, Ed. Safe and sound.
It should've been left up to the scientists.
It's a colossal mistake.
Tell the president I said so.
No, but... I'll get you an appointment.
By whose decision, General, was the site for Wildfire chosen?
Dr. Stone's. It seemed ideal because of its remoteness.
There was no inhabited area near Wildfire for a radius of 112 miles.
Las Vegas is to the north, Phoenix to the south, Los Angeles west.
Weren't you worried the infection might spread to them?
Yes, sir, I was, but Dr. Stone and Dr. Robertson assured the president...
Wildfire was foolproof because of its device for atomic self-destruct.
The military had to take a backseat.
At least they could've sent a licensed driver to meet me at that crummy airstrip.
They keep personnel to a minimum for obvious reasons.
You're lost! No one's been down this goat path for years.
That's how it's supposed to look. They spent $50,000 on it.
Putting in the potholes? Getting rid of the tread marks.
Those big tractors leave a lasting impression.
A lot of heavy equipment has passed this way.
Where's our leader? We'll catch up to him and Hall very soon now.
Why'd they pick Hall? He's no scientist. Who needs an overpriced M.D.?
Relax and enjoy your cigarette. It's your last.
It starts here.
It's a great place to grow pot.
Just a plain old crop of barley. Still, it is rather clever, I think.
Something wrong? I never liked red lights.
Reminds me of my years in a bordello.
Howdy.
Howdy-do-dee.
You got the time? My watch stopped at 11:46.
Darn shame. Must be the heat.
It's no fake, believe me.
When I retire, I'd like an agricultural station like this in Alaska.
You, a sourdough? Hmph! The sourest. This way.
Step in.
Cute.
The whole thing, what a world we're making.
I can see why the kids are dropping out. We should've.
It's an emergency, Dutton. We got tagged. Period.
Until I saw those photos from Vandenberg, I...
They brought it on themselves. Who? The people in Piedmont?
What you said before,
you don't believe the infection in that capsule was brought back deliberately, do you?
Skip it. I hope I'm talking through my hat.
Put your hands on that glass, palms down. It's a finger and palm print analyzer. It...
Reads a composite of 10,000 dermatographic lines.
How'd you know that? Oh, Dutton, I have a long criminal record.
Then you're in trouble. This machine has a long memory.
It gives you final clearance to enter Wildfire.
Isothermal reading for M.C. levels 4 and 5...
is Z.B. and R.A. over 2.9.
How's Piedmont? I had to order up a 7-12. How are you, Ruth?
No other way to halt the infection spread. Oh.
Oh, you two know each other, don't you?
By reputation only. Ah, yes, up to now we've had to worship from afar.
Be good, Ruth.
Any messages for me from the White House?
Not a thing, Dr. Stone, or you'd have it.
No personal messages? No, ma'am.
Nothing from Dr. Robertson? Are you sure, Sergeant?
Dr. Stone, sir, I have one thing to do. Just one.
Everything else is fully automatic, computerized and self-regulating.
I... I listen for a little bell in here.
Ding-a-ling. That means a message coming in is for the Wildfire Team.
Precisely! An M.C.N. communication. I'm expecting one.
Yes, sir! Top priority.
Ding-a-ling. I push a button...
and all five level control centers are notified the same time you are.
The bell hasn't rung, sir.
Thanks for the tour, Sergeant.
Dr. Dutton. Thank you.
Will you follow me, Dr. Leavitt? And may I have your glasses, please?
What for? They'll be treated and returned to you, Doctor.
They better be, or I'll need a white cane.
Who picked Leavitt?
Talk about the Odd Man Hypothesis, which we haven't yet. She's really an oddball.
We're lucky to have her.
She's the best equipped of us to double up for Kirke in microbiology.
When dressed, the team will proceed directly to conference room 7.
Keep this with you at all times.
What's it for?
You're the Odd Man. The key man, quite literally.
This other key, and Wildfire itself, depend on your key.
Wildfire's equipped with a nuclear device for self-destruct.
In an emergency, it's activated automatically.
I've just inserted the key in the main station that arms the mechanism.
The device is ready for detonation.
When? Never, we hope.
It only goes off if there's danger of infection breaking out from here.
That silver key can't be removed.
You're the only one who can disarm the mechanism by inserting your red key...
in one of the substations located throughout the facility.
There's a five-minute delay between the time detonation locks in and the bomb explodes.
That gives you a chance to think...
and, please God, call it off.
Look, I'm the new boy here. Why me? Because you're single.
You should have done your homework, sport.
Page 255, Robbie's Odd Man Hypothesis.
"Results of testing confirm the Robertson Odd Man Hypothesis:
"that an unmarried male should carry out command decisions...
involving thermonuclear destruct contexts."
Let me take a look at that.
It's of vital importance...
that you always know where you are in relation to the nearest substation.
To do that, you have to be familiar with the entire facility.
It can be studied on this electronic diagram...
which rotates to afford an overall view, or can be stopped at any section.
Detailed plans of the various levels and labs are also stored in the system.
We're on level 1 of a five-story cylindrical underground structure...
surrounded by solid rock.
Each level has three substations, indicated by the yellow lights.
In the event the nuclear device is triggered, you can still cancel self-destruct...
by inserting your red key in a substation.
After our last simulation run,
we decided to add two more substations per level, but they're not finished.
So don't confuse them with functioning ones.
At the bottom of the central core is the apparatus for self-destruct.
Each level is a different color...
based on a navy study of the psychological effects of color in environments.
Also, each level is biomedically cleaner than the one above it.
We don't want anything to contaminate a possible organism.
That would make it twice as hard to isolate and characterize.
It'll take us 16 hours to descend...
through the programmed decontamination procedures on the first four levels...
to level 5 where the main labs are.
Where, exactly, are we now?
There's one way you can always locate yourself or any of us instantly.
Simply by calling up projections from the electronic diagram...
on any video monitor anywhere in Wildfire.
Views such as this.
This shows we're in conference room 7, level 1.
Each of us is indicated by our initial.
Our movements are continuously monitored on the electronic diagram.
- Where are the patients? - Where's the capsule?
The patients are the yellow X's.
The red circle is the capsule.
On level 5, the patients and capsule will be isolated in biologically secure setups.
Are you sure the old man and the baby are still alive?
What are their chances, Hall? Uncertain.
I'm hoping the intravenous dextrose and saline will hold them until we get to them.
We start decontamination and immunization procedures now.
You really expect me to fire the thing?
I'm afraid you don't understand.
All you can do is stop it.
In a biological emergency, the bomb is activated automatically.
It'll then go off within five minutes unless you get to a substation...
and lock in your key.
Oh.
Delta Five to all levels.
We are checking out ray-ban emergency communications. This is a test.
Proceed to infrared radiation decontamination room 1-D.
Also it could be an organism from another planet released deliberately.
To wipe us out? Really, Charles!
Just the opposite. To make friendly contact.
A kind of messenger to show us life exists elsewhere in the universe.
It could be benign in its own environment. Pretty far-fetched.
We can't ignore any possibility.
You are about to undergo long-wave radiation.
A buzzer will sound. Close your eyes and stand still or blindness may result.
We face quite a problem:
how to disinfect the human body, one of the dirtiest things in the known universe.
That is without killing the human being at the same time. It gets tougher as we go.
Hard on the taxpayers, the way we burn up uniforms.
They're paper.
I'd swear it was cloth. New process.
Where's the next substation, Hall? Left of elevator on level 2.
Right. Across the corridor from body analysis, our next port of call.
Not for my alabaster body.
I mean it, Stone. You can take your body analyzer and you can...
Sit down, please.
Please look at the screen in front of you.
Please place your body so that all points are obliterated.
That is fine. We may proceed.
State your name for the records. Surname first. Mark Hall.
Hall, Mark. Thank you for your cooperation.
Yes, dear.
Please answer the following questions yes or no.
Have you any allergies? Yes, to ragweed pollen.
Okay, I'll repeat for your memory cells...
Please repeat your response for our memory cells.
Ragweed pollen!
This ends the formal questioning. Please undress.
This is a scan for fungal lesions.
Dr. Stone, this is level 2 control. The answer is affirmative.
Major Manchek contacted the White House at 11:23 this morning.
Contact on all leads is "R" for ready.
Do not be nervous. I'm not nervous.
Physical parameters are being measured.
There's no need to be nervous, Dr. Leavitt.
Please raise your left arm.
Please sit up, facing the scan screen and watch carefully.
You have received pneumatic injections of booster immunizations.
You may get dressed. Thank you.
This recording is now ended.
That body analyzer! I want to be there when the A.M.A. gets wind of it.
So far it's only been used by NASA to diagnose astronauts in space.
You doctors better start making house calls again.
This is a xenon lamp apparatus.
To insure complete effectiveness, spread your feet apart.
To protect scalp and facial hair,
place the metal helmet securely on the head.
Make sure the helmet is firmly seated and the visor lowered.
Then raise your arms and wait.
You may now remove helmet.
You will notice a fine white ash on your body.
This is the outer epithelial layers of your skin that have been burned away.
Please replace the helmet in compartment and proceed through shower in next room.
Then you may dress and descend to level 4.
We're required to rest for six hours on level 4 after exposure to the xenon lamp.
So go to your rooms and sleep.
At the end of the corridor is the cafeteria.
We'll meet there at 0400 hours... tomorrow.
Pharmacology to maintenance L.B.
One of our R.F.s shows six points over nominal at pressure 3.
Watchdog to all levels. Scoop 7 capsule secure.
Biocheck 66 plus 9 minus OL-5.
LEO control to KEEPSAKE 5.
The pressure integrity check runs 2.54 G-CM to the second.
Please confirm.
A new form of life.
Like Rudolph Karp's bacteria.
Fools!
They refuse to believe life exists in meteorites.
I showed them at the Astrophysics Conference what I just showed you.
But no, even with a microscope, they are blind.
What do I have to do? Hit them over the head?
I'm glad you're amused, gentlemen, but it might just turn out to be true.
During this symposium, we'll discuss the possibility...
that intelligent life on a distant planet...
may be no larger than a flea.
Perhaps no larger than a bacterium.
Time to wake up, sir.
Time to wake up, sir!
Hello?
Time to wake up, sir.
Who are you? Time to wake up, sir.
Do you wish something, sir?
Your name.
Will that be all, sir?
For the moment.
This is the answering service supervisor.
We wish you would adopt a more serious attitude, Dr. Hall.
Sorry. Her voice is quite luscious.
The voice belongs to Miss Gladys Stevens who is 63 years old.
She lives in Omaha and makes her living taping messages for voice-reminder systems.
Much obliged.
Let's not get sidetracked on Rudolph Karp and his meteorite theories.
His technique was worthless!
I still think we should contact him. Fair enough. Where is he?
Behind the Iron Curtain. He couldn't get a research grant here.
H.P. nutrient now available in the cafeteria...
for staff members from sectors 1 through 6.
Hemlock! All for you, Hippocrates.
Not your own venom?
Tastes like orange juice.
Nutrient 42-5.
Developed for the astronauts.
Eight ounces satisfy all daily nutritional requirements.
Except coffee.
And lipid soluble vitamins.
For that we have these. Help yourself.
So what's the point of the cafeteria?
Wildfire isn't always on crash status. Maybe there's some sugar.
Nope. Nothing that might provide a bacterial growth medium.
Precisely. No sugar in the gut.
I'd like a cigarette right now.
It's after meals you miss 'em. You should have no trouble on level 5.
You won't even get this close to a meal.
We'll be entirely on high-protein nutrients.
I planned our work in three stages.
One: detection.
First step is to confirm that an organism is present.
Two: characterization. How's it structured, how does it work?
Three: control.
How to contain and exterminate?
Jeremy, on this matter of extermination, we should go slowly.
Without ever realizing it, we might destroy a highly intelligent form of life.
Why don't we get going? I've got two patients down there.
- The team has two subjects. - They're not guinea pigs, Stone.
You may now proceed to level 5, gentlemen.
Um, stop by your rooms and insert these before taking the elevator.
I have risked drowning in that foul bath.
I have been parboiled, irradiated and xenon flashed. And now you suggest I...
I have to! We haven't done anything about the G.I. tract yet.
On level 5 we must be as nearly germ free as possible.
Anyone care to join me for a smoke?
Watchdog to level 2, sector D.
You are Red Kappa Phoenix status.
Off the main corridor on the outer rim...
are the living quarters, conference room, cafeteria, bio-safety maintenance, etc.
Inside are the labs.
Where is the library?
No need for books. Everything's in the computer.
Notice the capsule has already been delivered...
by the sterile conveyor system to the main control lab here.
Your patients are here in the hot room of miscellaneous.
We can't have any direct contact with them. Poor souls.
Dr. Dutton and Dr. Hall are wanted in main control immediately.
Hey!
If the patients are sealed off, how do I get to them?
Ever used a glove box? No.
Wildfire's gone a step further.
Whole rooms that operate like glove boxes.
You'll be working in one shortly.
We have a magnetic "K" indices. Give us a code 3 when you get it.
I wanted you here while we find out...
if there's anything still biologically active in the capsule.
Suggestions? Use a buffalo.
Audio.
Detectors "E" through "G" correction.
Negative "N" scan. Negative "N" scope in LY-1.
Affirmative. "N" indicator in MP-4. I will repeat.
Affirmative. "N indicator in MP-4.
Whatever killed them at Piedmont is still there and still as potent as ever.
If potent's the word. Let's try a rhesus.
Yeah. We'll want a postmortem on it anyway.
Housekeeping to level 5.
Clean sweep schedule "B" now in effect.
Germfree animal technicians, please consult schedule "A."
So, okay. Isolate and identify.
Right. You and I'll scan the capsule, Ruth.
Charlie, you work on these in autopsy. Open the S.L., Ruth.
Adjust S.Y. system for aseptricity as follows.
Points 2-A at 5. Points 9 through 12 at plus 1.
Plus 3, plus 6 at minus.
Run an initial vector study, Charlie.
Find out how the disease enters the body.
Charlie? Yes.
Yes, the vector study first, then autopsy. Incredible.
Dutton, be careful.
Let our distinguished surgeon handle the knife.
Fine, but not for a while.
First, I'm a pediatrician and a geriatrist.
Take it easy. Charlie will have a technician.
What's been done for them?
Just plasma for the old man, dextrose for the baby.
- Your therapy? - No. Medcom's.
Do I call you Miss Medcom?
If you like, Dr. Hall. My name's Karen Anson.
Good. I couldn't cope with two machines. How does this work?
You're lucky. Medcom's got one of the best minds here.
It's a medical data analyzer that can diagnose as well as prescribe.
It's hooked up to the main computer on level 1.
Every console and instrument in Wildfire...
is plugged into the main computer on a time-sharing basis.
All our key lab studies are done on automated machines.
I prefer the personal touch.
It's hard to come by in those suits.
Professional Translation Services
www.gts-translation.com