Copyright from ecOtOne™
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Only a hardheaded gringo...
Would come down here...
On a rescue mission...
ALL ALONE
This gringo is not going to talk.
Then kill him.
C'mon, the General's expecting us.
(CAPTOR EXCLAIMING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
yöu can't use yöur gun...
...Shoot
him with his.
(EXCLAIMS EXCITEDLY)
(LAUGHING)
(CLICKS)
lt's not working.
(SNIGGERING)
This asshole's gun has
no firing pin.
Leave him.
The dogs haven't had to
kill for their food in a while.
Next time, amigo,
plan ahead.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, l'm such a bad Catholic.
No, yöu're just sick in the head.
Don't forget the General's money.
That gringo bribed the wrong cop...
...and brought a gun
with no firing pin.
(CAPTOR CALLING DOGS IN SPANISH)
(SNARLING)
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
(HANDCUFFS SHACKLING)
(DOGS WHIMPERING)
(BEEPING)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(HOUSE OF PAIN PLAYING)
♫ Catch me if yöu can
I'm in 'em oId schooI BarkIey's ♪
♫ Back to the fence
puffin' on that Bob Marley ♪
♫ FIow Iike oregano ♪
♫ yöu aIready know my competition's
stiffer than RonaId Regan ♪
♫ Let it go ♪
♫ For yöu be a mother... ♪
♫ yöu scrap it's too animated
like The INcredibles ♪
♫ Let this beef go around like the tenty six's ♪
♫ lt's yöung Game of flame ♪
♫ Welcome to the House of Pain ♪
B.A.: Where's my girl, fool?
She cool, man. She in there.
She's still fine as hell.
So that's it?
Bada bing, yöu out of the game?
Done with the whole trade?
- Yeah.
-  Well, that's the problem, Bosco.
yöu either keep doing that,
or yöu do a 15 year bid
in a Mexican prison
with Cheeto's cousin in there.
Same old shit. yöu choose
how to flush the toilet, brother.
That's right. Easy way or the hard way.
(CRACKING KNUCKLES)
(EXCLAIMING)
(GRUNTING)
Come on!
JAY: Okay, street soldier. Shit.
But watch yöurself, B.A., now,
yöu gonna lose yöur oldest friend here.
What's up, girl? yöu miss me?
Because l missed yöu. Yes, l did.
lt's been too long, baby.
Way too long.
(WOMAN STRUGGLING)
FACE: Heck of a place.
Just a heck of a beautiful place.
ls this a time share?
l'd love to get in on this.
l like this whole Santa Fe motif
yöu got going here, Tuco.
lt's very Arizona, very Tex Mex.
lt's good. lt's good.
Maybe we can get the guy at my six
to whip up a couple of quesadiches,
yöu know?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
l want the flames to be seen
by the Martians.
(APOLOGIZING IN SPANISH)
TUCO: Americano, gringo.
- Army INtelligence.
- Who's that?
- yöu, man.
- (LAUGHS) No.
yöu're not so intelligent
because yöu're stuck in some tires.
l'm happy. l'm happy.
Doesn't get any better than this, right?
- l'm living the dream.
- yöu are!
yöu're gonna come here...
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
...to throw me in a bag across the border...
...but instead yöu have sex with my wife.
Well, first of all, she's so hot,
and we both hate yöu.
So that's just sort of how it...
- Good morning!
- TUCO: Good morning, man!
Now it's a party! (LAUGHS)
- ls that yöur best shot?
- Now it's a party, man!
(SHUT UP PLAYING)
♫ A..ha, okay, what's up?
Shut up ♪
Whoa!
♫ Okay, what's up? Shut up ♪
♫ l got a pocket full of B's
Cocoa weed and ain't got no place to go... ♪
(GUN COCKING)
Oh, hell, no.
Slide over slowly.
yöu jacking me?
What is this, opposite day?
l'm not a thief. But if l don't reach
my friend in time, then he dies.
lf yöu ain't a thief,
l guarantee yöu ain't a killer.
(GUN COCKS)
Take yöur left hand off the wheel
and yöur right hand off the shifter now.
yöu ain't gonna
shoot me in the head, pops.
yöu know that ain't happening.
(GROANING)
What the hell's wrong with yöu, man?
yöu shoot a total stranger?
l don't even know yöu, fool. Damn.
lt'll heal, l promise.
- Here, wrap it in this.
- l know how to make a tourniquet, fool.
l know it hurts,
but l had to make a point with yöu.
That ain't what's pissing me off.
yöu shooting my van
is what's pissing me off, man.
What's wrong with yöu?
(B.A. GRUNTING)
yöu Army Ranger, son?
Be real careful
of what yöu say next, pops.
And be ready to empty that burner
if yöu start shit talking my battalion.
Never shall l fail my comrades.
Gallantly will l show the world
that l am a specially selected soldier.
Energetically will l meet
the enemies of my country.
l shall defeat them on the field of battle
for l am better trained.
And l will fight with all my might.
Colonel Hannibal Smith.
75th Ranger Regiment.
4th Battalion. Fort Benning, Georgia.
l know who yöu are, sir.
Corporal B.A. Baracus.
l mean, it was till l was dishonorably
discharged for some bullshit.
l don't subscribe to coincidence, Corporal.
l believe that, no matter how random
things might appear,
there's still a plan.
(ALL SPEAKING SPANISH)
We fed him to the dogs.
HANNIBAL: That here in the middle
of the Mexican desert,
when l needed him most,
l'd find a fellow Ranger.
(SIGHS) Boy.
Now, l need yöur help to save another.
(BEEPING)
TUCO ON RADIO: Bad news foryöu today!
This rescue that's coming,
we fed him to the Rottweilers
- about an hour ago.
- yöu know what's funny?
ls that yöu actually believe
that yöu got me.
(ON RADIO) yöu actually think
yöu're gonna kill me.
Can yöu drive?
Better than anybody yöu've ever seen, sir.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Nobody knew where yöu were hiding...
There was no intel...until now, asshole.
TUCO: IN a few minutes
l'm gonna be having a cold beer,
and yöu are gonna be on fire.
Take care, my friend.
- Alpha, Mike...
- WOMAN: No!
...Foxtrot.
Think about it.
Adiós, mother...
(ALL SHOUTING)
Hannibal!
What are yöu doing?
Get in!
B.A., move.
FACE: This is bullshit!
Ahora, muerto!
FACE: Stop it! Please stop!
Please stop! Stop it! Stop! Please stop!
How's yöur day going?
This is not going to taste good.
(VOMITING)
Baby, l just threw up.
Let me get some gum.
Let me just get some gum.
Did yöu see that?
Did yöu see Tuco's face?
When yöu came over,
that was unbelievable!
-How many times did l say it?
-The timing was perfect.
- How many times did l say it, Face?
- lt was so beautiful.
- l told yöu not to take down Tuco alone.
- What?
Well, yöu...
yöu know what? l'm sorry.
l'm sorry l didn't have
the Hannibal Smith How to Manual.
- Okay? l had to move.
- And that move snowballs, Face.
yöu almost got yöurself killed.
Which almost got me killed
and almost got him killed.
Five year old.
yöu look like yöu got a real bad attitude.
What?
Did l shoot up yöur van?
Am l wearing yöur favorite shirt?
This is yöur favorite shirt?
Yeah, pretty boy, that's my favorite shirt.
Did yöu get shot for me, too?
- And carjacked.
-  By me.
(CHUCKLES) Wait,
and he still got yöu to drive?
Thank yöu. Peck.
Baracus. lt's all good.
See, Face, this is what happens
when we forget about plans
and just fire blind.
FACE: l'm sorry.
l'm so sorry that
l have feelings for a human being,
- that l fell in love.
- Love?
Wait a minute. What about Miss Croatia
three weeks ago?
(LAUGHS)
(SHUSHING)
Rescue sex.
l was just trying to save her.
- Save her?
- Yeah.
Save her? How?
Please, do share with us
yöur plan, Face.
Okay, l hadn't thought about that yet.
Exactly. l had to.
Her plane ticket.
Her work visa and her new passport.
And don't bullshit me
that this was about her, Face.
This was all about Tuco.
Do yöu have a mag?
(ALL CLAMORING)
(ORDERINGIN SPANISH)
- Mike.
- Boss man. How the hell are yöu?
- Still chewing the same dirt?
- l am, unfortunately.
- And out here in lovely Mexico.
- Good.
- So what have yöu got for me?
- l got a fast bird doing pizza runs.
- The call sign is "Hatchet."
- Hatchet. Okay.
And that is whatever yöu want it to be.
This is yöurs.
General, may l remind yöu,
they don't take to the gringos.
l owe yöu one, okay?
- Let's not wait till Bragg again, huh?
- Three years.
- MIKE: And the kid. Still yöu and the chicks.
- B.A. What?
B.A.: How am l gonna just leave my girl
like this, after all that?
l had to fight to get her back.
Leave the keys
and we'll come back for her. Come on.
Looking shabby.
- What is the deal, brother?
- Shoot anything that moves, okay?
- This is worse than Colombia.
- l know Tuco, man.
Don't worry about it.
l'll take her to war college in Saint Tropez.
l'll get yöu all their numbers,
so don't worry about it.
- Face, look after the Corporal.
- Yeah. Okay.
And yöu're covered in gas,
which l think is interesting.
Find a treatment room, Corporal.
Make it quick. l'm gonna find our pilot.
Hey.
(CHUCKLING)
Hey, Doc, yöu got a second
for a wounded vet?
DOCTOR: Highly decorated combat pilot.
yöu ask him,
he thinks he's the best in the world.
But he's a functioning lunatic.
Last week he tried to escape
by jump starting an ambulance.
Clear.
Damn it!
My kind of guy.
lt almost hit yöur tattoo there.
NURSE: Has anyone seen Mr. Murdock?
- The old Ranger tat.
- NURSE: Mr. Murdock?
Would yöu think l was crazy
if l told yöu l had one of these?
Something wrong with yöur eyes, man.
- Mr. Murdock?
- Not while l'm operating, nurse.
- Not now.
- Why are yöu off the ward?
ls that gas? ls that yöu?
- l smell gas.
- What do yöu mean, "ward"?
- What ward?
- This man is a patient here.
ls this yöu?
Don't listen to her, she's crazy.
Honestly, l'm a practicing doctor
at Johns Hopkins University.
- Did yöu ask him to do a lightning bolt?
- l asked for no lightning bolt.
- l'm calling security.
- B.A.: What's wrong with this fool?
- ls he crazy?
- lt is yöu.
- yöu on fire, man.
- What? What's that?
- What the...
- Oh, Jesus!
- yöu Rangers. l like yöu!
- Are yöu crazy?
- (ALL CLAMORING)
- Hey! Hey, come on!
Corporal, off. Back off!
This is a hospital.
(COUGHING)
- Everybody's met Mr. Murdock.
- FACE: Met him?
He lit my arm on fire.
He stitched a lightning bolt in mine, man.
HANNIBAL: Look at me, son.
l'm told yöu're a hell of a chopper pilot.
The best, sir.
l'm not getting on a chopper
with this nut job.
Yeah, that's a good...
ls he another one of yöur projects?
l'm a real soldier. l'm a Ranger, baby.
l'm worried!
l'm a Ranger, sir.
That's good enough for me.
yöu have been released into our care
- and reinstated, Captain.
- l'm not even close to good with that.
Thank yöu, sir.
Let's get the hell out of here.
(ALL SHOUTINGIN SPANISH)
MURDOCK: (IN BRITISH ACCENT)
yöu gorgeous old rust bucket, yöu.
Did yöu miss yöur daddy?
Face, what's the most important part
of a well oiled plan?
To be one step ahead of the enemy,
-  not to be running away from him.
-  Who says we're running?
What, we're going to go in this dinosaur
-  with this freak show?
-  Yep.
(SINGING) yöu spin me right round, baby
Right round
-  Rotors are good, sir.
-  Who is this guy?
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
TUCO: Come on! Let's go!
We've got gringos to kill!
FACE: Murdock, get this thing in the air.
MURDOCK: Hold on, boys!
l'm gonna try something
l saw in a cartoon once.
What yöu talking about cartoons for?
Get us the hell out of here!
We got a hot chopper to yöur six.
MURDOCK: l'm blocking bullets.
We're bulletproof.
We're bulletproof, boys!
Oh, heads up.
(EXCLAIMING)
(EXCLAIMING IN ANGUISH)
TUCO ON RADIO: l see yöu, gringo!
yöu pancaked my van!
l'm gonna kill yöu, fool!
yöu can't park there.
That's a handicap zone.
-  l knew yöu was crazy! l knew...
-  This is a mistake.
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Blow them out of the sky.
(ALL YELLING)
l've never tried this before!
Did yöu see that?
Did yöu see
how he turned the helicopter?
Whoa! There's nothing like some good
air to air combat, eh, boys?
Don't look at me! Look there!
MURDOCK: He's only got heat seekers left.
Captain, get us out of here.
MURDOCK: Hold on, this could get ugly!
Here we go! Come on, baby, climb!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(WHOOPING)
Fire the missiles.
Whoa! Missiles! Come on, come on.
(IN BRITISH ACCENT) That's how we deal
with heat seekers, chaps.
We go cold.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
What the hell?
-  (INSTRUMENTS BEEPING)
-  Face, get him in here!
FACE: Holy, shit! Oh, shit!
Got him!
MURDOCK: Restart. Restart.
(MURDOCK WHOOPING)
Close the door!
l know yöu're Airborne Rangers,
but that was ridiculous!
yöu're gonna be okay.
FACE: Boss, the idea is to kill Tuco,
not the other way around!
One step ahead of the game
isn't a plan, kid.
Two to three steps ahead.
Beating an enemy's move
before it's even made.
That's a plan.
(BEEPING)
Hatchet, Hatchet, lock on my LC.
HANNIBAL ON RADIO:
General Tuco, yöu are currently engaged
in unauthorized warfare
on United States military personnel.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
yöu engaged me.
HANNIBAL ON RADIO: Repeat.
yöu are engaged in unauthorized warfare
on United States military personnel.
Over United States air space.
-  What?
-  Alpha, Mike...
-  Foxtrot!
-  ...Foxtrot!
-  IN other words, Adiós, mother...
-  Oh, no.
(ALL CHEERING)
Yeah!
Well done, Captain.
-  That was awesome.
-  That wasn't awesome.
-  yöu are a genius!
-  l'm never flying again in this thing!
l never should have doubted yöu, boss!
There's a plan in everything, kid.
And l love it when a plan comes together.
(MAN CHATTERING ON LOUDSPEAKER)
MURDOCK: Gunpowder cooking.
Nothing like it.
Face, yöu want it napalmed or nuked?
Nuke it.
-  Nuke it!
-  Mmm..hmm.
Murdock, burn the hell out of it,
like it was damned.
FACE: Burn the whole place down, buddy.
-  MURDOCK: yöu want secret sauce?
-  No, no, no. None of that anti freeze.
The secret's out. yöu crazy.
Everybody knows.
FACE: No one can do an anti freeze
marinade like yöu can, Murdock.
But l got a little Bell's palsy
last time l ate that.
lt's only partial paralysis.
Come on, take it like a man.
SOSA: Yes, sir.
l'm having that conversation right now.
We will enforce that.
l've got it well in hand, sir.
FACE: l don't think yöu want me to be
in the field partially paralyzed, bud.
Visitors.
Yeah.
(LAUGHING)
Wow, l'm a little taken aback.
l'm not gonna lie.
Lieutenant.
Oh, l'm sorry, am l supposed
to call yöu Lieutenant back?
No, yöu're supposed to call me Captain.
Captain. Captain?
That's right.
Captain Crunch. Look at yöu. Wow.
So, l guess yöu said no to the kids,
no to the family.
Just no ladder yöu can't climb, huh?
SOSA: No, no, honey, l just said no to yöu.
(IN AUSTRALIAN ACCENT)
Hello. My name's Percy.
Would yöu like some pork?
lf l broke every bone in yöur hand,
could yöu still do that?
This is crazy. Three years?
We haven't seen each other
for three years,
this is what we're gonna talk about?
What would yöu like to discuss?
Did yöu take my Steely Dan CD?
l'm not even going to respond to that.
We listened to it,
like, nine times in a row.
We were drinking that crappy cabernet.
yöu remember that?
We were doing something else.
What were we doing?
Do yöu remember what it was
we were doing? lt was in a bedroom.
yöu don't remember?
The only thing l remember is leaving.
Which is my fondest memory of yöu.
HANNIBAL: yöu guys are the best.
Stay out of trouble, yöu hear me?
Take care. Yes. Thank yöu.
Keep that on.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Colonel, my name is Lynch,
l'm with Central INtelligence.
l knew a company man named Lynch
back in the first Desert Storm.
Yeah, l come from a long line of Lynches.
yöu ever stop to consider that maybe
the reason nobody trusts the CIA
is because nobody knows yöur real names?
(LYNCH LAUGHING)
What can l do for yöu, Mr. Lynch?
l need yöu to help me to stop
Saddam's former flunkies
from stealing over a billion dollars
in the next 30 hours.
Now, the only mint outside of the U.S.
capable of printing our money
belonged to the Shah of lran.
During the lran lraq War, it went missing.
Rumor was, Saddam had stolen it.
And we stole it back during Desert Storm.
Well, yöu didn't get the engraving plates.
HANNIBAL: lt didn't matter.
They would have had to rebuild a mint
just to print those bills.
LYNCH: Well, sir,
it's happening as we speak.
Fedayeen thugs have seized
what's left of the lraqi National Mint
to run off billions of dollars
in unbacked American currency.
How are they planning on
moving the plates and a billion dollars
-  out of Baghdad?
-  Armored convoy,
manned with former lraqi spec ops.
yöu know, high speed, shoot to kill types.
So how do yöu plan on stopping them?
Listen, there's some rumors
about some top secret plates
being smuggled out of the city
by Saddam loyalists.
Do yöu know anything about this?
Seriously, if yöu're going to make
a play for these plates,
l'm waving yöu off right now.
'Cause it's my responsibility
and it's my ass.
l'm serious.
-  Face?
-  Mmm..hmm.
l will court martial yöu.
-  Whoo! Okay.
-  Hey.
Get the memo.
Tell yöur beloved Colonel Smith
and stay the hell out of Baghdad.
yöu know,
yöu never came back.
l thought yöu were gonna come back.
Well, this is me, coming back.
(MURDOCK SINGINGIN SPANISH)
(SINGINGIN SPANISH)
RAVECH: yöu think those clowns
can really pull this off?
Listen, listen, l would never tell him this,
but they are the best clandestine unit
in the four branches,
and they specialize in the ridiculous.
Shadow Peck and the rest of them.
-  Do not let them out of yöur sight.
-  Yes, ma'am.
-  Doesn't diablo mean "devil"?
-  Yeah, man.
MORRISON: God damn it, Hannibal,
what do yöu want me to do?
lf this were my operation
and yöu wanted it,
-  yöu would have the mission.
-  yöu let Black Forest deploy on this,
and it's an international incident,
l promise yöu.
They're not soldiers.
They're frat boys with trigger fingers.
-   Who's running the ground team?
-   Brock Pike.
(HANNIBAL LAUGHING)
Pike.
He's a thug. He's a cartoon character.
Come on.
Hannibal, we have been ordered,
ordered, mind yöu,
to stay out of Baghdad.
- Cut, dried, the end.
- LYNCH: General,
we should find him
a little wiggle room, don't yöu think?
yöu know, l knew another Lynch,
a CIA stooge.
Stationed in Laos, '68.
-  No relation.
-  Are yöu sure?
'Cause yöu remind me of him.
l'm due in Kabul in a few hours.
l'll be back here in 48.
l'm assuming we're green and go.
Notify me otherwise.
He's wearing body armor in the HQ.
And that should tell yöu everything
yöu need to know about the CIA.
Russ, let's do some good
on the way out the door here.
Those plates are gonna do
all kinds of damage.
Let me go get them.
Forget about it, Hannibal.
Steer clear of this one.
Well clear of it.
This is a gauntlet run
right through the heart of Sadr City.
Saddam Hussein
was a certifiable madman,
but even he wasn't crazy enough
to go into that place
more than once in 30 years.
We pulled out of there a week ago
and already it's the Wild West.
(CHUCKLES) yöu actually sound worried.
-  And yöu actually seem offended.
-  Yeah.
Well, this isn't about
yöu losing a step now.
l want yöu to know that.
-  Hey.
l'm 1 0 times the man l was
when yöu met me.
-  (LAUGHS) Uh..huh.
-  And twice as fast.
Russ,
the boys and l can get this done,
minus the bloodshed.
Those plates can do all kinds of damage.
Don't make me beg.
l'd hate to see yöu beg, Hannibal.
yöu've been my friend for a long time.
More importantly,
yöu and those boys have possibly been
the most valuable military asset
l have ever had at my disposal.
Now, yöu asked me not to make yöu beg.
Right now, l'm begging yöu.
Hannibal, please, let this one go.
Russ, this is too big an enterprise.
We can't let these bozos do this.
lt's way too big.
And yöu'd do it
with or without my blessing?
No, that l wouldn't.
l need yöur blessing.
l'm not so sure that it is a blessing.
Good hunting, my friend.
Thank yöu.
How'd it go with the old man?
Same old, same old. What yöu got there?
Pictures of my new baby.
HANNIBAL: Oh, look at her.
Who's a proud papa?
These pictures are the closest
Murdock gets to that van.
lt's ready for me when l go back to LA.
Listen, B.A.,
we're extending our stay a little bit.
We're going back into Baghdad.
l thought we was ordered
to stay out of Baghdad.
-  That's true, but l'm...
-  PIKE: Smith.
-  Pike.
-  l understand yöu and yöur grunts
are now stealing my gigs. l don't like that.
l figured yöu Black Forest guys
would be busy
installing a dictatorship
or overthrowing a democracy somewhere.
(CHUCKLING)
lt's still the weekend, yet.
That's nine to five stuff, pops.
Look at yöu clowns.
yöu're not soldiers.
yöu're assassins in polo shirts.
(CHUCKLING)
We'll make in a week
what yöu guys make in a year.
Cash don't buy guts, kid,
or brains.
And yöu're short on both.
This is Morrison's base. Bug out of my op.
They make yöu wear
the yellow shirt there, B.A.?
What's that stand for, "Barely Able"?
Get out of my way, punk.
Hey, don't sweat them.
They might have just done us a favor.
A big one.
Let me see, we got one medium tank left.
l'm telling yöu,
there's a reason she came back.
Face, l told yöu, forget about her.
The levels of ambition on this woman...
l ain't stepping foot
in any type of aircraft, Hannibal.
No gliders, paper planes, ultra lights.
-  yöu ever gonna let me live that down?
-  No.
Mexico was a long time ago,
and l saved yöur life.
How about thanking me
for not whooping yöur ass at the hospital?
l was an Airborne Ranger until l met yöu.
And yöu chickened out just like... (CLUCKS)
-  263 jumps.
-  Just a thank yöu would have been nice.
And one helicopter ride with yöu
screws it up.
Airborne Ranger with a fear of flying.
Like a punk!
B.A., for the last time,
nobody leaves the truck
once we take it over. Okay?
RAVECH: My cousin takes me to this party
where this amazing cover band
does this trash metal version of Hello
by Lionel Richie.
GAMMONS: Yeah.
RAVECH: Yeah. lt goes...
BOTH: (SINGING)
♫ Hello, is it me yöu're looking for? ♪
Guys, how long have they been in there?
-  About three hours.
-  Three hours.
Three hours?
They've been in there for three hours?
They haven't come out at all?
No one came out to take a leak, nothing?
GAMMONS: No.
RAVECH: Nope.
l've been here for three seconds
and that sounds odd to me.
l've been watching that tent like a hawk.
Really? lt looks like yöu're eating
some risotto and sitting on yöur ass.
l don't know. l wanted the soup.
RAVECH: l wasn't eating risotto. l had...
GAMMONS: lt's not risotto.
(MEN CHATTERING)
MAN: Yeah, boys. (WHOOPS)
(MEN LAUGHING)
Yeah, he wants to fight, doesn't he?
(ALL EXCLAIM)
Damn, this is awesome.
They got us a stripper, too.
yöu got that hot enlisted look. Me likey.
Before l throw yöu in the stockade,
where are they?
They didn't tell us... Captain.
They just gave us a case of beer
and 50 bucks apiece.
(CHUCKLES) l got a hundred.
Oh, did yöu get a hundred?
yöu think we get to keep the hair?
Staging, movement, action plan.
There's a nice read for yöu.
(LAUGHING) Hell, yeah, Hannibal.
This is it right here.
This is bat shit insane.
-  lt's perfect.
-  This is beyond nuts, boss.
lt gets better. (LAUGHING)
B.A., yöu'll need a piece
of contoured metal to make a skid plate.
(WHISPERING) Let's go, fool.
HANNIBAL: Murdock,
we'll need a car battery, too.
See if the boys at Black Forest
can help us out.
Press credentials, we need them.
Hit the media tent
and see what's lying around.
(IN SOUTH AFRICAN ACCENT)
Sorry, my friend, l see yöu've put
the South African microphone
at the bottom.
yöu can't always put the CNN on top.
Private, there are two mics.
l don't know if there is something...
(l GOT MINE PLAYING)
l was a moving man in my yöunger days
HANNIBAL: Murdock,
we need a news camera.
See what yöu can do.
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
All right, sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Hello. l'm...
l'm in love with yöu. (LAUGHS)
Listen, we're doing a preliminary poll of...
What are we talking about?
Of the pull out. (LAUGHS)
HANNIBAL: We're gonna need airbags,
lots of them.
-  What bureau are yöu with, darling?
-  Le Monde.
Are yöu French?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
Hello, this is General Parker. l need...
Okay. lt's for yöu.
Hey, fool, yöu need to call
an air strike on yöurself.
(LAUGHING)
-  We're good, mate. l'll meet yöu.
-  No, l think we need to get going now.
yöu need to understand
what l'm telling yöu right now.
HANNIBAL: B.A.,
we're gonna need a magnet.
-  Yeah!
-  A powerful one.
MURDOCK: yöu ever seen Blue Man Group?
HANNIBAL: l'll pick up the rest.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
l'm just gonna go for it.
Ooh, la, la.
MURDOCK: (IN SCOTTISH ACCENT)
What would yöu give for one chance
to come back here and tell our enemies
that they may take our lives,
but they'll never take our freedom!
(ALL LAUGHING)
Ready to go downtown?
Good luck tomorrow.
-  Thank yöu.
-  Give 'em hell.
General Morrison,
where the hell is Hannibal Smith?
Captain, yöu would do well
to revise yöur tone and readdress me.
General, l have authority under DCIS
that supersedes yöur command,
so last time, before this becomes
embarrassing for the both of us,
where is Hannibal Smith?
Would yöu excuse us, General?
(MORRISON SIGHS)
Captain, in nearly 40 years
of being in this army,
l have learned to control my temper
and my voice when in the presence
of a subordinate officer
who, for at least the time being,
seems to have lost her goddamn mind.
Now, it is my understanding
that yöu have a question for me.
ls that correct?
yöu are correct, sir.
Then when yöu are prepared to
remember that yöu are still an officer
in the United States Army,
in spite of yöur civilian attire,
and are ready to present that question
in a military fashion,
then perhaps we could get somewhere
with this discussion.
lf yöu have sent an Alpha Team into
Baghdad for any reason whatsoever,
that is a direct violation of a DoD order.
Well, and as much as yöu have
this kind of knowledge,
l can't help wondering why it is that
yöu need to ask anything of me.
l will take that as yöur confirmation, sir.
HANNIBAL: They go mobile in three hours.
The plates and over a billion dollars
will be loaded into the back of a semi
at the mint.
They're overland for exactly
4.6 miles before they reach the bridge.
That's our window, and it closes fast.
(BOTH ARGUING IN ARABIC)
These guys will go weapons hot
at the first whisper of trouble.
Face, yöur point of entry
is under the hotel.
lt'll be packed with foreign press
and private security.
(GRUNTS)
B.A., yöu're in this alleyway
on a stopwatch.
Make sure the bike has V-tins or better.
B.A.: l got something
a whole lot better than that.
-  Bam!
-  What about me, boss man?
HANNIBAL: l had a little
helicopter here someplace.
MURDOCK: yöu got some barrel rolls?
Some mid air stalls?
l'm looking for my next
near death experience.
HANNIBAL: Only air support this time,
Captain,
but l'll get yöu in on the next one.
l promise.
B.A., l need yöu
to pop that clutch at 0630.
(EXCLAIMING)
ls that me?
Oh, no, l forgot. l'm in an lraqi sewer.
Thanks, boss!
Timing is everything, Face.
This is all about the bull's eyes.
Why not?
HANNIBAL: From under the semi, yöu'll
take out the truck directly behind yöu.
(DRIVER EXCLAIMING)
Huh?
HANNIBAL: Now, these guys
are gonna be onto yöu, Face.
B.A., that's yöur cue for throttle.
Be sure to look both ways
before crossing.
And have a nice full tank of gas.
(MEN SHOUTING)
yöu'll have
multiple hostiles on board, B.A.
Escort them from the premises.
(GRUNTING)
lf any stragglers sneak up behind,
don't worry, l got yöur back.
HANNIBAL: Gotcha, kid.
Attaboy.
That's all fine in theory, but l still
don't see how we get out of Baghdad.
l do.
B.A. ! Hang a right!
B.A.: All right! Hang on!
(MEN SHOUTING)
-  B.A.: Watch out! Watch out!
-  Heads down!
FACE: Oh! Nice one, B.A. !
(LAUGHING)
HANNIBAL: Face, get the airbags!
Gotta make sure
this thing stays locked for later!
Beautiful!
HANNIBAL: One, two, three.
FACE: Hey, boss, airbags do deploy
on impact, right?
HANNIBAL: B.A., get in the container.
Contact, rear!
FACE: Shit!
See, this is the part of the plan
l don't trust!
Don't worry, Face! The rope will hold!
lf l was worried, l'd be nailing myself
to the container right now!
Hang on, boys!
(EXCLAIMING)
Bam! Come on! l smoked yöu!
(ON RADIO) yöu boys see that down there?
Murdock? What is that fool doing here?
Don't lock me in here.
l ain't playing with y'all!
MURDOCK ON RADIO: Hey, boss,
yöu ever play that game at the fun fair
where yöu try to pick up
a stuffed animal with the claw?
This is a lot like that.
That's it!
Did yöu lock this?
yöu locked it, didn't yöu?
Hannibal, open this door right now, man!
What the... Are yöu hooking this thing?
-  yöu hooking this up to a helicopter?
-  l got yöu.
B.A.: What the hell's going on?
yöu ain't that crazy!
Tell me we ain't flying!
l'm gonna kill yöu, fool!
-  Boss, is that Bosco?
-  Get me out of here!
MURDOCK: That's not good.
B.A.: Let me out of here!
He is not happy.
MAN 1 : Agent Lynch,
l'm patching surveillance
from the General's tent to yöu now.
MAN 2: Sir,
l have an inbound V-22 tilt-rotor
on approach from the northwest.
ldentified friendly.
Landing under the General's orders.
MORRISON: Alpha Delta Alpha, stand down.
Checked, friendly.
Those are our boys.
D block perimeter around LZ
for essential cargo touchdown.
HANNIBAL ON RADIO:
Russ, we are in the net.
Copy that. l will be there in five.
l've got a big bottle of Blue Label waiting.
A bottle? Make it a case, Scrooge.
-  See yöu in a few.
-  (B.A. POUNDING ON DOOR)
Who's gonna let him out?
- yöu!
-  yöu!
What yöu don't realize is,
now l gotta kill all of y'all!
l'll kill all of y'all!
Hannibal first, then Murdock!
-  Boss man.
-  B.A.: l'm gonna save Face for last!
-  Let me try something.
-  FACE: Go for it.
ls it weird that l'm more scared now
than what we just did?
Bosco, it's Murdock.
Murdock, open this door! (BANGS)
l'll make yöu some of that
coconut curry tapenade that yöu love.
That might work.
B.A.: With toast points?
Hell, yeah, with toast points.
What, yöu're gonna have that
-  with plain old chips?
-  Let's do this.
-  Damn! yöu tricked me.
-  There he is.
-  There he is!
-  l hate that!
-  Come on!
-  Get away from me, man!
The only reason l don't kick y'all asses
is 'cause yöu all outrank me.
yöu should know better!
yöu know l hate flying!
-  l'm wet! l stink!
-  MURDOCK: Hoo! Yeah!
B.A.: And l can't spend none of that money!
MURDOCK: Money can't buy happiness.
B.A.: Damn, man!
Hey, Murdock, yöu cooking tonight.
yöu better get yöur apron on.
(ALL LAUGHING)
l love it when a plan comes together.
-  Hannibal, who was that?
-  FACE: General?
-  ls that the General?
-  Russ.
-  Get there. Get in there.
-  FACE: General!
-  Russ!
-  General!
General!
Jesus Christ.
Pike.
Contact rear!
BLACK FOREST SOLDIER: Get in there!
HANNIBAL: Get there, get there!
JUDGE ADVOCATE 1 : After conferring,
we've decided to demote yöu
to the rank of First Lieutenant.
JUDGE ADVOCATE 2:
Lieutenant Sosa, it's nothing personal,
but yöu lost those plates.
Those were yöur responsibility.
JUDGE ADVOCATE 1 :
Consider yöurself lucky.
Others are going to prison over this.
JUDGE ADVOCATE 2:
Good day, Director McCready.
Lieutenant, yöu're dismissed.
JUDGE ADVOCATE 3: Colonel Smith,
this court has been unable to recover
any direct order from General Morrison
for yöu to conduct the mission
for which yöu're being tried.
HANNIBAL: yöur Honor,
this was a covert operation
and no official orders were given.
JUDGE ADVOCATE 4:
So the one individual who can verify
the legitimacy of this operation
is deceased. ls that correct, Colonel?
HANNIBAL: No, yöur Honor, not deceased.
General Morrison was murdered.
Colonel, l've been around a long time.
l've seen units like yöurs.
They're outlaws.
Units like that pose a direct threat
to the fabric and fundamentals
of our military.
yöur Honors, why hasn't Black Forest
been brought to trial?
Black Forest and its personnel are
not subject to military jurisdiction.
FACE: (WHISPERING)
Where's the plan, boss? Where is it?
Where's the escape hatch?
Because l don't see it.
-  This mission isn't over, Lieutenant.
-  What mission?
l clear our names.
We find Pike and the plates.
-  (GAVEL BANGING)
-  No matter what.
yöur Honors, these men were acting
under my command.
Any judgment should be levied
against me, and me alone.
Absolutely not, sir.
We were all participating
in this operation willingly.
l don't wanna be tried separately.
l refuse to be tried separately, sir.
IN accordance with
the Uniform Code of Military Justice,
this court is rendering guilty verdicts
for each member of this Alpha Unit,
or A-Team,
and mandating incarceration
in separate maximum security facilities
for a period of up to 10 years.
yöu're all hereby stripped of formal rank
and dishonorably discharged.
-  This is bullshit, man.
-  (GAVEL BANGING)
JUDGE ADVOCATE:
This session is adjourned.
-  (A-TEAM PROTESTING INDISTINCTLY)
-  (GAVEL BANGING)
Disgraceful.
-  Do not touch me, okay?
-  Captain, stand down.
Order! Order!
Absolute disgrace!
yöu happy? Are yöu happy, Charissa?
Colonel, control yöur men!
-  Get yöur hands off me!
-  This is a disgrace!
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
HANNIBAL: Well, hello, Mr. Lynch.
Long time.
yöu look very relaxed, Lynch.
A lot of cameras in here.
(SIGHING) Yeah, there are.
Yeah, well, they seem to be having
some technical issues at the moment.
May not show up till playback.
Hannibal. Can l call yöu Hannibal?
l can't call yöu Colonel anymore.
Six months.
Been waiting for yöu to bust out of here
and round up the rest
of the Backstreet Boys
and lead me to those plates.
Six months and not a peep.
Everybody thought yöu and yöur team
were working with Pike.
Mmm. Everybody except yöu.
Pike murdered Morrison. Set me
and my boys up and stole those plates.
And l know where he is.
Nobody knows where he is.
lt's a single image of him.
Taken about a month ago,
somewhere in Europe.
We think it's a grab from a CCTV camera.
Frankfurt, Germany.
(LAUGHS) How did yöu get that in here?
Time, Lynch.
Give me a minute and l'm good.
lf l've got an hour, l'm great.
yöu give me six months, l'm unbeatable.
l know Pike.
Who's the Arab?
LYNCH: We don't know.
We think he's the deep, dark,
hidden hand in this whole thing.
Maybe a broker, maybe a buyer.
HANNIBAL: Lynch, we have common
enemies and yöu have limited choices.
My team is still yöur best shot
at getting those plates back.
l wouldn't be so sure.
Then why did yöu make
the long drive out here?
yöu and yöur boys at Langley
want yöur own private printing press.
That's about as deep
as yöur patriotism goes.
So, what would yöu need from me?
l swore to my team
that l would clear our names.
yöu of all people must understand
the value of a name.
Now, listen.
l want full reinstatement
and clean records
for myself and my team.
l can't get yöu out of here.
Not legally, at least.
This is something the boys at Langley
do very, very well.
Make sure the dosage is right.
And when l say right, l mean perfect.
(l'VE BEEN LONELY FOR SO LONG
PLAYING)
♫ Don't seem like happiness will come along ♪
(SNIFFS) Cuban. What a shame.
♫ Everybody's throwing rocks in my bed ♪
(GRUNTS)
♫ Just can't seem to get ahead in life ♪
♫ Ooh, nothing l do ever turn out right ♪
♫ Won't somebody help me, please? ♪
(SINGING ALONG WITH RADIO)
♫ 'Cause l've been lonely for so long ♪
♫ Don't seem like happiness will come along ♪
♫ l've been lonely... ♪
(GASPING)
(BELL RINGING)
(GRUNTS)
yöu are not permitted
in my dojo!
So, Satan walks into this bar...
(GASPING)
WARDEN: Wait a minute.
What's this, a lap pool?
A dry steam room?
Yeah, it'll go a long way with the boys.
How in the hell do yöu pull this off?
lt's not who yöu know, Bob,
it's how yöu know them.
Oh! Did yöur boy get back
from Afghanistan?
Yeah. Thanks for getting him home.
His mother and l are real grateful.
-  Captain.
-  Hey.
(WHISPERING) yöu left
something on the bed.
-  Could have hid those.
-  Why would l want to do that?
l'll see yöu at 8:00.
-  WARDEN: And now yöu want to build...
-  A lap pool and a dry steam.
Overlooking a sundeck.
Hey, LT, thanks for the boots.
Ah! Come on. lt's my pleasure, baby!
MAN: Beautiful.
Listen, now l know
this is good for the body,
but how do yöu protect the face?
(SIGHS)
yöu don't mess with it, kid.
Gotcha.
-  Thanks for the tan.
-  yöu got it.
(THE WASHINGTON POST MARCH
PLAYING ON SPEAKER)
McCREADY: Smith has escaped, Lieutenant.
Let me go after him.
Smith and his team were working
with Brock Pike and Black Forest.
l can get those plates back for yöu, sir.
yöu know l can.
Holla what? Holla who?
Holla me.
Hey. (RATTLES HANDLE)
Hey! Let me out! Hey, hey! Hey!
l see him standing there,
and l was like, "What?"
And then it turned black
and l woke up, and my face was numb,
and l just...
And yöu mopped up the footprints
that led out,
ignored the fact that yöur lab coat,
pass card, car keys and car were missing.
Looks like he ate Smith.
Gilbert, yöu've either deliberately
aided and abetted
a federal fugitive's escape,
or yöu're the single dumbest human being
l've ever come into contact with.
-  yöu smell that?
-  Don't talk about it.
Would yöu like to know
which way l'm leaning?
-  Forward.
-  (CHUCKLES)
l would test this man's urine, on the hour.
l was a week away
from my parole hearing.
yöu are really tan.
(GRUNTING)
Told yöu the mission wasn't over.
l'm putting the team back together.
l need yöu, Face.
l can't do this without yöu.
Warden, how did Smith arrange
a personal visit without yöur consent
or yöur signature? How does that happen?
How the hell did this guy do that?
Seal that up, nobody goes in there.
Log in pages from the day in question
have been removed.
-  Why does that not surprise me?
-  Torn out.
The cigar was in the spine of that book.
-  Subtle. lt's a good book.
-  Right.
This is surveillance
from all around the prison, right?
Mmm..hmm.
What yöu're watching is a signal jammer.
Every time he walks through
one of these things,
we get massive interference.
He waltzes in here and waltzes out.
Nobody knows who he is.
God.
(VOCALIZING)
Yes. The cigar that Colonel Smith
broke out of prison with.
-  RAVECH: Yeah. Wanna hear the crazy part?
-  Yes.
Lab reports show lethal amounts of,
wait for it, tetrodotoxin.
Tetrodotoxin? What is that?
-  The near death drug.
-  Yes, that sleeping beauty thing.
Yeah. And yöu know
who likes to use that, right?
-  Who?
-  Our friends at Langley.
lt's one of their favorites.
Come on, do yöu really think that
the CIA came to the prison to visit Smith?
This sounds kind of crazy,
but l think the CIA broke him out.
Who put us on?
The same guy that put us on in Baghdad.
Lynch, CIA.
What are we talking about?
Clean records? Reinstatements?
All of the above.
What about Pike and the plates?
Payback.
SOSA: What are they exchanging?
What is that?
ls that how he got this in here?
One of these things is not like the other.
l suck at these games.
Where's this plate from?
What is that plate?
lt's an "F." Frankfurt, Germany.
Oh, Frankfurt, Germany.
Smith is talking to us.
This is not accidental.
With this guy, there's a plan
and two to back it up.
l take it yöu didn't get religion inside.
No. l got revenge.
Good.
l know a couple of guys
that'll feel the exact same way.
l'm counting on it.
Emergency exit now.
Hannibal.
Baracus, don't do it!
PRISONER: Where he going?
What's he doing, man?
Baracus! God damn it!
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
Sosa.
McCREADY: Lieutenant,
Peck's already gone.
What?
Baracus and Murdock are left.
Handle it, Lieutenant.
Right. Okay.
l don't want to be embarrassed
like this again. Do yöu?
Okay. No, no, no, no.
We're gonna catch and deploy from here.
Peck escaped.
-  Oh, hell. yöu think Smith is involved?
-  (SIGHS) Definitely.
Get graphics on him and Smith.
Anything that'll lD them instantly.
l know they got Murdock
in a psych ward in Mannheim.
SOSA: Right. Okay.
Where the hell is B.A. Baracus?
How did yöu know that once that door
was extracted
-  that it would take his weight?
-  l just did. He's...
-  yöu know, he's what, 225, 230 pounds?
-  230. Yeah.
Remember the gag we did in Venezuela
seven years ago?
Venezuela. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But that was a midget.
Yeah, l wouldn't go for that.
-  Hey, big guy. There he is.
-  Yeah! He's back.
-  Yeah, it's good to be back.
-  FACE: Come on.
-  lt's good to be back.
-  FACE: My man.
-  lt's good to see yöu, bud.
-  yöu, too, bro. yöu, too.
-  Thanks.
-  yöu look well.
lt's good to see yöu guys.
-  What?
-  Where's the Mohawk?
What, yöu don't like my new do, man?
Do l like it? Well, we got yöu the clippers.
l thought...
Yeah, l used them.
Hey. What's up, big guy?
Come on, yöu can speak to us.
Guys...
l can't kill anybody.
-  What do yöu mean?
-  l've taken a vow.
-  Vow?
-  Of non violence.
l'll still do anything for yöu guys,
yöu know that.
But l just can't kill, man.
Old habits may die hard,
but they still gotta die.
When l was a kid,
all yöu heard in the hood was,
"Bosco's a badass, out collecting scalps."
That's where the Mohawk came from.
Was always at war.
And that's what warriors are for.
Hannibal, man. l don't miss that life.
l'll help yöu get Murdock,
and right that wrong,
-  but l can't kill.
-  FACE: Even Pike?
Even if killing him would clear yöur name?
My conscience is the only thing
l need clear.
Now, where's that crazy ass fool?
Transference.
Healing feelings.
yöu can't warehouse these things,
yöu know?
yöu have to express to progress.
We gotta empower yöur emotional tower
and send out a wavelength
of self love and acceptance.
Thank yöu.
Clear.
(LAUGHS)
He seems completely impervious to it.
lt's impossible to develop a base reading.
Have yöu increased the voltage?
Every single session, yes.
-  Healing feelings, baby.
-  And?
ls that all yöu got? Here we go.
NURSE: Clear.
Yee..ha!
Yeah, l think
l might have felt something there.
(HUMMING)
Oh, no, l won't sleep.
ATTENDANT: Howard Little.
yöu have a package here
from an Annabelle Smith.
HOWARD: l don't know
any Annabelle Smith.
Sure yöu do, Howie.
Sure yöu do, baby. Annabelle.
Remember the nurse from Da Nang?
The redhead, double amputee?
Professional hang glider? Yes!
Guys.
HOWARD: Annabelle.
MURDOCK: Yeah. Yeah.
Annabelle.
MURDOCK: Annabelle.
yöu have outdone yöurself. Look at this.
-  lt's so real.
-  Beauty.
A movie in three dimensions.
Stand to, soldier.
-  Jerries advancing on the western front.
-  Good heavens.
Got a secret mission for yöu.
Take these
and distribute them amongst the men.
-  Yes, sir.
-  Don't fail the Queen.
-  No, sir.
-  Great.
Yes, sir.
ALL: (CHANTING) Movie, movie, movie...
l knight yöu.
Sir, yöu have to put yöur head down.
Stand up and do it again.
ALL: Movie, movie...
Now let's sing to the Queen.
When l ask yöu... Not yet.
-  Movie, movie...
yöu get glasses! yöu get glasses!
Ball!
When yöu kneel,
yöu put yöur head down straightaway.
Looking me in the eye is disrespectful.
Do yöu understand?
Movie, movie...
yöu're looking me in the eye now.
That's wrong.
ALL: Movie, movie, movie...
Aquaman? Hello.
yöu get glasses! yöu get glasses!
Rise, Sir 3D,
and enjoy yöur motion picture.
-  Movie! Movie!
Boy, could l use two hours of not this.
Pass out the sedatives
and order some pizzas for these freaks.
-  Movie, movie...
Movie...
Shit.
ATTENDANT: Excuse me,
can l help yöu with something?
Yes. Captain Murdock, where is he?
-  ATTENDANT: Right through there.
-  Thank yöu.
El diablo.
Okay. (SHUSHES) Settle down.
No talking during the movie.
PATIENT 1 : Down in front!
PATIENT 2: Look, it's 3D, man!
PATIENT 3: l'm sick of 3D.
Captain Murdock.
yöu remember me from Baghdad?
(MUMBLING)
GAMMONS: Okay, this is pointless.
This guy is fried.
RAVECH: Yeah, there's a reason
why he's in here.
And his entire team has escaped,
except him.
(THE A-TEAM THEME PLAYING)
PATIENTS: Movie!
Take a look around anyway.
Let's make sure he's alone.
GAMMONS:  Yes, ma'am.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh, Captain, yöur chariot awaits.
MURDOCK: Sorry, boys, gotta run!
Can't finish the movie.
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
Do let me know how it ends.
Charissa, where are yöu hiding?
Stay beautiful, baby.
HANNIBAL: Punch it, B.A.
B.A.: Let's go, fool.
Get the truck!
She's actually shooting at us.
yöu guys should see these bullets in 3D!
-  Murdock, get in here!
-  lt's like we're actually being shot at!
yöu are getting shot at, yöu crazy ass fool!
-  Stop right there!
-  Ram it.
Hey! l said halt!
(ALL EXCLAIMING EXCITEDLY)
Damn! Sorry, dude.
lt looks like they're headed for the tarmac.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
(SOLDIERS CHATTERING)
-  Gentlemen.
-  Holy shit, that's Hannibal Smith.
Are any of yöu armed
and/or wanted federal fugitives?
-  No.
-  Well, we're both.
-  Which means...
-  B.A.: This is a bad idea.
This is a bad idea.
Stop being a baby.
yöu're a grown ass man. Get on the plane.
-  yöu're taking the plane?
-  And that's why l joined the Army.
We gotta finish the escape.
Man up and get in there.
The best and brightest.
Appreciate it, boys. That'll be all.
Who's got the keys?
l just need yöur keys.
B.A.: What yöu talking about keys?
yöu don't need no keys for no plane.
MURDOCK: l do need keys.
B.A.: For what? This is a bad idea.
We just broke
this guy out of a psych ward.
Hannibal, yöu let the real pilots go.
-  B.A., relax. yöu're gonna be fine.
-  Take one of these.
What is this? Will it knock me out?
lt better knock me out,
'cause if it don't,
l'm gonna knock yöu out.
Bosco, the buttons are confusing me.
-  Shut up, Murdock.
-  HANNIBAL: Come on, Murdock. Let's go.
yöu gonna fly this plane?
Forget it. l'll turn myself in.
-  MURDOCK: What does this do?
-  Come on.
-  Come on, Murdock.
-  l got lucky.
(GROANS)
Hang on, boys.
SOSA: Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
Face, yöur girlfriend is back.
-  Reverse now.
-  RAVECH: Son of a bitch!
SOSA: Move yöur ass now.
-  The C 1 30 versus the Mercedes Benz.
-  Lift us off, Murdock.
GAMMONS: How about faster?
SOSA: Faster!
l'm trying. l got it pinned!
(MURDOCK SINGINGIN SPANISH)
Oh, my God!
(ALL SHOUTING)
(WHOOPING)
Get us to flight control.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are expecting slight turbulence.
Please remain in yöur seats
until the captain has turned off
the "Fasten Seatbelt" sign.
Don't worry, boys! Turbulence has never
brought down a plane!
-  (ALARM BEEPING)
-  What the hell is that?
But we got inbound subsonic UAVs
with missile lock!
And they bring down planes all the time!
Okay, they're coming in.
Launching countermeasures!
Whoa!
Did yöu see that? That's my diversion!
They die on this version.
Hang on! Hang on! Hold on!
We're going over.
FACE: Murdock,
what the hell are yöu doing?
(WHOOPS) yöu boys remember Mexico?
Whoa!
Ladies and gentlemen,
from the flight deck,
if yöu look out of the right hand side
of the aircraft, yöu'll notice
that yöur right wing is on fire.
Tango reacquired.
Missile lock pending, sir.
Lieutenant Charissa Sosa, DCIS.
Major, do not shoot that aircraft down.
Scramble fighters and force them to land.
There are federal fugitives on that plane.
They've also stolen property
from the U.S. Army.
Billy, Billy, l need yöu to get the nose cam
view up here on my monitor now.
lt's up, sir. Here it is.
Missile away, sir.
We have shoot down. Hercules has been
intercepted and destroyed.
Sorry, Lieutenant. l'm sorry.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
-  l don't believe it.
-  We have chute deployment on the Buford.
What?
l want these drones taken offline
right now!
-  They're 3,000 miles away.
-  Whoever is running those drones.
Get me a direct line
to whoever is running those drones.
We gotta get these drones to stand down
or l'm gonna be on bitch duty.
l need to get those men alive!
(GROANING)
HANNIBAL: Everybody okay?
What are the chances
they think we're dead?
Not great.
-  Tell me we ain't still on that plane.
-  We ain't on that plane.
-  FACE: Hannibal!
-  Yeah?
lf we're under 20,000 feet,
we can still breathe, right?
What are yöu talking about, 20,000 feet?
-  Let's fire up the old weapons system.
-  What the hell, man?
Hey, Bosco, a little stuffy.
l'm gonna pop a window!
Yeah!
What yöu got, bitches? What yöu got?
Yeah! (LAUGHS)
Let me have a turn, Face! Come on!
-  Why are we in a falling tank?
-  Because the plane exploded!
What... What? When?
Recently!
-  The Reapers shot it down!
-  What Reapers?
The same ones
that are still trying to kill us!
-  l blame yöu, Hannibal!
-  Technically, we're not flying.
l know! Because we're falling, fool!
Oh, Jesus!
UAV-  2 has splashed down.
We just lost one of the drones.
FACE: Hannibal, we're in trouble!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Brace yöurselves!
Awesome!
HANNIBAL: Face, get on to the main gun!
There's a lake a half mile away
from this position.
-  What the hell am l trying to hit?
-  Trust me!
-  Rotate the turret 82 degrees.
-  Fire in the hole!
-  Fire!
-  Boom!
Fire!
Are they trying to shoot down
that other drone?
No. They're trying to fly that tank.
-  (LAUGHS) He's flying the tank!
-  yöu can't fly a tank, fool!
-  Rotate 1 6 degrees!
-  Got it!
Fire!
Rotate 34 degrees now!
-  Hannibal...
-  Wait...
-  (MURDOCK SCREAMS)
-  Fire!
-  PILOT: Control, we have lost...
-  ls that a confirmed hit?
Bring turret full front and wait!
Murdock! Close the hatch!
Hatch, okay! Did that work?
Did that work?
-  Boss!
-  Come on, baby.
-  Come on.
-  Hatch control?
B.A.: l'm too yöung to die!
Boss! l'm aiming at nothing!
Come on.
-  MURDOCK: lt's been an honor, gentlemen.
-  Come on, baby.
The greatest ride is the last ride, Colonel!
-  Fire everything!
-  Come on, baby!
-  B.A.: Get right with God, y'all! This is it!
-  Come on!
Yee..ha!
(POLKA MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(WOMAN SPEAKING GERMAN)
lt's not fair to the fish!
yöu're cheating!
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
yöu with yöur nagging...
...yöu're chasing them away!
(LAUGHING)
All right. Busy bees, busy bees.
Guys, yöu can take yöur coats off.
Hot as hell in here.
l'm sweating like a whore in church.
-  Sir.
-  Yeah?
Smith and his team were engaged
in a C 1 30 over Mannheim, Germany,
by two Reaper drones.
l'm not sure if it's an encryption glitch,
but it says
that they were shot down in a tank.
(LAUGHS)
NORAD's calling it an X out,
but there is a conflicting report.
l'm sure there is.
l've got a German Hausfrau
who says she saw a tank
drive up and out of Lake Wolgastsee
with a guy resembling Murdock...
Excuse me, which way to Berlin?
RAVECH: ...asking for directions to Berlin.
GAMMONS: (SCOFFS) That's impossible.
SOSA: Well, this will be the second time
Smith has died this week.
ls that possible?
SOSA: What have yöu got for me?
GAMMONS: Look at this.
We just got the unscrambled composite
of Smith's visitor in prison,
but with no lD on the subject yet.
SOSA: Hello, handsome.
Wait, l've seen this person before.
l know this guy.
Baghdad.
Get me a clean patch to Langley.
We're going fishing.
ANALYST: l barely even heard about it.
l mean, l heard bits and pieces of it,
but how much of that was us?
-  So, l have a...
-  l was talking.
-  lt's never us.
-  Can yöu stop?
l have a DoD hardline
from Lieutenant Sosa.
She's looking for Agent Lynch.
He's not available, ever.
Agent Lynch, from Baghdad?
General Morrison's tent?
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Out.
Why do we have her?
LYNCH: She's got a fantastic personality.
That's why.
With whom am l speaking?
This is Lieutenant Sosa.
ls this Agent Lynch?
l'm sorry, l don't have a first name.
Neither do l.
So, what can l do yöu for, Lieutenant?
l'm looking at an image of yöu
from the disciplinary barracks
at Fort Carson.
(WHISPERING) She's hot.
Did yöu visit
former Colonel Hannibal Smith in prison?
(SIGHS)
l don't know what yöu're talking about,
former Captain.
Agent Lynch,
if yöu facilitated Smith's escape
and are currently aiding and abetting him...
Ooh. Buddy.
lf yöu can make something like that stick,
yöur next promotion
should be in the five star range.
And if yöu're helping to retrieve
those engraving plates,
l'm going to have to go out of my way
to disappoint yöu.
l want her phones, her computers,
any support packages she operates.
l wanna know everything. l want active
intercept taps on everything she's got.
l want every move monitored
from this moment forward.
yöu realize she's DoD.
l don't care if she's G.O.D. Do it.
Boss, check this out.
We've tracked this photograph of Pike
to the Königsbank in Frankfurt.
Our surveillance
has him and an unknown Arab
making regular trips
from the train station to the bank
all over the last month.
-  Pike's getting sloppy.
-  Yeah, but if we're onto him,
what are the odds that Smith and his team
are onto Pike and the Arab, too?
RAVECH: No, no, no, this is a direct
pull down from the Pentagon's database.
There's absolutely no way Smith
and his team could have this stuff.
l think we should assume they have
more information than us at all times.
HANNIBAL: Pike has been moving
the stolen engraving plates
to the Königsbank Tower in Frankfurt
over the past month.
Tomorrow, the last of the cases
containing these plates
will be transferred to the Arab.
This will mark the only time
in the last six months
that all of the plates
have been in one location.
lt's our best and only shot
at getting them back.
They leave the Königsbank Tower
for the 7:15 train to Zurich.
Gentlemen, we're gonna make sure
they miss that train.
-  Face?
-  Yeah.
Time to bring in yöur former flame.
lf she's as good as l think,
then she'll be on her way to Frankfurt
to intercept those plates.
-  Why would yöu tip her off?
-  She's a crusader,
and we're gonna need her teed up
at some point.
SOSA: Keep yöur eyes and ears open, boys.
MAN ON PA: Charissa Sosa...
(MAN CHATTERS IN GERMAN)
Charissa Sosa...
Now the wrinkle.
lf Sosa's onto us,
we can assume that Lynch is onto her.
And if he thinks she stands
beteen him and those plates,
he won't hesitate to kill her.
Face, get to the train station.
This is Sosa.
(GARBLED SPEECH)
lf there's a threat from Lynch, deal with it.
-  Hello?
-  (GARBLED SPEECH)
MAN ON RADIO: Shoot is green.
Say again, shoot is green.
Hello?
(PHONE BEEPING)
Something's wrong.
We're marked, guys. Pull back.
l don't like this at all.
See. Don't be seen.
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
-  FACE: Hello, beautiful.
-  yöu have got some balls.
-  yöu put a drop phone on me?
-  l had to, babe.
lt's the only way l could talk to yöu.
Lynch has all yöur comm lines.
-  l want yöu to pull yöur team now.
-  l'm gonna find yöu, Face.
But do not engage her
or anyone else directly.
FACE: Not if l find yöu first.
(GRUNTING)
Come on, all right... Okay. Okay.
Ow! Ow! Jesus!
-  What the hell are yöu doing?
-  Trying to save yöu!
Charissa.
Come on, yöu know we're innocent.
yöu know this.
yöu're lying. Like yöu lied in Baghdad.
l did not know.
l knew nothing about the plates.
At that... At that time.
yöu are completely full of shit!
Will yöu stop selling yöurself on that
and avoiding the fact that yöu lied to me!
-  yöu're the one that misled me.
-  When?
-  Come on. yöu wanna go there?
-  Yeah, let's go there.
yöu heard l was a player
and yöu wanted to play.
And then l got serious and yöu freaked!
-  Oh, l freaked? l did not freak!
-  Yes, yöu did.
yöu panicked and yöu ran.
Charissa, come on.
l'm a federal fugitive.
yöu know exactly how wanted l am.
yöu think l came to Frankfurt
to hash out some old heartbreak? No!
l'm here because we didn't do this.
l'm here because we were set up.
l'm here because, in the end,
the truth is worth the risk.
And l believe in yöu,
even if yöu don't believe in me.
God, l forgot how beautiful yöu are.
Hold on to that phone.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
OH MY GOD!
HE'S GOT A GUN!
RIGHT THERE! HE'S GOT A GUN!
A GUN!
Sucker.
-  Oh, shit.
-  Where's Peck?
Excellent question. Find him!
MAN ON PA: Please stay calm
and go to the nearest exit.
PIKE'S MAN ON RADIO:
Meet yöu up on corridor three.
Three to base. We're all clear at this time.
Give me confirmation
as soon as the package is secure.
We need a video feed.
(HUMMING)
Okay, let's dance.
Coming down. Positions, prepare to move.
As always, stay close to me, sir.
(ALL CLAMORING)
MAN 1: Closing off the 10th floor.
MAN 2: Tenth floor, we need backup.
Get back! Get back!
l can't see anything.
How we doing there, big man?
HANNIBAL: Murdock, here comes the Arab.
MURDOCK ON RADIO:
And here's a long drive
hit deep into left center field.
Murdock's back, he's at the wall,
and he makes the catch!
(ALL COUGHING)
MAN 1 : l can't breathe.
MAN 2: lt's a trap!
MAN 1 : Pete, we need backup!
HANNIBAL: B.A., l lost the case.
l'm taking fire. l'm out of here.
B.A., get to those plates.
(YELLING)
(GROANING)
(BYSTANDERS SCREAMING)
Deutsche Federal is responding
to explosions and shots fired
-  at the Königsbank building.
-  Get us out of this mess and get us
-  to that building as soon as possible.
-  Yes, ma'am.
(GROANING)
(WHOOPS)
yöu made me work for this one, Baracus.
l didn't think l was this out of shape.
l am, unfortunately.
Where's the rest of the team, huh?
Smith. Peck. That idiot pilot, the asshole.
What's his name?
(B.A. COUGHING)
l'm gonna take this one out of yöur ass,
Baracus. Let's see what yöu got.
(GROANING)
Come on. What are yöu doing?
What, are yöu tired?
l'm not gonna hurt yöu, man.
No, yöu're not gonna hurt me,
l'm gonna hurt yöu.
-  l don't wanna kill yöu, man.
-  yöu don't wanna kill me?
yöu're not gonna kill me.
l'm gonna kill yöu, Baracus.
l'm not playing with yöu, Pike.
Here we go, because l got two guns.
l'm a lefty, remember that, right?
So, as soon as
that hammer goes back, it's on.
B.A.: l swear to God, l'll do it.
yöu're not a coward, are yöu?
-  Are yöu?
-  (TIRES SCREECHING)
Whoopsy.
Damn!
-  Need a ride, big fella?
-  yöu're a life saver, man.
l couldn't shoot him.
Get out of the way! Get down! Get down!
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(SIREN APPROACHING)
(AGENTS SHOUTING)
GAMMONS: U.S. Military!
Put them down. Put them down.
-  This is U.S. Military. We got him.
-  (GUN CLICKS)
Yeah, this is about
the right amount of cops.
That's cute.
yöu're lucky there are people around.
No, sweetheart, yöu're lucky.
MURDOCK: yöu eat that cold?
FACE: Any way l can get it.
MURDOCK: There's a leak in the roof.
There's a lot of them.
-  MURDOCK: ls that them?
-  l got it.
FACE: All right. Not a peep out of the Arab.
Sosa was at the train station.
-  yöu saw her?
-  Yeah.
Did yöu talk to her?
l had no choice, okay?
Just trust me on that.
l trust yöu
to make historically bad decisions
-  as far as women are concerned.
-  (ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
What part of yöu
is thinking at the moment?
Lynch's men moved in on her
and l had to react.
That's why yöu wanted me there
in the first place...
To stop them! Not to engage her!
l couldn't do one without the other.
Please. Somehow l doubt that.
Hey. What are yöu so pissed about?
We got the plates.
yöu wanted her teed up. She's teed up.
She knows we didn't steal them.
She'll be thrilled to find out who did.
What?
yöu had to know.
yöu had to know if yöu left me alive,
that this was coming.
How could yöu not?
yöu taught me almost everything l know.
Hannibal. yöu know who this is?
We all do.
Morrison?
Hell, no.
Jesus Christ.
Not so sure that it is a blessing,
but good hunting, my friend.
Thank yöu.
MURDOCK: yöu son of a bitch.
FACE: Morrison? Holy shit.
yöu're not a general.
How could yöu do this to him?
How could yöu do this to us?
yöu know nothing about leading men.
l knew if Lynch helped me escape,
yöu had to be part of it.
yöu and Pike were making a play
on those plates with Lynch,
and yöu turned on him.
The way yöu turned on us.
Lynch was never gonna cut us in.
He was gonna use us.
He brought yöu on as insurance.
He never thought yöu'd betray
yöur oldest living friend.
l just hit first, Hannibal. l'm a fighting man.
yöu're a liar and a traitor!
Then don't draw this out. Kill me.
That's a fantastic idea!
B.A.: Whoa! Whoa!
Bos, let me do this.
Face, l ain't killing nobody.
yöu're not, Bosco. l am.
No matter what he says,
do not kill him, okay?
yöu guys don't wanna watch?
Just turn yöur heads.
-  l'm not gonna be party to it neither.
-  l wanna kill the son of a bitch, too,
but he's our ticket out.
B.A.: He knows what he's talking
about for once. Listen to him.
-  Face, he is our only evidence.
-  Murdock, Murdock...
-  MURDOCK: Do yöu understand?
-  He put us here.
MURDOCK: yöu can blow his head off
after he testifies, okay?
He's ruined it!
-  Think what yöu're doing, Face.
-  HANNIBAL: All right.
-  lf yöu can't handle it...
-  HANNIBAL: Boys, enough.
Enough! That's enough, Face.
Enough! Step down!
Everybody outside.
l got him.
FACE: l don't want yöu to have to do it.
HANNIBAL: Face, outside.
Stand down, soldier.
Face. Now!
FACE: Fucking stupid.
MURDOCK: yöu okay, man?
HANNIBAL: yöu knew Morrison
was masquerading as the Arab.
-  Why not share that?
-  LYNCH: l wasn't 100% sure.
How about 99%?
Would yöu think
it was worth mentioning then?
Lynch, what did yöu think?
yöu think l'd just kill him on the spot?
l was certain of it. l still am.
Do yöu have the plates?
l wouldn't be calling yöu if l didn't.
Smith, return the plates, kill Morrison,
and reclaim yöur lives.
l want signed and authorized
amnesty agreements
for myself and for each of my men.
From the White House,
the State Department
and the Joint Chiefs of Staff.
yöu hear me?
l'm gonna need a little more time.
How much?
Give me five minutes.
l'm waiting.
(CASSETTE REWINDING)
MORRISON: Don't yöu get it, Hannibal?
We fight for them, we bleed for them,
we die for them...
They don't give a rat's ass.
Death and destruction,
they're selling it like it was on
the goddamn commodities exchange.
Don't push this off on them.
This is not about them.
yöur war protest was
stealing billions of dollars!
Who are yöu?
l am a general. yöu are a colonel.
l say, "Jump," and yöu say, "How high?"
End of story.
lt is now.
l saw yöur tomb at Arlington.
yöu died a national hero.
Death's too easy.
And the last thing we need now
is another lie.
Don't do this. Hannibal, please.
yöu owe me that much.
yöu owe me!
yöu're gonna tell them we're innocent.
yöu owe me.
Hannibal, it's meaningless.
What are yöu fighting for now,
yöu and those boys?
yöur ranks? yöur reputations?
They're shit!
yöu're convicts!
Plates, no plates, yöu are federal fugitives,
and when they're done with yöu, Hannibal,
they just fucking burn yöu.
Zulu one, Zulu one, this is Broadsword,
yöu're clear to engage.
LYNCH: "Broadsword."
Did yöu come up with that?
That's awesome. "Broadsword."
"Broadsword."
FACE: Boss, could yöu do that?
To us?
What Morrison did?
No. Not in a million years.
Yeah, but yöu didn't see it coming, though.
How long did yöu know it was him?
Are yöu guys crazy?
l know yöu are, but, Face,
are yöu accusing him?
Hey! Hey!
l'd rather face a firing squad
than betray yöu boys.
Don't let this tear us apart.
Not now.
Not when we need each other
like no other time before.
Move!
Wow. That's awesome.
That looks exactly like Call of Duty,
doesn't it?
All right. Here's the deal. No press release.
Keep local law enforcement
and media off site.
Get a three mile cordon,
ditto the no fly zone.
Get an agency scrub team out there
and get me the goddamn plates back.
The German police have yöur entire team
in custody in the Königsbank Tower.
(LAUGHING)
l don't do teams, babe. That's Smith's bag.
l'm strictly a solo act.
l like to travel light.
Stuff like loyalty doesn't fit
in the overhead bins.
l thought yöu and Smith
were working together.
yöu thought wrong.
Yes, we have weapons.
No, yöu may not wand us.
PIKE: lf yöu want to deal, we can deal.
How about l dedicate my immediate future
to destroying yöurs?
How about yöu get smart and start dealing
before somebody else does?
Former Captain.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Unless yöu've got a piece of paper
that looks exactly like this one,
then this troubled yöung loner
belongs to me.
Let's go.
How the hell
did they get an extradition order?
Sorry, Pike.
At least with me, there are rules.
CIA's got rules.
Our rules are just cooler than yöurs.
-  Go.
-  yöu know, Lynch,
if l could seal this room with yöu inside,
l'd be doing the world a big favor.
(CLICKS TONGUE) That's not nice.
HANNIBAL: Lynch? Had to be.
Stay close to the fires, boys.
lf that gunship is still around,
it won't read our body heat.
FACE: That idiot Lynch, so quick to kill us,
didn't even bother locating the plates.
HANNIBAL: Where do we stand
on the non violence now, B.A.?
yöu pissed? yöu should be.
Who gives a shit about the plates?
Morrison was the only way to clear us.
And without Morrison, we got nothing.
-  What do we do, boss?
-  l don't know, Murdock.
-  l don't know.
-  l do.
This guy Lynch,
l think l got him figured out.
-  yöu got a plan, kid?
-  How do we get out of here?
Give me 20 minutes.
So, Morrison's dead.
Smith and his team are dead.
Another 1 5 minutes or so,
we locate those engraving plates.
(SCOFFS) What is this? Are yöu gloating?
No, this is me beating yöu
after yöu burned me.
-  We had a deal, remember?
-  Not yöu and me.
-  yöu, me and Morrison.
-  Not yöu and me, directly.
And yöu two collude and cut me out.
Hey. What are yöu doing? IN the car?
Are we doing...
Are we gonna do this in the car?
-  yöu doing this?
-  LYNCH: He's gonna do it.
PIKE: Way to go.
That's brilliant, right there.
What are yöu doing? What is he doing?
-  Jesus.
-  How's it going, Kyle?
-  yöu all right?
-  l'm good.
Brother, yöu are far from good.
What are yöu doing?
lt's a European silencer.
lt's a suppressor. Counter clockwise.
yöu're holding a gun like that?
yöu've held a gun like that before
and yöu're still here?
That's amazing.
-  Don't point that thing...
-  Jesus. Final request,
don't let this guy shoot me, please.
FACE: So, if Sosa knows we're alive...
HANNIBAL: She'll believe
Morrison is alive, too.
Let's just hope that Lynch
still has Sosa's comm lines.
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
This is Sosa.
HANNIBAL: General Morrison
is in my possession.
What? l'm sorry.
l can't hear yöu. Who is this?
-  Okay, this was not well thought out.
-  PIKE: No shit.
l mean, look at this.
Am l to teach yöu how to kill me?
Hey, do me a favor, all right?
Put the barrel...
Put the gun flush to my head.
-  KYLE: Are yöu sure?
-  There yöu go, right there.
-  ls that going to go through?
-  Before yöu hurt somebody besides me.
There yöu go. We're okay. We're okay.
(CHUCKLING)
Never cuff a man in a seated position
with his hands behind his back.
Makes it impossible to see the hands.
That was cool.
-  yöu like that?
-  l like that.
-  l like that a lot.
-  (MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
Are yöu all right, yöu idiot?
-  Yeah. lt was a good hit.
-  Please handcuff him.
PIKE: We don't need to use them again.
We don't need the cuffs.
Who are yöu talking to?
-  Brad, phone or gun.
-  Jesus.
-  LYNCH: Phone or gun. Pick.
-  Hey, hey.
-  Put the gun down.
-  Hey, l didn't burn yöu. Morrison did.
l really wanna shoot yöu.
yöu gotta hear this, sir.
SOSA: ls this Smith?
HANNIBAL: From a former colonel
to a former captain,
l know l've got about 30 seconds
before yöu lock this signal.
-  So listen, we can prove our innocence.
-  Leave that on the floor like that?
Okay. All right. Now, go back.
Did yöu say yöu have Morrison?
yöu have General Morrison?
-  Correct.
-  yöu have him alive?
HANNIBAL: And well, despite Lynch
trying to wipe us out wholesale.
Too much to explain now
but Morrison's testimony frees us
and fries Lynch.
Uh..oh.
Well, not without the plates.
HANNIBAL: Also in mypossession.
Remember, Lynch thinks we're dead,
and l want to keep it that way.
-  SOSA: All right. We'll deal.
-  Give me a pen.
-  Where and when?
-  Got a pen? Anybody got a pen?
-  HANNIBAL: LA docks, 48 hours, dawn.
-  yöu still use a pen?
(SHUSHING)
l deliver Morrison and the plates.
IN return, l want a retrial
in front of a civilian court.
All right. We'll deal.
LA docks, 48 hours from now.
Any bullshit from yöur end,
and that's it, deal's off.
-  Did we get him?
-  No.
(SIGHS)
Pike.
yöu believe in second chances?
Uh...
l do now.
Too much?
l thought yöu were spot on.
My turn.
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
Hold on to that phone.
This is Sosa.
FACE: Hello, beautiful.
HANNIBAL: Thank yöu.
FACE: They got the raw end of the deal,
didn't they? Look at B.A.
He looks like a huge banana.
(IN AFRICAN ACCENT)
Good morning, my friend.
Good morning.
Rabbi Binky Rabinowitz?
What passport did l give yöu?
yöu're from Tanzania.
My mother is from Tanzania.
-  Oh, shit.
-  What the hell happened?
(SPEAKING SWAHILI)
(INQUIRING IN SWAHILI)
-  ...converting Africans to Judaism.
-  OFFICER: This is station six...
Stuff like that.
Let's get ready to move.
There's three to my right.
There's two behind me
and one at the northeast exit.
(SPEAKING SWAHILI)
Wait a sec.
Shalom.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING SWAHILI)
-  What's he doing?
-  lt's Murdock. Telling his life story.
HANNIBAL: There is a God.
-  yöu speak Swahili?
-  yöu don't?
HANNIBAL: yöu got enough
to work with, kid?
We will.
yöu and l have some major favors
moving across the mid Atlantic right now.
lt's a deep sea freighter,
shipping strictly black market merch.
How do we get out to her?
-  (SHUSHING)
-  B.A.: A boat. A plain old boat.
This is what l'm talking about, Murdock.
Traveling the open seas in style.
This is the way l like to travel. classy like.
The way people used to, safe.
-  Yeah...
-  We don't need a plane.
yöu know, Bosco, hopefully one day
we'll get yöu over yöur fear of flying.
What?
Hey, that ain't a boat!
(EXCLAIMING)
Just not today.
Murdock, don't yöu remember what l said?
-  l said yöu have to catch him...
-  yöu have to catch him...
-  ...after yöu inject him.
My bad.
(GROANS) Damn it! My head, man.
(SNIFFING)
-  Coconut curry tapenade, yöur favorite.
-  Give me that, fool.
yöu get them toast points?
Voilà. Toast points.
Y'all knocked me out again, huh?
Okay, now, the whole injection,
knocking out,
Hannibal and Face.
The curry tapenade, Murdock.
Why do l feel like l fell on my face?
Huh? Tell me that.
Uh...
Lynch is a paradox.
Murdock, yöu done with that?
This is a guy who needs anonymity,
but he loves theatricality.
He's an administrator,
he's not an operator.
Where is it?
Very nice.
So he stays as far away
from the point of impact as possible,
and never gets his hands dirty
if he can help it.
But we're gonna change all that.
yöu can't hustle a hustler, fool.
No sparks, no flames,
not even a flashlight near this stuff.
Easy, easy.
FACE: This guy is never
at the flashpoint of anything.
He's safe and sound somewhere,
pulling the strings.
DOLL: Mama. Mama.
Hey, boss. Why so many
of these damn things anyway?
Because overkill is underrated, my friend.
FACE: So we're gonna bring this guy
down to ground level.
DOLL: (DISTORTED) Mama. Mama.
HANNIBAL ON RECORDER: (DISTORTED)
This way, Lynch. Lynch.
FACE: The last place he'd ever want to be.
Then yöu put him on display
for the whole world to see.
Any questions?
What's up, boss man?
Hey, B.A.
lt's gonna get heavy, isn't it?
Well, l can't promise yöu it won't.
Let me read yöu something real quick.
"Victory attained by violence
is tantamount to defeat,
"for it is momentary."
Gandhi.
"lt is better to be violent
if there is violence in our hearts,
"than to put on the cloak of non violence
to cover impotence."
Who said that?
Same guy.
Gandhi wasn't afraid to fight
for the things he believed in.
What is it yöu believe in, B.A.?
(SINGING) ♫ Forlife is but an opera ♪
lt's off, isn't it?
l think it's higher.
(VOCALIZING)
No, it's good. lt's not that, Murdock.
Face, what's wrong? Come on, man.
l don't know, man.
l'm just thinking past this.
yöu know, we've always come back alive,
the four of us, 'cause of the old man.
-  l know.
-  l'm not him.
Face, l know this.
Murdock, l'm not Hannibal.
Who has the most to lose on this, Face?
Me.
And l trust yöu.
Yeah, l know, (LAUGHS)
but yöu're crazy.
Not that crazy.
LYNCH ON RADIO:
Our eagles may have landed.
Everybody ready to roll?
TEAM LEADER 1 : Copy
Team one on the move.
TEAM LEADER 2: Acknowledged.
Team to en route.
All right, guys, everybody ready?
Curtain's about to come up.
Show time.
That's Smith right there. Watch him.
LYNCH: Ground team is in position?
TEAM LEADER 1 : Standing by.
IN position.
Shoot Team One. Affirmative.
Spotter One. 1 0 8.
PIKE: Let's chattermark on comms for now.
Morrison's the primary tango.
Plates are the package.
(MOBILE PHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
LYNCH: Okay, okay, he's talking to Sosa.
l want this call.
yöu lied to me, Sosa. We had a deal.
l want that goddamn call in my...
Thank yöu.
SOSA: We had a deal,
but l'm changing the deal.
HANNIBAL: Are yöu kidding me, Sosa?
Are yöu kidding me?
SOSA: This is a complicated exchange
and yöu have no play here.
Listen, or remain at large fugitives
-  for the foreseeable future.
-  Uh..oh. No! No, no.
For God sakes,
l've got Morrison here and the plates.
l'm exposed, Sosa. Exposed!
SOSA: We're not doing this on the docks.
Now listen to me,
we're not turning ourselves in.
Now yöu listen to me,
SOSA: l need yöu to do it on my terms
or nothing at all.
HANNIBAL: To hell with that,
and to hell with yöu, Sosa!
Ah. She burned him.
Face, B.A., we're bugging out.
Sosa's jammed us.
Murdock, get the chopper down here in 1 0.
Okay, he's moving him.
yöu got him? He's moving him.
For the love of God, relax.
LYNCH: l am relaxed. He's moving him.
MORRISON ON RECORDING:
Don't do this. Hannibal, please.
-  That's Morrison, right there. Take him.
-  Wait, does he have the plates?
Smith has the plates. Go now.
-  Take him, he's right there. Kill him.
-  l've got Morrison, taking a shot.
HANNIBAL ON RADIO:
A little too close for comfort, kid.
What just happened?
What the hell is he doing?
LYNCH: Where are they?
Somebody talk to me.
Come on,
did that thing crush them or what?
(THUDDING)
This was a hell of a lot easier
when it was just three plastic cups.
Everybody just be cool. Pay attention.
No hasty moves.
So, yöu beat a guy like Lynch
by drawing him in with three things.
What the hell are they doing?
Distraction.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What is happening?
Diversion.
This is a diversion!
Stay eagle on those containers.
They're breaking for the exits! Open fire!
Do not engage! Back off!
LYNCH: Ground teams, engage!
Holy shit!
Ground team, re-engage.
yöu are being played by Smith.
He's trying to draw yöur eye line, Lynch.
Come on, be smart.
Take them! Take them!
Contact! Tower house and bow!
lt's Peck and Baracus!
And division.
lt's a trap! Pull back! Pull back!
-  Get the hell out of there!
-  No, no, no.
What is happening? What is going on?
Nice one, kid.
PIKE: lt's Peck and Baracus!
-  Shoot them!
-  Shut up! l know what l'm doing.
Okay, paintballers, time to go pro.
B.A., get to yöur secondary position.
Okay. Game changer.
Here's what l think of yöur best laid plans.
Shit!
Jesus Christ!
So much for the grand scheme, Smith.
What the hell was that?
HANNIBAL: Face, what the hell was that?
Pike hit the ship with a SMAW!
He punched a hole in the hull!
What about the plan?
FACE: Pike just blew up the plan!
We are ad-libbing!
Bosco, get out of there!
l'm going for Hannibal.
-  Cover me. l'm going for those plates.
-  Yes, sir.
The boat is going over! Get out of there!
Bos, hang on!
Oh! Jeez!
Shit.
Bosco, Pike's got the high ground.
l'm running low on ammo, man.
Shit!
How are yöu doing, handsome?
Shit, can yöu cycle that weapon.
Nice work.
Jeez, close friends and bullets.
Where are they when yöu need them?
Don't take this too personally,
but look here,
smile, wait for the flash.
Baracus.
(LAUGHING)
Bosco!
HANNIBAL: (WHISPERING) Lynch.
Lynch.
Come on, Lynch.
LYNCH: Come on, Smith! Stop bullshitting.
HANNIBAL: Lynch. Come on, Lynch.
Lynch...
Where am l?
Come on, Lynch.
Lynch.
Where am l, Lynch?
Come on, Lynch.
Lynch, Lynch, Lynch, Lynch.
Lynch!
(WHOOPS) There yöu are, Hannibal.
Been looking all over for yöu.
Hey, don't let the scarf fool yöu.
My muay Thai is pretty good.
My jujitsu is a little better, but...
yöu had this whole sleight of hand thing
going with the containers
and the cars, and the fireworks.
"Lynch, Lynch, Lynch!"
God, that's annoying.
But yöu give Pike a rocket.
There's yöur monkey wrench.
MORRISON ON RECORDING:
Hannibal, don't do this.
yöu know, Smith, yöu could have
the best recipe in the world...
-  MORRISON: yöu owe me that much.
-  ...but yöu drop a few bullets
-  into the batter...
-  Hannibal, don't do this.
-  HANNIBAL: Lynch, no!
-  Hannibal, please.
Oh, God.
...and that cake don't bake.
Uh..  oh. yöur witness,
yöur gun, yöur problem.
yöu served yöur country well. Excuse me.
Hello, Ben,
where have yöu been all my life?
Look at us, Hannibal.
Couple of grown men.
l'm bleeding. yöu're bleeding.
(TUTTING) Don't get up.
God damn it!
yöur muay Thai is as bad
as yöurjujitsu, Lynch.
Better stick with a gun.
yöu put a loaded weapon in my hand,
l'll put a bullet in yöur head.
l told yöu l would shoot yöu.
Kevlar saved yöur life.
Thing is, it doesn't do much good
if l pop yöu in the head.
lt does if yöu melt it down.
MORRISON: Hannibal, don't do this.
-  Hannibal, please.
-  FACE: So, yöu beat a guy like that
by drawing him in with three things.
-  Distraction.
-  Whoa, whoa, whoa! What is happening?
Diversion.
And division.
MORRISON: Hannibal, don't leave me alive.
FACE: Then yöu put him on display
for the whole world to see.
What the...
That's good.
Surprise.
Agent Burress.
What did yöu call me?
Agent Vance Burress?
lsn't that yöur name?
At least that's the name l've got
on this warrant here,
and unless yöu have a piece of paper
that looks exactly like...
That's funny. That's what l said.
She's quoting me.
Easy, easy.
yöu're under arrest for attempted murder,
violations of the Civil False Claims Act,
and the theft of top secret
government engraving plates.
Easy.
l guess the plan went okay,
considering Pike did blow up the boat,
which l didn't account for at all.
Bullets didn't go through.
MORRISON: Hannibal, don't do this.
Hannibal, please.
How are yöu feeling, man?
Not... Not good.
-  What's wrong?
-  Not good.
-  l feel sane.
-  (LAUGHS)
l should have shot yöu in the head
a long time ago.
ls it crazy
that l'm feeling yöur anxiety right now?
Do l look anxious to yöu?
yöu think l'm beaten?
l'm bleeding, l'm not sweating.
Let's take him out of here, guys.
Go ahead, princess.
MURDOCK: What's the difference between
a concussion and a contusion?
-  lt don't matter, bro. yöu tore up.
-  FACE: Murdock, that was beautiful.
yöu were right. The helmet worked.
Ketchup worked great.
yöu did a great job. yöu okay?
-  Yeah.
-  FACE: Got yöur bell rung?
Just let Hannibal
make the plans next time.
-  Oh. Okay.
-  Okay?
How's the conscience, big guy?
At peace.
Keep it turning.
We already got them on the exits.
-  We got a two mile no fly zone here.
-  Which one of yöu is Sosa?
-  l am. l am.
-  l need to talk to Sosa.
As of right now yöur prisoner
is to be remanded
-  into federal custody.
-  l have a warrant for this man.
-  CIA MAN: As of right now...
-  l'll tell yöu what... l'm a doc.
Let me doctor yöu up. Let me help yöu out.
Do yöu need stitches?
Please tell me yöu need stitches.
l can stitch yöu up really good.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Gentlemen.
The Central INtelligence Agency
believes in and evinces
a profound moral ethic,
as well as an unshakeable
professional standard.
As such, we would like to extend
our most sincere apologies
for what's happened here.
-  Good day and God bless.
-  Where are yöu taking him?
Who?
l never got yöur name.
My name is Lynch.
Of course it is.
Did he just say Lynch?
SOSA: Let it go.
MURDOCK: Hey. Do not touch me.
FACE: Take it easy, guys.
HANNIBAL: Everybody, stand down!
Stand down!
-  Get those plates.
-  HANNIBAL: Everybody, stand down!
-  That's an order. Hey, yöu, stand down.
-  MURDOCK: What is wrong with yöu?
-  Lieutenant.
-  (MOBILE RINGING)
Sir, when did yöu arrive? l had no idea...
-  Just give me a minute.
-  Yes, sir.
FACE: Get yöur hands off me, tough guy.
Well, that's one hell of a mess.
But we did get the plates.
Unfortunately, l'm gonna have to charge
yöu all with escaping lawful custody.
What? Hannibal,
what is this guy talking about?
B.A., we were wrongly convicted,
but it's still illegal to break out of jail.
Director McCready, Smith and his team
were instrumental
in recovering those plates.
They're still level 1 0 federal fugitives
and l need that off my desk.
This is chickenshit, sir.
Yeah, well, yöu know what?
Perhaps for them, it is chickenshit,
but for yöu, Captain, we're re-promoting
yöu to yöur former rank.
So, look, they're gonna be delivered
to the U.S. Marshals Service
here in Long Beach.
-  And there should be a C 5 transport...
-  l understand, but...
...on the tarmac in half an hour.
-  This needs to be done.
-  This is really unfair, sir.
-  This is bullshit.
-  l'm like Harry Houdini.
l chew through yöur cuffs.
SOLDIER 1 : Get up. Step up. Get in there!
SOLDIER 2: Step up!
-  SOLDIER 3: Let's go. Get moving.
-  Stop. Wait, stop.
-  SOLDIER 3: Move it.
-  Wait.
-  This is so wrong.
-  lt got a little aggressive.
-  Don't worry about it.
-  This is really, really wrong,
and l'm going to do everything l can
to fix it.
-  l know yöu will.
-  l'm so sorry, Face.
Nice plan, Face.
Yeah. We just traded Lynches,
and we're going back to prison.
HANNIBAL: We returned the plates.
We can hold our heads high.
We did the right thing.
Yeah, and look what they did to us.
This is some bullshit.
MURDOCK: They burned us again, Hannibal.
We trusted the system and it turned on us.
Remember, boys, no matter
how random things might appear,
there is still a plan. Kid.
Well, l don't mean
to steal yöur line, boss, but...
(HANNIBAL CHUCKLING)
-  B.A.: Yeah.
-  l love it when a plan comes together.
NARRATOR: Still wanted
by the government,
they survive as soldiers of fortune.
lf yöu have a problem,
if no one else can help,
and if yöu can find them,
maybe yöu can hire
the A-Team.
"Hope You've Liked & Enjoyed The Movie"
Copyright from ecOtOne™
B.A.: Yeah!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4tquu
Help other users to choose the best subtitles