Once upon ?,
Ever? ...
DUP? ST hundred years? P? Nirei
PR Ottoman Empire? Bu? EA.
? Try? ND desperately S? RECªTIGE
Lost territory, the Ottomans allied,
? N FIRST R? World War,
WITH GERMANY, AUSTRIA AND HUNGARY.
POPULATION? MINORITY STATEMENTS OF EMPIRE
Were declared as enemies overnight.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
OTTOMAN EMPIRE
Translation and adaptation
LAGARDE subs.ro team ///
You have a lamb pa? S home ??
Or me? Car ...
a g? in ??
Master of Nazareth ...
I studied Fe? Them Turks,
For as you said.
how do I look??
Grave, Master.
M? Tour? floor, Levon.
Here.
Well done, Blacksmith.
C? T ?? i ?? owe for scissors
1o pounds.
With it? S? In the Turks
away from the laity.
Pa ?? i want one?'re Happy.
S? For? M? Na past? you asked
only 8 pounds scissors ?.
? I told him to? m? Turi floor.
- On m linen, Levon.
- Mul? Thank you, Master.
- Good? day, Maron.
- Good? day.
S God? AIB you? ? N guard ?.
Forgive? -m? P? Rintala,
to c? I p? c? of charge.
I was m? NIOS.
What was the reason, son?
The people who are
May rich and than me,.
It? S jealous.
This is a p? As death.
I ?? m? Confessing? Ti p How many?
? I m? P confess Count
And regret p? My sins.
Milu? M you? Lord.
F? Ten stake? Christmas St. Mary,
And ask for forgiveness.
A s? I do.
- Girls!
- Father ?!
- Father ?, this is for you.
- We f? Cut it.
Mul? Nicely thank you.
Lest the f? Cut a mother?
? I name embroidered t? U on it.
See?
Nazareth Manoogian.
very nice.
Good? afternoon, Mr. Manoogian.
Good? Hello, Mrs. Balachian.
M? excuse? i ...
ave? i ve? r to us about your warfare?
It is terrible for the people.
There are very many and die? I.
- How to handle it? Geography twins?
- Geography?
It could be and better.
It could and better ...?
- Mul? Thank you.
- V? pl I wish one day? cut ?.
And you see? wish
pl one day? cut ?, Ms Balachian.
What is the capital of France? They?
- Paris?
- Roma?
- What, Paris or Rome?
- Paris, n? T? Ngo.
United States Capitol?
- New York?
- Chicago?
Is Washington.
It does not matter ?,
I v? I love anyway.
Look ... a crane.
Who sees a crane ...
will go? into a run? c? l? tory.
- So three of us?
- If? to and three we see? seen ...
then we c? l? tors to and three.
- Mom.
- I am here.
Look, I embroidered.
is beautiful.
Rakel!
Look what you f? Cut?
What, this?
Nazar.
No.
? Ceases ?.
Should they? wash your m? ini.
The English have landed at Gallipoli.
What? Means? this?
There will be several and die? I.
? I know, but why? Means?
for us?
I have no idea.
Ottomans they will face.
- Gallipoli is far from us.
-? Slowly and.
That do not concern us? On us.
Lucinee, Arsinee, stand and walk!
Come and.
Come and here.
Corgi told me?
to and b? Men? ii Armenian village disappear? rut.
- Ani, is not? Nfrico? The kids!
- But it is TRUE.
We have been? Always loyal.
You think? will involve us and us?
We craft and.
It needs us here.
Lucinee, Arsinee,
for the last time? ...!
M? s go? bring wine.
And then, the c? Nd through? ESA down? T
on Mount Ararat,
i was f sun? million cut? it ...
And turned it
? Into a beautiful? yellow flower ?.
And this? flower
It was? turned to the sun.
Therefore it name? You
Sunflower.
Why did you stop?
I thought? sleep.
How? sleep
if? do not you? I c? n? i?
Open door panel!
Nazar ... who is it?
- ARMEANU!
- Nazar.
Opens!
Mom...
Mom, I'm scared ?.
- Who?
- Gendarmerie.
what do you want?
Sultan gave an order ...
To and b? Men? II over 15 years,
grows tini or Muslims, go to r warfare.
Now it? S soldier.
- right now?
- Rakel!
A? Expect? I.
Lua and this ...
? N me.
Do not waste time.
? ?? NCAL - you.
Fi and brave and ...
for your mother ?, right?
Yes.
Do you care? B? ie? i.
R? M? S well, sister ?.
Do not forget and what I said.
You have the worry? to each other,
b? IE? My ii.
Come and!
I? C ?!
Watch ?, brother-?.
Come and!
Tat tat ?, ?!
T and forget it? Harp.
A s? -? I? In? warm.
F? R? fear ?.
M? ? Come back clean? Nd home ?.
Come and!
do not go. please.
I? C ?!
S God? AIB you? ? N guard ?.
Tata, r? M? S here!
Tata!
It? S okay.
M? ? Come back? Ass? Nd.
Tata!
do not go!
And after? I finish? m road
what would? nt? MPLA?
It will follow a different path.
Better here in December? T
c? mpul battle ?.
Why not work? You? C? Hold!
Get to work ?!
Come on!
Work? You son of a C ?? it!
- You mil ?!
- Mi? C ?!
Work? Yourself!
Pass and at work ?!
Come and!
Work and!
Up? Yourself quickly ...
? S before? wine? ? Back.
? Before mas? g? ndim
like us? Teflon? m? Nzi Lord,
but we will not be there? tui.
Fl? M? Nzi? I? NSET and.
Fl? M? Nzi justice.
Fl? M? Nzi love.
Fl? M? Nzi of hope ??.
Stops? Get them hunger, Lord ...
For as stops today? s
And our hunger ?. Amen.
Amen.
It? S good?
Where is it? You?
- Carpet.
- Enough talk! ? Back!
Come on!
Carpet'm from.
Where? I go?
No? I know.
Watch and V? there ...
Charlik, take your sister.
Come on!
- F? It!
- Mom!
Go? I!
come here!
not V? Remember? i? back!
Go? I!
Stop and I t? Lhari!
Why do not you stop? I?
not V? Remember? i? back?
B? Iete!
come here.
Come!
Vahan, d? S us? Te p? Holds.
M? N? Nc ?.
No? Ti fl? M? Nd?
I looked at the stars ...
And the Lord m f? S cut? Tulle.
Where are the tat? L? S your mother?
They died? N? Ert.
Micu? Ule, come here.
B? Iete, do not run.
Wait, or I'll shoot!
Fever ?.
- You have? continue work.
- It's sick, sir.
Was? Ng? Lbenit all.
Work? You, or crap ?.
Just a moment.
You have the million ?.
Nazareth, take this.
S? up.
? Itself struggles? s? get up, sistersinlaw.
? Itself struggles ?.
? N order?
Peace to you, soldier? S.
Peace to you.
Look!
M? Nec? I!
Apricots!
Lua? I!
Armeni!
Listen and!
Diyarbakir Governor
He was sent here.
He wants? ?? Show mercy,
And you? d? ruIe?'re free.
Also,
all your past deeds,
They will be forgiven.
To and those ...
which renounces ?? the faith? theirs,
And converting to Islam,
And give up ?? religion grows tin ?,
will be free and immediately.
Who wants to? pass? Islam ...
s? do? a step? forward.
Face and a step? On!
Come and!
Tr? D? Tori!
Ve and burn? Hell!
- Tr? D? Tori!
- Come and? Back!
- V? sell and souls.
-? Sells and Jesus!
Go!
Tr? D? Tors!
Do not do and that!
Your souls will arrive? Hell.
Judas!
Nazar.
they left.
what are we doing now?
We go home ?, brother.
Yes.
Watch and-you ?!
D? Me dolls that.
Hide and body
that s? I do not see him? anyone.
Leag? S one another.
One other, I say!
Come and!
Ruvanes and Medical ...
b? IE? ii my ...
m? the? expects? Nazar ?, home.
I? C ?!
Come on!
I arrived! Stop and!
this is not good.
The fa? Of the wall!
? Returns up!
? N knees!
? N knees, I say!
Do not squander and cartridge? Them!
Cut i g? Tulle!
No.
Cut!
- I killed him! It's mine!
- Asshole!
Wear and V? properly!
Bea.
Look, is it? Your harp.
Come on. Come on.
Up? Yourself.
If? r? m? s here, you die.
come with me.
Come on.
Come on!
what are you doing there?
I have not killed anyone, never ?.
I stole that? I was hungry,
And me? Closed with those beasts.
Then they let us ...
that s? v? kill you.
come with me.
We will go? Together ?.
M? Mehmet call.
Come garden BE? You up.
Rest? You up.
ARMEANU ...
Wake? Up!
Come on!
Bea.
? Itself struggles? s? go.
Attention:!
L? It? S everything you? I? I disappear? Re? I!
Im and deserters?
There are soldiers and.
R flee warfare.
We are deserters.
Ave and something of value?
How you name? You, comrade?
He can not talk.
Dursun.
E? T you cursed? Ask, comrade.
Urinate? e? your harp,
And tie it at g? T.
You Fere? Te of the infection ie.
? Ncotro go? I?
Nic? Yesterday.
Can we? come with you?
Stops? Te!
What are you doing here?
- V? a? wait on you.
- Get ?!
Yes and our guns and horses
And leave? I!
Do not run and!
I've pl? Tit!
Sta? I!
Blacksmith.
Blacksmith!
Tell people t? I,
c? are decent people.
C? Ut? M just a refuge.
? L informed? Ti?
Okay? N? Comprehensible.
We are in Mardin.
R has not? Mas anything? N Mardin.
All women and children no? Tri
were du? i? n Ras al-Ain.
Blacksmith ...
ISSUE? T you people? I.
I beg you.
ISSUE?'re With them.
I have a family.
please.
please!
why are not you saying anything?
? In- and mouth!
? Back? N c? Ru ??.
L? To? The m them? NCAR.
They have children.
S God? v? to curse and!
Tic? Lo? Ior!
Even you
c? ?? I'll reg? And family?
A? Expects ?!
Dursun, bring? MBR? C? Mind.
Ras al-Ain is three days dep? AWAY.
Cuno? Your way?
Ascunde- and cross.
It heals ?.
Bring water.
Do not squander.
? Mbrace? this ....
that s? not ba and eyes.
good luck.
Forgive? -m ?.
Up? I'm Nazareth.
Wake? Up!
R? M? Ne? I? N tents!
There? A quickly!
what do you want?
In ?.
Female, bring us? Te m? Nwhich!
Help? -m ?!
Get me? from here!
Please help? -m ?!
Get out? from here!
I know you.
I v? Seen on the road.
- Get ?!
- T? I remember?
- You helped me.
C? Zusem ...
thou hast lifted.
T and give face.
Want to? ? You know,
Where did I?
Ras al-Ain.
And c? Nd through? Esa,
descended? t
on Mount Ararat ...
i was f sun? million cut? it ...
And turned it
? Into a beautiful? yellow flower ?.
And this? flower
was? turned to the sun ...
And therefore
is called?'re sunflowers.
Goggle came from Mancin.
I s? I speed.
faster!
faster.
I left and here!
You have the worry? ...
s? not V? Steal one? NCAR.
Oh yes and your mother ?.
Aram ...
not drain the water.
M? Holds we go again? N time?
M? Aju and s? me? tat buried? l?
please!
please.
D? S me?'re Ap ?.
D? M me something? Nwhich.
- please.
- Get me? from here.
I'll do anything.
Get me? from here.
Nazareth ...
My brother ...
Bhabhi ...
They died to? I.
To and from our family ?.
Nazareth ...
I v? Seen how they died.
Rakel ...
your sister...
God did not mil ?.
Nazareth ...
Put your head? T my days.
I do not want? Getting there hell.
You have to? Take me via? A ...
my brother.
Take my life? A!
St? R? E?'re My suffering? A!
Nazareth.
St? R? E?'re My suffering? Of Nazareth!
St? R? E?'re My suffering? A!
Wait!
Here.
What? Nt? MPL? brother?
What are you doing here?
Words? S Arabic?
Then ...
Tell me.
Who? S the f? Cut it?
About? You.
It? S Armenian?
It? S Armenian.
- Peace to you.
- Acts!
The acts.
Here, please.
- Omar Nasreddin?
- Yes, Omar Nasreddin.
What are you? N c? Ru ???
I v? Nd Soap.
Soap.
Smells good, very nice.
Here. P? Keep and him.
Prostitutes in Aleppo,
a s? v? many? umeasc ?.
? Stretches it!
Yes, sir.
Come on, Aziza, come on!
Come on, Aziza!
Ali.
come here!
- Peace to you, Grandpa.
- Peace to you, nephew? ILOR.
This is not and will? Nt? MPLA anything.
You? S? N ?? safety.
Look who I brought ...
An Armenian. It's dumb.
D? S something there? drink.
This way, bro.
It is silent, not deaf.
Take him? N? Untrue and d? S ap ?.
Where is it? Ti, Mutu?
From where?
What?
Mardin
There? S know? read.
Nazareth.
He is Krikor.
And he is Armenian.
Busy? Yourself to him.
A? A.
Las? this. It? S okay.
good night?.
S? v? or ru? hold!
Tr? D? Tors!
November
Leave and home ?!
Leave and home ?, tic? Lo? ILOR!
-Pleca And home ?!
- Go? I ?, tic home? Lo? ILOR!
The English won ?? c.
Ottomans are complete and.
We are free now.
Tic? Lo? ILOR!
She and her killed? Ul.
That's for you!
I have no family.
Throw ?!
Nazar ?, Drop!
Killer? ILOR!
She and killed his brother.
I left and here!
- Killer? ILOR!
- Nazar!
Vino? Back!
Nazar!
Organize? Take help
for the Middle East,
offer? Refugees? ILOR a shelter,
? N factory Soap
Omar Nasreddin,
not produce
? N this time.
Dude, please.
I do not get refuge and.
I have no room.
Forget? Yourself and you ...
I and V? Somehow fallen son?
- Do you see anywhere here?
- I and V? Fallen son?
Where to? v? bring?
V? please. L-A and V? Seen
on it? site and my brother?
Here there is no room.
Look.
If? I stay? nghesui and
diseases will break out.
what can I do?
I can not help you.
? Ceases? s? do pressure
me.
Las? -m? ? Alone!
What did? stare? i?
S? v? or ru? holds.
S? v? or ru? hold!
What are you staring at, Nesim? ITUL?
S? - And be ru? Holds.
Nazareth ... let s? go.
not V? look and the wall.
The images that I? C?
They are the work of the devil.
Nazareth, come on.
The brothel is? N direction? Take this.
S? go.
You heard what he said.
It's the devil's work.
Hai? go to the brothel.
Good. You go here,
and I m? go there.
Good?
Hey, asshole, sit down!
Master Nazareth ...
I am ... Levon.
Apprentice t? U.
Six years, Master.
You can not and s? about? You?
? You know that? Your daughters tr? IESC?
I was then shared with your family,
? In March? The die? Ii.
? Before that Rakel s? die ?,
He gave the twins a family of Bedouin,
- That s? save them.
- Where?
No? I know.
You should? be somewhere
? Outside the city? Community.
Master, me? wanted
s? I can not help but ...
I leave? n America.
I'll work on the ship.
Disp? Ru? I ...
Family members Tasci
in Harput.
A b boy 7 years
And a fetus? having 5 years.
If? ave and Information,
yes and their Armenian Church priest
in Allepo.
They are C? Uta and p? Parents? Ii
Sanvel's and Manvel.
Draw in the province of Sivas.
Tat? It was blacksmith
and seamstress mother ?.
Any information? Ie
It will be received? gladly,
The church Orphanage
"40 martyrs" in Allepo.
I hope? you will g? and.
S? God help you.
C? Uta and are children
Zina's and Tikran,
Woven carpets Azarun smoking.
Last given? were you? zu and ...
He did not say anything.
Any information? Ie you? Please s? give it
the Red Cross? ie.
Your daughters are? N via ???
E? Are you sure?
It is well Nazareth.
it's good.
Listen ?!
This man must
s? -? i g? Seascale? children!
Why scream? N halul? Stand?
I hear you.
D? Me The notice t? U.
Nazareth Manoogian.
Blacksmith of Mardin.
Looking for? his twin daughters.
Lucinee and Arsinee.
Now would be 15 years.
They were given some Bedouin,
? N near Ras al-Ain.
Any information? Ie s? be given?
factory Soap in Allepo.
Looking for? Them up in brothels.
Filled with daughters
And sisters.
Disp? Rut ... Aram Chevorcian.
Priest in Mugi.
Last given? was it? seen
? In March? In the May 1916.
Sees and your daughters here?
Do not give up? A? I!
There are over 100 orphanages,
? N the French? Lebanon.
100?
- Yes.
- Mul? Thank you, sister? Anushka.
Let Nazareth.
S? go.
Name and address of FIEC? Rui orphanage?
Peace? be with you.
Allah s? AIB you? ? N guard ?.
Take the money.
Maybe s? you need.
C? L? S your Toria? flowing? water.
Lebanon
I buy our rat these girls
the Bedouins and Kurds.
Nobody wants
to c? They are tattooed.
Good? morning? a, Miss Niensen.
Are your daughters?
They? Always asked of you.
Looking for? Them up and you will g? And.
Your daughters are s? N? Safe and sound.
Less? In Lucinee.
Lucinee it? Chioap ?.
A c? R seen very? U,
? N March along ?.
And broke his leg.
Doctors no? Tri have? Tried to heal it,
but it was too t? rziu.
V? Age 16
had they? leave
that all and others and orphans.
That was a year ago.
In ?.
It is Ms. Gregorian teacher
math? Your daughters
- Good ?.
- This is Mr. Manoogian.
Tat? L twins.
Lua and place, you? please.
He wants? ? Knows where his daughters.
So, Ms. Gregorian?
Few b? Men and Armenians have survived? I forget.
I have cousins ​​oar? They have g? site girls
ni? I b? Men? s good.
where am I?
They? N Cuba.
Cousins ​​my time there ...
a s? help
s? -? i g? it? s daughters.
Hey, what are you doing here?
What is this? Sleep?
Court ??? floor
class? nt? i.
where are you going?
over there!
Po and the ass ?? now.
It is Cuba!
Cuba!
No, I think not? that
e? n near.
? I'm r? U, right? I know.
Here, sir, lovely flowers!
Address it not? Know,
but any and some flowers you?
- No, no? Tim.
- Sorry r? U.
But you? Good luck.
Yes. At the head? Tulle from the Prado,
st then? nga.
It? N back.
? N back!
At the head? Tulle Street? Say!
Right there, you fool!
? I close my right.
Nazareth Manoogian.
Tat? L twins.
Welcome? N Cuba.
I am Hagob Nakashian.
Did not you get my letter?
Tr? IESC? N Minneapolis ...
The Six months now.
one moment...
Your daughters working?
for this man.
MINNEAPOLIS
PETER EDELMAN
T and f? worry, Manoogian.
?? I'll g? And daughters.
We sent a telegram ?.
But today? Day is already too t? Rziu.
A s? I do this? holds.
Come on.
Should they? fl be? m? nd.
Mai? Nt? I m? Nc? M and then
g us? ndim as? -? i g? it? s daughters.
S? m? nc? m food that
d us? God has given her.
- Amen.
Longer wants? S?
Mr. Manoogian ...
I g? Sit two b? Men? S best
for your daughters.
Armeni rich and, in Havana.
But after? They were? nt? familiar for this kind ...
one did not want
It takes on Lucinee.
He did not want a woman? Chioap ?.
Then Arsinee refused
s? is c? s? toreasc? with the? other.
He did not want to? - And p? R? Seascale? sister.
E? M sure you? you do not want
s? sleep up?
Good night ?, Manoogian.
One, two, three ... again? ten.
Cost? 12 centavos.
Mul? Thank you.
Certainly ??
a s? we r? respond? ? Ass? Nd.
M? happy
c? I? nt? familiar for this kind of Nazareth.
Nazareth ...
I'm Peter Edelman.
I received your telegram.
Your daughters are no longer working?
for me.
not? I know where they are.
? I'm r? U.
It is ...
from Edelman, of Minneapolis.
Write c? Your daughters
no longer with him.
And not? Know where they are.
may have the daughters looking for me? N Minneapolis.
It's my only hope ??.
It? S move.
Do you want it? S been? enter.
The sick and send? Back.
? I know ...
Some of needles? You bastards
s come to me? is b? rbiereasc ?.
? Can it go? In America,
for $ 100.
It ?? s money at?
?? Give him 50.
A? instead use
for more rum.
His ass is small.
Do not do? more room.
Well, s? say 80.
50.
And I laugh a year for free.
agree.
You should? work.
C? Rbunarul!
10 kg.
Good? morning? of Nazareth.
Today? S day Sunday ?.
Hai? Go to church ?.
why?
There you go again? the church ??
Forget? Yourself to me.
Do not you think? N God?
I did not love? Your God?
And they named after?
place na? tere the Lord.
You portions and cross the m? Na you.
F? Her for me ...
if? you could not do for him.
Hai? go.
Come on.
A? Eza and V ?.
Nazareth.
Third b? Rbat,
r? ?? ndul front ...
He is the one who refused
Lucinee your daughter.
It? S either ru? Holds.
what are you doing?
Help!
I was robbed!
Help! A ho ?!
I did not I? Never asked? ...
Where did the money?
S God? AIB you? ? N guard ?.
I hope? ?? I'll g? And daughters.
Come and.
Bring and it? Days! Bring and rum!
Come and! I? The? I-v ?!
Gr? Bi? I see ?! Come and!
I? The? I-v ?! Come and!
Come and Chinese!
railroad crossing?
Tu. Come on. Lowers ?!
Lowers ?!
Trains come by
go to Tampa.
There descend
And travel to Tallahassee.
Tallahassee ... you? N? Understand?
Fere? You're the Clan!
M? N? Nc? Hebrew like you for breakfast.
Alvin!
what the hell...
Vino? Back!
You go there.
C? Ut? M workers.
I listen? ...
Minnesota Company International,
commits? wage workers,
according to union charges.
Ma? I insist: 70 cents and an hour ?.
Blacksmith: 70 cents and an hour ?.
L? C? You ?: 70 cents and per hour ?.
Electrician: 70 cents and an hour ?.
Take and a piece?
And d? -a Further.
Driver ?: various rates.
Stoker: various prices.
L? C? You? Boiler:
70 to 70.5 cents and an hour ?.
What difference ?? ...
Conductor: 70 cents and an hour ?.
EDELMAN
CLOTHES sewing M? N?
to search? WORKERS
AT C? ILE RAILWAYS
One, two, three, up!
Attention: where c? LCA and!
Here!
Down!
Love?'re Precisely the bowl ?!
Good.
A? A.
Beat it well.
Attention:? Behind you!
Look for yourself.
unbelievable...
Who wanted three?
D? Me ?, damn two.
Do not be stupid!
I put this down
And I take one.
B? Ie? I ...
Henry ... God ...
You shot well.
Not more successful? E? S? Nc? once ?.
Nimer? Get it? Between Eyes
And I pl? TESC.
- Good.
- P? N? to? Damn ?, wrist.
A s? - And reach the brain.
Forget? Yourself to that!
You ran out of reserves? Ie,? Oricel?
how do I look? ??? Them in?
Go? I ?, forget you Tom.
Indiano!
Go after? it, Tommy.
It was a? Wild ?.
- D? -i Tom.
- A? A, Tom.
D? -i Tom.
Yes, it? A!
What is dumb?
Attention: Tommy!
- End? It!
- Shit!
You bastard!
- Cursed Jew!
- Jesus ...
- Damn.
- Did you kill?
Cui and step ??
Father ?.
Up? You up, Father ?.
Father ?, wake? Up!
Up? You up.
Who's there?
Yes.
We are to and Armenians.
Workers at the c? S railways.
In ?. Come on.
I am Arman.
Who is it? You?
sit down.
Cau and these girls?
Are your girls?
Forget? Yourself and you.
I do not know.
No.
There are and the and Armenians.
C? Few families.
At 50 km from here. ? N Russo.
Cuno? S time? Ruso site?
Wait, huh? Expects ?!
Where you been? are you going?
? Freezing and out ?.
sit down. Harud!
F? dolls in? sup ?.
A? Expects? p? n? R? s? rite.
Lucinee!
Tata?
Dad.
where have you been?
Lucinee.
Where is your sister?
Where is Arsinee?
died,
CR? Christmas past.
It was full? parasites and.
He was attacked? parasites and
already in? our country ?.
You g? Site, tat ?.
You g? Site.
Arsin? E Manoogian
Rest? -SE? N PACE
N? SHIELD? ? N 1905? N Mardin
Death? ? In 1923? N RUSSIAN
? N MEMORY OF
FABIENNE VONIER 1947 -2013
KARL "Baum" BAUMGARTNER 1949 - 2014
Translation and adaptation
LAGARDE subs.ro team ///
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/5g55x
Help other users to choose the best subtitles