Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
What's going on?
Are you getting this?
Whoa.
What's he doing?
Do you think
they'll let us pass?
It doesn't
look like it.
Are you good to go?
Yeah, rolling.
Hidden within this
sprawling desert,
250 miles south of Cairo...
the public will
soon lay their eyes
on the Holdens'
groundbreaking research...
and the father-daughter team
could rewrite history
as we know it.
As you can see,
the pyramid behind me
has only three sides...
not four like
the Giza Pyramids.
This architectural feat
singles it out
as an exception
in this region.
You're gonna
have to start over.
The barking is covering
everything you're saying.
Oh, damn it.
What's wrong with those dogs?
Whose are they,
anyway?
They're just feral dogs
running around.
Can someone get
a shotgun or something
and get rid of
these dogs, please?
Driving me crazy.
All right, let's go again.
Okay, Sunni.
Whenever you're ready,
we're good to go.
Okay.
The way this works is,
I'll ask you a question...
you try to incorporate the
question into your response.
Like if I ask you
your name, you would say...
Dr. Miles Holden.
Wrong.
Oh. Oh, right.
Uh, my name is
Dr. Miles Holden.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Could you tell us what
exactly you're looking for?
Yeah. Uh, there are
certain ancient texts
which refer to this
geographic area...
as the possible site of the
lost pyramid of Akhenaten...
which may be related...
to the particular
and unusual
three-sided architecture
of our pyramid.
I just need to quickly
check your mic.
Yeah. It's a little
windy out here.
It's a great shot.
Just don't step backwards.
Yeah, okay.
You tell me when.
Uh...
Pyramids. Hit me with it.
Action.
Whatever we're looking at,
this is not the pyramid
of King Akhenaten.
The structure that we're dealing
with is buried below the surface.
It takes millennia for sand
to build up that high.
Which means that
this structure predates
the reign of Akhenaten
by generations.
Why are so many people
against the satellites?
Most archaeologists
are trapped in time
when it comes to
reworking methodologies...
and assimilating
new evidence
into existing historical
frameworks. Mmm.
Proving an
older genealogy
for Egyptian history
basically means...
throwing everything
they have been
working on their
entire lives into question.
Isn't that what
you're trying to do?
No, not exactly.
I respect the work
that they have done...
but we just need to know
when it's time to innovate.
Most of our pyramid is
buried deep beneath the desert.
Here is a scan.
Look at the size
of that thing!
That's got to be
600 feet on each side.
See this tunnel here?
This is our way in.
It leads directly
to the apex of the pyramid.
The apex?
It's the tip
of the pyramid.
Mmm. Pyramids don't normally
have apexes at the entrance.
But this one does.
Who dug the tunnel?
We don't know yet.
That's also part of our discovery.
Nora, tell me
about the satellites.
I'm not the first
archaeologist
to break ground using
satellite technology.
But I was inspired
to apply it...
after an article that I read
about SETI out of New Mexico.
SETI?
"Search for Extraterrestrial
intelligence."
They were using
the satellites...
to search for traces of water
underneath the surface of Mars.
I thought we were here to
talk about Egypt, not aliens.
What do you think
about all those theories?
About aliens
coming to Earth?
And that the pyramids
are just giant transmitters?
Whoa, come on.
Even I have my limits.
Do you see, uh,
how these ridges
form a barrier
around the pyramid?
Dad.Dad.
Could you please stop touching
buttons that you don't understand?
Ooh.
Where was that taken?
It doesn't matter
when it was taken.
I said where.
This technology,
the satellite stuff...
is such a small part
of what we're doing.
We should be talking
about archaeology,
about the pyramid,
about Akhenaten, and...
Actually,
the whole satellite angle...
is what interested the
network in the first place.
It's the dawn of a new age
in archaeology.
Using the future
to understand the past.
Anything else I'm not
supposed to see?
Would you just mind
your own business?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
You are my business, all right?
Archaeology used to be
about digs and dirt.
But we've lost
the raw sensation
with all this
technological mediation.
Great.
Uh, how was that, Fitz?
Oh, it was
award-winning.
Okay. Let's wrap up.
We're done for the day.
Sorry.
Hey.
No, I'm fine, Mom.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Cairo is far, far away.
And we're supposed
to break through tomorrow.
So if we get far enough,
we'll be safer underground...
than we will be
in a war bunker.
No, I'm not
taking it lightly.
I'm just trying
to focus on my work.
Could you please not worry?
You know Dad is enough
to handle as it is.
Okay. I love you, too. I do.
All right, tell...
Uh, Mom, I have to go.
I'll call you tomorrow.
I love you. Bye.
Zahir, get your
metallic junk out of here.
Jesus!
What the hell is that?
Whoa.
Uh, allow me to
introduce you to Shorty.
He's gonna be our first set
of eyes and ears inside...
after we make
initial breakthrough.
He stands just over
one foot tall...
with six wheels on a Rocker-Bogie
suspension system...
which was originally
designed
by NASA for their
Mars rovers...
to allow them to travel over
the rough Martian terrain.
I bet this thing
is a real babe magnet, eh?
Uh, some of the missions
Shorty has been on are...
Michael Zahir,
our robotics engineer.
But it seems
he wasn't briefed...
on which
million-dollar territories
he would be exploring.
Oh, don't you worry,
Nora.
I've got two
primary camera feeds...
sending back real-time footage
to our command center.
So everything Shorty sees
is permanently recorded.
Right, partner?
- Look out.
- Cute.
Look out.
We're not shooting
Days Of Our Lives.
Stop wasting
your memory space.
Oh, come on.
People would love to see
these two nerds get freaky.
Dr. Holden!
Wait,
what's he saying?
We break through!
What? Come on!
Come on!
Are you all right?
Give me your hand.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Slow down,
slow down.
You coming?
Tell them not to open it up yet.
Tell them to hold off.
Yeah, hold Off!
Zahir,
I need you to translate.
You got it?
Here it comes.
Jesus!
Get him out of here!
We have to get him
to medical!
Oh, my God.
We have to do something!
- He's alive.
- Oh.
Thank God.
So what happened to him?
Aspergillus.
What's aspergillus?
Inhalation
of toxic air.
It's actually not as
uncommon as it sounds.
What causes it?
A fungi usually found
in caves and tombs...
structures that
have been sealed off.
This pyramid
could be way older
than even I had
originally thought.
Nora, please.
Stop spinning out
your wild theories.
I am trying to
reassure the university...
that we're going to be
doing things on schedule.
And that
has to be turned off.
Nobody goes
near that pyramid
without my permission,
all right?
And nobody mentions the
word "curse." Understood?
I don't want any of that
crazy nonsense on my site.
Our site.
Goddamn sand.
What?
What's wrong?
You can't shut us down.
We're about to
launch Shorty.
It's not us,
it's the government.
The Ministry of Antiquities
is ordering all
research teams in the area...
to pull out immediately.
They want you
cleared out in 24 hours.
When will we be able
to resume the excavation?
We don't know yet.
I'm sorry, what?
I don't understand.
You've been in
the desert too long.
You should see what's happening
in the streets of Cairo.
It's mayhem.
Wide-scale violence between the
military and the protesters.
They're fearing a civil war.
But this isn't Cairo.
Yeah, we are in the
middle of the desert.
You don't get it.
I'm sorry, Miles,
but you have to be out
by tomorrow morning.
God.
We are so close!
There goes my Emmy.
Nora, this is not
a discussion.
The final answer is no.
Thank you.
Would you please hand these out
to everybody you see around here?
This place needs to
look like we were
never here by morning.
What is going on?
It's all written down there.
This is not a conference.
Now just go, please.
So, that's it?
Oh, what would you
like me to do?
How about anything?
You barely
put up a fight.
I don't fight battles
I can't win.
I have got a career
to think of,
and so do you.
Don't forget that!
Okay.
But we can't walk away from
here with nothing to show.
I am not...
Dad, please!
This is the find of the century.
And you're going to give
up when we are this close.
We owe this to our name.
What's the harm?
Besides toxic air poisoning?
We won't go in ourselves.
We'll just send in Shorty.
He can take some readings
and some pictures.
A couple of hours.
Nobody will even know
that we were gone.
Dad, I know
what you're thinking.
Look me in the eye
and tell me...
that you don't wanna see what's
going on in that pyramid.
Trust me.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Yes!
Guys, uh, Captain
Egypt is following you,
and he doesn't look happy.
Hold on.
Let me talk to him
real quick.
Zahir,
what is he saying?
He's wondering why we still
have our stuff here.
He's here to supervise us,
make sure we get on
the plane tomorrow.
Tell him not to worry,
that we are
wrapping things up...
that everything is on schedule.
Dad, what the hell?
Fine, fine.
How does
the air check out?
No. Don't even
think about it, Nora.
There's no way
you're going in there.
Actually,
according to the meters,
it's showing minimal traces
of toxic fumes...
but definitely
below dangerous levels.
But I'm assuming
it's because we're
still close to the entrance.
Can you enhance that?
Can you get out
of my workspace, please?
It's a $3 million rover.
Yeah, I can enhance it.
Okay, zoom in.
Zoom in right there.
Make that larger. Zoom in.
Dad, please.
What?
Ah! That.
This says "slaughter."
This says "God."
Yeah, this one
says "underworld."
What? Really?
Relax, Fitzie,
these are just symbols
to scare away
grave robbers.
Curved stick. Staff.
What the hell is that?
That, my dear,
is the symbol of Osiris.
Osiris?
He's the god
of the afterlife.
He's also considered by the
Egyptians as the first pharaoh.
Oh, God.
Okay, what was that?
It must've been a dog.
Got in somehow.
They left the opening
unguarded.
Let's just keep our
wits sharp, all right?
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
What?
You guys hear that?
I've lost
all external control.
Both the camera feeds.
Hold on, hold on.
Damn dogs.
You mean...
Hold on.
Shorty's offline.
- I got to go get him.
- No.
You are not going in there.
We have no idea what's in there.
Could be fumes still.
No. Be realistic, Zahir.
Be realistic?
I just told you how much
that rover costs, okay?
It's on loan.
Does he not know
how this works?
- We can't even be here.
- We have to be on a plane.
And you don't think
NASA's gonna be pissed
to find out
we lost their rover?
Okay, okay.
But just the two of us.
Uh-uh. Uh, no.
That is not happening.
Okay, we have no idea if we're
gonna be able to come back here.
You're crazy if you think I'm
not going in there with you.
The camera goes
everywhere you do.
You agreed to that
back in the U.S.
Actually, I'm all
right to just hang back here.
You guys can go on...
Get your ass in there.
Okay.
Hope you brought
those extra batteries.
We're gonna need them.
Oh, I thought we were
the only ones filming.
It's my version
of a notebook.
I don't want
to miss anything.
You ready?
Uh...
Yeah, we're coming.
Let's go.
So, how are we supposed
to get Shorty out,
if it doesn't work?
I'll figure it out.
Yeah,
he doesn't know either.
So, I think these
flares might help us
take care of our
stray dog problem.
He's saying
we can't go in there.
Keep rolling!
Tell him
to calm down!
I'm trying.
Let me try
to talk to him.
What are they saying?
I can't get it,
they're going too fast.
He's making a plea
of some kind.
Uh, from one Egyptian
to another.
I think it's working.
All right, guys,
we've got two hours
to get Shorty.
Here you go.
What's that for?
It's just something
to help us find our way back.
You know, in case we decide
to go in a little further.
Further?
Great.
They don't seriously expect
us to wear these, do they?
Yeah, guess so.
Come on, guys,
let's go.
Watch your step.
The structure could
collapse at any moment.
And don't touch anything.
Stay close.
Imagine, the last people
who walked these tunnels...
died thousands of years ago.
Also,
the ancient Egyptians
only stood about
five feet tall...
so watch your heads.
It's a little
taller in here.
The dogs couldn't
have dragged him too far.
I don't get it.
There's no tracks.
He couldn't have just disappeared.
Guys...
which way do we go now?
No, no!
Michael, what's wrong?
Oh, God.
I'm dead. I'm dead.
Ooh.
NASA's gonna be pissed.
I'm dead.
I'm freaking dead!
Death. Amazing.
Well, chin up, mate.
I'm sure we can find
the rest of him.
We're gonna find him.
Hey, Doc.
Is this the apex thing
you were talking about?
There's something
in the wall.
What's up there?
Well, there's only
one way to find out.
Nora, no.
Please don't fall.
Be careful.
Zahir, give me
your hand. Come on.
Okay, ready?
Yeah. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
All right,
I almost have the ledge.
Yeah. I got it. Okay.
All right.
You okay?
Oh. Guys, you got to
come check this out.
What do you see?
Just come up here.
I've never seen
anything like this before.
I thought this thing
was supposed to be a tomb.
It is.
What's with the arsenal?
It's ceremonial.
The ancient Egyptians
buried their pharaohs...
with an armory of spears,
for use in the afterlife.
Usually, they're placed
next to the sarcophagus,
never separately.
Dad?
Huh?
Look at that.
Mended at the shaft.
It's broken.
And I wonder...
Yeah, look at this.
There's a chip in this blade.
So these...
These were not
just ceremonial.
These saw battle.
Switch off your lights.
Lights Off.
- Whoa.
- Look at that.
What is that?
That is dried blood.
What does that mean?
I'll have to take it back
and analyze it
and date it.
We won't know until then,
so go ahead and take that
as a sample.
- Okay.
- Wow.
- That's cool.
- Hey, your wire.
- Huh?
- Your wire.
- What?
Oh.
It must have snapped.
It's high-tension
wire, Doctor,
it doesn't just snap.
- Well, how...
- Fitzie, you stepped on it.
No, I didn't.
You probably
didn't realize
but you must've done it
as you were filming.
Realize
I stepped on it?
You probably stepped on it!
It's all right.
Probably Zahir,
with his stupid robot.
It's all right,
just calm down.
We're not that far
from the entrance.
We'll set up
another wire.
All right.
Whoa.
- Okay?
- Okay, it's this way.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's not this way,
it's that way.
Look, I copied down
the hieroglyphs
in my notebook
before we set off...
- as we entered.
- No.
No, I think we came
from this direction over here.
They all
look the same.
Uh, eeny, meeny,
miny, moe.
Oh, yeah.
That's enough, Fitzie.
Look, guys. It's this way.
It's this way.
See? This is why
we attach a wire.
That's strange.
These hieroglyphs
are all the same.
We only walked
for a few minutes.
Guys, is it just me
or is it becoming really,
really hard to breathe
in these masks?
Pyramids
are incredibly airtight.
Explains how
mummies can remain
so perfectly preserved
after all these years.
Yeah, no,
I'm not talking about
some pyramid
mumbo-jumbo here.
I'm being serious.
Something's off.
Now stay close.
I don't want to
lose anybody. Okay?
Shouldn't we go
back to where we were?
Yeah,
I think it was back...
No, it's impossible.
I was positive.
Mmm.
I'm sorry, honey.
We have to go back
in the other direction.
This looks...
Yeah, we definitely
came the wrong way.
What could this
chamber be?
Holy shit!
- What?
- Oh, no.
- There's Shorty.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, come on!
We should not be here.
Let's get out.
Oh, my God!
Wait, nobody move!
Nobody move.
All right.
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
The floor
is about to collapse.
What?
We have to back
out of here one at a time.
Fitzie? Come on.
You first.
Easy.
Move toward me, and try
not to step on the cracks.
That's good.
Come on.
That's good, Fitzie.
Don't jump! Just...
Okay, Okay-
Just come on,
come on, come on.
Good, good, good.
All right,
that's good, that's good.
That's right.
- Oh, my God.
- That's right, that's right.
That's good.
Come on.
That's good, Fitzie.
Okay, now, Zahir.
Come on. Come on.
Are you sure?
Come!
Oh, my God.
It's all right,
it's all right.
Come on,
Michael, faster!
Whoa!
Everybody run!
Nora? Nora?
I'm good. I'm good.
Is anyone hurt?
I'm alive.
Where are we?
Jeez,
I can't breathe
with this stupid mask.
Oh!
What is that smell?
Smells like shit.
Where are we?
I'm guessing
where the animal
who destroyed Shorty decided
to relieve itself.
That's a lot of shit
for just one dog
who got trapped.
Not only that,
where did it go?
How'd it get out?
The only way out is up.
Still, we've got
to get out of here soon.
I haven't smelt anything this
bad since Zahir's tent...
when he had the beans
the other day.
What the hell
is wrong with you, man?
Help me!
Nora, wait!
Michael, Michael!
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God!
- Help me!
What do we do?
Okay, man, don't worry.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Okay, come on, guys!
Help me, please!
Michael, Michael.
Okay.
Calm down.
We need to push,
all right?
All right.
All right, push!
- One, two, three.
- My God.
Come on.
Push, push, push!
Stop! Stop!
Hey, hey, hey, hey-
Okay.
What are you
doing with the phone?
You're not gonna get
reception down here.
We're 90 feet below ground.
The walls are six feet thick.
Jesus, use your head.
We're never
gonna be able to get
this rock off of him
by ourselves.
And even if we do...
There's water
in there, get it out.
Hey, hey.
Listen to me.
Look at me. Look at me.
Look at me. Take these.
I want you to
swallow these, okay?
I want you to swallow.
Here you go.
He's gonna be
okay, Doctor?
He's not gonna die, is he?
Fitzie!
Just shut up, please!
You're not helping
right now, okay?
Michael, Michael. Breathe.
Hey, baby.
Look at me. Michael.
You are going to
get out of here, okay?
Just breathe, that's right.
Breathe.
Stay back,
something could still fall.
What are you
looking at?
This shaft should take us
back to where we came from.
You know, I think
I can get up there.
No, no,
that's not a good idea.
I've been rock climbing
my entire life.
If you give me a boost,
I can brace myself
in there and shimmy up.
Guys, she wants
to climb this shaft.
Can you tell her
she's crazy?
I can do it.
Don't worry.
Help me, come on!
Here, take this.
That way we can
watch on the monitor.
Jesus.
How's that? You're picking
that up? Yeah?
All right.
Okay. All right.
Okay, Sunni,
be careful.
Michael, calm down.
- Go slow!
- Yeah.
- Okay, be careful, Sunni.
- Go slow, go slow!
Yeah.
Right,
just take your time, okay?
You got it.
At the same time,
don't take too long.
Just let us know
if you see anything.
- Okay.
- Okay, Sunni?
Oh, God.
- You okay? Go slow, okay?
- Yeah.
What do you see?
I see two people
trying to break
my concentration!
Are you okay?
Did you guys
hear that?
I can't see anything.
It's too dark.
Hang in there, Zahir.
Let us know as soon as you
see anything, okay, Sunni?
I think something
is up here.
There's some kind of low
tunnel perpendicular to us.
Oh, my God!
Sunni, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, God.
You okay, Fitzie?
Okay.
- I think I've got shit in my ear.
- Dad, give me my bag.
Here, use this.
What happened up there?
I saw something.
I was almost there
and it popped out at me.
This is gonna
sting, okay?
So, was it a dog, yeah?
I didn't get
a good look.
But when I saw it,
I lost my...
I have another bag.
I saw its eyes.
What was it?
Yeah, hold on.
It was the same thing we saw
before we lost
contact with Shorty.
Sorry, sorry.
You know,
maybe it's the soldier.
He knows we're down here.
He's probably gonna be
looking for us.
A soldier popped out of a hidden
tunnel and scratched my face.
Maybe there's a way
out over there.
Hey, Michael.
Michael.
These carvings
tell a story.
You see these figures
holding the spears.
These are the same ones
we saw in the apex.
This is a warning.
A warning?
A warning for what?
I don't know.
I think we should
just stay here.
That soldier will come
looking for us eventually.
No, Michael might not
have that long.
We have to look
for another way out.
All right, then, fine.
What is your
plan now, Nora?
If there is
a gate here...
then behind those stones
there is a passage...
and maybe another way out.
And if the gate has been standing
here for thousands of years...
maybe it's standing here
for a reason.
Who are we to destroy it?
Jesus!
Stop being an archaeologist
for a minute here...
and start being
a human being!
Look, she's right,
okay?
We have to look
for help!
Maybe we can try the shaft.
Nora!
Look at her face!
We don't know
what's up there!
Look, guys, we can't
just sit around here.
Okay, we've got
things up there
scratching people's faces.
It stinks in here!
So put your mask
back on.
No, I'm serious, man.
Listen...
if we can survive this drop
then so can it.
Whatever it is.
And while we're
trapped in here
we're like food
in a bowl right now.
All right, fine.
There. You got it?
I got it.
Let's go over here.
Yeah, we're fine.
Okay, one more.
Ready? One, two...
Oh, God.
I don't know
if it's safe in there.
For all we know
that air could be...
Yeah, we'll take
our chances.
If you ask me, it's
not gonna be any worse...
than the air
we're breathing in here.
Yeah.
Hey.
You take it.
No. Mmm-mmm.
No. What, you want
to sit here in the dark?
No.
And besides,
if we get lost
then maybe we can
follow the light back.
Okay?
You're not gonna
need the hatchet,
but it's just in case.
I'm gonna go get
you help, okay?
I'm gonna
come back for you.
Hey, listen.
It's that soldier!
What's his name?
Shadid!
- Shadid!
- Shadid, help us!
- Hello!
- We're right over here!
Shadid!
Where's it coming from?
Uh, can't tell.
Did you guys
hear that?
Help me! Help me!
What's happening to him?
You guys, that's not Shadid.
That's Michael.
Michael!
You should go!
Go, go!
Find Shadid!
Nora, wait!
Shouldn't we
just go with them?
How are we supposed
to find Shadid?
Hello?
Shadid!
Are you still there?
Michael.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no-
No, this isn't happening.
No!
Okay.
No, this is
not possible.
I think we have
to get out of here.
No, no, no.
- It's not safe.
- No, where is he?
No, no...
No, it's not happening. No.
Nora.
I don't believe it.
Nora, Nora.
No, I...
Honey, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I know you cared for him,
but we have to go.
Michael...
I'm so sorry.
Honey, we have to go.
Michael!
We have to join
the others, okay?
I can't...
Okay, honey, you've got
to focus now.
We got to get out
of this pyramid.
It's not safe for us.
Come on.
Where did he go?
Okay, come on.
Come on.
I can't.
We should never
have followed them.
What's taking them
so long?
Should we go back there?
Shadid!
Shadid, can you hear us?
All right.
What happened
to Zahir?
Zahir is dead.
He tried to
shift the boulder.
It rolled over
and crushed him.
That's impossible.
We couldn't shift
that thing
between the four of us!
I don't know.
I think he was
chipping away at it
with the hatchet.
Oh, that's
a load of bull.
We heard the screams.
If there's anything
we've learned today
it's that you're talking
out of your ass.
No,
she's right, yeah.
You're lying to us.
What about the eyes I saw
at the top of the tunnel?
Whatever took a chunk
out of my face killed Zahir!
Calm down, lady. Oh,
don't tell me to calm down!
I'm sorry...
but robot guy
has just been devoured...
by a creature we cannot
identify, for Christ's sake!
"Calm down."
Who the hell
do you think...
Nobody made you come!
My job is to follow
you guys with the camera.
What, are you just
following orders now?
Step up and take
responsibility
for your own actions!
Hey! Back off!
Keep her away from me!
Back off!
Jesus, Sunni, relax.
Don't tell me to relax!
This asshole has led us
into a death trap!
I don't need
this right now.
Look, Sunni,
all right?
You're panicking
and you're freaking out!
You're just looking for
someone to blame right now.
Oh, I found him.
Well, that attitude
is not going to help us out
right now, is it?
All right, just relax.
Come on,
just breathe.
I'm sure we can find
a way out of here.
What we need to do
is to find Shadid.
He got in here,
we can get out.
Yeah.
How's that?
Yeah, great.
What's up?
No, it was nothing.
Come on, Fitzie,
you go first.
What?
Me?
Yes.
What am I,
a bloody guinea pig?
Oh, for God's sake.
Are you seeing
how tight this is?
Just go.
Bloody hell.
Are you sure
this is the way?
Can't be sure
of anything in this place.
So...
remind me again, guys,
what do I do if this
thing jumps out at me...
and scratches my face off?
You try to put as much distance
as you can between you and it.
Right, this is probably about
as fast as I can move right now.
Just move faster, Fitzie!
I don't want to be here
long enough to find out!
Guys.
- Guys?
- Yeah.
Something's behind us!
What do we do?
- Keep going!
- Just move! Move!
Just move, Fitzie! Move!
Go! Go! Go!
Go as fast
as you can, Fitzie!
It's coming faster!
Shit.
- Oh, God!
- Don't stop.
Oh, God. Oh, my God!
There's something here.
Shit!
Keep going.
It's coming faster!
Oh, guys, the soldier's here!
It's Shadid.
Where the hell
did he come from?
Hurry up, Fitzie!
Keep moving. Keep moving.
Come on. Come on.
Get back.
Everybody, get back!
Get back!
Jesus.
What the hell was that?
Oh, my God.
Holy shit!
Lights! Fitzie!
Come on.
Turn it off.
Kill the light!
- We should...
- No, no, no.
Just don't move a muscle.
Fitzie, shut up.
We should be very quiet.
What the fuck
was that?
I have no idea.
Did you see
the claws on that thing?
What the hell
is going on down here?
All right.
Don't go too close.
Is it gone?
Whoa, Sunni, that scratch
is becoming really infected.
Your eye is not looking
too good, either.
We need to find
an exit right now.
Please tell me there is
something on this wall...
that explains how
to get out of here...
or at least what the
bloody hell is after us.
This panel depicts
the final judgment,
the weighing of souls.
What?
It's from the
Egyptian Book of the Dead.
When a person died,
they passed into a room.
They were brought before
Osiris and a panel of judges.
And next to them
was a massive scale.
Then the god Anubis
weighed their heart
against Maat,
the goddess of truth.
And if it balanced
perfectly,
they passed
into the afterlife.
They believed
they were sent to the sky
to dwell among the stars.
I thought
the Book of the Dead
was just full of spells
and incantations.
No,
it's more than that.
It's a guide
to immortality.
This was central
to Egyptian philosophy.
This is the final milestone.
What, and you believe
in this rubbish, do you?
They believed it.
I think the priests
acted out this ritual.
None of this matters
unless we get out of here.
We've got to go.
Let's go! Let's go.
What do you see?
It's a dead end.
Fuck!
What was that?
I thought you said
don't touch anything.
What now?
What...
We'll get buried
if we don't go!
Come on!
Go, go, go!
- Nora!
- I'm trying!
Nora.
Nora, come on!
- Come on!
- Dad, I can't move!
I'm stuck!
Guys!
Dad!
Help!
Whoa!
Guys, I'm stuck! Help!
All right. Give us...
Sunni!
Oh, God!
Oh, my God! Sunni!
Come on.
Give me your hand.
Give me your hand. Come on!
Just pull! Wiggle your legs!
God!
I'm gonna help you!
I'm gonna get you!
Guys!
Shit!
No!
No, no, no, no! Don't!
Sunni!
Guys!
Oh, God! No!
Help! We need your help!
Oh, God.
Get away!
Please... Sunni...
Help!
Dad!
Give me your hand.
Give me your hand!
Help me.
Just don't...
Keep at it!
Dad!
You're doing great.
Come on. Give me...
Dad!
Wiggle your legs!
Come on, honey!
You have to keep squirming!
Nora!
Sunni!
I'm gonna get you! Guys!
Right there.
Come on. Come on.
Come on,
and give me your hand!
Come on! Come on, Nora!
Hold on! Nora!
Got it! God...
Come on. I got your hand.
I got you, I got you.
Aah!
Pull!
I am...
Nora...
Thank God. Thank God.
Oh, God!
Fitzie!
Doctor!
Jesus. Oh, my God.
Okay!
Come here, guys.
Fitzie, get on the corner.
Take the rope.
I'm gonna throw it to you.
All right?
- Get the end. You got it?
- Yes!
Great.
Sunni, just hold on,
we're coming
right down, all right?
Watch out!
Wait.
Be careful.
Grip tight.
Grip tight. Grip tight.
That's right.
You're doing great.
Oh, Jesus. She's...
Here, here.
Okay-
Lift up...
Right there, okay.
Is that better?
Is that better? Okay.
Just try not to
breathe so hard,
all right?
Long breaths, yeah.
Ow!
Nora. Come on,
change places with me.
Cradle her head.
Okay. Okay.
Just take her head.
Aah!
Oh, God.
We're gonna get you
out of here, okay?
- Right, guys?
- Let's do it.
All right,
we're gonna get you off, Sunni.
Okay, you got her legs?
Yeah, yeah.
I got her shoulders.
Okay.
Pull straight up,
all right?
On the count of three.
One...
two...
three.
Pull.
Come on!
Stop! Stop, stop!
Okay, okay, okay.
It's not working.
If we lift her off,
she's gonna bleed out.
Okay, okay.
HOLDEN; Shit!
- Okay, let's try again.
- No.
No! She can't take it.
Just give her a second,
all right.
Oh, God.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Jesus. Jesus.
Hold her.
Hold her, hold her.
Oh, my God!
Sunni! I'm trying!
Hold her! Hold her!
I'm trying!
Hold her! Hold her still!
I can't, I can't!
She can't twist!
Hold her!
I can't!
She's gone into...
Okay.
Oh, God.
Sunni?
Oh, my God.
I think I can
get her leg off.
I think if I just
get her leg off,
then we can get her
out of here.
Fitzie, that's it.
Oh, my God.
No. No, no, no.
We need to get her off.
Oh, my God.
Those creatures
can come back at any minute.
We have to go now.
Dad?
Your neck.
Oh, shit, is that...
Like the digger!
Probably.
- Just...
- What?
But why has it
appeared now?
The masks
stopped the onset.
For some reason,
the progress has been slowed.
Why didn't you
say anything?
What difference
does it make?
If I'm infected, we all will be.
It doesn't...
Sorry.
Okay, we got to get
out of here right now.
Well, that's
our only choice.
You okay, Fitzie?
Yeah.
All right.
Those things...
I think they're Sphynx cats.
Like the statue?
The ancient Egyptians
believed that cats,
like Bastet...
were the guardians
of the underworld.
They could have
been placed here
to protect whomever
was buried in here.
All right, this way.
How have they
survived all this time
without any food or water?
I think
they ate each other.
Each generation
feeding the next.
Like, uh, rats.
Great,
so to survive down here,
you have to resort
to cannibalism.
That would explain
the air toxicity.
Okay, I see
an opening overhead.
Fitzie,
bring your camera here,
I need the light.
How can we
possibly be back here?
It's a labyrinth.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's just think
this through logically.
All right,
we can't go that way,
that's a sand trap.
And we know that
that's a dead end.
But Corporal Shadid
got in here somehow,
so there has to be
a way out.
How can we...
Look.
Shorty.
You know, this antenna
might still be
broadcasting a signal
to the outside.
Well, what are you thinking?
Hold on one second.
I can rewire
my camera to it
and we can record
a message...
and send it to one of
the outside monitors.
Well, will that work?
It's worth a shot.
I mean...
I can't guarantee
anyone's gonna see it,
but, it'd improve our odds.
What's that?
Ah.
- Look. Ah.
- Brilliant.
Okay, so, uh,
be quick, Doctor.
I'm not sure how long this
aerial battery's gonna last
And also, you know,
the cat creatures.
Hopefully someone
will bother to play back
these tapes
when they find our gear.
If they find it.
My name is Dr. Miles Holden.
And I was a professor
at Princeton University.
I am trapped in the excavation
site with my daughter...
Dr. Nora Holden,
and cameraman
Terry Fitzsimmons.
And we need help.
Two of our team members,
engineer Michael Zahir...
and documentary filmmaker
Sunni Marshe, are dead.
This pyramid, unlike any other
structure I've ever encountered...
seems to have been built
with the express purpose...
of keeping whatever
is inside from escaping.
If you come down here,
bring guns.
Is that good?
Yeah, it was good.
It was really good.
Did you feel that?
Yeah.
Huh?
Oh, wow.
It's like a vacuum
pulling the air out.
What is it?
I think something's
back there.
I think it's a way out.
How do you know that?
I don't.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Careful, Doc.
Remember the last time
you started touching things.
Whoa!
How did you
find that?
I didn't spend my entire life
behind a desk, you know.
Creepy stuff.
Do you think
Shadid came this way?
I do.
This doesn't
look like the Egypt stuff
you find at
the British Museum,
eh, guys?
This possibly
could be a link
to an older civilization.
So, um...
how are you feeling, Doc?
I want to
get out of here.
Oh, yeah.
What?
Do you, um...
I mean, do you feel
any sicker or...
You know what?
I really haven't
had that much time
to think about it.
Mmm.
Oh, man.
Whoa.
So...
Ugh.
From the shitty room
to the kitty tomb...
that, you know,
also smells like shit.
You think this was built
to be some sort of prison,
then, Doc?
Oh, well, many temples
in the ancient world...
were thought to be the earthly
dwelling places of the gods.
Some were benign
and giving.
Others, like the gods
the Aztecs worshipped,
were violent.
They were imprisoned...
and then they were
fed a steady diet
of human sacrifice
to appease them.
Thousands were sacrificed.
As their hearts
were cut out...
their bodies were kicked down
the pyramid steps.
So, what's your point?
Whatever
we're dealing with,
it's not benign
and giving.
Let's go deeper
into this hellhole.
Make it completely impossible for
them to discover our bodies.
Oh, shit.
I think we found
the bottom of the pyramid.
Well...
now we just
have to find...
the right escape shaft.
- Dad?
- Huh?
Dad?
What?
Jesus.
Well, well, well, well.
We were not
the first ones here.
What happened
to him?
Shit.
Shit, look at that.
Hey, hey.
What?
- That's a Freemason symbol.
- Huh.
They must've built the offshoot
tunnel that we entered.
Yeah, it makes sense.
All right,
yeah, this is all
very interesting...
but our main priority should
be getting out of here.
The Masons
aren't important.
They were
excellent tomb robbers.
If they couldn't
find a way out...
Shit.
What?
I can't read this.
What is that?
Here, give it to me.
Guys, can we drop the history
crap for five minutes, please...
and get out of here?
Just read it!
It's a journal.
Fitzie, I need your light.
"May 21st, 1897.
"The path we took
upon our entry
"into the pyramid
has been blocked.
"We may have located
"a means of escape
in the burial chamber."
That's the last entry.
And this looks like
the burial chamber to me.
All right. Well, then...
there might be
a means of escape!
You're right.
We have to keep going.
We don't want to end up...
- Dad! Dad!
- Nora! Run!
Nora! Let's go!
No! I have to go
back for him!
No, we can't!
I have to go back!
I'm sorry,
we've got to go!
Keep going!
Oh, my God!
What? No!
No! No!
Oh, my God.
I can't...
He's gone.
There must be
some sort of latch...
or mechanism
that your dad found.
I don't know.
I don't...
You know what?
Screw it.
I'd rather face him
once and for all
than spend the rest
of my life running.
Are you out of your mind?
Nora, come on.
Look at all this shit
we've been through!
Someone will find
our tapes.
The least I can do
is let people know
who killed me.
What is wrong with you?
My dad just died and all you
care about is getting your shot.
It's not about
the shot, Nora.
I just don't know
what else to do.
Fitzie,
please don't leave me.
Fitzie, please...
Fitzie...
Oh, God.
Help!
Oh, he's still alive.
Help... Help, help...
No...
Nora.
It's me.
This isn't real.
No, this can't be happening.
It's impossible.
It's Anubis,
or the Devourer.
He took my father's heart
to weigh his soul.
What are you
talking about?
Anubis, half man,
half jackal.
He ate the hearts of those
he found to be impure.
In the Book of the Dead...
the Last Judgment
is the final gate
before resurrection
or damnation.
If there's a way out,
it's inside that room.
We don't have a choice.
We can either stay here
and die, or we...
Or we can die trying.
Oh, God,
it's the soldier.
Come on, Nora.
I'm so sorry, Dad.
Grab his flare.
Wait.
It tells the story of Osiris.
Osiris. No, no, no.
You said Anubis.
Osiris was his father...
or his creator.
It's the same symbol
for both words.
Egyptians believe Osiris
came from the heavens...
and brought agriculture
and tool-making...
I get that you find
this stuff fascinating, okay?
But right now
what we should be
working on is
how to get out of here.
That's what
I'm trying to tell you.
Osiris knew that his time
had come on Earth...
so he had
this pyramid built
for his journey
into the afterlife.
Nora, I promise you,
look...
I've got it all
down on tape. All right?
You can watch it back
as soon as we're out.
Anubis turned his wrath
on the people.
He had hundreds
of them sacrificed...
so he could join his father
in the afterlife.
Since his soul
was corrupted,
he was looking
for a pure one...
a pure heart, if you will.
The only way to enter
the final gate of heaven.
My father was right.
This pyramid
became a prison.
Closed by the Egyptians
to get rid of their own god.
Nora, does this thing
give us any clues
on how to get out of here?
It says something
about a star map.
Then you got
to find it, okay?
Because your friend Anubis is
gonna be back any minute now!
The exit shaft
points to where the dead
was supposed to be
resurrected.
Well, then...
There must be at least
six shafts in this room.
How do we know
which is the right one?
The stars...
Look at the ceiling.
Fitzie,
turn off your light.
Look at the ceiling.
In between the hieroglyphs,
all those dots.
That's the star map!
So what exactly
are we looking for?
The tetrahedron.
The three-sided
pyramid is also
the hieroglyphic symbol
for the Sirius star.
Look! There it is.
The brightest one.
It's right above
this shaft.
It's got to be our way out!
Okay. Well, let's go
check it out.
Okay. Come on!
It's got to be the one.
Look! The rope.
That's got to be
how the soldier entered.
Ah. Thank you,
Captain Egypt.
You think that thing
will hold us both?
I guess we have to see.
Okay-
All right, you go first.
Here, take this.
Just in case.
I'll be right behind you.
Okay, hold that.
Okay-
You okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Try and get
your leg up on that ledge.
Can't be much further now.
Shit! He's back!
Go, Nora! Go!
Don't look back!
Fitzie, keep going!
Don't look down!
Shit, he's back!
Go, Nora! Go! Go! Go!
Come on, Fitzie, move!
I'm coming!
Move! Move!
Go on!
Come on, Fitzie!
You can keep going!
Come on! Don't look down!
Climb!
Fitzie!
Help! Help!
No!
Aah!
Fitzie.
No!
Ah...
Yeah...
Help me.
Help, please...
Please help me.
The only thing
My silhouette
I meet my fate
with every breath
My heart escapes
Rising through a hole
in the ceiling
Disintegrate
The body that I'm holding
I will sacrifice
more than a thousand lives
My soul won't be crucified
I'll come back
with light shining
Whoa, whoa, whoa
Get back what
you took from me
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey
Get back what
you took from me
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Prepare my grave
For what I know,
it's waiting
I welcome in
All that I am fearing
There's no way out
Now I must shed my skin
The only way through
the flame of fire within
I will sacrifice
More than a thousand lives
My soul won't be crucified
Get back what
you took from me
Me...
In the dark there is light
In the day there is night
In the peace there is fight
I started a war
In the dark there is light
In the day there is night
In the peace there is fight
I started a war
In the dark there is light
In the day there is night
In the peace there is fight
I started a war
In the dark there is light
In the day there is night
In the peace there is fight
I started a war
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org