Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Come on.
- I am coming.
There you can see it clearly.
How far is it?
- Up to the top.
I'm tired.
We are almost there.
Wait till you see the view.
Are you up?
- Yes.
You're right.
It's beautiful.
We should bring a blanket.
Brett, I said that we have a blanket
should have brought.
Brett?
Brett, for God's sake!
Luke.
- How are you, Simon?
I'm not surprised to see you here.
Dito.
Who found it?
- Two festival goers.
They fell into a crack in the ground.
The police found them only after a week.
What happened?
- The boy was killed instantly.
The girl has been there for five days.
She died when they found her.
My God.
Michael.
Michael, keep up with it.
My God...
Michael, sit.
Do not move.
My God.
You had an accident.
I will notify an ambulance.
Do not move.
How is she?
- There are still testing.
But you have not so severe her
wonder if you thought.
That is impossible.
I know how hard I hit her.
She just has a cut on her head
and some scratches. No serious injuries.
But she is unconscious.
- No, she sleeps.
All results are fine.
She's a little disoriented.
Her short-term memory may be confused,
but there is no reason to keep her here.
You let her go?
- I'll see her in my practice.
I can not just leave.
Who will look after her?
I'm not leaving until I know her name.
- Cassie Grant.
Michael ...
The figure of Christ stands with his back to the church.
That's true.
That seems completely opposite.
This is a significant discovery, Luke.
I know.
I'm surprised you visited me.
Simon San Severa is a long time ago.
- Two years.
You were not my first choice.
The building itself is made of stone and clay.
This church was built in
the first century.
And the altar?
The altar from the same period.
It is unusual for a Crucifixion
seen from behind the cross.
Now it's destroyed.
- How fast?
I should be as fast as possible in all
card can bring.
When can you start?
- From the moment that I have a team.
Professor Kirkman, I prefer that you
only works at this time.
We believe that it is better
that as few people as possible outside the church ...
be aware of the works.
As long as it falls under our responsibility ...
we want to make our own analyzes.
And not press.
- We will cooperate in every way.
We will do everything necessary is provided.
Are you sure about this?
- It's the least I can do.
We still have too much space.
You can as long as necessary to.
You do not remember why you
went to Ashby Wake?
No. I need to know people here.
Sorry. It's all
still unclear.
Doktor Byworth said you confused yet
could have been in the beginning.
Ashby is a small village.
Someone will recognize you.
Michael is quiet.
- Yes.
How do you know his name?
You've probably already mentioned.
- Of course.
We are here.
This is Emma.
Hi Emma. I'm Cassie.
This is a great house.
We did it a year ago
bought, just after our marriage.
I am their stepmother.
But I must still work.
You have lots of beautiful objects.
That's my husband, Simon.
He is the expert in that area.
Your calm down.
I put some tea.
- I will help you.
What about that girl?
- Cassie?
I could do nothing else.
Imagine that I had slain her.
That would have been awful.
I was paralyzed.
I thought she was dead.
I have no idea what I
would have done.
Fortunately, we can help her.
She is almost all her belongings.
We can at least give her a bed.
Hey. How do you feel today?
- Much better, thanks.
I hope you do not mind.
I made breakfast for the children.
I showed her everything.
- You do not have to do this.
I do not mind.
Mrs. Groves there?
I've got a meeting in Oxford.
- I can take the kids to school.
It does not though.
- I want to do it with pleasure.
You do not know where the school is.
- Emma can show me.
Michael, how do you like your eggs?
Beaten or not?
He's a silent one.
If they do something weird here? She
mix with jam or something.
Thank you.
Hi.
- Sorry.
Most of the damage was caused by ...
salt which is in the building itself.
Especially the right are images
affected by it.
There are a lot of bumps and dirt
in most others ...
but it is remarkable, is not it?
Joseph of Arimathea.
He was at the crucifixion ...
and later went to England.
With the spear that wounded Jesus.
And?
He built a church in Glastonbury.
A Romanesque church of the first century.
Probably this.
That is possible.
- It is probable.
You know what we're watching
if we look at the altar?
A relic of the Crucifixion
of a person who was present.
Cassie, I made this for you.
I saw two people following me
known for coming.
I think they have recognized me, but
I have no idea who they were.
That happens to me all the time.
Headache?
- No.
Something else?
When I saw people,
it felt weird.
I do not think you worry
must make.
You've had a stroke. It takes
while before everything is back in order.
Ok?
Yes. Thanks.
Where did you find that?
- Is this yours? Did you write this?
- Yes.
- "A study of the faith."
It's about my work.
- I thought you restored art?
I will. I find out where the
comes from and whether it is authentic.
And that causes a lot of noise.
And it keeps me busy.
- For a long time.
It's nice to have you here.
- It's fine here.
The kids are very sweet.
Have you previously been babysitting?
- Not that I know.
Do you remember anything from your family?
No not yet.
There I also take a glass.
- Excuse me.
How long have you lived here?
- A year.
Emma was born in Ashby Wake.
She was nine when we came here.
We thought it a good place
was to make a new start.
The children have had a difficult time.
- Michael was four when his mother died.
Sorry.
- She had a long illness.
It was bad for Michael.
He took it hard on himself.
It was hard to see him suffer.
Idiot.
Everything alright?
I know you. Not true?
You do not recognize me?
- Yes, it does.
At the school.
- Exactly.
From where in the US you just come?
- Midwest.
I stay here with family.
I got hit by a car
a few days ago.
You hit?
- Yes.
Apparently I'm fine.
I just have a concussion.
Ocharme. That should be a huge
shock have been for you.
You stay in Ashby Wake?
- On the outside of the city.
Big house? With ma? Svelden?
- Yes that is it.
Do you live around here?
- I have not decided.
I like this region.
I'm looking for something to Stukeley Hill.
The report shows an unusually low pH value
and high salt concentrations in the ground.
This could damage the walls.
- I know that. I wrote that report.
What is interesting is that the land in 1200
years after the construction of the church has been.
That's not in your report.
This church was buried deliberately
around the time of the plague.
Luke, we've known each other long.
Why do you want to keep this secret?
There are things we still
do not understand.
If the church deliberately buried,
then there must have been a reason.
No!
Michael?
Was that you?
Are you weeping?
Can not sleep?
Tie a good dog.
Just like the ones outside of barks.
You heard it, right?
And the kids?
Have you heard them?
It's all right.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Ms. Groves?
Know someone who kind of a
pitbull dog is?
What pitbull?
- I do not know.
A caramel brown.
One with a very large head.
I've seen him here on the domain.
- A dog, I have not seen in a long time.
Where are the children?
I am almost finished.
How was the mother of Michael and Emma?
- Caroline? She was a treasure.
A good mother.
It's not about me ...
but it soon marry again has
the children no favors.
That should have brought them upset.
- Not as hard as when they moved here.
They should not buy this.
Would you call them in?
Michael? Emma?
You would not think straight.
Michael?
Everything is fine.
A journalist tries to reach the bishop.
Nobody should talk to the press.
No. Do you think I was?
No of course not.
- Yes.
Did you do it?
You still think you
was right, right?
About San Severa.
I just told the truth.
Like you saw. You undermined
people's faith ...
who were told that a piece of wood ...
- A holy relic.
A 19th century piece of driftwood
was a piece of the Holy Cross.
And they believed it was sacred.
I'm just ge Interested in fact.
- I know that.
I know that.
What we have here is authentic.
This may come in the newspapers.
This is the oldest crucifixion
we have thus far.
That's not what it is.
Aristobulus, a British bishop,
wrote a series of letters.
He was in Glastonbury,
in the first century, is not it?
Aristobulus mentions a church
founded by Joseph of Arimathea ...
and in the same letter, there is a footnote ...
where many people disagree about.
"They just came to watch ...
from the east and the west,
from the cities and the countryside.
They were not worshiping the Lord ...
but from desire. "
Your Latin is better than mine.
"They just came to watch.
Not out of adoration, but of desire. "
I think the bas-relief? F
it has to face.
In the course of time are
there have always been people ...
which just go to the show
came to watch.
People troepten together at the guillotines
during the French Revolution.
Masses that show up at the hanging
of the prisoners of Newgate.
People camping at a prison
before they turn on the switch.
But it remains a crucifixion.
A little unorthodox, but ...
It is not just a crucifixion.
It's not about Christ, Simon.
It's about the people who came to watch.
Alstubieft.
- Thank you.
Good morning.
Michael?
Sweetheart?
It's all right. He
you can not do anything.
Come on.
Come on, let's move on.
That looks like fun.
Michael!
I will see that they can do nothing.
I promise.
I am fine.
- I will let anything happen to you.
I promise.
- I am fine.
I'm sorry, Dan. I know no one
else I can address.
Cassie, what is it?
In recent days I have
of those ...
I do not know how to call them.
Images. Hallucinations.
I see horrible things.
And then I'm not sure
or I they really have seen.
You have been hit by a car.
But it's so real.
I am afraid that his characters.
For Signs? What?
I do not know.
You know what they mean?
- I have no idea.
How do I know if they are going to come true
if I'm not sure what they mean?
I will help you.
I feel so lonely.
You're not alone, Cassie.
You are not alone.
The dog barked like crazy to us
from the trunk of the car.
That guy just stared at Michael.
It was horrible.
There's only one ?? garage.
We'll stop there.
That is it.
That is certainly the car.
What are you doing?
Can I help you?
Can you tell me
Who is this car?
Why do you want to know that?
- I would not want to buy m.
He is not for sale.
He ?? one of my mechanics.
Is he here?
- No.
We get his number?
He has no phone.
- His address then.
Tine Cottage. Longridge Road.
His name is Argyle.
Jesus.
So that's that dog?
Yes, that's him.
In England, calls this burglary.
I'm nothing to break.
My God, look at this mess.
This is sad.
LOCAL ANGLER WINS
NATIONAL COMPETITION
My God, I know these people.
Then, I know these people.
That's my doctor from the hospital.
Come on, let's go.
That is Limecourt.
LIME INVESTIGATION INTO COURT
WILL BE OPENED
In the 60s it was a Limecourt
Children stay. A church residence.
They have been indicted for
child abuse.
What's new about that?
Come now, Cassie. We really have to go.
My God, they were all
involved with the case.
All these people.
Child abuse
Everyone must know.
The whole town must know.
He's on Lime Court.
He must have lived there.
My God. Then, that's Michael.
He has a picture of Michael.
Why does he have it?
I do not know.
Let's get out of here.
Wait.
My God, Dan.
You've seen it there.
This guy is obviously crazy.
I saw a pathetic life.
- We go to the police.
To tell what? That he
Photos of Michael?
Yes! And what about all those other pictures?
He sees himself in Michael as a child.
He wants to be clear from there.
?? In one of my ...
- Visions?
Yes, see in one of my visions ??
I Michael with a maimed face.
You can not go to the police
go and tell.
We have to do something.
Jesus.
Why do we seek not before
we proceed to drastic means?
... And all that happiness so early
piece is beaten.
Jackie went with him still on
his last political trip.
In Dallas he stayed with governor
Connally ...
and Vice President Lyndon Johnson,
who is also from Texas.
In which state are
Democrats unpopular.
But the charm of the Kennedys
turns out to be positive.
It was closed after all the noise.
It was scrapped.
And then bought Mrs. Kirkman
it and put it in order.
Did you come here earlier?
Did you know the priest who was in charge?
That does not matter.
It's all over now.
Nobody wants it back rake.
It seems to me that someone must have known
what was going on.
Cassie, nothing has been proven.
There were some rumors.
And it was bad. Terrible.
But it's over.
... But the safety standards are
changed compared to the early years.
The controversy surrounding the
Measures taken ...
... who were insolent and
often posed for the camera.
How many people have seen this suffering
have is unknown.
He's dangerous.
I think he wants revenge.
On whom he wants revenge?
- I do not know.
The people who hurt him.
Possibly the whole city.
- The whole town?
He is obsessed with a child
I pass on. Michael.
And why he wants to hurt this child?
- I do not know.
Because of his youth.
The way he was abused.
Do you have a name for this person?
- Frederick Michael Argyle.
Fred?
You do not have to worry about Fred.
Everybody in Ashby Wake knows Fred.
You'll find this funny?
What's going on here?
I fear that without proof
can not do much.
Stunning. Thank you.
And from the 19th century this male
figure on the right.
A close up of his face.
The figure of the bas-relief? F.
Here we look at the face of
the older woman in the background.
This is the close up of her face.
And again the same face on the bas-relief? F.
We must bury it.
Is not that too drastic?
I think we are all in agreement
are. As from the time of the discovery ...
and in memory of two young people.
However, this discovery is not
surprise for the scientists among us.
You're not the first to adopt
that these figures over and over again ...
appear in places with human suffering.
It has been documented
by certain Catholics.
And we must not forget that the church
already once been buried.
Bishop, forgive me, but the church
break off, even stone by stone,
will these tragedies
not prevent.
That is quite true.
Nothing on earth can.
But we can make sure that ...
which is not a place
of superstition and fear.
If people have to deal with it
calamity that could possibly happen ...
they go that which is good
lose sight of .
Can you handle this
Professor Kirkman?
Yes, I will be there tomorrow
right to drive.
Frederick Michael Argyle.
- Fred?
Everybody in Ashby Wake knows Fred.
He has a picture of Michael.
Why would he do this child pain?
- He wants to get rid of this child.
You do not have to worry about Fred.
Do not!
Please!
I will teach you, Argyle.
You were again walking around.
But always making noise, Argyle.
- No, please!
Furthermore you. You will remain in that room.
No!
Michael?
Take a deep breath.
It's all right.
- I heard voices.
I heard them dear.
What is going on? Michael?
He had a nightmare.
- It's all right. It's just a storm.
I'll take him.
- It's okay Michael.
Go with Marion.
Michael open this done?
Yes, he ...
Simon, where are these photos?
That's my job.
You have to tell me.
From where are these photos?
They are of an altar,
a bas-relief? f I'm working on.
But I've seen these people.
Here in Ashby Wake.
No, they are a work of art.
A very old art.
I've seen these people in your city.
- What are you saying?
It here.
And this one.
That's enough.
Please go to bed, Cassie.
My God...
Ladies and gentlemen.
Here is the mayor.
I will just say that I
am very excited to be here ...
and I with great joy
this carnival to declare open.
Wait for me.
- Walk.
To the fastest.
Yes, certainly.
Thanks. Day.
Luke Fraser died
in a car accident.
He was on his way to me.
The car did a somersault
and he died instantly.
I have to go.
The bishop asked to see me.
You wait here?
- Of course.
I'm thankful for you
conscientiousness, professor Kirkman.
It's a huge blow.
Luke was a remarkable man.
Yes.
There are things you to
my opinion is yet to see.
Aristobulus called it "the meeting".
The people who do not attend the
crucifixion came to honor ...
but to watch.
"They came from the east and the west,
not worship, but out of desire. "
Indeed.
In the church's tradition one goes there
from the meeting is cursed.
Enchanted by the darkness,
so that their members were doomed ...
eternally to witness
human misery.
The first World War.
The explosion of the first atomic bomb.
The barbaric lynching
of a person.
I have compromised your faith?
No, I am not religious.
- You believe in science.
Do you have a phone?
- Yes.
I know who these people are.
They are now here.
Cassie, look at me.
See my legs.
Look at me.
Cassie, look.
- Come on, let's go.
They are here.
Ms. Groves?
- Do you want a balloon?
Do you want to fit as them?
- I do not know about.
This is very important.
Cassie, where are the kids?
- They're over there with Mrs Groves.
Simon said that we were in danger.
You have to believe me.
Bring the kids out of here.
Look who's here.
It is Actionman.
Nice to see you again come around, Freddie.
What you got there?
Weather on rabbit hunting?
Damn!
You two!
And where are you now?
No, I've never done.
Hello, stranger.
Cassie ...
- Stay away from me.
Who are you?
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a skulptuur
that was created 2,000 years ago.
I have tonight images
seen. I've seen you.
You stood by.
Yes.
What does it mean?
Who are you?
You should not have gone to the police.
I did try to warn you.
You could get out of it,
and I could not admit.
There was a cop here. Where is he?
Right behind you.
My God.
Frederick, what brings you here?
It all began 2000 years ago.
A crucifixion on the hill.
We went to look.
But we were punished.
Unfairly in my opinion.
Curiosity is a natural thing.
You knew it all the time in Argyle.
- Just like you.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to hurt you.
I would never do.
You know something is going to happen.
That's why you're here.
You're one of us, Cassie.
You just forgot.
We are previously condemned
always come back and watch.
And that's what happened.
Through the years we experienced
we could make us useful.
We can make sure that everything
in order for what must happen.
Ensure that there is nothing in the way.
- That's pathetic. That is obscene.
People see suffering and
there get a kick out of.
No, there's no rush.
We can not prevent
what is going to happen, Cassie.
Walk to the pump, Dan.
There is nothing you can do.
A warm welcome for doctor Byworth.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Can you help me?
Can you help me push?
Sure.
- On the backside.
Are you done?
- Yes.
Can you start the engine?
- Faster.
Uncoupling.
- You're going to hit the wall!
My God.
- Get out of here!
Walk!
There's a bomb in that car! Walk!
You're a little late. You missed it.
I'm sorry if I blew it.
You do not have to gedaan.Je
seen it, you know it's coming.
He is going to be listed.
He now goes to Michael.
Michael is sitting on a train to London.
Michael join Emma in Lime Court.
Cassie ...
- Do not touch me.
It does not matter.
Marion!
Where is Marion?
- Cassie, is that you?
I can not reach Simon. The train has been canceled
and I thought we'd be safe here.
There is a man there.
- Marion ...
Cassie, take Michael.
Take Michael with you. Loop.
Walk! Come on.
The field.
Have you seen Marion?
Stay here.
Forward.
Marion? My God.
I'll call an ambulance.
The children. I am fine.
Get the kids.
Get the kids. I am fine.
Stay as low as possible.
Cassie!
No, please.
Cassie.
Cassie?
I saw that man to shoot you.
- Yes, he did.
But he can not hurt me.
Nobody can. I'm not like you.
A long time ago there was a
girl on a field outside the city.
And she saw something that was very bad.
She stopped and looked.
That they did not do.
Why not?
- Because it was terrible.
She should stop
or try to help.
She could at least protest,
but she did not.
She just looked.
What has become of her?
She wandered around long.
And she was very unhappy.
But then she learned something important.
Everyone gets a second chance.
You have to seize only they know.
You need to sleep.
- I can not do that.
And what about the voices?
Who are away. You should
not be afraid anymore.
Are you going to stay with me, Cassie?
- No.
You do not need me.
We are both fairly, Michael.
Everthing allright?
Sleeping Time?
Do you want your bear?
Good night.
Translated by: Enigma
http://nlsubs.sucks.nl/
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7trya
Help other users to choose the best subtitles