Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
[CHURCH BELLS RINGING]
[SOBS]
KRALER:
Mr. Frank.
Mr. Frank?
Kraler.
Mr. Kraler.
Miep.
My good friends.
KRALER:
It is so good to see you home.
We had heard nothing.
l'm alone.
MIEP:
You must come home with us.. .
...and rest now.
-You must stay with us.
FRANK: No, l can't stay in Amsterdam.
Mr. Frank, this is your home.
-Amsterdam is your home.
-lt has too many memories.
Everywhere there's something, Miep.
Everywhere.
Even seeing you and Mr. Kraler....
l shouldn't talk to you
like this, after all you did.
Why, we'd do it again.
Everything's gone. The book....
They took everything,
except some papers.
We saved your letters and papers.
FRANK:
Please burn them.
Burn everything.
l told her...
...if l got back here,
l'd find her book.
Anne's diary?
lt's where she left it.
''The 9th of July, 1 942.''
1 942. Is it possible, Miep?
Only three years ago?
''Dear Diary, since you and l
are to be great friends...
...l will start by telling you
all about myself.
My name is Anne Frank.
l am 13 years old.
l was born in Germany,
but since my family is Jewish...
...we emigrated to Holland
when Hitler came to power.
Things went well for us until the war
came and the German occupation.
FRANK AND ANNE:
Then things got very bad for the Jews.''
ANN_: You could not do thís
and you could not do that.
We had to wear yellow stars.
l had to turn ín my bíke.
l couldn't go
to a Dutch school anymore.
l couldn't go to the movíes
or ríde ín an automobíle...
.. .or even on a streetcar.
And a míllíon other thíngs.
But somehow. we chíldren
stíll managed to have fun.
Thís morníng.
Father woke me at 5:OO.. .
.. .and told me to hurry
and get dressed.
We were goíng ínto hídíng.
l was to put on
as many clothes as l could.
lt would look too suspícíous
íf we walked along carryíng suítcases.
We were goíng to dísappear.. .
...vanísh ínto thín aír.
l'm lívíng a great adventure.
Three other people were comíng
ín wíth us. Father knew them.
We had never met them.
-Something's happened.
VAN DAAN: They had a 3 mile walk.
PETER: Mother.
-They've been arrested, l know.
VAN DAAN: Will you stop that?
-Mother. Father.
We're here.
VAN DAAN:
You see?
-Mr. Van Daan.
VAN DAAN: Hello.
-Mrs. Van Daan.
-Mr. Frank.
Peter. There were too many
Green Police on the streets.
We took the long way around.
Did you introduce yourself?
My daughter Anne.
My wife, Edith.
Margot.
Mr. and Mrs. Van Daan.
Oh, and this is our son, Peter.
So, now, please let us take off some
of these clothes.
KRALER: Good morning.
EDITH: Good morning, Mr. Kraler.
FRANK: Morning, Mr. Kraler.
-Mr. Frank.
You're all here. That is good.
-We hoped to have everything in order.
-Please, don't even think of it.
We'll have leisure
to arrange everything ourselves.
-Brought sandwiches for lunch.
-Thank you, Miep.
The canned goods are here,
and your beans and potatoes.
-l'll get you ration books this afternoon.
-Ration books?
lf they see our names on ration books,
they'll know we're here.
Don't worry. It won't be your names
that'll be on them.
[CHURCH BELLS RING]
ANNE: Father! The Westertoren!
-Anne! No!
You must never touch a curtain. Never.
No one must ever touch a curtain,
day or night.
lf someone on the streets should
Iook up or someone should see...
...we would be lost. Remember,
it's not only our lives at stake...
...but Miep's and Mr. Kraler's.
-You have 13 minutes to get settled.
FRANK: Thank you.
Miep or l will be up each day
to bring you food and news.
Come, Miep, we must go.
-Goodbye.
FRANK: Goodbye, Mr. Kraler.
EDITH :
How can we thank you?
l never thought l'd live to see the day
when a man like Mr. Frank...
...would have to go into hiding.
When you think of it....
FRANK: Goodbye.
PETRONELLA: Thank you, Mr. Kraler.
Goodbye.
EDITH: Anne!
-lt's all right, l have on three more.
PETRONELLA:
Excuse me, Mr. Frank.
-What do they mean, ''13 minutes''?
-Before workmen come.
Now...
...while the men are in the building
below, we must be quiet.
Every sound can be heard down there,
in the offices and in the workrooms too.
The men come at about 8:30.
They leave at about 5:30.
So to be perfectly safe,
from 8 a.m. until 6 p.m...
...we must move about up here
only when absolutely necessary...
...and then in stockinged feet.
We must not speak above a whisper
or run any water.
We cannot use the sink or even,
forgive me, the W.C.
The pipes go down through
the workrooms. No trash must ever be--
[SIREN APPROACHING]
[SIREN FADES]
No trash, which might reveal someone's
living here. Not even a potato peeling.
We must burn everything
in the stove at night.
This is the way that we must live
until it is over, if we are to survive.
Until it is over.
After 6:OO, we can move about.
We can talk and laugh...
...have our supper, read, play games,
just as we would at home.
Now it would be wise
if we all went to our rooms...
...and were settled before 8:OO.
Mr. and Mrs. Van Daan, you're upstairs.
l regret there's no place up there
for Peter. But he'll be here, near us.
-And where am l?
-You and Margot will be in there.
PETRONELLA: Excuse me, Mr. Frank.
FRANK: Yes?
PETRONELLA: Where do you sleep?
FRANK: This room is our bedroom.
Oh, no, no. You take the upstairs.
We'll sleep down here.
l've thought this out.
It's the best arrangement.
The only arrangement.
Edith? You must have some rest, dear.
You didn't close your eyes last night.
Now, go in the girls' room.
-Well, how about Anne?
-l feel fine.
l'm going to help Father.
This way, Mrs. Van Daan.
ANNE:
Excuse me.
Up here.
PETER:
Mr. Frank?
-Mr. Frank?
FRANK: Peter?
-l have time to get water for my cat?
ANNE: You've a cat?
Go ahead, but be quick.
-You only have about five minutes.
-He couldn't live without that cat.
l didn't know you had a cat.
l love cats. What's its name?
-Mouschi.
-What is it? Mouschi. A him or her?
-lt's a tom. It doesn't like strangers.
-Then l'll have to stop being a stranger.
-ls he fixed?
PETER: No.
You ought to have him fixed,
to keep him from fighting.
MARGOT :
What a nice cat.
ANNE:
Where do you go to school?
-Jewish Secondary.
ANNE: That's where Margot and l go.
-Yeah, l know.
-l've never seen you around.
-l used to see you sometimes.
-You did?
Why didn't you ever come over?
Oh, l don't know.
l'm sort of a lone wolf.
You can't be a lone wolf here.
l wonder what our friends will say
when we don't show up today.
l had a date with Sanne.
Do you know Sanne de Vries?
-No.
ANNE: Sanne's my best friend.
She's thin like me.
They always yell at us:
''Anne and Sanne,
the skinny bananas. ''
You took off your star.
PETER:
That's right.
ANNE: You can't do that. They'll arrest
you if you go out without your star.
Who's going out?
[PETRONELLA GRUNTS]
-Help me.
-l'm helping.
-What are you going to do with it?
-Burn it.
lt's funny,
l don't think l could burn mine.
-l don't know why.
PETER: You couldn't?
Something they make you wear
so they can kick you around.
l know. But after all...
...it is the Star of David, isn't it?
Annele, it's almost 8:OO.
Don't you wanna sit with us?
It'll be a long day.
No, thanks. This is fine.
You won't forget to take off
your shoes, will you?
Peter.. .
...it's nice to have you with us.
Yes, Mr. Frank.
See you later.
Did you know that he went
to the same school that--?
[CHURCH BELLS RINGING]
ANN_: It's comfortíng that
Mr. Kraler and hís secretary.. .
...are down there below us.
ín the offíce.
Our protectors. we call them.
l asked Father
what would happen to them.. .
.. .íf anyone found out
they were hídíng us.
Father saíd they would suffer
the same fate that we would.
We are over an old spíce factory.
You can smell the spíces
all through the buíldíng.
[YELLING IN DISTANCE]
[BELL RINGS]
[FOOTSTEPS IN DISTANCE]
[BOAT HORN HONKS]
ANNE: l read A Tale of Two Cities
through ín that fírst day.
''lt ís a far. far better thíng l do...
.. .than l have ever done.
lt ís a far. far better rest
that l go to...
.. .than l have ever known.
The end_'
lt was the saddest book l ever read.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[KNOCKS]
KRALER:
It is us, Miep and Kraler.
FRANK: Good evening, Mr. Kraler.
Good evening, Miep.
KRALER:
Good evening, Annele.
-Oh, Mr. Frank.
-Yes?
-This is the box you asked for.
-Thanks.
Oh, my dear friends,
you were all so quiet up here.
-l thought you'd gone out for a walk.
ANNE: Can you imagine me?
l didn't talk.
l hardly moved for one whole day.
Wish they could hear that
at school.
MARGOT: Mouschi!
ANNE: Mouschi!
PETRONELLA: Peter!
VAN DAAN: Peter.
ANNE:
Mouschi.
[MEOWING]
-Annele!
EDITH: Annie!
-Peter, l'm warning you.
FRANK:
Please, quiet. Margot. Margot!
-What are these?
-You don't have to whisper now.
-There you are.
-He's such a nice cat.
PETER: Thank you.
MARGOT: You're welcome.
Annele.
There's a box there.
Will you open it, please?
Know how l'm going
to think of it here?
As a boarding house,
a very peculiar boarding house.
Father, my film stars!
l was wondering where they were.
And Queen Wilhelmina.
How wonderful.
There's something more.
Go on, look further.
A diary.
l've never had a diary.
And l've always wanted one.
A pencil?
l'm going downstairs to get a pencil.
-Anne, no!
-There's nobody down there.
Doesn't matter.
Don't go beyond that door.
-Never?
-Never. l'm sorry, Anne, it isn't safe.
-l see.
FRANK: It'll be hard, l know that.
But always remember
there are no walls, no locks.. .
...no bolts that anyone can put
on your mind.
As a matter of fact,
just between us, Annele...
.. .being here has certain advantages.
For instance.. .
.. .remember that battle
with your mother about overshoes?
You said you'd rather die
than wear overshoes. Remember?
What happened?
In the end, you had to wear them.
Now, for as long as we are here,
you won't have to wear overshoes.
lsn't that good?
And the piano.
You won't have to practice it.
l tell you...
...this is going to be
a fine life for you.
ANN_: It's an odd ídea for someone
líke me to keep a díary.
Mot only because
l have never done so before.. .
.. .but because ít seems to me. neíther l.
nor for that matter anyone else.. .
.. .wíll be ínterested ín the unbosomíngs
of a 13-year-old schoolgírl.
Stíll. what does that matter?
l want to wríte. but more than that...
...l want to bríng out
all kínds of thíngs...
...that líe buríed deep ín my heart.
I
Fírst of all
l expect l should be descríbíng...
...what ít's líke to go ínto hídíng.
But l don't really know yet myself.
l only know ít's funny never
to be able to go outdoors.
Mever to breathe fresh aír.
Mever to run and shout and jump.
Wednesday.
the 23rd of September. 19$2.
The news of the war ís good.
Stalíngrad ís stíll holdíng out.
The Russían offensíve contínues
ín the Moscow area.
-lt's safe now. The last workman has left.
-Whee!
-Anne!
-l'm first for the W.C.
-Six o'clock, Margot. School is over.
-Where are my shoes?
-Have you seen my shoes?
-What shoes?
-You're gonna be sorry.
-l am?
-Annie, dear.
-Wait till l get you.
l'm waiting.
ANNE: Stop! Peter!
-Annie! Peter!
ANNE: Peter, where are you going?
-Gonna give Mouschi his dinner.
-Peter!
EDITH: Annie, dear.. .
...you shouldn't play like that with Pete.
That's not dignified.
Who wants to be dignified?
l don't wanna be dignified!
You complain l don't treat you like
a grownup, but when l do, you resent it.
l only want some fun.
l don't know what's the matter
with that boy.
Give him a little time.
He isn't used to girls.
Time? Isn't two months time?
l could cry.
And what about Miep?
She's usually so prompt.
[SIREN APPROACHING]
[SIREN FADING]
[HUMS]
-Margot, come and dance with me.
-l've got more work to do, Anne.
You know, we're going to forget
how to dance.
When we get out,
we won't remember a thing.
[SINGING]
-Where is Peter?
ANNE: Where would he be? With his cat.
He hasn't finished his lessons, has he?
Peter.
-Peter!
-What is it?
Your mother says to come out.
l'm giving Mouschi his dinner.
You know what your father says
about wasting time with that cat.
-l haven't looked at him since lunch.
-l'm only telling you.
ANNE: l'll feed him.
-You stay out of here. And l mean out.
ls that any way for you
to talk to your little girlfriend?
Mother, l asked you...
-...would you please not say that?
-Look, he's blushing.
-He's blushing.
-Please, l'm not, but--
-Leave me alone.
-Like it's something to be ashamed of.
Nothing to be ashamed of
to have a girlfriend.
That's crazy. She's only 13.
So what? You're 1 6. It's just perfect.
Your father's 10 years older than me.
Mr. Frank, l warn you...
...if this war lasts much longer,
we're gonna be related.
-Mazel tov.
-l haven' t seen my cat since lunch.
l'm giving Mouschi his dinner.
My little Mouschi.
l couldn't live
without my precious Mouschi.
You wonderful cat, you.
PETER: All right, Miss Quack-Quack.
-What's that?
-Miss Quack-Quack!
-You!
You talk so much
they call you Miss Quack-Quack.
You're the most
intolerable boy l ever met!
Quack, quack, quack!
-Quack!
-Ooh!
Anne, dear, you're hot.
-You're warm. Are you all right?
-Mother, please.
-You don't have a fever, do you?
-No.
You know we can't call
a doctor here, ever.
There's only one thing to do,
watch carefully.
Prevent an illness before it comes.
Let me see your tongue.
-Mother, this is perfectly absurd.
-Anne, dear, don't be such a baby.
Let me see your tongue.
Otto.
Anne, you hear your mother,
don't you?
Come on, open up.
Quack.
Annie.
-Otto.
-Anne.
You're all right.
l think there's nothing the matter
with our Anne that a ride on her bike...
...or a visit with her friend
Sanne de Vries wouldn't cure.
lsn't that so, Anne?
ANN_: l keep wíshíng that Peter
was a gírl ínstead of a boy.
Then l'd have someone to talk to.
Wíth all the boys ín the world...
...why díd l have to get locked up
wíth hím?
[EXPLOSlONS IN DISTANCE]
[FAINT FOOTSTEPS]
EDITH: Is it someone?
-ls it Miep?
lt's strange we don't hear.
PETRONELLA: Maybe she got hurt.
-She'll come.
l wish she'd get here.
l'm going crazy without cigarettes.
Anne, you got ''excellent''
in your history paper.. .
-...and ''very good'' in Latin.
-Yes, but how about algebra?
Well, l have a confession to make.
Up until now, l managed
to stay ahead of you in algebra.
Today, you caught up with me.
We'll leave it to Margot to correct.
-lsn't algebra vile, Father?
-Vile.
-How did l do?
-Excellent, of course.
Anne, please.
Your French composition today, Margot,
was just wonderful.
-Mrs. Van Daan, may l try it on?
-No, Annie.
lt's all right, really.
But please be careful with it.
My father gave me this coat
the year before he died.
He always bought me
the best money could buy.
Mrs. Van Daan, did you have a lot of
boyfriends before you were married?
Annie, that's a personal question.
lt's not courteous to ask
personal questions.
l don't mind.
Anneke, our house
was always swarming with boys.
-When l was a young girl--
-Oh, no, not again.
Shut up!
VAN DAAN & PETRONELLA: One summer,
we had a big house in Hilversum.
VAN DAAN:
The boys....
The boys would come buzzing around
like bees around a jam pot.
When l was 17....
Well, we were wearing short skirts then,
and l had such good-looking legs.
l still have. l may not be
as pretty as l used to be...
...but l still have my legs.
How about it, Mr. Frank?
All right, all right.
We see them.
l'm not asking you,
l'm asking Mr. Frank.
-Mother, for heaven sakes.
-Oh, l embarrass you too, do l?
Let me tell you something. l only hope
the girl you marry has as good.
Anneke, my father used to worry
with all the boys hanging around.
And he used to say to me:
''lf any of those boys get fresh,
you just say to him:
'Remember, Mr. So-and-So,
remember, l am a lady#  ''
Look at you,
talking that way with her.
Don't you know she puts it
in her diary?
PETRONELLA: So what if she does?
l'm only telling the truth.
VAN DAAN: Haven't you finished?
-No.
-Oh, the thinker.
VAN DAAN: Leave him alone.
-l'm a dunce. A hopeless case.
PETRONELLA: Don't talk like that.
lt's just you haven't got anyone
to help you...
...like Father helps Anne and me.
But if l--
Well, if we could help....
What about it, Peter?
Would you like to study with us?
Shall we make our school
coeducational?
Thanks, yes.
-Mr. Frank.
FRANK: Yes?
You are an angel,
an absolute angel.
Why didn't l meet you
before l met that one there?
l think it might be better if you went
into your room, Peter, to work.
Excuse me.
Peter, you listen to Mr. Frank.
Mr. Frank is a highly educated man.
VAN DAAN:
It's after 8:OO. Where are they?
-At least one of them should've come.
-They'll come. Don't worry.
Don't tell me.
l know something's wrong.
lsn't it bad enough here
without you sprawling all over?
lf you didn't smoke,
you wouldn't be so irritable.
-Am l smoking?
-You already smoked all the cigarettes.
-Miep only brought me one package.
-lt's a filthy habit...
-...and this is a good time to break it.
VAN DAAN: Oh, stop it. Please.
You're smoking up all our money.
Will you shut up?!
And what are you staring at?
l never heard grownups quarrel like that
before. l thought only children quarreled.
This isn't a quarrel, it's a discussion.
l never heard children so rude before.
-l, rude?
-Yes!
-Annie, drink your milk.
-You've been spoiled.
What you need is a good spanking.
Remember, Mr. So-and-So,
l am a lady.
You're the most aggravating--
Why aren't you nice and quiet.. .
...like your sister, Margot?
Why do you show off all the time?
Let me give you a little advice.
Men don't like that in a girl.
Do you know that?
A man likes a girl who'll listen to him.
A girl who cooks and sews and cleans.
l'd cut my throat first.
l'd open my veins.
l am going to be remarkable.
l'm going to Paris...
-...to study music and art.
-Yeah, yeah.
l'm going to be an actress
or a writer or a dancer.
[GASPS]
-Look what you did.
ANNE: l'm sorry.
You clumsy little fool!
-My father gave me this coat!
-l'm so sorry.
All ruined, and what do you care?
You ruined it!
l could kill you!
l could just kill you!
Petronella.
Petronella, it's only a coat.
Only a coat.
Anne, you must not behave
in that way.
lt was an accident.
Anyone can have an accident.
l don't mean that.
l mean the answering back.
You must not answer back.
They're our guests.
You don't hear Margot getting
into arguments with them.
Try to be like Margot.
And have them walk all over me
the way they do her? No, thanks.
l don't know what happens
to you, Annie.
lf l had ever talked to my mother
as you talk to me....
Things have changed, Mother.
People aren't like that anymore.
''Yes, Mother. No, Mother.
Anything you say, Mother.''
l've got to fight things out for myself.
Make something of myself.
lt isn't necessary to fight to do it.
Margot doesn't--
''Margot.'' That's all l hear.
''Why aren't you like Margot?''
Everything she does is right,
and everything l do is wrong.
You're all against me,
and you worst of all.
[DOOR SLAMS]
l don't know how we can
go on living this way.
l can't say a word to Annie,
she flies at me.
You know Anne. In a half an hour,
she'll be laughing and joking.
And them.
l told your father it wouldn't work
with two families.
But no, no, he had to ask them.
Shh.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[KNOCKING]
Every time l hear that sound,
my heart stops.
MARGOT :
It's Miep. Father.
FRANK: Yes?
EDITH: It's Miep.
-Here's your list.
EDITH: Thank you.
VAN DAAN: Is it Miep?
-Yes.
-At last, l'll have some cigarettes.
-Miep's here.
l can't tell you how sorry l am
about the coat.
Don't worry.
-Hello.
-Miep.
Mr. Kraler.
When Mr. Kraler comes,
the sun begins to shine.
-Dirk has had to leave.
-Dirk is Miep's fiancé.
He had to go into hiding in the country
to escape a labor call-up...
...but he has let me have
the radio for you.
-He shouldn't have.
-lt was too dangerous.
Look!
[MUSIC PLAYS]
ANNE:
Our blessed radío.
lt gíves us our eyes and ears
out ínto the world.
We lísten to the German statíon
only for good musíc.
MAN ON RADlO:
The Axís forces ín the Western....
ANNE:
And we lísten to the BBC for hope.
MAN ON RADlO: --ceaseless attacks _y
Iand and aír forces are now ín full retreat.
The 8th army contínues
to advance.
PETRONELLA:
It's good.
All right, Peter. Now, let's see what
they have to say about the Nazis, huh?
Berlin.
[MAN ON RADlO
SPEAKING IN GERMAN]
Must we listen?
All right, Peter, that's enough.
The Green Police, they've found us.
MAN :
Hmm.
[FLOOR SQUEAKS]
Hm.
[HUMS]
Hm?
Hm.
[SIREN WAILING]
[COUGHS]
[SIREN FADING]
[CLOCK CHIMES]
[EXPLOSlONS IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
MIEP:
This way, Mr. Dussel.
[AIR RAID SIREN WAILS]
[KNOCKS]
KRALER: It's Kraler.
MIEP: And Miep.
KRALER: Please open.
PETRONELLA: Bless them. They're here.
FRANK: Kraler?
KRALER: And Miep, yes. Open, please.
-Well, we had a visitor last night.
-We had a visitor last night.
-Yes, yes.
-A thief.
-lt was a thief?
-Did you hear him?
-Yes.
-He was right under you.
ln the office right under here.
EDITH: We did not know.
MARGOT: We thought it was the police.
-Are you sure, Miep?
-You were, of course, quiet?
We didn't move.
We hardly breathed all night.
-That is good. It was close.
-Too close.
He went through everything,
the desk and the files.
And he found the safe,
but he could not get it open.
He's looking for our ration card supply
from the underground.
-Somebody knows.
-They are in that safe.
They'll come back. You should get rid
of that safe. Get it out of here.
Yes, put a sign on the door:
''Burglars do not come back.
The safe is gone.''
-Jokes, yeah.
-Mr. Frank, l must talk to you.
-Of course.
-Maybe we should get rid of the radio.
Put it in the stove. Burn it.
If the Green Police found that radio....
Then they'd find her diary.
We'll burn that too.
Not my diary.
My diary goes, l go with it.
-Where is it?
-Mr. Van Daan.
lf they find us, they might as well
find the diary, the radio....
-Usually, l try to bring good news.
-Yes, l know.
But something has happened.
A man came to me.
He told me that he has
a Jewish friend, a dentist.
He begged me, could l find him
a hiding place? So l have come to you.
lt is a terrible thing to ask of you,
living the way you are...
-...but could you take him in?
-Well, of course we will.
-His name is Jan Dussel.
-Dussel. l think l know him.
EDITH: l think it's fine to have him.
-Thank you.
But, Otto, where are we going
to put him? Where?
-There's so little food as it is--
-We can stretch the food a little.
PETER: He can have my bed.
-No, thank you.
Margot will move in with us,
and he can have her bed.
MARGOT :
l'll get my things out.
[BELL RINGS]
Mr. Dussel.
Don't bump your head.
Come in, Mr. Dussel.
This is Mr. Frank.
-Mr. Otto Frank?
-Yes. Let me have your things, please.
Thank you, Mr. Frank.
l leave you in good hands.
Mr. Dussel, l must return your coat.
-What can l say to thank you?
-Mr. Kraler and Miep...
.. .they're our lifeline.
Without them, we couldn't live.
KRALER: Please. You make us seem
very heroic. It isn't that at all.
-We simply don't like the Nazis.
-l know, l know.
''Nobody's going to tell us Dutchmen
what to do with our damn Jews.''
We'll be up tomorrow,
see if they're treating you right.
KRALER: Goodbye.
DUSSEL: Goodbye, Mr. Kraler.
MIEP: Goodbye, Mr. Dussel.
DUSSEL: Goodbye, Miep.
-Welcome, Mr. Dussel.
-Thank you.
This is my wife, Edith.
Mr. and Mrs. Van Daan. Their son, Peter.
My daughters, Margot and Anne.
DUSSEL: Hello, Anne.
-How do you do?
-Margot.
Please, Mr. Dussel, sit down.
Thank you.
l'm dreaming, l know it.
Mr. Otto Frank here.
You're not in Switzerland, then?
Someone said that you had escaped.
-And you've been here all this time?
-Ever since July.
Did Mr. Kraler warn you
you won't get much to eat here?
You can imagine.
Three ration cards
among the seven of us.
Now you make eight.
DUSSEL: Mr. Van Daan, you don't realize
what's happening outside...
...that you should warn me
of a thing like that.
You don't realize what's going on,
right here in Amsterdam.
Every day, hundreds of Jews disappear.
They surround the block.
They search house by house.
Every day, children come home from
school to find their parents gone.
Hundreds are being deported.
People that you and l know:
the Hallensteins, the Wessels.
EDITH :
Oh, no.
DUSSEL:
You get your call-up notice:
Come to the station on such
and such a day and hour.
Bring only what you can carry.''
lf you don't, they come drag you
from your home...
...and ship you off to Mauthausen,
the death camp.
We didn't know that things
had got so much worse.
Forgive me for speaking so.
Do you know the de Vries?
They're gone.
Sanne and l are in the same class.
Sanne is my best--
My best friend.
She returned home from school
to find her parents gone.
She was alone for two days,
and then they came and took her away.
Gone?
Yes, with all the others.
Oh, no.
People named Meyerberg,
they lived near us.
-Do you know--?
-We should put this off.
l'm sure Mr. Dussel would like
to get settled.
Would you take Mr. Dussel
to his room now?
ANNE:
If you'll come with me, Mr. Dussel.
Forgive me if l haven't expressed
my gratitude.
This has been such a shock to me.
l always thought of myself as Dutch.
l was born in Holland.
My father was born in Holland,
and my grandfather.
And now, after all these years....
lf you will excuse me.
[MUSIC PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
lt's so different from what
Mr. Kraler tells us.
Mr. Kraler says that things
are improving.
l like it better the way Kraler tells it.
Good night.
-Say good night!
-Good night, Mother.
PETRONELLA: Good night, Mr. Frank.
FRANK: Good night.
Do you have any children, Mr. Dussel?
No, l never married.
-Have you no family at all?
DUSSEL: No one.
ANNE:
How dreadful.
You must be terribly lonely.
l'm used to it.
l don't think l could ever get used to it.
Didn't you even have a pet?
-A cat or a dog?
-No.
No, no, l have an allergy
to furbearing animals.
-Gives me asthma.
-Oh, dear.
What?
Peter has a cat.
-He has? He has it here?
-Yes.
We hardly ever see it.
-He keeps it in his room all the time.
-Yeah.
-l'm sure it'll be all right.
-Well, l hope so. Yes.
l hope l won't be too much
of a bother to you, Mr. Dussel.
No.
l seem to be able to get
everyone's back up.
Oh, l always get along very well
with young people.
My patients all bring
their children to me...
...because they know l get along well
with them.
So don't you worry about that.
Thank you, Mr. Dussel.
Good night.
l'll be back.
Good night, Mr. Dussel.
Be careful.
[CLATTERING]
[BELL CHIMES]
[MEN CHEERING FAINTLY]
ANNE:
Sanne.
Sanne?
Sanne!
[LAUGHING AND SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[GUN SHOOTING]
[SCREAMS]
Save me! Save me! No, no!
-No! Don't take me!
DUSSEL: Stop it! Stop it!
[LAUGHING]
ANNE:
Save me.
EDITH: Hush, Annie, hush.
It's all right. It's all right.
Please, Mr. Dussel, turn on the light.
It was just a dream.
You're here, safe, you see?
Something must be done with that child.
Yelling like that.
Who knows who might be in the street?
She's endangering our lives.
Mr. Dussel, after all, Anne is not
exactly a trained frontline soldier.
Please, Mr. Dussel, go back to bed.
She'll be herself in a minute or two,
won't you, Annie?
DUSSEL:
Go back to bed. Hmph.
Excuse me. l'm going to the W.C.,
the one room where there's peace.
FRANK:
Go back to bed now.
EDITH :
Would you like some water?
Was it a very bad dream?
Perhaps if you told me?
l'd rather not talk about it.
EDITH :
Try to sleep, then.
-l'll sit right here beside you.
ANNE: You don't have to.
But l'd like to stay with you.
Very much, really.
l'd rather you didn't.
EDITH :
Good night--
You'll be all right?
There's nothing that you want?
Will you please ask Father to come?
Yes, of course, Anne, dear.
She asked for you.
-Edith....
EDITH: Go to her, Otto.
She's still trembling with fear.
[CRYING]
She wants nothing of me.
She pulled away when l leaned down
to kiss her.
They broke down the door and tried
to drag me out, the way they did Sanne.
Anne.
MARGOT :
It's just a phase.
All girls turn to their fathers
at this age.
They give all their love
to their fathers.
EDITH: You weren't like this.
You didn't shut me out.
So....
-Do you want me to read to you?
-No, just sit with me for a minute.
Was l awful?
-Do you think anyone outside heard me?
-No. Now, lie down quietly so.
Like this. Now try to sleep.
l'm a terrible coward.
l'm so disappointed in myself.
l think l'm really grown-up...
...and then something happens,
and l run to you like a baby.
l love you, Father.
l don't love anyone but you.
-Annele. Annele.
ANNE: It's true.
You're the only one l love.
l've been thinking about it
for a long time.
FRANK:
It's fine.
lt's fine to have you tell me
that you love me...
...but l'd be much happier if you said
that you loved your mother as well.
She needs your help so much.
Your love.
We have nothing in common.
She doesn't understand me.
Whenever l try to explain my views
on life, she asks me if l'm constipated.
You hurt her very much just now.
She's crying.
She is in there crying.
Oh, Father, l was horrible, wasn't l?
What's the matter with me?
Tell me.
Don't say it's just a phase.
Help me.
There is so little that we parents can do
to help our children, Annie.
We can only try to set a good example,
point the way.
The rest you must do yourself.
ANNIE:
l'm trying. Really, l am.
Every night, l think back over all the things
l did that day that were wrong.
Like putting the wet mop
in Mrs. Van Daan's bed.
And now this with Mother.
l say to myself, ''That was wrong.''
And l make up my mind never
to do that again. Never.
l may do something worse,
but l'll never do that again.
l have a nicer side, Father...
...but l'm scared to show it.
l'm afraid people will laugh at me.
So the mean Anne comes
to the outside...
...and the good Anne stays
in the inside.
And l keep on trying
to switch them around...
...have the good Anne outside...
...and the bad Anne inside.
lt would be what l'd like to be.
And might be.
lf only....
She's asleep.
ANNE:
Thursday. the 29th of October. 19$2.
Mr. Dussel and l had
a great battle yesterday.
Yes. Mr. Dussel.
Accordíng to hím. nothíng. l repeat.
nothíng. ís ríght about me.
Whíle he was goíng on at me.
l thought:
''Someday. l'm goíng
to gíve you such a smack.. .
...that you'll fly ríght up
to the ceílíng.''
Why ís ít that every grownup thínks
he knows the way to bríng up chíldren?
Partícularly the grownups
that haven't any.
Monday. the 9th of November. 19$2.
Wonderful news?
The Allíes have landed ín Afríca?
MAN ON RADlO:
That measure of....
ANN_: Churchíll spoke on the BBC
from London.
MAN ON RADlO: --whích they have
so often meted out to others.
Ah. thís ís not the end.
lt ís not even the begínníng
of the end.
Mo. but ít ís. perhaps.
the end of the begínníng.
ANNE:
The aír raíds are gettíng worse.
The Brítísh planes come over. day
and níght. on theír way to Germany.
[EXPLOSlONS RUMBLING]
lt's too much.
It's just too much.
Suppose they hit this house?
What will we do?
We can't go out in the street.
lf they hit this house,
your worries will be over.
That big explosion,
an English plane fell right in this block!
Peter.
Peter!
FRANK: It's far away from here.
VAN DAAN: Please don't.
FRANK:
Just look at them.
Mrs. Van Daan,
this should be music to your ears.
-Music?
FRANK: Of course.
The more planes they send,
the sooner the war will be over.
-The sooner we'll be home again.
-l don't believe it'll ever be over.
Do you know what l'd like right now?
A cup of tea.
Oh, yes, please.
You can't have tea, then,
for breakfast.
lf you have it now,
you won't have any tomorrow.
-l don't care.
-Neither do l.
Me too, please.
How about you, Mr. Dussel?
Tea now or tomorrow morning?
-Tomorrow morning.
-Sure?
Sure.
l'll take mine now.
The skylight!
FRANK:
Edith, come!
PETRONELLA:
Oh, Peter!
Peter! Peter!
Peter!
FRANK: ''Praised be thou, Lord,
ruler of the universe...
...who's sanctified us
with thy commandments...
...and bidden us kindle
the Hannukah lights.
Praised be thou, O, Lord, our God,
ruler of the universe...
.. .who wrought wondrous deliverances
for our fathers in days of old.
Praised be thou, O, Lord, our God,
ruler of the universe...
...that thou hast given us life
and sustenance...
...and brought us to this happy season.''
Amen.
-Amen.
ANNE:
Monday. the 7th of December. 19$2.
The Hannukah holíday
came early thís year.
''We kindle this Hannukah light...
...to celebrate the wonderful deeds
wrought through the zeal...
...with which God filled the hearts of
the heroic Maccabees 2000 years ago.
They fought against indifference.. .
.. .against tyranny and oppression,
and they restored our temple to us.
May these lights remind us
that we should ever look to God...
...whence cometh our help.''
Amen.
-Amen.
l lift up mine eyes unto the mountains
from whence cometh my help.
My help cometh from the Lord,
who made heaven and earth.
He will not suffer thy foot
to be moved.
He that keepeth thee will not slumber.
He that keepeth Israel doth
neither slumber nor sleep.
The Lord is thy keeper.
The Lord is thy shade
upon thy right hand.
The Lord shall keep thee from all evil.
He shall keep thy soul.
The Lord shall guard thy going out
and thy coming in...
...from this time forth and forevermore.''
Amen.
-Amen.
May l have the hats, please?
Thank you.
Very nice, very nice.
-That was very moving.
-lt isn't over yet.
-Sit down!
VAN DAAN: Where are you going?
There's lots more.
Songs and presents.
-Presents?
EDITH: Not this year, unfortunately.
But always on Hannukah,
everyone gives presents. Everyone.
-That's right.
-Like our St. Nicholas Day.
St. Nicholas Day.
No, not like St. Nicholas Day.
What kind of Jew doesn't
know Hannukah?
EDITH :
l remember particularly the candles.
First one, as we have tonight.
The second night, two.
The next night, three, and so on,
until eight candles are burning.
When there are eight candles,
it's truly beautiful.
What l remember best are the presents
we used to get, eight days of presents.
Each day, they got better and better.
We are all here, alive.
That's present enough.
No, it isn't.
l've got something.
What is it?
-Presents.
-Real presents?
-She made it herself.
-Look!
-lsn't it festive? Isn't it gay?
-Oh, it's beautiful.
For Margot.
Read it out loud.
You have never lost your temper
You never wíll l fear
You are so good
But íf you should
Put all your cross words here
Let's see what it is.
lt's a new crossword-puzzle book.
lt's one you've done, but l rubbed it out.
If you wait and forget...
...you can do it all over again!
-lt's wonderful.
-Clever.
Thank you.
For Mrs. Van Daan.
Oh, l feel terrible.
l don't have a thing for anybody.
lt's hair shampoo.
l took all the bits of soap and mixed
them with the last of my toilet water.
-Oh, thank you, Anneke!
-She's got your number.
l wanted to write a poem for all of them,
but l didn't have time.
Yours, Mr. Van Daan,
is really something.
Something you want
more than anything.
Cigarettes!
Look at that!
-Cigarettes!
-Two of them.
Father found some pipe tobacco in the
pocket of his coat, and we made them.
Rather, Father did.
PETRONELLA:
Look at that.
Light it! Go on, light it!
lt's tobacco.
Really, it is.
There's a little fluff in it, but not much.
Ah, yes.
[COUGHS]
PETER: It works!
-Look at him!
Thank you, Annie. Thank you.
EDITH :
Mr. Van Daan!
For Mother.
A Hannukah greeting.
Here's an lOU that l promíse to pay
Ten hours of doíng
Whatever you say
Signed, Anne Frank.
Ten hours of doing what you're told?
Anything you're told?
That's right.
You wouldn't want to sell that,
Mrs. Frank, would you?
Never. This is the most
precious gift l've ever had.
For Father.
Annele, l wasn't supposed
to have a present.
-Look at that.
-lt's a muffler.
Oh, l know.
To wear around your neck
like an ascot, you know.
l knitted it in the dark each night.
l'm afraid it looks better in the dark.
lt's fine. Thank you, Annele.
Thank you.
-lsn't it a dream?
-Lovely, isn't it?
Thank you, Anne.
For Mouschi.
He'll like it.
And this is for you, yourself.
From Miss Quack-Quack.
Go on, open it.
Aren't you going to open it?
PETRONELLA:
Come on, show us what it is.
-lt's a safety razor.
-What?
lt's not new.
Miep got it, secondhand.
But you really do need a razor now.
-What for?
-Look at his upper lip.
See?
He wants to get rid of that?
Put some milk on it
and let the cat lick it off.
You think you're funny, don't you?
Look, he can't wait.
He's going in to try it now.
l'm going to give Mouschi his present.
-Mouschi, Mouschi, Mouschi.
-Enough!
And last, but never least,
my roommate, Mr. Dussel.
Something for me?
-Capsules.
-They're earplugs.
To put in your ears so you won't
hear me when l thrash around at night.
l made them myself. Try them.
See if you can hear me.
-Watch him.
-Wait, l'll put--
-Like that? Is that what you mean?
-Are you ready?
-What?
They work!
They went in!
He can't get them out.
What's the matter with you?
Get them out. Take them out.
l got it.
Thank you.
-That's a real Hannukah.
-lsn't she cute?
-A real Hannukah.
-Now let's sing the song, Father.
Wait till you hear the Hannukah song,
Mr. Dussel.
[ANNE SINGS]
Annele. l'm afraid we shouldn't
sing the song.
lt's a song of jubilation
and of rejoicing.
One is apt to become
too enthusiastic about it.
ANNE: Please, let's sing it.
l promise not to shout.
Very well, but quietly, Annie.
l'll keep my eye on you. If you get--
Oh. Oh!
l told you not to come in with that cat.
Get out of here!
What's the matter with you?
Haven't you any sense?
-Get that cat out of here.
-Cat?
You heard me, get it out of here!
l have no cat.
Mr. Dussel.
lt doesn't have to be the cat.
Just the hairs on his clothing...
...from the cat is enough
when he comes in the room.
You won't be bothered anymore.
We're getting rid of it.
At last, you listen to me.
And l'm not doing it for you.
That's all in your mind, all of it.
l'm doing it because l'm sick
of seeing that cat eat all our food.
That's not true.
l only give him scraps.
Don't tell me.
He gets fatter every day.
Damn cat looks better than any of us.
Out he goes tonight.
No!
Mr. Van Daan, you can't do that.
That's Peter's cat.
-Peter loves that cat.
EDITH: Annie.
lf he goes, l go.
Go. Go.
He's not going and the cat's not going.
What's wrong with you? It's Hannukah.
Look, please, Annie, sing.
[ANNE SINGS]
Annele. Annele.
l think we should first
blow out the candles.
Then we'll have something
for tomorrow night.
Father, you're supposed to let it
burn itself out.
l'm sure that God
understands shortages.
Praised be thou, Lord,
who has permitted us...
.. .to celebrate this joyous festival.
Amen.
-Amen.
[FAINT CLATTERING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[CAT MEOWS]
[CRASHING]
-l think they've gone.
-They've found us.
lf they had, they would be
up here by now.
l know it was the Green Police.
They've gone to get help.
Maybe the Gestapo
Iooking for papers.
Or another thief looking
for money.
l'm going down.
They may still be there.
Annele, this is Saturday.
We won't know what happened until
Miep or Mr. Kraler come here on Monday.
We cannot live with this uncertainty.
Now, please. Please.
Get our money.
They say you can buy them off.
-Quick, go get the money.
-Keep still!
You want to be dragged off
to a concentration camp?
You gonna stand there
till they come get you?
Will you keep still?
Someone go
and make Father come back.
VAN DAAN: Haven't you done enough?
ANNE: Please, Mr. Van Daan.
Annie!
EDITH: l lift up mine eyes unto the
mountains, from whence cometh my help.
My help cometh from the Lord,
who made heaven and earth.
He that keepeth thee will not slumber.
He that keepeth Israel
doth neither slumber nor sleep.
The Lord is thy keeper.
The Lord is thy shade
upon thy right hand.
Over here.
[SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
-l better go and look and make sure.
-Yeah.
The Lord shall keep thee from all evil.
-He shall keep thy soul.
VAN DAAN: Hear me, O, Israel.
The Lord shall guide thy going out
and thy coming in.
Took the typewriter and ran away.
He didn't shut the street door.
lt was swinging wide open.
The watchman was passing.
[SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
[MEOWING]
[SPEAKING IN GERMAN]
We had a burglar.
He got out as he heard me coming.
WATCHMAN :
l will lock the door and report it.
PETER: They've gone and locked the door.
EDITH: Oh, thank God, they've gone.
l'd just as soon they take us
than to continue with this agony.
l can't think.
lt's all right.
The danger has passed.
Who says the danger has passed?
Don't you realize that we're
in greater danger than ever?
Please, will you keep still?
Thanks to this clumsy fool,
someone now knows we're up here.
-Someone knows we're hiding.
-lt's a thief! You think...
...he'll go to the Green Police
and say, ''l was robbing a place...
...and l heard a noise above my head''?
Would he do that?
-l think he will.
-You're crazy.
l think that someday that the thief
will be caught...
...and he'll make
a bargain with the Gestapo.
He'll say to the Gestapo,
''lf you let me off...
...l'll show you where some Jews
are hiding.''
-That's what l think.
-Oh.
He's right.
MARGOT: Oh, Mother, let's get out
of here. We can't stay here now.
ANNE: Please, let's go.
-Go? Where?
Yes, where?
Have we lost all faith?
All courage?
A few moments ago, we thought they
had come for us, didn't we?
We thought it was the end. Well, it
wasn't the end. We're alive. We're safe.
We thank thee, O, Lord, our God,
that in thy infinite mercy...
...thou hast again seen fit
to spare us.
-Amen.
Annele.
The song.
How about the song?
[ANNE SINGS]
[ALL SINGING]
-Happy Hannukah.
[BELLS RINGING]
ANNE:
Saturday. the 1st of January. 19$$.
Another new year has begun.. .
.. .and we fínd ourselves stíll
ín our hídíng place.
We have been here now.. .
.. .for one year.
fíve months and 25 days.
One of our famíly has left us.
Mouschí ran away.
We're all a líttle thínner.
The Van Daans' díscussíons
are as víolent as ever.
Mother stíll doesn't understand me.
But then.
l don't understand her eíther.
There ís one great change. however.. .
.. .a change ín myself.
l read somewhere that gírls of my age
don't feel quíte certaín of themselves.
That they become quíet wíthín.. .
...and begín to thínk of the míracle
that ís takíng place ín theír bodíes.
l thínk that what ís happeníng
to me ís so wonderful.
Not only what can be seen.. .
.. .but what ís takíng place ínsíde.
Each tíme ít has happened.
l feel l have a sweet secret.. .
...and l long for the tíme when l shall
feel that secret wíthín me agaín.
FRANK:
Annele! Peter!
A wonderful surprise,
Mr. Kraler and Miep are here.
Thank you. You shouldn't have come.
You should have
at least one day to yourselves.
ANNE: Don't say that.
It's so wonderful to see them.
-What is it? What is it?
ANNE: Mr. Kraler.
-Happy New Year, Mr. Dussel.
-Happy New Year.
How are you, Margot?
Feeling any better?
-l'm all right.
-We filled her full of every kind of pill...
...so she won't cough
and make a noise.
Look what Miep has brought us.
A cake!
ALL:
Ooh.
-A cake.
-Well.
l'll get some plates.
-Thank you, Miep.
-Thank you.
You must have used all
of your sugar rations for weeks.
lt's beautiful, isn't it?
lt's ages since l've even seen a cake.
Not since you brought the one last year.
Remember?
lt had ''Peace in 1 943'' written on it.
''Peace in 1 944.''
Peace has to come sometime,
you know.
Here you are, líef_e.
Now...
-...how many of us are there?
MIEP: None for me.
-Oh, you must.
-Please, Miep.
Good. That leaves one, two, three....
-Seven of us.
-Eight.
The same as it always is.
l left Margot out.
l take it for granted Margot won't eat.
-Why wouldn't she?
-l think it won't harm her.
All right, all right. l just didn't want her
to start coughing again, that's all.
And please,
Mrs. Frank should cut the cake.
What do you mean?
Well, Mrs. Frank divides things better.
-Just what are you trying to say?
-Forget it, we're wasting time.
Don't l always give everybody
exactly the same?
-Don't l?
-Forget it.
-No, l want an answer. Don't l?
-Yes, yes, yes.
Everybody gets exactly the same.. .
...except Mr. Van Daan gets
a little bit more.
That's a lie!
She always cuts the same--
Mr. Van Daan, please.
You see, Miep, what a little sugar cake
does to us? It goes right to our heads.
-Here you are, Mrs. Frank.
-Thank you.
-You're sure you won't have any?
KRALER: Very sure.
-Miep.
-No, thank you, really.
Cut the cake.
Thank you.
EDITH :
That's yours, Peter.
Maybe Mouschi went back
to our house.
You ever get over there?
Do you think that you could?
l'm afraid with him gone a week,
Peter....
Make up your mind. Already someone
has had a big nice meal from that cat.
-lt's delicious, Miep.
-Delicious.
Well, l must run.
There's a party tonight.
How heavenly!
Remember what everyone's wearing.. .
...and what you eat and everything
so you can tell us.
MIEP:
l'll give you a full report.
-Goodbye, everyone.
FRANK: Goodbye, Miep.
Just a minute. There's something l'd
like you to do for me.
PETRONELLA:
Where are you going?
What are you going to do?
No. Don't you dare take that coat.
-What is wrong?
PETER: Father is going to sell her fur coat.
-She's crazy about that old fur coat.
-lt's mine, you hear me?
My father gave me that coat.
No! You have no right!
ls it possible that anyone can...
...be silly enough to worry about
a fur coat at a time like this?
PETER:
It's none of your darn business.
-And if you say one more thing--
FRANK: Peter.
Just...
...a little discussion on the advisability
of selling this coat.
As l have often
reminded Mrs. Van Daan...
...it's selfish of her to keep it
when people outside...
...are in desperate need of clothing.
So if you please, sell it for us?
lt should fetch a good price.
And by the way...
...would you get me cigarettes?
l don't care what kind, get all you can.
lt is very difficult to get them,
Mr. Van Daan, but l'll try.
-Goodbye.
Mr. Frank, could l talk to you?
Something's happened, hasn't it,
Mr. Kraler? What's happened?
lf it is something that concerns us
here, we'd better all hear it.
-The children--
-What they'd imagine.. .
...would be worse than any reality.
lt is a man in the storeroom.
His name is Karl.
You knew him.
One day, he came to the office.
He closed the door and asked:
''What do you hear
from your friend Mr. Frank?''
l said there's a rumor
you were in Switzerland.
He said he had heard that rumor too,
but he thought l knew something more.
l did not pay much attention.
l tried to forget it.
And then yesterday, we were coming
out of the storeroom, out there.
l had started down to the office.
l looked back.
He was standing,
staring at the bookcase.
He said, ''l thought l remembered
a door up here.
Was not there a door code(0125)ere leading
to the loft?
Then he asked me for more money.
-20 guilders more a week.
-Blackmail.
-20 guilders? Very modest blackmail.
-That's just the beginning.
You know what l think?
He's the thief who
was down there that night.
That's how he knows we're here.
How was it left?
What did you tell him?
l told him l had to think about it.
What shall l do, pay him the money?
Take a chance on firing him, or what?
-l do not know.
-For heaven sakes, don't fire him.
Pay him what he asks.
Keep him here,
where you can keep your eye on him.
ls it much that he's asking?
What are they paying nowadays?
He could get it in a war plant.
But this is not a war plant.
Mind you,
l do not know if he knows or not.
Offer him half, then we'll soon know
if it is blackmail or not.
And if it is?
We've got to pay, haven't we?
-Whatever he asks, we've got to pay.
-Let us decide when the time comes.
This may be all my imagination.
You get to a point, these days...
.. .where you suspect everyone
and everything.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
What does that mean,
the telephone ringing on a holiday?
That's my wife. l told her l had
to go over some papers in my office...
...to call me here when she got out
of church. Goodbye.
Happy New Year.
-Goodbye.
-Goodbye, Mr. Kraler.
KRALER: l will offer him half, then.
FRANK: Thank you, Mr. Kraler.
DUSSEL:
You can thank your son for this.
Him and his damn cat!
That night, there.
l tell you,
it's just a question of time now.
Sometimes l wish the end would come,
whatever it is.
-Margot!
-At least we'd know where we were.
You should be ashamed of yourself,
talking that way.
Think how lucky we are.
Think of the thousands dying
in the war every day.
Think of the people
in concentration camps.
What's the good of that?
What's the good of thinking of misery
when you're already miserable?
That's stupid!
We're young,
Margot and Peter and l.
You grownups have had your chance.
But look at us. If we begin thinking
of all the horror in the world, we're lost.
We're trying to hold on to some kind
of ideals when everything--
ldeals, hope, everything
is being destroyed.
lt isn't our fault the world
is in such a mess.
-We weren't around when this started.
-You listen to me!
So don't try to take it out on us!
VAN DAAN:
She talks as if we started the war.
Did we start the war?
-You left this.
-Thanks.
l thought you were fine just now.
You know how to talk to them.
l can't think when l'm mad.
l say too much.
l hurt people's feelings.
l think you're just fine.
Thank you, Peter.
J
Dussel, what he said about Mouschi
about somebody eating him...
...all l could think is l wanted
to hit him.
That's what l used to do at school.
But here a fight starts,
l duck in my room.
You're lucky, having a room to go to.
His Lordship is always in mine.
When they start in on me,
l have to stand and take it.
You gave some of it back
to them just now.
l get so mad.
They've formed their opinions.. .
.. .about everything.
But we're still trying to find out.
We have problems here that
no other people our age have ever had.
And just as you
think you've solved them...
...something comes along and bang!
You have to start all over again.
-l think your father's fine.
-Oh, he is, Peter. He is.
He's the only one who's ever given me
the feeling that l have any sense.
lsn't it funny, you and l?
Here we've been together
all this time.. .
...and this is the first time we've
ever really talked.
lt helps a lot to have someone to talk to,
doesn't it?
lt helps you let off steam.
Anytime that you want
to let off steam...
...you can come into my room.
l can get up an awful lot of steam.
lt's all right with me.
Do you mean that?
l said it, didn't l?
-Good night.
Good night.
-May l come in?
ANNE: No, l'm not dressed yet.
Margot.
-Tell me, am l terribly ugly?
MARGOT: Oh, stop fishing.
No, tell me.
Of course you're not.
You've got nice eyes...
...and a lot of animation and....
-May l come in?
MARGOT: Come in, Mother.
EDITH: Mr. Dussel is impatient to get in.
ANNE: He takes the room all day.
You're not going in again tonight
to see Peter?
That is my intention.
Aren't you afraid
you're disturbing him?
Mother, l have some intuition.
Then may l ask this much, Annie?
Don't shut the door when you go in.
You sound like Mrs. Van Daan.
No, no. l don't mean
to suggest anything is wrong.
l only wish you wouldn't
expose yourself to criticism.
l'm sorry, Mother.
l'm going to Peter's room.
l'm not going to let Petronella Van Daan
spoil our friendship.
Just a moment, Mr. Dussel.
ln my day,
the boys called on the girls.
EDITH: You know how young people are.
Peter's room...
-...is the only place where they can talk.
-Talk?
That's not what they called it
when l was a girl.
l'm sorry, Margot,
that you have to be the one left out.
-l feel so guilty about you.
-Why?
l mean,
every time l go into Peter's room...
...l have the feeling
that l'm hurting you.
l know if it were me,
l'd be desperately jealous.
l am jealous, a little,
but not of you and Peter.
l'm....
l'm only feeling sorry
that l haven't anyone...
...with whom to discuss my feelings.
-Margot, l won't even--
-Listen, you've found a companionship...
...and l want you to enjoy it.
Only, in my heart, l feel l've got a
right to share feelings with someone too.
But l'm sure that Peter, that that boy,
he could never be that person for me.
[KNOCKING]
Maybe there's nothing
to be jealous about.
Maybe l'm just taking
the place of his cat.
-Will you please let me in my room?
ANNE: Just a minute, dear Mr. Dussel.
Well, here l go, to run the gauntlet.
Thank you so much.
Look at her.
A lot of good it did me to have a son.
l never see him.
Just a minute, dear.
l'd like to say a few words to my son.
Do you mind?
Peter, l do not want you staying up
till all hours tonight.
You need sleep.
You're a growing boy.
Annie won't stay late.
She's going to bed promptly at 9.
-Aren't you, Annie?
-Yes, Mother. May we go now?
Listen for the chimes, dear.
Aren't they impossible?
Treating us as if we're still
in the nursery.
Don't let it bother you.
It doesn't bother me.
l suppose you can't really blame them.
They think back
to what they were like at our age.
They don't realize
how much more advanced we are.
Already l know what l want to do,
don't you?
l want to be a journalist or something.
l love to write.
What do you want to do?
l know what l'd like right now.
l'd like to go to England and get
with the Free Dutch forces.
Peter, you wouldn't try a thing like that.
You'd never make it.
l'd make it.
Only a few of the hundreds that try do.
l know, but l'd like
to get in it and hit back.
To just sit here, it's not for me.
You like Margot, don't you?
Right from the start, you liked her.
Liked her better than me.
-l don't know.
-lt's all right.
Everyone feels that way.
Margot's so good.
She's sweet and bright and beautiful,
and l'm not.
-l wouldn't say that.
ANNE: Oh, no, l'm not.
l know that.
l know quite well that l'm not a beauty.
l never have been and never shall be.
l don't agree at all.
l think you're pretty.
That's not true.
And another thing.
You've changed. From the first, l mean.
l have?
l used to think
that you were awful noisy.
And what do you think now, Peter?
How have l changed?
Well.. .
.. .you're quieter.
l'm glad you don't just hate me.
l never said that.
l bet when you get out of here,
you'll never think of me again.
That's crazy.
When you get back with all your friends,
you're going to say:
''Now, what did l ever see
in that Miss Quack-Quack?''
-l haven't got any friends.
-Peter, of course you have.
-Everyone has friends.
-Not me.
l don't want any.
l get along fine without them.
Does that mean
you can get along without me too?
l think of myself as your friend.
No.
lf they were all like you...
...it'd be different.
[EXPLOSlONS IN DISTANCE]
Peter.. .
...did you ever kiss a girl?
Yes.
Once.
Was she pretty?
The girl you kissed?
l don't know. l was blindfolded.
lt was at a party.
One of those kissing games.
l don't suppose that really counts,
does it?
lt didn't with me.
l've been kissed twice.
Once, a man l'd never seen before
kissed me on the cheek...
...when he picked me up off the ice.
l was crying.
And the other was a friend
of Father's who kissed my hand.
You wouldn't say those counted,
would you?
l wouldn't say so.
l know, almost for certain,
Margot would never kiss anyone...
...unless she was engaged to them.
And l'm sure, too, that Mother
never touched a man before Father.
But l don't know.
Things are so different now.
What do you think?
Do you think a girl shouldn't kiss anyone
except if she's engaged or something?
lt's so hard to try
to think what to do.
Here we are with the whole world
falling around our ears...
...and you think...
...well, you don't know
what's going to happen tomorrow.
What do you think?
l suppose it depends on the girl.
With some,
no matter what they do, it's wrong.
But others.. .
.. .it wouldn't necessarily
be wrong with them.
[BELL CHIMES]
l always thought that--
l think l should go now.
That's right.
Good night.
PETER: You won't let them
stop you from coming?
No.
l might bring my diary.
There are so many things in it
l want to talk over with you.
There's a lot about you.
PETER:
What kind of things?
Well.. .
...l wouldn't want you
to see some of it.
l thought you were nothing.
Just the way you thought about me.
Did you change your mind?
l changed my mind about you.
You'll see.
Good night, Annele.
-Good night, Anne.
-Good night.
Mm-hmm.
ANNE:
Outsíde. there's a quíet excítement.
lnvasíon fever ís mountíng
from day to day.
And people talk nothíng else
but the hope of líberatíon.
lt had best come soon.
We here have had bad news.
The people from whom Míep got
our ratíon cards have been arrested.
Mr. Kraler ís ín the hospítal.
It seems he has ulcers.
l'm afraíd we are hís ulcers.
Míep has to run the busíness
and us too.
How very fortunate we are. when
you thínk of what ís happeníng outsíde.
l feel that spríng ís comíng.
l feel ít ín my whole body and soul.
l'm utterly confused.
l'm longíng.. .
.. .so longíng for everythíng.
[BOAT HORN SOUNDING]
EDITH :
Otto! Otto, quick!
He's stealing the food!
Mr. Van Daan has been stealing!
FRANK: What is it?
EDITH: Mr. Van Daan! Let me--!
What happened?
Mr. Van Daan.
EDITH :
Look, the bread!
DUSSEL: Dirty thief! You good-for-nothing!
FRANK: Mr. Dussel! Help me, Peter!
Let him go.
Peter, help me!
PETER:
Let him go.
Let him go!
Putti, what is it?
He was stealing the bread!
lt was you.
And all the time
we thought it was the rats.
FRANK:
Mr. Van Daan, how could you?
-l'm hungry.
-We're all of us hungry.
l see the children getting
thinner and thinner.
Your own son, l've heard him moan
in his sleep, he's so hungry.
And you come down in the night and
steal food that should go to the children!
He needs more food than the rest of us.
He's used to more. He's a big man.
And you!
You're worse than he is!
You're a mother!
And yet you sacrifice your son
to this man! This--
Edith.
Don't think l haven't seen you.
Always saving the choicest bits for him.
l've watched you day after day,
and l've held my tongue.
But not any longer. Not after this!
Now, l want him to go.
l want him to get out of here!
Edith.
VAN DAAN:
Get out of here?
PETRONELLA: What do you mean?
-Just that.
-Take your things and get out!
-You're speaking in anger.
-You can't mean it.
-l mean exactly that.
For two years,
we have lived here side by side.
We've respected each other's rights.
We have managed to live in peace.
Are we now going to throw it all away?
Mr. Van Daan, l know this is never
going to happen again, is it?
-No, no.
-He steals once, he'll steal again.
l want them to leave. You go now!
ANNE:
Mother.. .
...you're not putting Peter out.
Peter hasn't done anything.
l don't mean Peter. Peter can stay.
l have to go if he goes.
He's my father.
EDITH :
He's no father to you, that man.
He doesn't know
what it is to be a father!
l wouldn't feel right.
l couldn't stay.
EDITH :
Very well, then.
Peter. No.
PETRONELLA: Mrs. Frank, you would
put us out on the street?
EDITH :
You can find another hiding place.
Where would we even find a cellar?
A closet?
Mr. Frank...
...you told Putti...
...you would never forget what he did
for you when you first came to Holland.
That you'd never be able to repay--
lf my husband had any obligations
to you, he has paid it.
Edith, l don't know you.
l've never seen you like this.
l should have spoken out long ago.
You can't be nice to some people.
There would be plenty
if you hadn't come.
No, Mrs. Van Daan. Please!
We don't need the Nazis
to destroy us.
We're destroying ourselves.
Mother.. .
...please don't send them away.
It's daylight and they'll be caught.
EDITH: They're not going now. They'll
stay until Miep finds them a place to hide.
Mrs. Frank, Mr. Frank, Margot.
No, no. We haven't sunk so low
that we're going to fight...
.. .amongst ourselves over food.
That's Anne...
...Mrs. Van Daan, Mr. Van Daan.
-See what he's doing?
-''l'm standing by...
...to bring news of the invasion.
For those who haven't heard, l'll repeat.
The landings began this morning
on Normandy.'' It's started! Listen!
MAN ON RADlO: D-day has come. D_ríng
the níght and early hours of thís morníng...
-.. .an ímmense armada of $OOO shíps....
-Listen!
DUSSEL: Peter and myself.
-Keeping the big ones for yourself.
-No.
-Yes. All the big ones. Look at its size.
-That's mine.
-Look at that one.
That's Mr. Van Daan's.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop counting potatoes!
-Mr. Frank! Mrs. Frank!
-Mr. Dussel, l beg of you...
-...don't let her see a thing like this.
-This is Mrs. Frank!
The invasion has begun!
MIEP: It's the most wonderful news!
Only prelímínary reports have... .
Did you hear? They have landed
on the coast of France! In Normandy!
-The British, the Americans!
MIEP: They're all in it!
Dutch, French,
Poles, Norwegians, everyone!
-D-day they call it.
-D-day!
[KNOCKING]
KRALER: It's me, Kraler!
-lt cannot be Mr. Kraler!
But it is Mr. Kraler.
KRALER:
Did you hear? Oh, God!
lsn't it wonderful?
When the nurse told me the news...
...l said, ''There's only one place
to be, with my friends.''
[SINGING]
[BELL CHIMES]
Shh. Shh.
[SINGING IN A WHISPER]
MIEP:
Quick, before the workmen come.
-l'll be up later.
-Goodbye, my dear friends.
FRANK: Goodbye, Mr. Kraler.
Thank you, Miep.
[LOUD SOBBING]
PETRONELLA:
Putti, what is it? What happened?
VAN DAAN:
l'm so ashamed!
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Putti, don't.
Mr. Van Daan.
Didn't you hear?
We are going to be liberated.
This is a time to celebrate.
VAN DAAN:
To steal bread from children!
Oh, darling,
things that we're ashamed of.
Look at the way l treated Mother,
so mean and hard to her.
-No, Anne. No.
ANNE: Oh, l was, Mother. l was awful.
VAN DAAN:
Not like me.
No one is as bad as me!
Stop it! Let's be happy!
Edith.
When l think
of the terrible things l said....
No, no. You were right.
That l should speak that way to you.
Our friends, our guests!
[MUSIC PLAYING ON RADlO]
Stop it!
You're spoiling the whole invasion!
[PLANE ENGINES ROARING]
MAN ON RADlO: _lmíghty God,
our sons. príde of our natíon...
...thís day have set upon
a míghty endeavor.
Líft up your heart. Out of the depths
of sorrow and of sacrífíce...
.. .we'll be born agaín.
the glory of mankínd.
[MAN ON RADlO
SPEAKING IN GERMAN]
KMM_: We are all ín much better spíríts
these days.
There ís stíll excellent news
of the ínvasíon.. .
...and the best part about ít ís that
l have a feelíng that fríends are comíng.
Our beloved queen spoke.
She used words líke ''soon''.. .
.. _'when l am back ''
''speedy líberatíon.''
Who knows?
l may be back ín school by fall.
Wednesday. the 2nd of July. 19$$.
The ínvasíon seems
temporaríly bogged down.
Mr. Kraler ís back ín the hospítal.
He has to have an operatíon.
lt seems D-day was too much for hím.
Thank you.
ANNE:
Ha. ha. The joke ís on us.
Míep says the warehouse man
doesn't know a thíng.. .
...and we're payíng hím
all that money.
[BELL CHIMES]
Our dear vegetable man ís on hís
way to a concentratíon camp.
He was pícked up today
for hídíng two Jews ín hís house.
[SIREN WAILING]
MIEP:
There's not much.
lt was Mr. Hauk,
our greengrocer, they arrested.
The other news is, the Gestapo have
found our typewriter that was stolen.
No!
They'll trace it back and back
until it gets to us.
You watch, you!
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
ANNE:
Everyone ís low.
Even Father can't raíse theír spíríts.
l have often been downcast myself.
but never ín despaír.
l can shake off everythíng
íf l wríte. but.. .
.. .and that ís the great questíon.
wíll l ever be able to wríte well?
l want to so much.
l want to go on lívíng
even after my death.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
There it goes again.
Mr. Frank, do you hear?
Yes, l hear.
This is the third time.
Third time in quick successions.
lt's a signal.
l tell you, it's Miep, trying to get us.
For some reason, she can't get to us.
She's trying to warn us of something.
-Please, Mr. Dussel. Please.
-You're wasting your breath.
Something's happened, Mr. Frank.
lt's been three days now
that Miep hasn't been to see us.
And today,
not a man has come to work.
There hasn't been a sound
in the building.
EDITH :
Perhaps it's Sunday.
We may have lost track of the days.
You with the diary there,
what day is it?
l don't lose track of the days.
l know exactly what day it is.
lt's Friday, the 4th of August.
lt's Friday and not a man at work.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
l tell you, Mr. Kraler's dead.
That's the only explanation.
He's dead. They've closed down the
building, and Miep's trying to tell us.
She'd never telephone us.
-Please, l beg of you, answer the phone.
-No.
Just pick it up and listen. You don't have
to speak. Just listen and see if it's Miep.
For God's sake, answer the telephone!
l've told you, no.
l'll do nothing that might let anyone
know that we're in this building.
Mr. Frank's right.
-No need to tell us what side you're on.
-lf we wait here quietly and patiently...
...l believe that help will come.
Mr. Dussel.
Mr. Dussel. Mr. Dussel!
[RINGING STOPS]
Too late.
So we just wait here...
-...until we die.
PETRONELLA: l can't stand it.
-l'll kill myself.
-For heaven's sake, stop it!
l think you would be glad if l did.
You want me to die.
Whose fault is it we're here?
We could've been safe in America
or Switzerland. But no, no.
You wouldn't leave when l wanted to.
You couldn't leave your precious things.
-Your furniture!
-That's right, blame it all on me.
-lt's all my fault.
VAN DAAN: Your hats, shoes, dishes!
PETRONELLA: l never had anything l really
wanted. Everything was for your pleasure!
[DOOR SLAMS]
Look, Peter.
Look at the sky.
Aren't the clouds beautiful?
What a lovely, lovely day.
You know what l do...
...when l think l can't stand
another minute of being cooped up?
l think myself outside.
l think l'm on a walk in the park
where l used to go with Father...
...where crocus and jonquils
and the violets grow along the slopes.
You know...
...the most wonderful part
of thinking yourself outside?
You can have it any way you like.
You can have roses and violets and
tulips all blooming in the same season.
lsn't that wonderful?
When l was outside,
l used to take it all for granted.
And now in here,
l've just gone crazy about nature.
l've just gone crazy.
l think if something
doesn't happen soon...
...if we don't get out of here...
...l can't stand much more of this.
l wish you had a religion, Peter.
No, thanks.
Not me.
l don't mean you
have to be Orthodox...
...or believe in heaven and hell
and purgatory and things.
l just mean some religion.
lt doesn't matter what.
Just to believe in something.
When l think of all that's out there...
...trees and flowers...
...and those sea gulls....
When l think
of the dearness of you, Peter...
...and the goodness
of the people we know...
...Mr. Kraler and Miep,
the vegetable man...
...all of them risking their lives
for us every day...
...when l think of these good things,
l'm not afraid anymore.
l find myself.
-And God, and l--
-That's fine. But....
When l begin to think...
...l get mad.
Look at us.
Hiding out here for two years.
Not able to move. Caught like--
Waiting for them to come and get us.
We're not the only people
that have had to suffer.
There have always been people
that have had to.
Sometimes one race,
sometimes another.
-And yet--
-That doesn't make me feel any better.
l know it's terrible,
trying to have any faith...
...when people
are doing such horrible....
But you know
what l sometimes think?
l think the world
may be going through a phase...
...the way l was with Mother.
lt'll pass.
Maybe not for hundreds of years...
...but someday.
l still believe...
...in spite of everything...
...that people are really good at heart.
l wanna see something now.
Not a thousand years from now.
But, Peter...
...if you'd only look at it
as part of a great pattern...
...that we're just a little minute in life.
Listen to us.
Going at each other
like a couple of stupid grownups.
Look at the sky.
lsn't it lovely?
Someday,
when we get outside again.. .
...l'm going to--
[SIREN APPROACHING]
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[MEN CHATGTERING]
[DOORBELL BUllING]
[DOOR BANGING]
MAN :
Open! Open! Open!
[MEN CHATTERING]
Open!
[ALARM SOUNDING]
[CRASHING]
For the past two years,
we have lived in fear.
Now we can live in hope.
[BANGING AND CRASHING]
ANNE:
And so ít seems our stay here ís over.
They've gíven us just a moment
to get our thíngs.
We can each take a bag and whatever
ít wíll hold of clothíng.
Nothíng else.
So. dear díary.. .
.. .that means l must leave you behínd.
Goodbye for a whíle.
P.S.. please. please. anyone.. .
...íf you should fínd thís díary.
wíll you please keep ít safe for me?
Because someday l hope that--
No more.
l had gone to the country
to try to find food.
When l got back,
the police were in the building.
We made it our business
to learn how they knew.
lt was the thief who told them.
We knew the thief. He was--
lt seems strange to me now.
But we were all full of hope in the camp
here in Holland, where they first took us.
The news of the war was good.
The Allies were sweeping
through France.
We felt sure they would get
to us in time to--
But....
ln September,
we were shipped to Poland.
Men to one camp,
women to another.
From there, they were sent to Belsen.
l stayed in Auschwitz.
ln January, we were freed,
the few of us who were left.
The war was not yet over, no.
Took us a long time to get home.
Each time the train would stop...
...we'd all get out at a siding
or a crossing.. .
...and walk from group to group.
''Where were you?
Were you at Belsen?
At Buchenwald?
At Mauthausen? Where?''
''ls it possible
that you ever knew my wife?''
''Did you ever see my husband?
My son? My daughter?''
That's how l found out
about my wife's death.
Margot's. Van Daans'.
Peter.
Dussel.
But...
...Anne....
l still hoped....
Yesterday, l was in Rotterdam.
l met a woman there.
She'd been in Belsen with Anne.
l know now.
ANNE:
In spíte of everythíng.. .
.. .l stíll belíeve that people
are really good at heart.
She puts me to shame.
Subtitles by
SDl Media Group
[ENGLISH SDH]
Want sharper video quality? Want
clearer audio? Try GOM Player now!