So how'd it go last night?
Oh, no!
- Would you hand me that?
- Nice gloves. Are they new?
What do you got when you
have a lawyer up to his neck in cement?
- Your boyfriend out of jail yet?
- Not yet.
Jack, one guess.
Four Seasons. That's easy.
What's the flip side?
Flip side? Flip side.
What is the flip side?
Oh, shit, now my whole day's ruined.
Is everything laid out?
Everything you like.
Oh, these are my favorites.
- What's the story on our friend?
- He jumped, five floors.
Oh, good grief.
What do you want on this?
Pickle, lettuce, tomato? Onion?
What do you want?
Want a coke? No coke?
No, use more Betadine, sweetheart.
He needs the color.
Let's go, Jack. I'm having trouble
keeping his pressure up.
Just splash and slash.
You know, Murray, they ought
to teach a course in suicide technique.
I mean, five floors
is just not good enough.
People use the wrong knife,
can't tie a decent knot. It's terrible.
Nancy, when are you gonna run away
with me? I'm desperate.
I can't eat. I can't sleep.
OK. Blade.
I'm going right in.
We'll tidy up on the way out.
Oh, look at that. You made him bleed.
Retractor.
- Oh, boy, he's a gusher.
- I hate blood.
Cell-saver suction. Malleable, Nancy.
The BP's dropping all the time.
I can't keep up with his loss.
This guy's aorta is in big trouble.
Cut down on the ventilation, Joe.
- Move the lung out of the way.
- OK, I'm hand-ventilating.
Oh, shit.
The aorta's completely transected.
- What do you wanna do?
- Turn off the music.
Clamp and run.
Give me a 20-millimeter Dacron graft.
On my way.
Clamp? Thank you.
- We need some over here.
- I'm getting in a clamp above.
- Snap!
- Clamp. I'm getting in a clamp below...
- I got it, I got it.
- Start the clock!
OK. Take this, will you?
Get it. Take it out.
Graft.
I got it.
- 4-0 Prolene, let's go!
- 4-0 Prolene, Doctor.
- Give him more blood, Joe.
- He's got all we had. We sent for more.
Knit one.
He's 60 over zip.
But we still have a cardiac rhythm.
Not for long.
- Nancy, are my hands shaking?
- No, Doctor.
That's amazing.
I always tremble when you're near.
You've got about three minutes, Jack,
and then he's in big trouble.
What's the difference between a...
Nancy, if you know this one,
don't say anything.
What's the difference between
a lawyer and a catfish?
- You know?
- No idea.
One is a scum-sucking bottom dweller...
and the other one's a fish.
- Right over left and under.
- Left over right and under.
Good scout.
OK, here we go. I'm going
to unclamp slowly. Watch the BP.
- Clamp.
- Easy.
- Off.
- No leaks. We made it.
Looks beautiful.
Ooo-wee!
Let's pack our bags, guys,
and go home. Closing music, Joe.
Oh, that was great, everybody.
And, Nancy, I wanna hear you sing.
Sure, Doctor.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Nancy, you're not singing, doll.
One day, Nancy, one day before I die,
you're gonna sing for me.
Doctor, please.
Sing it. Sing it, buddy! You're gonna
be OK. What's this kid's name?
Sing it, Nancy, baby.
Dr. MacKee? Dr. Blumfield
would like you to stop by OR 2
and take a look at his patient.
- Wow. Where ENT meets ESP.
- Rabbi calls. Go take a look.
- The spirits wait.
- Will you finish up here?
My pleasure. Don't forget your crystals.
Or a Ouija board.
Jack, you throw the wildest parties.
Come on, little doggie.
Come on, fella, wake this kid up.
Have him join us.
When that boy wakes up, tell him,
next time, ten floors minimum.
- Reach for the sky!
- Look out!
You hear that, boy?
That was Dr. Jack MacKee.
- I need a gown.
- Here you go.
Here, Doctor.
Thank you for coming, Doctor.
I've got a rigid bronchoscopy, and...
I'd like you to take a look. I think I found
a lesion in the right main bronchus.
- He's under for another 20?
- Mm-hmm.
Sergio, this is Dr. MacKee.
He's an expert in heart and lungs.
And I'd like him to check you out.
There's nothing to be nervous about.
Hi, Serge. How's it hanging?
I gotta tell ya, if you can hear me,
I'd fire the anesthesiologist.
Dr. MacKee likes to joke.
Doesn't mean he's not caring,
that's just his way. He's a fine doctor.
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah.
- Blumfield's amazing.
- Yeah. He published a paper:
"Dialogue With Unconscious Patients".
Personally I keep it under my pillow.
But this guy really believes
that they hear us.
- I talk to you.
- But I pretend I'm conscious.
- You eating?
- I don't know. I have some chores.
What is it with this throat thing, huh?
You know, Pete wants to do a bypass
on that short order cook.
What's his name? Such a stupid name.
Heart the size of Pennsylvania.
He's 65, he's 250 pounds, he had
a stroke, smokes two packs a day...
Sounds in pretty good shape.
So the guy crumps in six months
and it shows on our survival stats. Hi.
Hi.
- Hello, Doctor.
- Sarah.
See you later.
You hunk.
- Ta-ta.
- Toodle-oo.
Aaah.
- How long have you had this throat?
- All my life.
I don't know. A couple of... A little while.
I can't really see anything.
A little swelling, some inflammation.
Nothing to really worry about.
Are you steaming or what?
What?
- No, nothing.
No wonder you still got a tickle.
What are you doing wasting my time?
- I'm married to a doctor's wife.
- You too, huh?
- Should I be referring you to someone?
- No.
You're right. I should be steaming.
I'll write you a note for some antibiotics.
Better I should write to Anne,
prescribe TLC. How is she?
She's terrific.
I never see you guys
since your dad passed on.
No, I-I kept clearing my throat,
it was like this habit thing.
- Here, Jack.
- Thanks.
- How's business in the big league?
- We're killing 'em.
Hi. How're we doing?
I'm sorry I kept you waiting. Busy day.
- Are we looking after you?
- Yes, thank you.
Good.
- Have you been sore?
- A little sore, yeah.
OK.
Oh, yeah. That's healed fine.
Let's just get those staples out.
Doctor, my husband...
He's a good man, and he...
I think he's a little nervous.
Will the scar always be so...?
Tell your husband you look
like a Playboy centerfold.
You have the staple marks to prove it.
No, no. No! No, no.
I can smell tobacco from 50 paces.
I can smell it through the phone.
You know how I quit?
I'll tell you the truth.
I could kill for a cigarette
this very second.
I'll give you back to my secretary. We'll
arrange to have you in for some tests.
Carrie, take him back. Slap his wrist.
He's not taking the cyclosporine
and he's smoking again.
Whoa. Wait a minute.
What? Pete? Just tell him I'll call back.
My, my.
Legs! Whoo!
I wouldn't be caught dead with someone
stupid enough to drive that car.
Too bad. You'll be missing
my electric roll-in-the-hay bar.
Well, why didn't you say so?
- Hi.
- We have a dumpster.
- Mm-hmm.
Do we have a contractor? No.
- We do.
- This is a record. They've started.
- Yeah, they started wrecking the place.
- Anne...
- What?
They'll have the old kitchen out and the
new one in, and you won't feel a thing.
- And I know about pain. I'm a doctor.
- "I'm a doctor."
- Is it OK about tonight?
- I'm a little nervous, but it'll be fine.
- Why are you nervous?
- Gee, I don't know.
I'm usually so comfortable
speaking in front of 200 people.
You don't have to speak. I'll speak.
You just stand by my side
and look gorgeous.
No, I have to speak. Wait, wait. Are we
talking about the same thing here?
Jack? The parents' meeting?
- Oh, no. No, Jack.
- Hello?
Don't tell me you forgot again.
And then you wonder why the kids
call me "Miss" MacKee!
- You're a total disaster.
- Well, I need you tonight as well.
- Hey.
- I have to change.
We can have dinner together
somewhere later.
And you'll still forget next year,
won't you? Yeah.
- Hola. Lucy. Como estas?
- Bad.
OK.
- Hey, kneepads and helmets.
- Why? We're staying in our yard.
And what, you think
our concrete is softer?
- Hi, Max.
- Hi, Dr. MacKee.
- You, too.
- OK.
- How was school?
- Pretty good.
Good.
If it leaks again, just...
- Hi.
- Hi. How'd it go?
Not bad. I only fainted once.
How was yours?
I personally collected a check
for $50,000 towards a new wing
from some guy who's big in glue.
- Let's go spend it.
- Yeah.
Well, what do you know? Oh, you're
not gonna answer it? Come on.
- No.
- Jack.
You're sounding tired again, you know.
You are. You're doing too much, honey.
Let's just skip dinner and go home
and I'll fix you something
while I still have a kitchen.
OK.
- Hello.
- Jack...
Yes, OK. Yeah, OK, put her through.
Mrs. Street, this is Dr. MacKee.
- Dr. MacKee?
- Yup.
Well. You know what it is.
I'm lying here worrying.
Why would that be?
You took out my husband's lung
a month ago.
Now he wants to mow the lawn.
Can he do that?
- Well, it's pretty dark, but...
- Excuse me?
What's he saying?
Does your husband have
a power mower, or does he push it?
Power mower? I don't know. Whatever
you say. He'll mow the lawn anyway.
- That's the way he is.
- You know I got a damn power mower!
- What?
- I got a power mower!
He says it is a power mower. Hello?
I'm sure it'll be fine.
The exercise will do him good. OK?
OK.
- You OK?
- What? Yeah, I'm fine.
What's that on your shirt?
Jack, is that blood?
You know what? I must have burst
a blood vessel trying not to laugh.
Jack, I have blood on my dress.
My God, I have it in my hair, Jack.
What's going on?
- Hey, relax.
- Relax? Has this happened before?
I'm not bleeding to death here.
There's a danger in feeling
too strongly about your patients.
A danger in becoming too involved.
Surgery is about judgment.
To judge, you have to be detached.
But isn't it unnatural not to become
involved with a patient?
There's nothing natural about surgery.
You're cutting open someone's body.
Is that natural? One day you'll have
your hands around someone's heart.
And it's beating. And you'll think,
"Uh-oh. I shouldn't be here."
Well, then all the more reason
to care about what the patient feels.
- The patient feels sick.
- A surgeon's job is to cut.
You've got one shot.
You go in, you fix it and get out.
- Fix it. Get out.
- Get out. Yeah.
Caring's all about time.
When you've got 30 seconds
before some guy bleeds out...
I'd rather you cut straight
and cared less.
Now, Harris here took a walk
from a fifth floor window.
Should we come back?
I'll be back.
Here, Alan.
"Transected aorta,
partially controlled by the pleura."
- Procedure?
- Clamp above and below.
You can suture the tear direct
or use a Dacron graft.
What do we look for
when we go in, Jay-Jay?
Apart from a great deal
of caring? Anyone?
Significant continuing
blood loss and color.
Yeah. How're we doing?
I hadn't planned on ever waking up.
I feel stupid.
You want my advice, Robert?
Next time you wanna give yourself
some real punishment... try golf.
There's no greater torture.
Thank you.
I need you to take
as deep a breath as you can.
If you were looking for a good ENT man,
who would you go to?
- The Rabbi?
- Give me a break.
Had the lowest mortality stats
in hospital.
So would I if I took out tonsils.
- Jack, my arrested lung's aphasic.
- You mean Richards? Shit.
Obviously some damage from the
arrest. He must have had a stroke.
Transfer him to Neurology.
No one dies in our service.
I can't. I'm out. His wife fired me.
She's already phoned their lawyer...
- How bad is he?
- Horrible.
As of now, his speech is slurred,
he doesn't make any sense.
So he moves to Texas.
And you wonder why I'm so uptight
about our malpractice insurance.
- It's never enough, you wait and see.
- Calm down.
You did a responsible procedure.
Sure. If you sneeze in this place,
they slap a lawsuit on you.
Jack. There's your ENT man.
Ooh!
- Who is she?
- That's Leslie Abbott.
- I think we're talking different talents.
- Absolutely not. She does great throat.
- Puh-lease.
- I'm serious.
- Is this for you, Jack?
- What?
He's been doing
a little coughing for months.
Well, if you won't see Leslie,
I'll check you out.
- You're a gynecologist.
- So? Drop your pants.
Hello. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Busy day.
- Jack MacKee.
- Hmm? Yes, I know. Have a seat.
Right.
Murray Kaplan sends his best.
Oh, that's right.
You're in practice together?
Till we get it right.
- So what seems to be the trouble?
- What?
Nothing. I mean, I have... a tickle.
I've been hoarse.
- Mm-hmm.
- So...
All right. Let's take a look.
Uncross your knees. Back in the chair.
Sit up. Hands on your knees.
Chin forward. And open.
Let's take a look. Close.
Uh-huh. Open.
Open.
All right. Open.
This might be a little bitter.
- That's an anesthetic.
- I want to take a closer look.
Whoa. A periscope!
Won't be pleasant.
Tongue out.
All the way. And hold it... with your hand.
Head forward. And open.
- And "E".
- E-E-E.
- Again.
- E-E-E-E...
- One more time.
And that's all I need.
Doctor, you have a growth.
What?
A tumor. Laryngeal.
Here on the true vocal cord.
I know what "laryngeal" is.
We're gonna need chest X-rays,
blood chemistry,
blood count, UA, EKG...
I'll have to check with my secretary,
but if it's remotely possible,
I'd like to do a biopsy tomorrow. OK?
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Hi.
You OK? I thought you had
a bypass tonight.
His EKG wasn't so good.
We postponed.
I'm fine.
So great! So we have
an evening together.
Yeah.
- Yeah. I'll call Nicky. Nicky!
- Coming!
- Say hi to your Dad!
- Oh, OK.
Hi, Dad. Dad?
Mom, we got disconnected.
- Oh! Hi, Dad!
- Special live appearance.
- How're you doing?
- Pretty good.
Your dad's home tonight.
- What are you doing?
- Hi!
Hi.
So, tell me.
There's nothing to tell.
You know, the longer you don't tell me,
the more frightened I'm getting.
Anne...
What is it, Jack? What have they found?
Huh? Have they found something?
Yep!
OK, so... we'll beat it.
- "We"?
- Mm-hmm.
'We" don't have it, Anne!
"We" don't have it!
It's not a team game.
OK.
Why don't you come to bed?
I have a biopsy tomorrow.
It's a laryngeal tumor.
Oh, God.
A doctor tells this man,
"You have a growth."
Man says, "I demand a second opinion."
Doctor says, "OK... and... you're ugly."
Oh, sweetheart.
Oh, baby...
What am I doing sitting here
like one of the herd?
- Name?
- Dr. MacKee.
- First name?
- Jack.
I've been an attending surgeon
on the staff of this hospital for 11 years.
Then you should know
all about filling in forms.
We've been sitting here for 30 minutes.
Why didn't she give us these
when we first arrived?
She should have.
MacKee!
- MacKee!
- Yeah.
- Go home, Anne.
- No, I'll wait.
- Really, it's no big deal.
- But I want to...
I'll call when I can manage a croak.
OK.
MacKee.
- I don't need a wheelchair.
- You have to sit in the chair.
Listen. I know you. I'm Dr. MacKee.
I don't need a chair.
I'm perfectly capable of walking.
Please sit in the chair, Doctor.
If you fall over, the hospital is liable.
I don't fall over in hospitals.
I know that Dr. Abbott
has been a little delayed.
But we'd like you to undress, please.
Put on the gown you'll find on the bed.
They'll be down for you shortly.
There's been a mistake.
This isn't a private room.
Yes, I'm afraid we don't have
any private rooms just at the moment.
- I'm not about to share a room.
- We don't have any private rooms.
I understand Dr. Abbott felt
this biopsy was urgent.
Hey!
- Hey.
- Don't let her rattle you.
They want your bare butt hanging out
just so you don't get up
and bother them.
I'm Ralph. My bowels are all
screwed up. What are you in for?
Jack MacKee. Throat.
What, your tongue,
your voice box, your tonsils?
There's a lot of software in there.
- Voice box.
- Oh, you poor bastard.
Your first time under the knife?
I bet you feel like you don't know
what's going on? Am I right?
Well, don't worry.
They don't know, either.
My doctor, the son of a bitch,
half the time he's lying to me.
And I can tell. I'm a cop.
What's your line?
I'm a doctor.
They're gonna cut you, doc?
Yeah.
Hey, Jack. How's it hanging?
Don't tell me, I can see for myself.
Hi. What's going on here?
The Ritz was full.
- What time are they doing you?
- When Madame shows up.
I spoke to her lawyer. He's very bullish.
He says you're the expert, so we need
you on the witness stand, OK?
- Don't go shuffling off to Buffalo just yet.
- But after that...
Sure, after that, do what you like.
I couldn't care less.
You OK?
You want me to go in with you?
I want you to go in instead of me.
- I did your bypass. Very clean.
- Great.
- I even played your closing music.
- Did Nancy sing?
- No, Nancy did not sing.
- That's good.
Yeah, it's this one.
She's never
gonna come back 100%.
I know.
Do you suppose you could get me
a thinner sheet?
I'm not sure everyone
can see through this one.
It must be some sort of a shunt.
What do you think
of those blood gasses?
- She's hypoxic.
- I know.
But I saw the chest today
and the atelectasis is almost gone.
There's something else going on.
Does she have a murmur? You could be
dealing with an Eisenmenger Syndrome.
Yes, it talks! Amazing!
I have the radiographic video.
You wanna take a look at it?
- Yeah.
- Who's the internist?
Oh, hey, hey, Barry,
I've been looking for you.
- So?
- I was late. It was very late.
Good morning.
Everything all right there?
- Now you're gonna feel a little prick.
- Please, Doctor, we've only just met.
Looks like a sweet dream.
Huh? Now, just keep dreaming.
Don't wake up.
There's no need for you
to wake up, OK? Keep dreaming.
We're just gonna roll you over
on your side. Come on.
Help me out. Help me out. Help me out.
Nice. You just stay there for me.
Hey! Mr. Brown, relax.
Mr. Brown, relax, man.
Hey, hey! Just relax, don't strain.
Keep dreaming.
Mr. Brown, you know you're scheduled
for a barium enema.
Relax. It's just an enema! Now breathe.
Just tell Mr. Jaconelli
Dr. MacKee's wife called
and that I expect him to get back
to me personally about this, OK?
Right. Thank you.
I'm Leslie Abbott.
Jack? Jack, honey. Dr. Abbott's here.
Hi.
I'm sorry. I understand
there was some confusion
regarding beds and procedures.
Yeah.
I hope you biopsied my throat
and not my colon.
I'm sorry.
So, did Path throw the I Ching?
The tumor is malignant.
It's a T-2 lesion.
You're welcome to a second opinion.
No. One enema's enough for any tumor.
- How will you treat it?
- I'm recommending radiation therapy.
I want it cut out.
Radiation will reduce the mass
for this kind of tumor,
and we got a high cure rate.
80% or better.
And if I have to cut,
I risk losing the voice.
- Do you know a good radiation man?
- Clark Kent.
Charlie Reed is terrific.
You could meet with him, get an MR
and they could start fitting you
for treatment as of tomorrow.
What time tomorrow?
I have open heart scheduled
for tomorrow.
Dr. MacKee... you've got cancer.
Tomorrow's great. Thanks.
I've signed you out. I think you're gonna
be more comfortable in your own bed.
And you shouldn't be talking.
OK, we'll see you later.
- I can do it.
- OK.
Honey, listen, just...
bring the car around, OK?
OK.
Dr. MacKee?
I just heard. Did they get
the biopsy results back yet?
Yeah. It's positive.
How'd you hear?
Did they post it in the men's room?
No.
Come on, I'll walk down with you.
I'm fine, thank you. I'll be just fine.
I feel like having a cigarette.
I have a tumor, my throat feels
like shit, and I want a cigarette.
Yeah.
We should have come
in the red lobster.
This car always makes you depressed.
We're laughing. They cut my throat
and we're laughing. Can you believe it?
I couldn't bear it if...
Better.
Not better.
We'll strip it down
on the weekend. Nicky?
- Max is waiting.
- Yeah.
Your mother told you
I had a test yesterday?
Yeah.
Well, it turns out I've got a growth,
a lesion in my throat which is...
not great.
But it's the kind of tumor
which responds well to radiation,
which is great. Which is...
It... it's pretty great.
- Dad, I gotta go.
- OK.
This MRI examination
takes about 40 minutes.
And it's very important that you don't
move at all during that time.
- Are you claustrophobic?
- Only in cramped spaces.
I just filled in all these forms.
I don't get this.
Why don't you get this stuff from
Radiology? It's 50 feet down the hall.
I know. I'm sorry.
It's the same for everybody.
- We have to have our own records.
- Yeah, but...
- Hi.
- Great hat.
- Thanks.
- Hello. Radiation Therapy,
Laurie speaking. No. Yes.
Yes.
Wait till you see the disclaimer
forms. They deliver them in a truck.
- Uh-huh. Let me have a look.
- Um...
I'll be right with you.
Let me call you back once I've located it.
Well, you know, busy. Yeah.
What seems to be the problem?
I don't wanna pull rank,
but I don't know if you realize
I'm an attending surgeon at this hospital.
I knew that, Doctor, yes.
OK, good. So you'll appreciate
when I say I have patients of my own
who are waiting for me
while I'm waiting for you,
which is why I mention
I'm not looking for VIP...
You know, the pity is
you were late getting here, so...
Hang on! I was not late getting here.
Radiology was late with my MRI.
I was not...
Please don't
make me strain my voice.
- Dr. MacKee?
- Yeah.
I'm Charles Reed.
- Oh.
- Come in.
- How we doing?
- Super.
Sit down.
No, I've been sitting.
Dr. MacKee, my feeling - for what it's
worth - if we're going to treat you,
you're going to meet the team here
every day for the next six weeks.
And?
I don't know what it's like
at the top of this building,
but down here, we try to be civil.
Oh, well, upstairs we're very hostile.
We meet our patients, we come
right out and tell them our feelings...
for what they're worth.
OK.
So... we're not gonna fall in love.
What else do I need to know?
Your chest is clear.
We'll get the MRI from tomorrow
and get started
assuming there's no spread
to the lymph nodes.
And the rest of this visit,
we'll fit you up for treatment.
Good.
And if the lymph nodes show positive?
I'll discuss a different treatment
with Dr. Abbott.
And me.
Yeah, sure.
Watch your step. Through here.
If we can just have you come around
on this side... and hop up on here
and lie so your head faces that way.
Careful.
Your last guest stole the bed linen.
Here, we're gonna put
your wrists in the straps.
When I ask you to,
I want you to pull up really hard. OK?
Head down. OK, and pull.
- What are you doing?
- Just marking the target.
- OK. This mark'll come off.
- Hey, it's nothing to worry about.
We just need to take a film and make
sure we're hitting the right spot.
- What are you doing?
- We're just making a mask of your head
in this position, all right? It's real fast.
All right.
...for an hour already.
- I understand. I'm sorry.
- Great. Finally! Dr. Taylor...
- I know, I know.
- Just give me five minutes.
- Doctor...
Hello, Mrs. Arcari.
We'll be right with you.
Oh, man.
- Hey, partner.
- Hi.
God, Jack, you look like shit.
Is this the radiation?
- No, this is nearly the radiation.
- What are you doing here?
I have a room full of patients.
What about the valve job later?
What's his name?
Choy. That'll be fine.
I wouldn't want you
cutting my heart today.
I told you, I'll be fine.
Jack, we had a talk this morning.
Nobody planned...
- "We"? Who's "we"?
- Pete, Ed, me. The practice.
No. Pete, Ed, you and me
is the practice!
Gosh, wherever I go these days,
I'm getting cut out of the talk.
- What?
- So...
What did "we" talk about?
Jack, you're sick. Stay home.
Stay home a week, two weeks,
three weeks, whatever it takes.
- I don't want to stay home.
- Annie called me. She's worried as hell.
- I don't wanna stay home!
- OK.
What we don't want to happen, buddy...
is to start canceling surgery time,
missing appointments,
losing ground on the stats, that's all.
From tomorrow,
I have 15 minutes' treatment a day.
- Sure, Jack.
- 15 minutes in six weeks,
that's it, it's gone.
So let's go back to work.
And can everybody wipe that caring look
off their face! Is that possible?
Because it's a royal pain!
Come on, Carrie, let's go.
- Ow! Ow! What are you doing?
- I'm just giving you a tiny tattoo.
What? You're what?
Nice and still now.
These are gonna be permanent marks.
Shouldn't there be a lead apron?
Oh, no. The beam is focused
on your larynx, doc. You don't need it.
But can we have the apron
anyway though, please?
Really, you don't need it, doc.
But, don't move.
- I don't wanna wear kneepads.
- You've got to wear 'em.
- Anybody need a doctor?
- Yes.
It's an abrasion. Leave it open.
- Good day?
- Great.
I thought to myself, "What the hell?"
I went out and I got drunk,
and decided to have myself tattooed.
What do you think?
That's where they shoot the X-rays.
Dr. Reed's not here yet?
Oh.
- Um...
- Oh, thank you so much.
I'm not doing so well today.
Hi.
Sit down. I'm leaving anyway.
Thank you.
Oh, Dr. MacKee. I'm sorry.
Dr. Reed can't be here this morning.
No. No. Why not?
He's been held up. I think there's
some admin meeting all day today.
- When do I see him?
- He'll be here next week.
No, look it, if I can't see him today,
I'll see him tomorrow!
- We're closed weekends.
- Laurie?
I'll be right there, Carol.
I was told this was
to be a daily treatment.
Well, I'm sorry. I don't make the rules.
I'm sure that...
Why don't we from now on,
in this hospital,
we should drop "I'm sorry"
from conversation, OK?
Let's just assume
it begins every sentence.
"I'm sorry, the doctor
can't see you today",
"I'm sorry you have
to fill in another form",
"I'm sorry we gave you
the wrong treatment."
What do we think?
There's not much point
shouting at Laurie.
- Excuse me?
- She's just doing her job.
If you want to shout,
go shout at a doctor.
- I am a doctor.
- Not when you're sitting here.
- How come you're so calm?
- Who?
You. You seem to be taking it so well.
No. I have a grade four brain tumor.
It took my doctors three months to
find it. I didn't take that so well at all.
Actually, they didn't find it.
I rear-ended a few cars,
fell over, blacked out.
Short of the tumor
jumping out and singing,
there was nothing else it could do
to get recognized.
See, now I'd call that negligence,
wouldn't you?
Well, that's-that's...
it's difficult to comment.
Oh, yeah. It's a club, isn't it? I forgot.
- Did you get tests?
- Sure.
- What?
- CAT scan... two.
Of course that was way down the track,
after they gave me aspirin
and sent me home.
Oh, and then what?
There was stress management.
Yeah. Oh, and then traffic school.
That was really helpful.
My father had a patient.
Same diagnosis, grade four.
He has grandchildren now.
- Are you serious?
- Sure.
- June. Let's do it.
- That's me. June.
See you later, June.
You look good today, June.
- I'll check it.
- Thanks, Walter.
- Anytime.
- Murray, do me a favor, will ya?
Call Radiology and ask them
for the results of my MRI.
- Doesn't Leslie have them?
- I can't get her. I can't get Reed.
And I can't wait any longer.
They ought to release them
to you straight off.
I mean, I don't know what you think
I'm going to accomplish.
Hi. Who's this?
Hey, Joanne, Murray Kaplan.
How you doing?
Good. Listen, do me a favor, Joanne.
Pull me an MR file, would you?
Jack MacKee. Capital "M", capital "K".
No. No, it's Leslie Abbott's.
No, I know that, Joanne. Sure...
Hello, this is Dr. MacKee
and this is my file.
No, it's not my patient.
It's in my name. I'm the patient.
No, you do not need
to clear it with anybody.
You just go now, open the file
and tell me if it shows any spread
to the lymph nodes.
Thank you.
Dr. MacKee. We're ready in one.
We'll be right with you.
Thank you. Thank you, I appreciate that.
- Zero spread.
- Oh, thank God! Oh, God!
Dr. Blumfield...
This is the ghost
of a thousand murdered tonsils.
Put us back...
Dr. Eli! This is your
tongue depressor - lick me!
Hi.
Anne!
Nick!
Well, hello. Chicken or sausage?
Uh, hi. What are you doing out here?
I'm celebrating. No spread
to the lymph nodes. They're clear.
- What?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God, that's wonderful.
That's, um...
- Oh, thank God!
- Yeah, I thought so.
So join the party.
Have a piece of sausage.
Oh, no, no. I'm... I've eaten.
OK.
- Where's Nicky?
- He's sleeping over with Max.
Great. Doesn't this smell great?
Jack, are you angry about something?
You know, I always work late
on Friday nights.
- Sure. Do these look burnt?
- I mean, if I'd known...
But, I didn't even know
you were expecting this news.
Why didn't you tell me?
You should've called me. I would have...
Let's go inside.
- Aren't you cold?
- Yeah, you are cold.
Will you just tell me
how you want me to be, Jack?
OK? Because I never know these days.
Really. Like, like, like, what are we now?
Are we happy, are we not happy?
Are we close, not close?
Please just tell me, I'll be there.
Well, this is quality time.
Why couldn't they send us the new IDs
through the mail? Do we know?
Tell them you're a big doctor. Cut in line.
Are you angry with me?
You lied to me.
What?
My tumor. I see it giving me
certain freedoms I never allowed myself.
Yeah, like being incredibly hostile.
Like being honest and expecting
people around me to do the same.
What did I lie about for Christ's sake?
I'm dying. Please don't waste my time.
- Miss Ellis.
- Thank you.
Your card.
They should've found your tumor.
You were right. Somebody screwed up.
You should've had an MRI.
But the system stinks.
Insurance companies tell us
what tests we can and cannot do.
An MRI, which I know
would have found your tumor...
costs about $1,000.
It's appalling.
And what about your father's patient?
The one who recovered?
There was no patient.
OK.
Just don't lie to me again.
One, two, three, four. One...
You wanna try? Show him how to do it.
- Pretty amazing.
- I'm not that bad.
I got a date.
- Great.
- No, I wish.
In court. So we got to get
our stories straight.
What stories? Alan, who's first?
- The terminal in 1217.
- Terminal?
What terminal? Bus terminal?
No... the dying patient in 1217.
What's the patient's name?
- Jay-Jay?
- Mr. Winter.
OK, now Mr. Winter
is either alive or dead.
So, is Mr. Winter alive,
or should we advise the morgue?
Call another patient "terminal" and that's
how you'll describe your career!
What room is he in?
Barbara died.
The older woman with the knitting.
She didn't wake up this morning.
- What are you thinking?
- I don't know.
That Barbara had been knitting
that big shawl for her granddaughter
for months... and she finished it.
And I've never been to London...
or Italy.
I never had a baby.
I never learned to use chopsticks.
And I had a front-row ticket
to see the American Indian Dance
Theater. They were touring here.
God, I've always wanted to see them.
You know, they have
these great costumes.
And I was in this place.
So...
It's just one more thing to add to my list.
They'll be back.
In six months.
Mr. Maris, any questions?
You know, Doctor... it seems strange.
There's somebody out there
alive, walking around...
Then something terrible will happen,
and they'll die.
Then I'll have their heart.
I think about that.
Yep.
So, we wait.
It may take a little while
before we have a heart to harvest.
I know.
Mr. Maris, it's always a good idea
to set your affairs in order.
My affairs are in order.
Good.
I have confidence in you.
OK.
Thank you.
Dr. MacKee.
I want you to have another MRI.
- Really? Why?
- Your exams were not what we'd like.
I spoke to Dr. Abbott, she agreed.
We'll do the MRI, and then I think
you should talk with her.
What do you mean,
"Not what we'd like"?
We had hoped to be seeing
some reduction in the tumor by now.
We haven't.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
I came up here when they finally
diagnosed my tumor.
I thought I'd throw myself over the edge.
God, I was so...
I felt... like my skin was coming off.
Oh, I screamed and screamed and...
There was... there was this bird
perched right over there.
And it just looks at me real strange,
like "Lady, what is your problem?"
And I laughed.
I felt so stupid that I just...
laughed out loud.
You know what?
I think it was an angel.
Go ahead and scream.
No one can hear you.
I don't wanna scream.
- Go ahead and jump.
- I don't wanna jump.
Then fight it. Fight it!
That tour, that tour...
is that still happening?
- What tour?
- The Indians, the dancers.
- I think so.
- Good.
If they're in New York, we're in trouble.
But we might find
they're just down the block.
- I can't do that. I can't go.
- I'll take care of it. It's my treat.
No, no, no. It's not that. It's just...
Excuse me, is this my intrepid friend
or not? We're going!
Come on.
Wait, this is crazy. Look at me.
I'm not dressed for a...
You look great. OK, Carrie,
call me back when you know.
- Hi. Winnemucca?
- Nevada.
We fly to Reno, we drive
for two hours into the desert.
OK, what do we need?
We need two tickets to Reno, a car,
and two tickets to the concert.
No, it's for me and a Miss June Ellis.
You got that?
Thanks, Carrie, you're great.
Can you just pickup and go like this?
"I see my tumor giving me certain
freedoms I never allowed myself."
I had a strange,
wonderful dream last night.
I flew right over your house
with a full head of hair.
I love that song.
- Can we stop?
- You mean, take a break or...?
No, I mean, just stop.
OK, I just... I'm a little nervous
about missing the concert, the Indians.
Jack... it wasn't the concert.
It's the time.
It's rushing past me.
I don't wanna rush past this.
I don't wanna rush past
anything anymore. I can't.
I just can't, Jack.
Anything. Anything you want.
I'm sorry
for dragging you out here.
"Get in, fix it, get out."
That's what I tell my residents.
She missed her concert,
take her to the concert.
You know what's special to me, Jack?
I mean, truly special?
This.
Now.
Do you pray, June?
Is that what holds you together?
Oh, I pray.
I meditate.
I eat chocolate.
I go dancing.
- Hello?
- Anne, did I wake you?
Oh, God. Jack, where are you?
I don't know. I'm in the desert,
in a phone booth
somewhere between Reno and home.
Why? What are you doing, Jack, huh?
I went a little crazy. I'm OK.
I'll explain in the morning.
No, no, no, no. Tell me now.
- I can't.
- Just tell me, OK?
- I don't think the radiation is working.
- Oh. God...
- They don't seem to think it's working.
- Oh. Sweetheart.
Let me come and get you.
- I'm with a fellow patient.
- Oh...
She's a friend, Anne.
She has a brain tumor.
Oh. I missed the plane.
I'll be home in the morning.
Good night. Jack.
- I'm late.
- Anne, can we meet?
Can I find you and talk?
You're breaking my heart, Jack.
- "Where's my lung?"
- Where's my lung?
That's exactly what he said,
this is two years later.
No, it's true.
Apparently he'd seen some shrink
who told him he was suffering
from "organ bereavement".
He should ask for his lung back.
I told him he should dial 1-900-LUNG.
Yeah. "Hello, remember me?
I want my lung back."
I don't believe it. It's Mr. Dribble.
The guy's a fruitcake.
- That's your patient.
- That's Richards? What's he doing?
I saved the guy's life,
and then he just fucks me over.
- He's suing me. Is that crap?
- See you later.
Jack, where are you going? Jack!
The guy's taking us to court!
I'm telling you, man. It's unbelievable.
- Hey, Mister, you need a hand?
- Keys. Locked... car.
I'm sorry, you lost your keys?
Locked... Keys. Locked. In car.
You locked your keys in the car. Oh, my.
I'm late. Speech therapy.
Look, you go on ahead.
I work here at the hospital.
I'll have your keys left for you at the front
desk. I come equipped. I'll make a call.
It's not a problem.
Name is... Richards.
Mr. Richards? Don't worry.
It's not a problem.
This... just driving me crazy.
- It's gonna be OK.
- Thank you.
Aahhh...
OK.
I'd make a gag,
but I'm busy gagging.
How's it look?
Well, I think Dr. Reed
had already mentioned that the, um,
the tumor had gotten bigger.
No. No, no!
He said it was worried it hadn't
gotten smaller. He didn't... Is it bigger?
It's disappointing because we, uh... we
get a very good cure rate with radiation.
Yeah, that's disappointing as hell.
Look, look. OK, I'm asking.
This is torture.
What is the prognosis on my
vocal cords? Can you save them?
I won't know until I'm there.
But that would be the idea, yes.
Maria? Yeah, I'm looking at moving
the tongue or the parotid a day or two
to make way for the laryngeal.
Or the other option is doing
the adenoids late on the 20th.
Yeah, that works. Adenoids late on the
20th and laryngeal afternoon of the 18th.
No. No, I don't want you
cutting me in the afternoon.
Excuse me?
You'll be tired in the afternoon,
and ragged and hungry.
You'll have been on your feet for hours.
Come on, we both know how it is.
I am the doctor and you are my patient.
And I am telling you
when I am available.
Now let's get this thing out
before it does any more damage.
Knife.
Let's go, boy.
- Are you OK, Doctor?
- Jack?
Let's go, Jacko.
OK, here we go.
It's Jack.
I lost it.
June, I lost it today.
I should go home. It's too late, I'll go.
No, it's OK. It's OK. Come in.
And then, there's Anne. But...
No, you know.
Um, I'll go. This is terrible.
I woke you up.
"There's Anne, but..."?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I've kept her there, you know,
over there, for so long.
And now... I can't get my arm down.
I have to have the operation, June.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, you can't go...
Dr. MacKee's headed back there.
You'd better come out.
Dr. MacKee. What is it?
Do you have a minute?
You can see for yourself.
I have a waiting room full of patients.
- One fewer.
- What?
You have one fewer patients. I'm out.
Look, Doctor, I know
how you must be feeling.
That's the problem. You don't have
the first idea what I'm feeling.
I think we better continue this
conversation some other time.
I think you ought to brush up
your act, Dr. Abbott.
Because today I'm sick.
Tomorrow or the day after
or 30 years from now, you'll be sick.
Every doctor becomes a patient
somewhere down the line, and then...
it'll hit you as hard as it's hit me.
I'm finding you very offensive,
so if you don't mind...
Sure.
If I had a patient like me
when I was a doctor like you, I'd...
I'll just... wait for my file.
I'll get you your file.
Airmail. Thank you.
- Eli...
- Jack.
- May I speak with you for a minute?
- Sure.
I need a partial laryngectomy.
Would you do it?
I don't know a doctor I trust more.
I'll do it tomorrow.
Tomorrow...
Yeah, I'm not working,
so... we'll get you in.
Thank you.
You know, I've been pretty...
No, very insulting about you in the past...
which I'm ashamed of.
Dr. Blumfield. Ready in two.
Yeah, well, that's OK, Jack. I, um...
I've always wanted to slit your throat.
Now I'm gonna get a chance to do that.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Murray, can I speak to you, please?
- What's wrong?
- Let's go in here.
- What's going on?
- I have to have surgery on my throat.
- A partial laryngectomy.
- Jesus, Jack. Why didn't you say?
I knew you were jumpy,
and then yesterday...
I was saying to Pete,
I thought it was me or something.
- I asked Eli Blumfield.
- The Rabbi?
It's tomorrow. I trust him.
I don't wanna lose my voice.
Well, me neither. I need you talking.
Tomorrow...
But even if I can talk...
I won't be testifying.
Say that again?
I won't testify because I tell the truth
and the truth is that poor guy
had a history of thrombophlebitis.
- Well, how did you know that?
- I called his internist.
What'd you think?
You could just tear up his records?
It's not relevant, Jack.
You could argue as an expert.
No.
What did you do this for, huh?
Checking up on me?
You wanted a witness.
I wanted to know what I was witnessing.
14 years is what you're witnessing.
Me covering your tail,
you covering mine.
Why did you pull his file?
You can't do that.
It's not relevant. It's a judgment thing.
I'm sorry, Murray.
No, no.
It's not just me, partner.
Your neck is on the fucking line, too.
Yeah, that's right.
Jack, you're killing me.
I have a surgery.
I'll find someone else to help me out.
Jack, hell you will. Hey, Jacko.
Jack!
Carrie told me about your surgery.
I was going to...
Oh, Anne...
Yeah, well, that's how I find out
most things about us, you know.
Dinner dates, messages,
your problems...
through your secretary.
It's the 28th, is that right?
It's tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Eli Blumfield's gonna do me.
You heard that from me first.
Last night... Did you go
to your friend? June?
Yes, I did.
You know what I resent?
I don't resent her.
Truly, I... I'm sure she's...
She must be very special.
It's just that...
You have a friend to go to. You know?
And you were always my friend,
and... now I can't go to you.
Anyway, blah-blah-blah. I have to go.
You know, it's funny.
I wake up every morning,
and I have this... this feeling.
This sensation.
And I didn't know what it was.
What is it? Am I hungry? Am I tired?
Am I sad?
Then I realized... I'm just lonely.
June?
- June, it's Jack.
- I don't think she can hear you.
It's me. It's Jack.
And I came over last night
and I made you so tired.
I have my operation tomorrow.
And selfish to the end, I was hoping
you'd be there to help me through it.
Oh, June...
I'm... I'm really terrified.
That's the truth... which I got from you.
The truth.
Do you know, I don't even
know anything about you.
Not really.
I know you love life.
And I know you can dance.
I hope you always fly over my house...
with your lovely long hair.
My friend June died today.
How you doing, Jack?
I'd rather be in Philadelphia.
- Hi, Doctor.
- Nancy. Hi.
My, my, my.
- We're rooting for you, Jack.
- Thank you, Joe.
Yeah, do. Root like crazy.
Did you find it? Great.
OK, Jack, your neck feels clear to me.
Good.
I'm gonna keep telling you everything
that I'm doing as I'm doing it.
So I want you to just relax
as much as possible.
And before I scrub in,
we have a little treat for you.
Oh...
We got the tumor, and there was
no cross-over, which is good.
It's great.
I was not able to save
all of the vocal cords,
so I... I can't make any guarantees
about the voice, Anne.
It was very clean,
and we're just gonna have
to wait and see.
- Are you OK here?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine, thanks.
Nicky?
I meant to give this
to you at the hospital.
Sorry.
That's not the color I asked for!
No, I wanted the wall
to match the cupboard!
How many times
do I have to tell you that?
We sat down yesterday and I circled
the one I wanted. Remember that?
Yeah... Oh, great, so now I'm color-blind
on top of everything else?
I know what I was doing.
This is what you asked for.
- Terrific.
- Well, I warned you that color...
Look, just forget it!
I'll paint it myself, OK?
Jack, let go of me. What are you doing?
I don't wanna go outside. Jack!
No!
No, I don't wanna yell at you.
I want to go inside! Do you mind?
Yeah, right. And now it's done.
Are you happy?
Now would you please
let me go inside? God, Jack.
You're crazy.
Jack, stop it. Jack, stop it!
Stop it, OK! OK.
But get in the house.
If you want me to yell at you,
I'll yell at you in the house, OK?
Now get inside!
Jack!
Look, Jack, I don't know
what you want from me.
No, you don't. You don't need me.
No, I don't believe you.
I was there. I was there for you, Jack,
and you didn't need me.
Yeah, me, too. Me, too.
Stop it! Stop blowing that thing! Stop it!
Stop it!
"Start again"? Jesus...
Jack, stop it!
Stop it! Stop it! God...
Goddamn it!
I just wish I'd never given you
this stupid whistle!
I love you.
You're talking.
Shh.
Aah!
Hello, Jack. Welcome back.
So...
They're harvesting the heart
any minute now.
It'll be flown in from New York,
whence all good things come.
- What's the problem?
- Nothing, Doctor.
What?
My wife wants to know what's
impossible to know about the donor.
She thinks because we say
things like "kindhearted"...
"good-hearted"... that these
qualities come from the heart.
Tell her I think they do.
Yes?
The helicopter's landed.
15 minutes, Doctor.
Thank you, Nancy.
Arturo... here we go.
- Here you go. Good luck.
- Thanks.
OK. We're all hooked up.
Watch your flow
and watch your pressure.
Ross clamp is... off.
Start beating, sweetheart.
Go, heart!
Your wife will be delighted, Arturo.
It's a beautiful heart.
Any messages for me?
These... and something personal.
Oh, thanks.
It's been an hour already.
I'm out of here, people.
- Hasn't been an hour.
- Yeah, it has.
Hi! Sorry, I kept you waiting.
Good, good, good.
OK, well.
Can you strip naked and put on your
hospital gowns, quick as you can?
- Dr. MacKee, this is a joke.
- I'm not laughing. Ah, here they are.
Alan, Roger, Lonnie...
- Let's go. Sarah, Jay-Jay, Michael.
- Anything in a paisley?
Doctors...
You have spent a lot of time
learning the Latin names
for diseases your patients might have.
Now it's time to learn...
something simpler about them.
Patients have their own names.
Sarah.
Alan. Jack.
They feel frightened...
embarrassed and vulnerable.
And they feel sick.
Most of all, they want to get better.
Because of that...
they put their lives in our hands.
I could try to explain what that means
until I'm blue in the face.
But, you know something,
it wouldn't mean a thing.
It sure as hell never did to me.
So, for the next 72 hours,
you'll each be allocated
a particular disease.
You'll sleep in hospital beds,
eat hospital food.
Hospital food?
You'll be given all the appropriate tests.
Tests you will one day prescribe.
Unbelievable.
You are no longer... doctors.
You are hospital patients.
So, good luck. I'll see you on my rounds.
Dear Jack...
You've just left. And I've been
sitting here worrying about you.
You were talking about Anne
and not knowing how to let her close.
How to let anyone close.
And I thought of this little story for you.
I hope you get it before your operation.
Going up?
There was a farmer
who had a lot of fields.
And he kept all of the birds
and creatures away from his crops
with traps and fences.
He was very successful.
But he was very lonely.
So. One day. He stood in the middle
of his fields to welcome the animals.
He stayed there from dawn to dusk with
his arms outstretched calling to them.
But not a single animal came.
Not a single creature appeared.
They were terrified. You see.
Of the farmer's new scarecrow.
Dear Jack. Just let down your arms...
and we'll all come to you.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/ub5x
Help other users to choose the best subtitles