Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Come on, Doc.
- You gotta stay down here.
- Yeah.
Check this out.
Prints right here.
Reporting live from the home...
...of Dr. Richard Kimble...
...a prominent surgeon
at Chicago Memorial Hospital.
Details are sketchy...
...but we know that Dr. Kimble's wife,
Helen, was found murdered tonight.
Area 6 detectives are bringing
Dr. Kimble out.
We assume they will take him
to the Area 6 police station...
...where they hope he can shed some light
on what happened tonight.
As I indicated,
she was found shortly before midnight.
We know that she made a 911 call to police...
...indicating that there was an intruder
or that she was being assaulted.
Details are very sketchy.
We know that he and his wife, Helen...
...were at the Four Seasons Hotel
earlier tonight...
...at a fundraiser
for the Childrens' Research Fund.
– Hey.
– Rich, remember Cara?
– Nice to see you.
Straighten that arm. You'll slice.
Golf pro teach you that?
My wife.
Before I forget...
...thanks for the loaner. Keys are downstairs.
– Any gas in it?
– Yes. Enough.
Alec, Richard Kimble.
– How are you?
– Dr. Kimble.
– Guess that works too.
– Absolutely.
– Anytime.
– Oh, yeah.
I think that's a great idea,
getting the guys to try that project.
All right, knock it off.
There's nothing to see here.
You, come with me.
Excuse me.
Thank you. I was down to my last joke.
You look really beautiful tonight.
Thanks, honey.
I know you hate these things,
but I love looking at you in a tux.
I feel I look like a waiter.
- – Hello?
- Dr. Kimble?
– Yes, it is.
– Sorry to bother you...
...but Dr. Stevens is in Emergency OR
and asked if you could give him a hand.
Call him and say I'll be right there.
– Thank you, doctor.
– Yup.
Thank you. Good night.
I'll wait up for you.
Talk to me. What do we got here?
Thanks for coming.
A 58-year-old. Just pulled his gallbladder.
Bleeding.
Big time. It's in the liver bed.
What are his coags?
– They're all messed up.
PT's 36 and the rest are off the wall.
Where'd he come from?
Lentz's name is on the chart.
We paged him, but no answer.
Let me in there. Give me some room.
Give me a clamp.
Give me suction.
Have you been getting
any threats at work?
Co-workers, hospital staff,
anything like that at all?
Uh....
– No.
– Anything unusual going on...
...as far as phone calls, people hanging up?
People coming to the door?
Tradespeople?
Not that I know of.
Back on this fight
with this guy with the one arm.
Did it happen upstairs or downstairs?
– Upstairs.
– Uh-huh.
And he had which? A right or a left arm?
With a gimmick on it?
Right arm.
Is it one of those with the hooks, or--
No, he had, like, a--
He had a cosmetic hand.
The security system in your house,
it's a pretty good one.
Anyone have the coding
besides you and your wife?
Our maid.
She knows the code and has a key.
Those scratches on your neck...
...did the one-armed guy do that?
Helen scratched me when I moved her.
Before or after the fight
with the one-armed guy?
I told you.
You own a gun?
Do you own a gun?
Yes, we have one in the house.
It's in your name?
Yes.
Where do you usually keep that gun?
The one that you own.
It's in Helen's table.
Bedside table.
Do you keep much jewelry in the house?
Uno.
His fingerprints are all over the lamp...
...the gun and the bullets...
...and the good doctor's skin
is under her fingernails.
Your wife's got the money in the family,
hasn't she?
Helen comes from a wealthy family, yes.
Is she insured?
Yes, she is.
Who's the beneficiary?
– I am.
– The sole beneficiary?
Yes.
Financially,
you won't be hurting after this, will you?
She was worth a lot of money.
Are you suggesting that I killed my wife?
Are you saying that I crushed her skull
and shot her?
How dare you!
When I came home,
there was a man in my house.
– I fought with him.
– Uh-huh.
– The one-armed man.
– He had a mechanical arm.
– Plastic? Rubber?
– Find this man!
You find this man!
How tall?
He took everything from me.
Oh, Jesus.
What did he weigh?
What color was his hair?
What color were his eyes?
We can't help you if you don't help us.
Book him.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury...
...you will hear iron-clad proof
of Richard Kimble's guilt.
Indisputable scientific evidence...
...that on the night of January 20...
...Richard Kimble did viciously...
...attack...
...and brutally murder his wife.
You'll hear more than that.
You will hear a voice from the grave.
The voice of Helen Kimble
identifying her killer...
...her husband, Richard Kimble.
Detective Kelly...
...tell us what you saw at the victim's home
on the night of the murder.
No forcible entry was found.
From the beginning of the investigation,
it didn't appear to be a break-in.
Nothing was missing.
I'm home.
Who won the game?
His prints were on the gun and bullets.
No other sets were found,
other than the housekeeper's...
...and the deceased's.
Mrs. Kimble's skull fracture caused
a massive hemorrhage to the brain.
It took less than 5 minutes for her to die.
Your Honor, we'd ask to play
Helen Kimble's 911 emergency call...
...previously identified
by the Chicago Police Dispatcher.
Emergency 911.
Please help me.
What seems to be the problem?
He's here still, in the house.
Did I hear you right?
Someone's in your house?
He's trying to kill me.
Could you repeat that?
Ma'am?
He's trying to kill me.
Is your attacker still in the house?
- Richard....
- Ma'am?
Richard....
He's trying to kill me.
Mr. Kimble...
...having considered all the aggravation
and mitigation in this case...
...and found the offense was brutal
and indicative of wanton cruelty...
...it's this court's judgment that you be
remanded to Illinois State Penitentiary...
...where you will await
execution by lethal injection...
...on a date to be set forth
by the attorney general of this state.
May God have mercy on your soul.
- Carlson.
- Here.
- Partida.
- Yeah.
Copeland.
– What?
You be nice now.
Kimble.
Yeah.
Let's go, gentlemen.
Four prisoners conning out.
Prisoners coming up.
Let's go, gentlemen.
Kimble, you're here.
Carlson, right over there.
Partida, up front left.
Copeland, you're back here with me.
Make yourselves comfortable.
You know the routine, gentlemen.
I'm tired.
Twenty miles from Menard.
We'll be there in about 40 minutes.
I'll be glad to get rid of this load.
Let McKenzie take care of them.
I hope he's got something
good to eat there. I'm starving.
Me too.
Had enough prison chow.
Old Ed, he don't care.
His old lady's got him on a diet.
Right, Ed?
Get in here, quick!
He's getting sick! Move!
- – He's foaming at the mouth.
- We're almost at the prison.
He's choking!
Wait!
Ah!
Oh, shit!
Kimble!
Get over here.
You're a doctor, do something!
Unlock me. Unlock me!
Here.
You'll be okay.
What the hell is that?
Shit!
– Ah!
Give me a hand with this man.
The hell with you.
Copeland, help me with this man!
Kiss my ass, Doc.
Listen....
I don't care which way you go.
Just don't follow me. Got that?
Yeah.
Hey, Copeland.
Be good.
My, my, my, my.
What a mess.
It's a circus.
You got my bag?
Point of impact right here.
The first engine uncoupled,
the rest of the train jumped the track.
– About 100 yards?
– Yeah.
You must get new boots.
I told you not to wear the heels.
I want you to wear two coats.
Next train wreck.
Why do we always mother her?
Because she loves us.
- How'd you like to be the driver?
- I bet he did a Casey Jones.
Hold it, sir.
Who's in charge?
– Sheriff Rawlins.
– Rawlins.
– Just follow the TV lights.
– Good, good.
Sheriff Rogers.
Rawlins.
- – Look down there and take Newman.
- Right.
Time to go to work.
The bus rolled over several times
before settling down the hill.
I don't know if I passed out...
...but when I looked up,
the train was bearing down on us. Fast.
I don't know how. It's still kind of hazy.
I grabbed him and pushed him
out of the bus.
– You're brave, you could've been killed.
– I know.
He's my partner.
He'd have done the same for me.
Excuse me, I'm Deputy U.S. Marshal
Samuel Gerard, I'd like to--
– I'll be with you in a minute.
– Okay.
Again, just for the record...
– ...these three are dead?
– Yeah.
And this one?
Everything happened so fast.
I don't think he made it.
You came a long way for nothing.
With all due respect, sheriff...
...I'd like to recommend checkpoints
on a 15-mile radius...
...at I-57, I-24 and over here on Route--
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait. The prisoners are all dead.
Checkpoints will get people frantic
and they'll flood my office with calls.
Shit, I'd hate to see that happen...
...so I'll take over your investigation.
You just....
On what authority?
The Governor...
...the U.S. Marshal's office...
...5th District, Northern Illinois.
All right, you want jurisdiction over this mess,
you got it.
Okay, boys, gather around and listen.
We're shutting it down.
Wyatt Earp's here to mop up--
That's very funny, Wyatt Earp.
– Sam.
– Oh, wow, gee whiz. Look here!
We're always fascinated when we find
leg irons with no legs in them.
– Who held the key, sir?
– Me.
Where are they?
I don't know.
– Care to revise your statement, sir?
– What?
Do you want to change
your bullshit story, sir?
– He might've got out.
You said he was part of the wreckage!
Set up operations by the fire truck.
Listen, everyone!
A fugitive has been on the run
for 90 minutes.
Average foot speed over uneven ground,
barring injury, is four miles an hour.
That gives us a radius of six miles.
What I want from each of you
is a hard target search of every gas station...
...residence, warehouse, farmhouse,
hen house, outhouse...
...and doghouse in that area.
Checkpoints go up at 15 miles.
Your fugitive's name is Dr. Richard Kimble.
Go get him.
Don't give me shit.
I got three very unhappy dead people.
Put him on.
Stevens, it's Cosmo.
I'll have a satellite telephone
hook up in two seconds.
Police just found a blood trail...
– ...two miles southwest.
– Robert.
Yo.
– Match that blood against the prisoners'.
– Right.
– Renfro.
– Yo.
– Get a fax I.D. on Kimble...
...to every local hospital.
Follow that with troopers.
Newman.
– Yes.
– What are you doing?
I'm thinking.
Think me up some coffee and a doughnut
with sprinkles on top...
...as long as you're thinking.
We got a live body!
A live one?
Hang in there, brother.
We'll get you out of here.
- Got it?
- I got it. All right
Get that ambulance down here!
Is this what you want?
That's it.
I'll make copies.
Good morning, Mr. Johnson.
I have your breakfast for you.
We're thirsty today, aren't we?
Eat up before it gets cold.
It really gets dry in here, doesn't it?
Here you are.
Now, eat something.
You need your strength.
Shit.
Doc, we're looking for a prisoner
from that wreck. Might be hurt.
What does he look like?
Six-one, 180, brown hair, brown eyes, beard.
Seen anyone like that around?
Every time I look in the mirror.
Except for the beard, of course.
Doc!
Yeah?
Thanks.
- – I'll give you a hand.
- Thanks, doc.
It's....
How is he?
Good, considering we dug him out
from under a train.
Tell the attending he's got a puncture
in the upper gastric area.
How could he tell that
by looking at his face?
Background just came in from Chicago.
About time. What've we got?
"Richard David Kimble, vascular surgeon."
What's that?
Somebody that makes more money than you.
"Convicted of 1st-degree
murder of his wife.
Pleaded innocent.
Says a one-armed man did it."
Lots of friends.
Doctors, hospital staff.
We'll start there. I want phone taps.
First, his lawyer.
Whoa, you'll never get that.
Call Judge Rubin.
Tell him I want phone taps.
Why are you yelling at me?
I'll tell him on who later
if I'm in a good mood.
– Why not yell at her sometimes?
– Sam.
– What?
– We got a call from the hospital.
The wounded guard swears
he saw Kimble there.
That's hot.
And an ambulance is missing.
Where's he going in an ambulance?
Sam!
Sam, ambulance just spotted...
...two miles west of Doverville,
heading north, State Highway 53.
Running out of map!
Get your maps out.
Check, sound check. Get your maps out.
I want to know all routes in and out of town.
We're headed north on Route 13,
toward the Barkley Dam.
Son of a bitch!
Don't lose that ambulance.
Visual location of an ambulance headed north
on Route 13 toward Barkley Dam.
We'll pass through a viaduct.
Get on the horn. Bring Biggs
and Newman in from south of the viaduct.
He's hauling ass.
Is there a tunnel between here and there?
We have Biggs and Newman?
Look on your map to know how to get there.
We got him!
Watch out! Watch out!
– What's going on?
– Get back in your car, sir!
Newman! Rock and roll!
Put a light in there!
What do you got?
I got nothing.
– Talk to me. What do you got?
– You must be kidding me!
– What--?
Seal off the tunnel! Seal it off!
We got a gopher.
Shit! I just bought these shoes.
Shut up, Cosmo.
Which way, Sam?
Ah!
I didn't kill my wife!
I don't care!
Put that gun down!
Now!
Hands up!
Over your head!
Turn around!
Do you want to get shot?
Pay attention!
Get down on your knees!
Right now!
Sam!
– Yo.
What happened? Where'd he go?
He did a Peter Pan right off this dam!
Right here!
Down! Boom!
Holy shit!
Can we go home now?
No. No.
Holy shit!
– There's no way out of here.
– Down that way.
- Down that way.
- No, no. Go up. Go up!
Go up the stairs! Up, up!
Get them down here now.
Helicopters, divers!
Have that water turned off. Come over here.
Put two cars on that bridge down there
and four patrolmen.
Have them glass this river
upstream and down.
I want a helicopter 100 feet off this
river. Make him aware of these wires.
Are you crazy? He's dead!
That'll make him easy to catch.
I want hounds on both banks of this
river for 2 miles...
...upstream and downstream.
– You've got a search-and-rescue team?
– Yeah, we do.
Get them down here
and drag the bottom of this spillway.
– Why isn't the water turned off?
– Somebody from County's working on it.
Hurry it up. They're running out of daylight.
No. Bring in the helicopter now.
We're out of here!
I don't think there's anything to find.
Find it anyway.
You've got lights and generators coming.
– I won't tell you how to do your job...
– Put the helicopter on the bridge!
...but only one in a million could survive
that fall. He's fish food!
Get a cane pole and catch
the fish that ate him.
Get Stevens.
Tell him we're on the way in.
That man took everything from me.
We can't find the guy.
You find that man!
Find that man!
The generators
and searchlights are there now.
They'll continue the search into the night.
Good. Call Kentucky
and thank them for the dogs.
Remember,
opera ain't over until the Big Dog howls.
Need a ride?
Check it again.
All right, we got him.
He shacked up with some babe in Whiting.
She left work tonight and took him home.
– About 2 hours ago, her boss said.
– They spotted her car outside her house.
Does she run with anyone?
No one we could find. No family either.
Tell the police not to move till we get there.
We'll go early in the morning.
– Your cousin still got his truck?
– Mm-hm.
Tell him we need it.
– Be drunk, Newman.
– Yeah.
Stay close.
Right on your ass, bud.
I don't want you getting lost.
Stick with me.
U.S. Marshals! Everybody down!
- – Ah!
- Hold it right there!
Show me those hands!
Give me those hands.
Keep them up!
Get your ass in there.
I got your man!
I got your man, you hear me?
I want out of here!
I got your man!
I'm going to blow his brains out!
I want out of here!
Do you hear me, cops?
Do you hear me?
I want out of here!
- – Listen! We can work this out!
- Yes, we can.
- – Shut up! Shut up!
- Listen to me.
Do you hear me?
Listen, and I'll tell you what I want.
I want a car out front.
– Don't shoot.
– It's over.
Shut up.
I can't hear anything. My ears....
I can't believe you did that.
You think I should've bargained with him.
Yeah.
I do.
You could've missed.
– You could've killed me.
– Yeah.
How bad is that ear?
Terrible. I'll have permanent damage.
Let me see it.
Come here.
Can you hear me now?
Yeah.
I don't...
...bargain.
You hear that?
Yeah.
Good.
Walter, this is Richard.
Jesus! Why did you run?
It only makes you look guilty.
I wasn't worried about appearances.
Tell me where you are,
so I can meet you and you can surrender.
I won't surrender. I need help, money.
Richard, you're asking me to aid
a convicted felon. I can't help you that way.
My advice as your friend and attorney
is to give yourself up.
Now tell me, where are you?
St. Louis.
Give me an address.
I'll get there as soon as I can.
Mr. Copeland was a bad man.
He was going to kill one of my kids.
You can blame me. I'm the one that shot him.
Raymonds, take care of that.
...give yourself up.
Now tell me, where are you?
St. Louis.
So he's not dead.
Let that be a lesson to you.
Don't ever argue with the Big Dog.
Big Dog is always right.
You been right before.
All right.
- Walter, this is Richard.
- Richard, Jesus.
Why did you run?
It only makes you look guilty.
I wasn't worried about appearances.
Tell me where you are,
so I can meet you and you can surrender.
I won't surrender. I need help, money.
That train sounds like an El.
St. Louis doesn't have an elevated train.
How do you know it's an elevated train?
I lived under an El for 20 years.
Explain the difference between the sound
of an El and a train on the ground.
You must have ears
like an eagle.
Play that back.
I want to hear the sound of an elevated train.
What cities have Els? New York does.
– Philly.
– We do.
Milwaukee.
Hold it right there where the lawyer says
he sounds guilty. There's bells.
There's a guy on a P.A.
Can you drop everything but him?
I'll try.
Okay.
– Walter, this is Richard.
– Richard.
Right there.
What's he saying?
Sounds like, "Next stop." Do that again!
– Next stop...
– "Next stop"....
– ...Merchandise Mart.
– "Merchandise Mart."
Son of a bitch. The boy came home.
That bell is on the Wells Street bridge,
six blocks away.
I knew it was an elevated train.
Yeah, Big Dog. You're never wrong.
– I'll call the C.P.D.
– This is his Chicago file.
When I die, I want to come back like you.
Happy and handsome?
- – I'll notify the press.
- No press.
Right, no press.
Chicago.
– Hi, Billy.
– How's it going, sir?
– Good, and you?
– All right.
Here you go. See you.
Spare change? Dollar, Mister?
No, thank you very much. I don't want it.
No, I....
Oh, my God. Richard!
How are you, Charlie?
Jesus, you're back.
I need money.
Sure. Get in.
No, I can't. Whatever you got on you.
You're hot. If not now, you will be.
Have you got a place to stay?
How can I help you?
The light is green. Move!
I'll call you.
Yeah, but Rich--
Why did Kimble kill his wife?
For the money.
For the money? He's a doctor.
He's already rich.
She was more rich.
– Is this the entire Chicago police file?
– Yeah.
That's everything.
– I want to do all the interviews again.
The list of hospital staff is there?
– Sure is.
– Thank you.
You don't want to use the media?
We want him to relax. Make himself
comfortable. Try to re-enter his life.
Here's the apartment.
You can see here is heater.
You will have warm.
Here is kitchen. Sink.
Over there is bathroom.
And here is the room.
Is nice bed.
Plenty space.
You can look at.
You like the place?
It's okay?
It's perfect.
All right, people.
This morning we were notified
by the Marshal's office...
...that our old friend Dr. Richard Kimble
is alive and well and back in Chicago.
You know in what high regard
we hold this scumbag.
I'm personally donating a bottle
of 12-year-old Scotch...
...to whoever collars this quack.
Dick Rosetti's passing out bulletins.
– Gunshot wound to the left shoulder.
– What are his vitals?
120 over 60. 98 pulse.
Help you?
You went to medical school together?
Yes, we did.
The class of '73.
Do you know Morton Feinberg?
– I do.
– He's a real nice guy.
When did you see him last?
– Who, Richard?
– Yeah.
I saw Richard this morning.
– What?
– This morning?
He stopped my car. I gave him money.
Uh-huh.
Where was this?
Outside my tennis club.
Did he ask for help?
I volunteered. He wouldn't accept that.
How much did you give him?
Oh, couple of bucks. What I had on me.
– He won't get far on that.
– Why'd he come back to Chicago?
He didn't tell me.
I'm sure he's trying to protect you
from having to lie for him, but....
Dr. Nichols. You really want
to be his friend and help him?
Help us bring him in unharmed.
Why?
So he can go back to prison?
If you want help, gentlemen,
you've come to the wrong man.
Richard is innocent.
You'll never find him. He's too smart.
– We're some smart guys.
– What about us?
– Last time I looked.
– We're smart. We are.
How smart could he be, really?
Is he as smart as you?
Smarter.
Peripheral vascular surgery.
Fixing arteries as they come out of the heart.
– How long have you known Richard Kimble?
– Ten years. Since I've been here.
What kind of medicine did he practice
at the hospital?
I want you to know that I believe
Richard Kimble to be innocent.
Would he seek your help?
If he did, I'd help him.
But he wouldn't come to me.
That's not his style.
A warrant remains outstanding...
...for Chicago surgeon Richard Kimble.
This is where the one-armed guy
and he struggled and fell down the stairs.
I fell down these stairs, I'd be a goner.
I'd be dead.
What a waste.
When I came home,
there was a man in my house.
Richard.
Police!
- Police. We're the police!
- Where is he?
Get him, get him!
Hold it!
– Freeze!
– Get down. Where you going?
It's over.
You like stringing out 12-year-old girls?
What are you doing with my baby?
Your baby's a drug dealer, lady.
– What he--?
– Come on, ma'am.
What they doing to my baby?
It will be crazy here tonight.
Did they get a count?
A lot of kids.
They bring them all here?
All coming to County.
– Hi.
– Hi, hi, hi.
– I've come to do those blinds.
– Okay.
I'll get the door.
– I'll start in here, huh?
– Oh, okay.
Let's go over it once more.
What time did he arrive at the house?
About 10:30 in the morning.
– He was alone?
– Yeah, he was alone.
– You got a good look at him?
– Yeah, really good.
You better be straight with me.
This is the guy
staying in your mother's basement?
That's what I'm telling you.
- – Is she stable?
- Just barely.
Just breathe, stay calm.
– I need a doctor over here!
Watch the bag! Watch the bag!
Call vascular and ortho
and call her parents for consent.
Okay, thank you, doctor.
Hurts.
Hello, Marshal. It's right there.
My chest hurts.
Check the film on that kid.
Take a deep breath.
Inhale, exhale. Again.
Slowly.
Check the film.
- Take it easy.
- It hurts.
Check the film.
What's the status on that kid?
Possible fractured sternum. Stable.
I need you here.
Can you help us?
Bring this kid to Observation Room 2.
Yeah, you. Help us out, okay?
How are you, champ?
My chest hurts.
Yeah? Does it hurt when you breathe?
Yes.
That's good. That's good.
- What's your name?
- Joel.
Look at this.
We're eating oranges and making IDs.
"C.C.H." What's that?
Cook County Hospital.
Just hang on, okay?
– It hurts.
– You'll be okay, pal.
You'll be fine.
Hold that elevator.
Thank you.
How're you doing?
My chest hurts.
Where's your mom?
I don't know.
Is she at home?
I think she's with my brother.
They downstairs?
I don't know.
Don't worry.
We'll find her.
Do you play football? Baseball?
Football.
Hold on, son.
Uh....
Hey, doctor.
They sent this one from downstairs.
Bob, get this one into Room 4, stat.
Bye-bye, Joel.
Where's that boy I sent down
with the janitor?
– What boy?
– The one with the fractured sternum.
He never came here.
– He didn't?
– No, he didn't.
Hey, you have a particular interest
in our patient's X-rays?
– What do you mean?
– I saw you looking at that boy's chest film.
– It's a hobby of mine.
– A hobby, really?
– Yeah.
– What's your other hobby, brain surgery?
– What do you want?
– To know how that boy got to surgery.
I'm a janitor. I do as I'm told.
Bullshit. Who changed those orders?
I don't know what you mean.
Stay there.
Maureen, call security!
Hey!
Excuse me.
Tell Stevens to get hold
of that guy Kelly over at C.P.D.
A guy disguised as a janitor orders
an emergency medical procedure...
...and all you did
was take away his ID card?
No. I called Security.
He took off down the hall. What was I to do?
Listen, Mr.--
Deputy.
Gerard.
I'm really tired.
I'd like to go home.
– Okay. How's the boy doing?
– He saved his life.
Thank you.
"Desmondo Jose Ruiz."
Whoa.
Where are you, Desmondo?
Sammy, this is my problem:
– The place is crawling with cops, right?
– Yeah.
Everybody's looking for Kimble, right?
So why would he be stupid enough...
...to hang out in the trauma ward
and play Mother Teresa?
– Excuse me.
– Yeah, sorry.
Have a problem?
– No.
– No, no problem at all.
Excuse me, could we have a word with you?
This is Dr. Elway at Cook County Hospital.
I'm following-up for the Prosthetic Clinic
on Matthew Zelick.
Oh, he did?
I'm terribly sorry.
Right or left?
Right.
- – Age?
- 35 to 45.
This is Ted Riley
with the High School Reunion Committee.
25 years is just around the corner...
...and Clive is on our list
of missing in action.
Information gave me a number,
but when I tried it....
Oh.
No kidding.
Armed robbery?
He's where?
- – Point of attachment?
Mid-humerus.
That gives us 47 possibles.
- – 47?
- Robert.
Cross-check these people
for criminal records.
Wait a minute.
Happy St. Patrick's Day to all.
How you doing?
– Hey.
– What's happening?
Driscoll, Clive R.
One-armed man, armed robbery.
That's funny.
Let me ask a question:
If they can dye a river green today...
...why can't they dye it blue the other days?
Do I know?
– Are you Irish, sir?
– Who, me? No.
Are you?
No, man.
Name of inmate?
Clive Driscoll.
Driscoll, Clive.
ID, please.
Driscoll, Clive R.
2-0-1-0.
Be advised that, by court ruling,
your conversation can be recorded.
This is hinky. He went to college.
He wouldn't go through all this security...
...go to lock-up to find someone
his own people say doesn't exist.
– Hinky.
– What does that mean, "hinky?"
– Strange.
– Weird.
Say "strange" or "weird."
"Hinky" has no meaning.
Well, we say "hinky."
I don't want you using meaningless words
around me. I'm taking the stairs.
How about "bullshit"?
How about "bullshit," Sam?
Visitor for Driscoll.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
Over there.
Let's go, Driscoll.
You got 5 minutes.
Who are you?
Look, I'm sorry. I made a mistake.
You got me down here...
...might as well talk.
Down here you got no entertainment.
Ain't no cable here.
I wish I could, but I can't. Sorry.
Richard!
Officer, a man in a blue coat is waving a gun
and screaming at a woman.
Stop that man!
He's a U.S. Marshal! Let him go!
Let him go! U.S. Marshall, let him go!
Shut the gates!
Hold it.
Open the doors!
We're on the roof.
Take some men! Look down there!
He's in the plaza!
He's heading east!
– East through the plaza?
– Where?
– Towards the Picasso?
– He's going east toward the Picasso!
We want you to give
all these groups a big round of applause.
They've been waiting a long time
to get in the parade.
They're cold, just like all the rest of you.
Deputy Gerard, why do you feel
that Dr. Kimble came back to Chicago?
I have no idea.
We understand your deputies
were at the hospital today.
Was Dr. Kimble there?
I have no comment on that.
Let me get the chronology straight.
The subject was tried, convicted,
incarcerated...
...escaped, presumed dead,
and is now at large in Chicago. Correct?
Except for being presumed dead.
Do you believe that Kimble's
armed and dangerous?
I believe he's dangerous, yes.
He's taking chances, conning back.
Do you feel that perhaps he's innocent?
No, he's not innocent. He was convicted
in a court of law. He's guilty.
How will you try to catch him?
We have no further comments for now.
Alec. Alec.
Richard Kimble.
Hi, how are you?
– Good, Dr. Kimble.
Lentz.
We've been trading phone calls
the last few days.
A cruise sponsored
by Devlin MacGregor...
– ...could be fun.
– Enjoy.
Hi.
- Cancun, Richard.
- Sport fishing.
Pina coladas.
What does the hospital have to buy?
What's the catch?
Sailfish.
No strings attached.
What do you say? What do you say?
This guy is bleeding
from every needle puncture.
Lentz sent this guy in?
Is he on that wonder drug?
Yes, he's on the RDU-90 protocol,
Provasic.
Drug of the future.
Clean out those arteries
and put us out of business.
"Parade Master of Ceremonies
Ed O'Flaherty said...
...he didn't recall a livelier parade
during the last 20 years.
That Kimble...
– ...is some kind of lad to be running out--"
– "Lad"?
He says "lad."
Maybe he's a leprechaun.
– I'm quoting this guy.
– Sam.
A guy on line 3 claims he's Richard Kimble.
– Who?
– Another Kimble on line 3.
- – Let me see the phone.
- Tell him he looks good in a beard.
- – What line?
- Three.
"I hope he was able to wear
a little green, sip some whiskey...."
This is Gerard.
Remember what I told you in the tunnel?
It's him!
– I remember it was noisy.
I think you said something like...
...you didn't kill your wife.
Remember what you told me?
I remember you pointed my gun at me.
You said, "I don't care."
He's on the south side.
That's right, I don't care.
I'm not trying to solve a puzzle.
I am trying to solve a puzzle.
Five seconds to location.
And I just found a big piece.
Richard.
Richard?
Richard? Richard?
Hello, Richard?
He didn't hang up. Where is he at?
– Here it comes.
– Where is he at?
256 South St. Lawrence.
Get the C.P.D. over there.
We got a car there now.
Get some shots of that.
Fredrick Sykes...
...45, ex-cop, and quite a clotheshorse.
You want to look at this?
Yeah.
Kimble's prints.
They're all over, but mainly on the desk.
He sure had interest in these photos.
Flipped through the whole package.
– Paused here.
– Negatives in there?
– Right there.
– Let me have them.
Camera boy's on his way.
– We got you.
How you doing, Mr. Sykes?
– Fine, if you tell me what's happening.
– We had a problem.
– My place or the place upstairs?
– Your place.
- – Well, now.
- Step right in, Mr. Sykes.
Everybody knows my name here.
Big happy family, huh?
What is this, a trench coat convention?
What's going on?
Who are you guys? What's going on?
You had a break-in, Mr. Sykes.
I sure hope you're a cop.
No, I'm Samuel Gerard,
United States Marshal's office.
This morning a fugitive named Richard Kimble
made a phone call from here.
Why would he do that?
I don't know any Richard Kimble.
Okay, I got it.
The doctor who killed his wife, right?
Blamed somebody with a prosthetic.
Is he coming after me?
Does he have reason to do so?
I have a prosthetic arm! I must've done it!
Give me a break.
I went through all this a year ago.
I was questioned here about the whole thing.
I told them I wasn't in Chicago that night.
I was away on business.
Fifteen people verified it.
What line of business are you in?
Security.
– Who do you work for?
– A pharmaceutical company.
– Which one?
– Devlin MacGregor.
I handle security for the top executives.
Any idea why Kimble would be interested
in these photographs?
No.
Where were they taken?
Jeez, that's a big fish!
Cancun, Mexico.
It was a junket the company paid for,
for some doctors.
– Kimble go with you?
– You don't see him there, do you?
No. I told you I don't know him.
Mind if I check to see if anything's missing?
No, I don't mind.
How'd you lose that arm?
In the line of duty.
Cosmo, this guy's dirty.
Yes, he is.
– You want our people on him?
– Yes. Build a camp here.
– Henry.
– I'll take care of it.
- – Noah.
- Yes, sir?
See this picture? I want you to find out
who the guy is next to Sykes.
Find out his name, age, weight,
social security number...
...his location, relatives, pets, everything.
Sorry, doctor, they said it was an emergency.
Thank you. Excuse me.
- – Hello.
- Mr. Bolton.
– Chuck.
– Richard.
Can you talk?
Yes, I'm on a hotel phone.
How are you? What's going on?
I found him.
I found the man who killed Helen.
– What?
– It was me they were after.
Who are they?
Devlin MacGregor and Lentz.
Lentz was supervising the protocol
for RDU-90.
He knew I found out
it was causing liver damage. It was Lentz.
Richard, Lentz is dead.
What? How?
He died in a car accident last summer.
– Richard?
– Yeah.
Can you prove this about the drug?
I think so.
I need your help.
Call Bones at the hospital.
Tell him to give me any help I need.
Sure.
I'll call him now.
Okay. Thanks.
– Dr. Nichols.
– Hey!
– How are you doing?
– Good.
Dr. Nichols!
Can we ask you a few more questions?
Mr. Gerard.
You got a copy of that photograph?
U.S. Marshal Service.
Excuse us.
This is Fredrick Sykes.
He's a security specialist
at Devlin MacGregor Pharmaceuticals.
Richard Kimble broke into his apartment.
– Do you know this man?
– No, I don't.
You're getting pretty desperate, aren't you,
Mr. Gerard?
Oh, yes.
I told you you wouldn't find Richard.
Has he been to see you?
No.
We've been over this ground before,
haven't we?
Yeah.
So if you'll excuse me.
– Sure. Thanks, doc.
– Thank you, doctor.
Dr. Nichols.
Sorry. One more question
about the photograph.
See the guy standing on the right side
of the fish?
– Ever see him before?
– No.
– This guy right here?
– Mm-hm.
I've never seen that person before.
– Okay.
– I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you, doctor.
Enjoy the rest of the convention.
"Alternatives to Cardio-Non-lnvasive...
...Arterial Plaque-Reducing Therapy.
Keynote speaker, Charles Nichols."
Bet they line up for this one.
If you were Richard Kimble...
...why would you hunt for a one-armed man
you say killed your wife...
...break into his house,
call us up and then split?
I should have been a doctor.
Look at this blowup.
This guy in the picture with Sykes. On his shirt.
Chicago Memorial. Kimble's hospital.
I want to go there.
Go.
Wait.
Devlin MacGregor...
...did 7 and one half billion dollars
in net sales...
...last year alone.
That company's a monster.
Talk to me.
Absolutely.
It's a liver sample...
...from a patient on the RDU-90 drug study.
January 21st?
Ah!
The last one!
1-7-4-3-0?
1-7-4-3-0. You got it.
Thanks.
I'll make sure all this gets back to you.
– It's good to see you again.
– Good to see you.
Whatever happened to that thing
with your wife?
It's not over yet.
What's going on?
How should I know?
I think his name is Alec Lentz.
A pathologist.
I remember because he died last summer.
Oh, my God. Richard!
What are you doing here?
Hi, Kath.
Have a look.
– What do you think?
– Cold normal.
Clearly not the same tissue.
And not only did they all come
from healthy livers...
...they came from the same liver.
Kath, you beauty.
Excuse me.
Mr. Roosevelt?
Yes.
We're deputies Biggs and Newman.
We're U.S. Marshals.
Need some information about a Dr. Lentz
who was on staff here.
Did he know or have any contact
with a Dr. Richard Kimble?
I haven't seen Dr. Kimble.
I didn't ask that.
I wouldn't know.
If you'll excuse me,
I have prior obligations to attend to.
- Mr. Roosevelt.
- Yes?
I think you're lying to us.
Lentz is the bad guy?
Yeah, why not?
He was one of the original
patent holders in RDU-90.
I was sending in my tissue samples...
...he was replacing them with healthy samples,
issuing path reports...
...shit-canning my stuff. Easy.
Wait a minute.
Lentz died August 21st.
Yeah.
Half the samples he approved
were signed the day he died.
You're kidding.
Someone else must have been
manipulating this.
Someone with access.
Thanks, Kath.
Where are you going?
To see a friend.
This is giving me a headache.
That's surprising.
Where did Roosevelt say Kimble was going?
He says he doesn't know.
– Do you believe him?
– Yes, I do.
– He says he picked up tissue samples...
– What?
...for a drug study.
Get this:
The release was approved
by Dr. Charles Nichols.
Nichols also knew Lentz.
Whoa.
– He was Lentz's boss.
He was covering for Kimble.
Send the C.P.D. there right now.
We're sending cops.
Make sure they turn that place inside out.
Don't let them give you shit
about your ponytail. Well done.
My pleasure.
Henry.
Dr. Nichols lied to me.
– Go find him.
– I'm on it.
Okay, it's gone by now.
I looked every place you told me
and I didn't see him.
I'm telling you.
If he was in the hospital,
I would have found him.
What do you want me to do?
Hold on. Wait a minute.
I marked him. I got him now.
Dr. Alexander Lentz.
"A noted pathologist
at Chicago Memorial Hospital...
...was walking to his daily tennis match
when an unidentified vehicle...
...slammed his body into the barriers
separating the Drive from Lake Michigan."
Yuck.
Sam, you won't believe this.
Sykes' records for the past two years
show no calls to Kimble.
It was a thought.
But when I cross-checked Kimble's records,
one came up.
Kimble called Sykes--
Get Sykes in here now.
--on the night of the murder...
...7:30 p.m...
...from his car phone.
Do you have Kimble's arrest report?
– 7:30 p.m.
– 19:30 hours.
They just went in. Sykes is gone.
He's nowhere to be found.
– What?
– He's gone.
Uh, listen, this is transit unit number 23.
Possible sighting of Richard Kimble
on northbound El coming into Van Buren.
Move to the door.
Next stop, Balbo Station. Balbo.
This is my stop.
My stop too.
Kimble.
You missed your stop.
A transit cop saw Kimble on the El,
heading toward Balbo.
The C.P.D. is on the way.
Attention all units.
Transit police report officer down
at Balbo Station.
Kimble is suspect.
What'd he do, shoot a cop?
Chicago P.D. will eat him alive.
It is a joy and a privilege...
...to introduce tonight's keynote speaker.
For the past four years...
...he has served
as the A. Jude Robinson Fellow...
...and administrative chief of Pathology...
...at Chicago Memorial Hospital.
Where are the emergency exits?
Suspect seen entering
Hilton Tower Mall, lower level.
You don't think--
– Yeah, I know where he's going.
Biggs, Newman, where are you?
He was appointed to the Board of Directors
of Devlin MacGregor Pharmaceuticals.
Will you please welcome...
...Dr. Charles Nichols?
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen...
...friends and colleagues.
It's great you're all here tonight.
C.P.D. reported an officer down
and a guy with two guns--
– Kimble do it?
– Conflicting reports.
He entered the hotel from the subway.
- – That's my man!
- Not anymore.
He's going down.
You can help by staying out.
Arrest us!
Lock it up! Start at the lower level.
All units report when
lower level is secure.
All units, secure all lower level exits.
Noah, find the hotel security office.
Stay in touch with me by radio.
Now, a new drug...
...on the cusp of approval
by the Food and Drug Administration...
...is poised to change
these old methods forever.
– Deputy Newman, U.S. Marshal's Service.
– How you doing.
Good. Sam, I'm in.
--through the normal metabolic
pathways in the liver.
The drug's name is...
...Provasic.
As I will show you tonight...
...Provasic is remarkably effective...
...and has no side effects whatsoever.
It is also noteworthy that this drug--
This drug was developed...
...in cooperation, not competition
with Chicago Memorial Hospital...
...in what we hope will be...
...the model for a continued dishonest....
Excuse me, honest...
...open joint ventures...
...between academic medicine...
...and the pharmaceutical....
Richard.
I'm sorry, I'm in the middle of this speech.
You almost got away with it.
I know all about it.
I can prove it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my friend Richard Kimble doesn't feel well...
...obviously...
...so just go on with your
dessert and coffee....
Richard, do you mind stepping aside
and let's talk.
Okay.
So I'll be back in just a second.
You changed the samples, didn't you?
You switched the samples...
– ...after Lentz died.
– Richard, let--
Let's stay calm, people.
After Lentz died,
you were the only one who had access.
You switched the samples...
...and the pathology reports.
Did you kill Lentz too?
Call Security.
Did you?
He falsified his research...
...so RDU-90 could be...
...approved and...
...Devlin MacGregor could give you Provasic.
It's all over, folks.
Just stay calm.
You never give up, do you?
You never give up!
Why Helen?
Glad you're here.
Which way'd they go?
– Toward the Presidential Suite.
– Where's that?
– Southeast corner.
– How many exits are there from this room?
We got a total of four:
two on the east, two on the west.
Kimble's on the roof!
Cosmo, that way.
Stop! Stay where you are!
This is the Chicago police!
Put your hands in the air!
The building is totally secure.
I repeat, do not move!
Put your hands in the air!
I repeat, stay where you are!
Talk to me.
They're headed to the north end of the roof.
Newman!
Get that helicopter out of here!
As soon as you get a clean shot...
...take him out.
Get rid of the helicopter!
Why?
– Because I don't want to get shot!
C.P.D., there's a U.S. Marshal on the roof.
Hold your fire!
Call off the helicopter!
Ah!
Don't shoot.
This guy ever quit?
Find out where that elevator stops.
Newman. Newman!
Northwest elevator! Where does it stop?
Where did they go? Where did they go?
– Stopped on 5th floor.
– They're on the 5th.
- – What's on the 5th floor?
- The laundry.
It's the laundry.
They stopped at the laundry.
We're on the 5th floor. What's your 20?
Right behind you.
What's going on here?
We must keep the C.P.D. out.
They're too hot for me.
Get rid of all these people.
Okay, people, stay calm.
Cosmo, come with me.
Dr. Richard Kimble!
There's no way out of here!
The entire building is locked down!
Give it up, you don't have any time!
Chicago Police thinks you're a cop killer!
They will shoot you on sight!
I know you're innocent!
I know about Fredrick Sykes!
I know about Dr. Charles Nichols!
He borrowed your car
the night of your wife's murder!
He had the keys!
No forced entry.
He telephoned Sykes from your car,
Richard!
Give it up!
I'm either lying or I'm gonna shoot you!
What do you think?
Give it up! It's time to stop running!
They killed my wife.
I know it.
But it's over now.
Whew. You know, I'm glad.
I need the rest.
Who killed Kimble's wife?
Kimble was convicted of it.
You've got a one-armed man in custody.
- – Is that the guy?
- I have no idea.
How many one-armed men are there?
There're a lot of them.
Could you have made a mistake?
The one-armed man is also there.
I've never seen so much
since I've been around here.
You got a deadline, play the weather again.
Tell Samuel Gerard I'm going home now.
I'm taking my vacation.
Clear this area. Everybody clear.
Watch your head.
Where is that thing?
Let me see those hands, doctor.
I thought you didn't care.
I don't.
Don't tell anybody, okay?
[English – US]
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org