Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
- I swear, if'n you don't
learn to share this honey...
I'm gonna give you a real whupping
Now go on!
- Is the doctor in?
- No doubt about it.
- What's ailin' ya, Fat Elmer?
- I et too much cheese.
Now I can't burp.
Can ya fix me, Granny?
Dang.
Before I sign anything...
I want to know how much money
we're talkin' about.
Mr. Clampett, there's more petroleum
in your swamp...
than there is in all of Kuwait.
- That bad, huh?
- Mr. Clampett...
you are sitting on the biggest
domestic oil strike in history.
And when you sign these contracts,
we're going to pay you one billion dollars.
Do you have anybody
who can advise you on these contracts?
Cousin jethro's a-comin'tomorrow night
for Sunday supper, Pa.
He's the one with the learnin'.
He went to school at Oxford.
- Jethro.
- Yes, Ma?
Did you fix those bare-as-bones brakes
like I told you?
Of course.
I pulled 'em off yesterday.
The new ones are
comin' in the mail next week.
- Jethro!
- Howdy, Granny.
Oh! You dadblamed
simpleminded yahoo!
Your crack-bucket head's
emptier than last year's bird's nest.
If your head was filled with dynamite...
- Ow! Ow!
- You wouldn't know how to blow your nose!
- You...
- Ow!
- Granny! Ow! Granny!
- Just get out of my sight!
Now, jedediah...
you're fixin' to be the richest man
in this here county.
Look at how you live. Why, your land's
overrun with snakes and skunks.
You got no TV, no telephone and no radio.
You're right, Pearl.
We are a-livin'in paradise.
No, Jed!
Paradise is someplace like...
Beverly Hills, Californy.
- They got swimmin'pools.
- Mm-hmm.
- And movie stars.
- And smog.
What's a smog?
I reckon it's a small hog.
Now, if you're not gonna think about yourself,
think about your daughter.
You need to get remarried, jed,
and she needs a ma...
someone to teach her
womanly ways.
- She's runnin'wild, jed.
She's no different than a boy.
Imagine that. Elly May
wearin'fancy dresses...
and actin' ladylike!
Well, that don't sound like much fun.
Beverly Hills.
Listen to what I'm saying jed.
It would be the best thing for y'all.
Just pack up all your belongin's
and move on out there.
Jethro could drive you out
in his truck.
I ain't drivin' in no movin' vehicle
with no dunderhead.
I ain't no dunderhead.
- Come on! Put me down!
- Set him down.
- See what I mean?
- Who are you, mister?
Ozark Mountain Oil. Mr. Briggs sent me
to see if you'd signed the contract.
- Oh, my.
- Elly May Clampett.
Well, that's it.
I've made my decision.
For the good
of this here family...
I'm a-movin' us to Beverly Hills.
Now, don't you worry, Elly May.
We gonna take good care of your critters for ya.
Okay, Sam. I know you will.
Oh, Ma!
What's all this I hear about you
not wantin' to go to Californy?
I like it here.
Say what you will...
but there ain't nothin' you can do
to get me off of this rockin' chair.
- I ain't goin' nowheres! Cut me loose!
- It's a long ride to Californy.
Jedediah Clampett, I'm gonna skin you alive!
Hush up, Granny.
Get goin', boy,
before she breaks loose.
I ain't a-going!
Watch your head, Granny.
There's so many people
in this here town.
Goin' to take a long time to meet everybody.
Hey! Nice wheels, buddy!
- Jethro, why do you think
that feller's pointin' at us?
I reckon that's the way
they wave "howdy" in Californy.
- Has, uh...
- Uh.! Excuse us.!
Has escrow closed
on the Clampett estate?
Yes, chief. With an offer
of 22 million in cash, it closed swiftly.
And I must say,
it is inspirational...
how you happened to find a place
for the Clampetts right next-door to your own.
Hathaway, the people
who lived there...
were my best friends and neighbors
for over 20 years.
It's a shame they had
to file for bankruptcy.
Yeah. I just hope my call to the I.R.S.
didn't have anything to do with it. Well.
- Now, um, what time does their fight arrive?
- That's just it, chief.
- They're driving.
- Driving?
From Arkansas?
I know it makes no sense whatsoever.
Not to you, perhaps.
But to a man with vision,
like myself...
- That is a sign of daring, self-confidence, vigor.
- Of course, chief.
Hmm. Doesn't he look busy at work.
Tyler.
- Would you step in here for a moment, please.
- Oh!
- Geez.
- It's an earthquake.!
Oh.
- You wanted to consult with me?
- Sit down, Tyler. Relax.
I have heard that you are quite excited
about the arrival of the Clampetts.
I think that you and I,
together...
can fully exploit the potential
of the Clampett financial portfolio.
Hmm.
You and I. The two of us.
I've already taken the liberty of drawing up
the power of attorney papers.
- Have you now?
- So I can write checks, arrange investments...
make international transactions.
- Really work the Clampett account.
- Hmm.
We'll be quite the team, sir.
Mmm.
Tyler, you will personally
rescind, shred and burn...
every paper you have drawn up
with regard to the Clampett account.
- I'll be handling that account personally.
- Duly noted.
And nice kick, sir.
Took me completely by surprise.
Tyler.
- The Clampetts will not be badgered.
- Sir?
They are not your common
garden-variety millionaires.
They are, in fact, billionaires.
By definition, people of,
uh, discrimination...
discernment, great refinement.
Boy, howdy.!
Hey! Jethro, we's supposed
to go that away.
Hey! You cut us off, you bunch of nothin's!
That's real nice, son.
This here's what I carry.
Okay. Go! Go, go!
Margaret!
Morgan, come in here
a minute, please.
Hi. I'm Doug Llewelyn, and welcome
to the People's Court.
Where is your mother?
She's changing.
That would be
too much to hope for.
- Oh.
- Milburn, I'm sorry. I have to cancel our lunch.
- What?    - I have to spend more
quality time with Babette.
Margaret, dear, we are trying to do more
things together, put the spark back, remember?
You claim the defendant
has your dog?
- Um, well, actually...
- Yes or no?
- Yes, we do. - Morgan.
Morgan. - It's my dog.
- It's your dog?
- Yes. I raised this dog from a pup, and due to...
Morgan, I have a little job for you.
- A job?
- Yes. J.D. Clampett has a daughter your age.
Now, she's goin'
to high school with you.
I want you
to show her around.
- Just be her friend.
- Oh, man.
You wanna pay me
to hang out with her?
She must be a major bowwow.
Son.
Morgan.
Close your eyes.
Now picture this.
I cut off your allowance...
Cancel your credit cards...
And delete you from my will.
Now, how do you see
your future?
Grilling frozen cow parts
at Burger King?
And people say you're stupid.
Monday morning,
first period, 8:00 a. M...
she'll be like the little sister
Mom thought would ruin her figure.
- The dog will go to the plaintiff,
Rusty.
Honey, I'm home.
Why don't you come here and give your little
embezzling cowboy a ride around bungalow.
- No.
- Why not?
'Cause I'm still living in this dump when I
should be living in a mansion in Beverly Hills.
Laura, sweetheart.
Bungalows 3A, 3B and 3C
are in Los Angeles.
We live in 3G
which, technically, is in Beverly Hills.
You're all talk, Tyler.
You said we'd have
enough money this month...
to buy me that little
baby sealskin coat.
- We will.
- Promises, promises.
Sweetie, we will.
J.D. Clampett, the billionaire,
just opened up an account at the bank.
Who is this Clampett guy?
If he's so rich, how come
I've never heard of him?
Baby cakes, this guy's got more money
than he knows what to do with.
Now, that's a problem
I think we can help him with.
Stop the car, Jethro!
They's a fresh kill in the road.
- Can't just leave it there.
- You're right, Granny.
Roadkill stew sounds
mighty good right now.
Oh, no, you don't, you old coot! I seen it first!
- Milburn, call Westec Security.
- Well, I...
I'm sure there's enough for us all.
Eww! How revolting.
Easy now, Granny.
They're probably just bein' neighborly...
like them nice folks we met
on that extry-wide road.
Well, let's give 'em
a Californy howdy.
- Howdy, y'all.!
- Howdy.!
Milburn!
Did you fip me off?
You reckon we're at
the wrong spot, Uncle Jed?
Could be. Don't know.
It's the right address, Pa.
Whee doggies!
The whole place looks brand-new.
Hey, Uncle Jed, there's
a whole 'nother house up here.
This is a big ol'house.
Why do you reckon
they got two sets of steps?
That's easy.
One's for goin' up.
The other's for goin' down.
Oh.
What a pretty critter.
Hello, police?
This is Miss Jane Hathaway.
I wish to report
the unlawful entry...
of a gang of armed and dangerous
hooligans at the Clampett estate.
518 Crestview Drive.
I need you here code three,
and I will be timing you.
I think you got you
a new friend, Duke.
Cease and desist.!
Everyone.!
If I were you, sir,
I would yield, submit and capitulate.
What are you desperadoes
doing here?
- Well, it's a mighty long story.
- But he don't mind tellin' it.
- Pa was a-huntin' one day with old Duke.
- Duke spotted this jack rabbit.
- So I throws up my gun, and I takes my aim...
- Don't shoot!
Pardon, ma'am?
Two minutes and 46 seconds.
Go.! Go.! Go.!
I need three men
over there on the south side.!
Attention, inside.!
You're surrounded.!
Drop your weapons
and file out one at a time.!
- Don't shoot! Oh! They've taken me hostage!
- Attention, inside.!
Drop your weapons
and file out one at a time!
This is the Beverly Hills
Police Department.
Told you this warn't no house.
- You heard him. It's the police department.
- This is your last warning.!
All right!
Fire one in!
Look.
They's a-playin' kick the can.
Move in!
I knew we shouldn't have never left home.
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
Right this way.
We've I.D. 'd them all.
- Excellent.
- We want the wheels of justice to spin quickly.
These criminals must be
prosecuted and incarcerated...
before our client finds out
what happened.
Exactly.
The reputation of Milburn Drysdale is at stake.
Would everyone turn
to the right, please.
Huh.! Hmm.! Pathetic.
Now we have, starting on the left,
a Jedediah Clampett.
- Then, next to him, his daughter, Elly May.
- Huh?
And a Daisy Mae Moses, a. k. a. "Granny. "
And a nephew, jethro Bodine.
And some woman involved in a drive-by slapping.
Oh, chief. Chief. Are you okay?
Chief. Quickly! Say something!
Say something!
You're fired!
Mr. Clampett, sir!
I am deeply sorry...
for any embarrassment
my former assistant might have caused you.
- I... I...
- Yes, sir. I... I...
I- I humbly apologize
for my egregious error.
And rest assured
that it will never happen again...
as I am no longer
in the employ of the bank.
Chief, Mr. Drysdale,
I will clean out my desk at once.
Oh, dear.! Oh, please,
don't trouble yourselves.
Please, gentlemen. Oh. Oh, thank you.
Don't trouble yourselves.
Oh, I'm... Thank you. Thank you so much.
Oh, thank... No.
So, then everything is fine?
Mr. Clampett, please don't
take your money from my bank.
I'll do anything you want.
I'll contribute to charities, anything.
I'll eat mud.
That won't be necessary.
All I want is for this here lady
to watch over my affairs.
Me? You want me?
Well, I reckon
you done what you done...
'cause you didn't know
we was who we was.
And if we hadn't have been
who we was...
we'd have still been much obliged
for you a-doin' what you done.
Mr. Clampett, I will work
very hard for you.
I trust you will.
Is that all right with you,
Mr. Drysdale?
That's exactly what I'd do
in your situation.
- So we got ourselves a deal.
- Ah!
Absolutely!
Yeah.
Just to show you
there's no hard feelin's...
we'd like to invite you and your family
to Sunday supper.
Thank you. We'll be there.
It'll give me the opportunity to
swap recipes with your wife.
Oh, she'd love that.
Here you go.
- What-What are you doing?
- We're just payin' our respects.
- You...
- Oh.
Oh. Oh, no.
This is a limousine.
You'll be going home in this.
You take this, and I'll follow you
in my Rolls-Royce.
- There you go.
- Is that your car?
- Yes, it is.
- Ain't that fancy!
Can I drive it?
You drive my $180,000
Rolls-Royce?
Uh, well, of course you can, son.
I think that's a great idea.
Hot dog!
Howdy!
Oh, isn't this exciting?
Elly May Clampett,
sit down!
Oh, excuse me.
Hello.
Let Mr... Let Mr. Clampett know...
that the full weight of the bank
is ready to help them.
- Yes, chief.
- She thinks she's talkin' to somebody.
Ain't even a cord there.
Like real estate, bonds, securities.
Whatever it is he wants, it's his.
Mr. Drysdale wants you to know that the bank
is ready to help in any way that it can.
There's one reason and one reason only
I moved out here.
I'm lookin' to get hitched.
Chief, he says
he wants to get hitched.
- "Hitched"?
- Married.
- Married?
- Chief, that's what I said.
Miss Hathaway, if...
if Clampett wants a wife...
tell him that you will
personally find him one.
Oh, chief, capable as I may be,
matrimonial brokering is...
Is now one of your specialties.
Congratulations, Miss Hathaway,
and good luck.
Yes, sir.
Oh, dear.
No problem.
Uh, Mr. Clampett.
Just exactly what
are you looking for in a fiancée?
A "fiancée"?
"Fiancée"is French
for the person you intend to marry.
Well, I'm lookin'
for a refined lady...
to help me
raise my daughter, Elly May.
Aw, Pa,
I'm already raised up.
And refined.
- Ah.
- Elly May, don't spit from a movin' vehicle.
Wait till it stops.
Jethro, save some for our guests.
Here you go, Uncle Jed.
I think old Duke
is sweet on your critter.
She's not a critter.
She's a champion French "Barbonet. "
And her purebred puppies
are gonna be worth $3,000 each.
Uh, son, what, uh...
What do you do?
Don't know.
Oh, I'm just
president of a bank.
Wow. Uncle Jed, can I
be a president too?
Now, Jethro, that's a mighty disrespectful
thing to say to Mr. Drysdale.
- No.
- Ask him if you can be vice president.
Vice president.
Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm. I think so.
We can... We can always use another good man.
Hoo-whee. I'm gonna get me
a fancy office and a pretty secretary.
There's them bells again.
Jethro, I bet you there's somebody
standin'at that front door right now.
If I was you,
I'd eat real quick whilst he's gone.
Oh, that's good.
Margaret, why don't you help yourself, dear.
- Oh, good Lord.
- What is it?
- Howdy, mister.
- Hi. I'm Woodrow Tyler.
- I'm here to see Jed Clampett.
- Well, come on in.
No, no. No.
- Tyler. Well, what brings you here?
- Sir, hello.
We took up a collection to buy these
beautiful flowers for our newest clients.
Welcome to Beverly Hills.
Well, thank you, sonny.
Tyler, can the ham. Just introduce yourself
and get out of here, okay?
- Very pleased to meet you.
- Howdy!
Elly May Clampett!
- He was fixin' to bite my hand.
- Well, stand him up.
- Tyler, apologize.
- My fault completely, Mr. Clampett.
I moved too quickly.
You have a beautiful daughter...
and very strong.
- Mrs. Drysdale.
- Hmm?
What could help Elly May
be as refined as you?
Well, I went to
finishing school in France.
No one understands refinement and
sophistication better than the French.
Hmm. Do you think we ought to
move ourselves to France?
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't. No, she doesn't.
Actually, you can find a good French tutor
that'll come right to your home.
I don't wanna change.
I just wanna be who I am.
- And I ain't goin'to no France.!
- Oh, my.
Excuse me.
- Mrs. Drysdale.
- Hmm?
If you ain't gonna eat them vittles,
can I have 'em?
Of course you can, son.
Bon appétit.
Thank you.
Elly May, come on down here.
- How'd you know where I was, Pa?
- 'Cause ever since you could walk...
you've been climbin' trees
and cuddlin' with your critters.
It's high time you started thinkin'
about changin' some things.
You need to start wearin' dresses
and fixin' up nice.
But, Pa,
folks would call me a sissy.
It ain't sissy for girls
to act like girls.
Ever since your ma died,
I done what I knew best...
and raised you up like a boy...
rough housin', fishin', fightin'.
Yeah. That stuff's fun.
Elly, nature made you a girl,
and here lately...
she's been gettin' more
and more positive about it.
Aw, Pa.
Every time
I look into your eyes...
I can see your ma there.
Was my ma refined?
Oh, yes.
She was a real genteel lady.
I miss her so much...
even now.
I wanna be
just like my ma was.
I reckon I do need somebody
to teach me the ways.
Yeah, reckon you do.
And now I got the means
to make that happen.
Tyler, don't you have anything
better to do today?
I just thought you'd wanna know more
about the richest dumb guy in America.
- He's a hayseed, a hillbilly.
- Mm!
So this Clampett guy
should be easy, huh?
Yes, but we better do it fast
before he gets married.
Married? Tyler,
Clampett's getting married?
No, but he wants to.
- He's a horny old goat lookin' for some action?
- Nah.
He's just looking for a refined lady...
- to help raise his hellcat daughter, Elly May.
- Hmm.
But he did seem interested when somebody
brought up the idea of a French tutor.
Hmm. A French tutor.
Bonjour.
My name is Laurette Voleur...
and I am a...
French governess.
Well, come on in, ma'am.
Bonjour.
I am going door-to-door...
to see if anyone
needs my services.
- My business card.
- "Mademoiselle. "
"Mademoiselle... "
- Sorry, ma'am. I don't think so.
- Are you sure?
- Yep.
- There is not a young woman in the house...
who is perhaps a bit, uh, unruly?
Not that I can think of,
but, then again, we just moved here.
Nobody in need of refinement
and sophistication?
No. Maybe you oughta
try the neighbors.
Oh, well, I am so sorry
to bother you.
I will be going now.
Well, what's the problem, ma'am?
I was just hoping that my services
would be needed, but...
- Well, what do you do?
- I teach, um... how do you say this...
oh, rambunctious teenage girls
how to be more ladylike and proper.
Well, dog my cats. You know,
Mrs. Drysdale was just telling us...
about how the French was the best
at finishing a gal out.
Oui, they are. They are
the very, very best...
at making a woman a woman.
Hey. I just thought of somethin'.
Maybe she could help
with Elly May.
Oh.
Here, Rascal.
Yeah.
You like swimmin'
in this cement pond, don't you?
You like it too, Frankie?
Takin'that duck for a swim?
And over here by the cement pond
is my daughter Elly.
Elly, say hello to Miss Laurette.
- Howdy, Miss Laurette.
- Bonjour, Elly May.
It is such a pleasure
to meet you.
I was thinkin',
every day after school...
maybe Miss Laurette
could help teach you to be a lady.
- How about that?
- Okay.
Spanky likes you.
Not as much as I like him.
Go on, now,
and stay out of trouble.
I finally figured
this game out, Spanky.
You take this ball...
you put it down
this here gully.
It rolls down yonder.
Then you hurl yourself
down this slippery gully...
and see how many of them there
snake-bashin' clubs...
you can knock down...
before the ball gets there.
What a stupid idiot.
Did you say somethin', ma'am?
What a stupendous intellect.
That's 'cause I graduated
the sixth grade, ma'am.
Only took three years.
Now, Elly May,
sit straight, chin up...
and try to practice looking interested
when people are boring you.
Ah, greetings, Mr. Clampett.
- Well, howdy, Miss Jane.
- Hello, Elly May.
Miss Jane, this here
is Miss Laurette Voleur.
Bonjour, Mademoiselle Laurette.
Comment allez-vous?
Tut-tut-tut-tut-tut.
- I must only speak the English
in front of Elly May.   - Of course.
Uh, Mr. Clampett, drawing
from Commerce Bank clientele...
I have selected some preliminary
bridal prospects for you.
Oh.! Oh, dear.! Oh, my goodness.!
Mon Dieu.!
How clumsy of me. I'm so sorry.
Oh. Oh, it's no... no problem.
No problem whatsoever.
At the bank, I have these in triplicate.
- I shall return.
- I'll walk you out, Miss Hathaway.
Why, thank you, Jethro.
So, Mr. Clampett...
perhaps we should discuss
my, uh, weekly salary?
Shoo!
Shoo, cow. Excuse me, I'm just going to
reach over here and press this button.
Hello. Can anyone hear me?
Can anyone hear me?
- Yeah.
- Can somebody help me?
- Hello?
- Miss Hathaway?
How's it feel to live in Beverly Hills?
- Hello?
- I can hear you. Where are you?
Please, can somebody
let me out of here?
I am trapped inside the wall.
Hello? Hello?
- Hello? Hello?
- Just stay put, Miss Hathaway. I'll get ya out.
Hello?
Watch your head.
Miss Hathaway?
Yoo-hoo!
I'm in. This is gonna be
easier than I thought.
So, they bought the French thing?
Mais oui.
They're bumpkins.
It's a crime
they have so much money.
It's worse than a foreigner
winning the lottery.
I know exactly
what I'm gonna do.
First, I'll lure in Clampett.
That'll be easy.
Next, I'll take Elly May
and slap on a little window dressing.
Make him think I turned her into a real lady.
Then, when the time
is just right...
I'll play one off the other
and... wham!
- They won't know what hit 'em.
- You're not gonna sleep with him, are you?
- That's not your problem.
- Okay, Laura?
I got my hand on your butt.
Okay. Hold on.
I got someone on call waiting.
Hello? Hello?
It was nobody. Okay, now.
I got my hand on your butt,
and I'm squeezing.
Tyler!
Get your hand off my butt.
- Mr. Drysdale!
- Get a pencil and write this down.
Yes, Mr. Drysdale.
Right. Uh-huh.
I can do that.
Howdy, I'm Elly May.
You must be Mr. Drysdale's son.
Well, thanks for picking me up.
Is this here your car?
Are we goin' to school,
or are we just goin' to stand here all day?
- Hey, y'all. Howdy.
- She's with me.
Heck, Morgan, I'm tryin' to be friendly-like...
but these folks don't seem
to want to say howdy back.
- They sure are shy.
- So what?
Elly May, who cares?
They're losers.
Not one of them is worth
over 300 million.
- Uh-oh.
- Well, if it isn't Morgan...
spelled big "M,"
little "organ. "
- We've gotta go.   - Not so fast, bank boy.
Cough up your lunch money now.
All I have is $400
in traveler's checks.
So just sign them
and hand them over.
Jake, show these two what happened
to the last guy who didn't pay up.
Well, I can wire the money
to your account.
Before the close
of the business day.
I don't see why you
had to give anything to that gorilla.
Well, that gorilla
is the captain of the wrestling team.
Wow. I never wrestled a team before.
- Well, 'lessen you count the McCarter triplets.
- Cappuccino?
- What?
- Two.
Thank you, Tiffany.
This here electronic whittler
works real fine.
Why, hello, Jethro.
Well, howdy, Miss Hathaway.
My, don't you look strapping
in your new business suit.
- Armani?   - No. I'm pretty sure it's wool.
Sure does itch like wool.
- Miss Hathaway?
- Oh, no, no. We're colleagues.
Call me Jane.
Me Jane, you Jethro.
Okay. Okay, Miss Hathaway.
Can I get one of these
electronic whittlers for Uncle Jed?
- It's his birthday coming up real soon.
- Let me make a note of that.
And speaking of your Uncle Jed,
back to the job at hand...
- Finding him a suitable wife.
- Can I help?
Heck, back in the hollow, my ma
was the best matchmaker around.
- Is that so?
- Uh-huh.
First thing she'd do is get
the back-fence gossips start a-jawin'.
Why, we could drop some
items in the trades.
- Excellent.
- Thank you.
And then she'd...
What'd she do?
She'd hang a sign
on the church bulletin board.
Maybe we can get
a big bulletin board.
No, no. We'd better be
a bit more discreet.
Tell me, what are your
uncle's favorite things?
Shoot, that's easy.
- He likes smoked crawdads.
- Mm-hmm.
Sowbelly and hand-slung chitterlings.
And sponge cake.
Besides food, Jethro.
- Oh. He likes people who don't waste nothin'.
- Oh, go on.
And his favorite song is "I'm So
Lonesome I Could Cry" by Hank Williams.
- Yes!
- Yes, ma'am.
Entrez.
Excuse me, ma'am, uh...
is that Hank Williams I hear?
I'm sorry.
It must be too loud.
- I will...
- No, no.
I was just listening to it
while repairing this old dress...
and, uh, waiting for
my sponge cake to bake.
You're cookin' a sponge cake?
Oui.
It is my spécialité.
I love this music.
It makes me want to dance.
It's so romantic.
You are a fine dancer...
and a very attractive man.
Whomever Miss Hathaway
finds for you to marry...
is going to be
a very happy woman.
Well, thank you, ma'am.
And all women know
"a-penis" is hard to find.
- Excuse me?
- "A-penis. "
Oh, happiness!
Well, uh...
I've disturbed
your work enough, ma'am.
Jethro, have you considered
getting a new car?
Nope, but I told Uncle Jed we should slap
a new coat of paint on this'n.
But he said just
'cause we had money...
we didn't need to go
showin' it off.
I was just thinking,
oh, you should, you should.
You would look so good
in a big new fashy car.
Big fashy car, huh? Maybe.
Yep.
Okay, Miss Jane,
I'm 'bout ready to pull over.
You are so impossibly romantic.
Close your eyes.
Hot diggity dog!
Okay, now,
keep 'em closed.
How charmingly old-fashioned.
Mm.
Open your eyes
and look up.
Ain't she pretty?
Oh, my God!
The chief is going to kill me.
We'll be back
with the financial news after this message.
Howdy.
I'm jethro Bodine.
I'm talkin' to all
you ladies out there.
Are you looking for
the perfect husband?
Then considerjed Clampett.
Yes, Jed is rated triple A's...
for a-ttractive, a-vailable,
and a-billionaire.
So come on down
to the Commerce Bank of Beverly Hills...
and see me, jethro Bodine,
vice president.
- Dear, what's the matter?
- And remember.
I'm not only Jed's wife finder.
I'm also his nephew.
I'm ruined.
Oh!
Howdy.
Thank you.
Hathaway, you are embarrassing
this institution!
This is a carnival.
What kind of a numbskull would
think up a harebrained scheme like this?
That'd be me, Mr. Drysdale.
Y- Your idea.
Well...
Well, it's brilliant.!
Insightful. Cutting edge.
You're a born leader, son.
We've have had 1,215 women
respond to the ad.
- And two men.
- Wh...
Once I've entered the data into the computer,
worked my magic... presto.
- We will narrow them down to a precious few.
- Send in the next five.
Oh, uh, Hathaway, uh,
you're not validating parking, are you?
Parking? Um...
Oh, that was my idea too,
Mr. Drysdale.
Well, it's a brilliant idea,
if I may say so.
Let's see, uh...
1,215 women... and two men.
At a dollar and a half
every 15 minutes.
Ah, well, that's only
gonna cost me 5...
5-5-5-5... $5,000.
Well...
- Bonjour, Jethro.
- Well, howdy, Miss Laurette.
What is all of this?
Miss Jane said a big fancy car
would be more suitin' to my personality...
so I'm fixin' on makin' one
out of my truck.
Personally, if it would have been me,
I would have just bought a new one.
But... carry on.
What a moron.
Hey, organ,
what are you doin' here?
- You come here to wrestle me?
- No.
Or did you just come here
to kiss the gym foor?
Come on, Morgan, just kiss it.
Come on, kiss it.
Why don't you pick on
somebody your own size?
And what business
is it of yours, baby?
What are you doing here, anyway,
corn pone?
I came by to join
the wrestlin' team.
I don't wrestle girls,
at least not in the gym...
but in your case,
I'll make an exception.
- Good. Then let's get started.
- Whoa!
- I'm gonna kill you!
- I'm goin' to kill you.!
No one is going to kill
anyone here!
Not without a signed
permission slip from home.
- Got it?
- Got it, Coach.
So, Jethro...
building on your visionary plan
for finding your uncle's wife...
I've... I've created
this rather modest database program.
I've cross-referenced the applicants...
against the parameters
you indicated he desired...
by specifying the search criteria
into functional groupings...
and selecting the field values...
through the use
of embedded commands...
and, of course,
basic Boolean algebra.
Miss Jane, I have no idea
what you just said.
Oh, Jethro, you are
so delightfully... primitive.
Uh, Miss Hathaway, would you
step into my office, please.
- And bring the, uh, the Arlington file.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm sorry.
- Mr. Drysdale...
since I have trained three Kentucky Derby
winners for other people...
it seems a logical extension that I'd want
to own and operate my own stud farm...
Arlington Acres.
Well, it's just...
It's just a very exciting idea.
Then you agree that his net worth
and rural background...
make Jed Clampett
the perfect partner for such a venture.
Absolutely. You and Clampett,
partners in a stud farm.
- I think it's a wonderful idea.
- So you'll call him and arrange for us to meet?
You bet I will.
- I'm sure he can't wait to see you.
- Oh.
In fact, as soon as you leave, I'm going
to call Mr. Clampett on the phone.
- Ah! This is very exciting.
- Isn't it?
Yeah.
But, chief,
you specifically told me...
that you did not want Mr. Clampett
involved in such a risky venture.
Exactly.
Shred and burn that.
And don't ever let that lady
back in this office.
It went fantastically.
Mr. Drysdale said I would
be a perfect partner for Mr. Clampett.
Yes. I'll tell you more
when I get back. Bye.
Excuse me, ma'am. If Mr. Drysdale thinks
you'd be perfect for my Uncle Jed...
I can take you over
to meet him right now.
- Wonderful!
- Come on.
I think you're gonna
like Miss Arlington.
Miss Jane picked her out
with her computer-datin' base.
Then Mr. Drysdale
personally approved her.
Computer-datin' base, huh?
What'll they think of next?
- Hello, Miss Arlington.
- Mr. Clampett.
Well, gee, uh, I don't know
quite how to begin.
Then let me start.
I know, by just looking at you,
you are the perfect man for my stud farm.
- Stud farm?
- If it makes it any easier for you...
I am willing to take on
multiple partners.
Multiple partners.
Uh, no offense, ma'am... but I'm afraid
I'd find that just a tad uncomfortable.
Well, what if it was with somebody
you really trusted...
like Mr. Drysdale?
I don't think this is
the sort of thing...
Mr. Drysdale would want
to be involved in.
Oh, well, you should
have seen his face...
when I showed him the pictures
of what I have in mind.
- He was very excited.
- I don't doubt that.
Would you like to see the pictures?
They're very detailed.
Not just yet!
Don't you think we're
movin' awful fast?
Oh, not as far
as I'm concerned, Mr. Clampett.
I've got my license,
and I'm ready to breed.
Excuse me, ma'am, uh...
I could use a glass
of iced tea.
- Yourself?
- Sure.
I'm learnin' Elly May to ride my motorcycle!
- How do you stop this thing?
- I'm gonna tan your hide.!
You're doin' real good.
Now put on the brakes!
- Granny?
- Whoa.!
I'm gonna get you!
Granny! Watch your head!
Stop! Oh-oh-oh!
- Dang!
- I'll help you, Granny.
Come on. Swim over here.
There we go. Give me your hand.
Upsy-daisy.
Come on.
There we...
Ow.! Granny.!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Granny!
Miss Arlington, you reckon if we got hitched,
you could help me tame
my daughter, Elly May?
Are you proposing
we get married?
Well, I wouldn't feel
right about breedin' if we didn't.
Okay, men, that's it. Hit the mineral baths.
- Howdy.
- Well, well. Look who's here.
- Missed you at practice, babe.
- She didn't come alone.
Hey, Morgan.
What are you doin' here?
- Well, who's all these folks?
- Just to keep things fair.
- Is this some kind of joke?
- Well, come on, baby.
Let's wrestle.
- Come on!
- Come on. Give it to him.
Oh, wait. That's mine.
It's mine.
Come on, man.
You can do it!
- Fight in the gym.
- All right. - Cool.
Wait. Hold on. I'm getting a fax.
Meet me there.
This here's what I call
the Clampett clamp.
That's not legal.
Really?
Well, try this one.
Hey, come on.
- I call it the possum pretzel.
- That ain't legal either.
- Well...
- Ow!
What about
the hickory nut crunch?
That's definitely not legal!
Well, ain't nothin' legal 'round here?
One, two...
- Yeah!
- Three.
Young lady!
I think we've found
a new team captain.
Sorry, Derek.
You're demoted.
Come here, Morgan.
Thanks, y'all.
I truly appreciate y'all a-tossin' me
this here fancy birthday party.
Everybody looks just as nice as peach pie.
I just got one
question for you...
- Who are these people?
- Well...
Howdy, Miss Jane.
Oh, my goodness, jethro.
I took your advice...
made me a big fashy car.
It's very you.
Very, very macho.
- Thank you.
- Well, shall we?
Is Pa here yet?
Elly May Clampett,
you look plumb elegant.
Thanks, Pa. I feel kind of funny
gettin' all gussied up like this...
but Miss Laurette
says I'll get used to it.
You've done a fine job in
turnin' Elly May into a lady.
Thank you,
Monsieur Clampett.
She is a diamond in ze rough,
just like you.
What's all this?
Sushi, calamari, caviar.
What? Speak American.
Listen, I was wondering if, um...
maybe sometime
we could go out.
Not on a date or anything, but just maybe
to go get some burgers or something.
Take off that silly hat.
Then again, I would, uh...
understand if you didn't want to.
Sounds like fun.
So, Jethro, once we find
your Uncle Jed a wife...
- Perhaps it'll be your turn to get hitched.
- Me? No.
I'm gonna be
a Hollywood bachelor...
date all the hot young starlets.
Well, let me remind you not to overlook
the charms of the slightly older woman...
who more than makes up with experience
what she may lack in other arenas.
Okay, Miss Jane.
No problem.
- Oh, please, let me.
- Tyler, clam it. It's showtime.
Miss Laurette?
Why are you cryin'?
I- I have just spoken
with your father.
And he says I would make
"ze" [the] best wife for him.
- He did?
- But as happy as I would make him...
I am afraid that you will think I'm too young
and beautiful to be your mother.
Who'd of thought it...
Miss Laurette and my pa? Hmm.
Oh, where is he? Oh.
So I can call you whenever I want?
You'll hotfoot it right over?
- Mm-hmm.
- Hot dog.
Thank you.
I will miss Elly May so much
when you find yourself a wife.
- And I will miss you too.
- I hadn't thought about you not bein' here.
It's sure been a pleasure
to have you stay with us.
Thank you.
Jed?
Elly May said ze strangest thing
to me tonight.
She said she would love
for me to be her mother.
I'm sure she'll get over the disappointment
in whomever you choose.
I love Elly May
just like a daughter.
Perhaps you should
speak with her.
I'll do that.
Well.
This here's a big night for you...
all dressed up and ladylike
at your first Beverly Hills social.
Your ma would be so proud.
Thanks, Pa. Miss Laurette said
she was right proud too.
You like her, don't you?
Well, I like her just fine,
and I guess you like her too.
I certainly do.
All I want is for you
to be happy, Elly May.
I just want you
to be happy, Pa.
Well, I reckon
there's no time like right now.
- Happy birthday, jed.
- Happy birthday.
Oh!
Well, I got a feeling you're
worth every dime of it too.
Step up here. Let me take
a good look at you.
Boy, you're looking good
on your birthday.
I think we need a speech,
don't you? Speech.
You know, I have more
than any one man deserves...
yet there is something
I'd like for my birthday.
I'd like to ask the one who helped Elly May
become a lady to be my wife.
Miss Laurette Voleur.
Oh, I am so surprised.
This is ze happiest day
of my life.
Huh?
All right.
Congratulations.
- You don't say.
- I do say!
Well, I'll be.
Who's he marrying?
Oh, some foozy
with a fancy accent.
She seems sneaky to me.
I don't trust her.
Oh, Granny, you
don't trust anybody.
Never mind about that.
I'm invitin' you to the weddin'
and the cousins.
But just from Jed's side,
not includin' the Kelloggs nor the Daggs.
Now, Granny, you're not gonna
get into your tonic...
and disappear like you did when Jed
married your daughter, are ya?
Jethrine, your Uncle Jed's
gettin' married.
I always cry at weddings.
Oh, now, honey.
I do.
Well, you got both kinds
of chickens here, Jed.
- White and the brown.
- What you got there, son?
Oh, it's just a standard
prenuptial agreement.
Miss Hathaway said for you not to tell
anyone that you signed it, not even her.
Well, if Miss Hathaway says so,
I don't even have to read this. It must be fine.
They'll be comin' from miles around
to get my expert doctorin'...
and I won't
turn a one away.
I done took me the "hypocritter" oath
to help everybody.
Kinda weak.
Probably good enough for city folk.
Tyler.!
Did you get him
to sign the papers?
Oh, yeah.
He's a very trusting man.
He thinks everyone's honest.
That's a quality I admire in a man
I'm taking advantage of.
Hey, uh, you're not
sleeping with him, are you?
Tyler, you know once I move in with a man,
I stop having sex with him.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
- Keep your mind on business. Now go.
- Hey, wait.
- How about a little good-bye kiss?
- All right.
I knowed it!
I done catched you red-handed,
you two-timin' hussy!
When I inform jed, the weddin'will be off!
Let's get her.
Uh-oh. Oh.
No! No! No!
Shut up, you old hag.!
We got just the place for you.
Let me down!
I've already input the info
into the computer.
Soon as you say "I do"... bing!
I press "Enter. "
Boom! The money goes
via modem to Switzerland.
Bing, bang, boom.
We're rich!
- Oh.
- Look at those legs.
I can't wait to get them
wrapped around me.
Get her off of me!
- Get those legs off him!
- She's got crap on her boots!
She doesn't even think we're her grandchildren.
And you say you fear
for your lives?
Yes. I'm afraid the poor old dear
tried to shoot us with a shotgun.
Are there any other
indications of dementia?
Last week, we caught her
trying to eat a raccoon.
- Really?
- She calls us kidnappers.
They are! They are!
The old buzzards are!
- Wait, now.
- Grandma, please.
Ow! She bit me again, honey!
Better check her for rabies.
- Get two orderlies in here stat!
- Poor old dear.
We can't take the heartbreak a minute longer.
We need to admit her someplace...
where she can be kept in a straitjacket
away from sharp objects and pay phones.
From what you've told me,
I'd say that your grandmother...
is a perfect candidate
for, uh, electroshock therapy.
And nobody... I repeat nobody... is allowed
into the Clampett estate without an invitation.
Sans invitation, non.
Miss jane, this fella's all mad at me
'cause I opened up...
this box of wedding food...
but there ain't nothin' in there
but a bunch of snails.
I think the snails got up in there
and et all the food.
No problem. Jethro,
we'll just buy some more.
And, Henri, the snails go back
to the garden where they belong...
s'il vous plâit.
To your posts.
Everything's going fine,
but I have one small question.
Granny has not been available for her
fitting, and the wedding is tomorrow.
Hmm. Come to think of it, I ain't seen
hide nor hair of Granny since yesterday.
And you're not concerned?
No. She done the same thing
when I married Elly May's ma.
Came pourin' in
about three days later...
naked as a jaybird and
reeking of her medicine.
Hmm.
Play it, George.!
Whoo!
Miss Hathaway, if the immediate family
isn't concerned enough...
to file a missing persons report,
then there's nothing we can do.
But, Captain Gallo,
I suspect foul play.
I'm sorry,
but my hands are tied.
But if you're desperate,
you might try this guy.
He's expensive, but he's also the best
private investigator around.
Oh, this case was pretty easy
to crack, Miss Hathaway.
I have met unsavory characters before,
but she takes the cake.
Laurette Voleur,
a.k.a. Laura Jackson.
A.k.a. Lili Lebecque.
Married 12 times to any guy
with a little extra money to throw around.
I should've known.
Voleur. French for "thief. "
Now what about Granny?
The old lady is being forcibly held
at the Los Viejos Retirement Home...
a disreputable establishment,
often cited for patient abuse.
Be tough to break her out.
What a calamity,
and the wedding is just hours away.
Reverend, do you think Cousin Bill's gonna
be too busy to make it to the weddin'?
Hillary, where did I put that invitation?
Flowers, come here. Quick.
They need tent stakes
in the backyard right now. Let's go.
Hello. Clampett residence.
Mr. Drysdale?
- I have an urgent call for Mr. Drysdale.
- I'll take that.
He works for me.
- Woody Tyler. Can I help you?
- Tyler, what are you doing there?
Um, I just dropped by
to see if I could be of help.
Tell Mr. Drysdale
to stop the wedding.
- Okay.      - Laurette is a phony
who is after Mr. Clampett's money.
Well, that's not good.
- Do it, Tyler, or your job is toast.
- I got it.
- She's getting fat, Mom.
- Where is Hathaway?
She was supposed
to check in with me hours ago.
- Well, I don't know, dear.
- Mr. Drysdale.
- What do you want, Tyler?
- Miss Hathaway called.
She said something had come up and to go
ahead and start the wedding without her.
- Well, what could have come up?
- I wish I knew.
My, what a lovely dog.
Oh, thank you.
Tyler, make yourself useful.
Go count the olives.
Oh, yeah. Right away.
Oh, I hate that little worm.
What could possibly be more important
than this to Miss Hathaway?
- Look at that. New nurse.
- Yeah.
- Howdy, Mama!
- My baby! Oh! Why!
My goodness, Beverly Hills
has made you so sophisticated.
Doesn't your twin brother
look handsome?
- Hi, jethro.
- Give him a kiss, Jethrine.
Howdy, Jethro.
Oh, excuse me.
- I reckon.
- Yep.
Young man...
I am here to see
Daisy Mae Moses.
Ah, then you must be here
for the rabies test.
Yes. Rabies test.
Exactly right.
Then you want Room 525.
Oh, nurse.
Better be careful.
She's a wild one.
We had to give her
electroshock therapy.
Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- No problem.
My God.
Oh, Granny.
Your elixir.
I will take you
out of here immediately.
Your hair is just
a bit disheveled.
Miss Jane?
Is that you?
- 'Tis I.
- Oh!
- Granny says she don't trust Miss Laurette.
- Oh.
Take off that silly hat.
I heard she's so skinny, you couldn't
hit her with a handful of corn.
Look where they're parking the cars.
My God, how tacky.
This place is turning into a zoo.
I think she's tryin' to
take him for all he's got.
Hmm.
Hi there, handsome.
- You mind if I sit in this chair?
- This chair?
- I was kind of saving...
- Thank you.
Lovely wedding, isn't it?
Go.
Oh. We've got to get back.
I called. I told them
to stop the wedding...
but that Tyler
is so incompetent.
Tyler? Him and Laurette's the ones
that stuck me in this hellhole!
So, stabbed in the back
by one of our own.
And she ain't no foreigner.
There they are.
Stop them.
Jethro, hold up.
- Come on. Come on.
- Oh, there she is.
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Oh, she looks beautiful.
Oh, I've got the vapors.
My makeup.
Oh.
"Dearly beloved, we are gathered here
in case of an emergency.
"Oxygen masks will fall from
the overhead compartment.
"Your seat cushion can be
used as a floatin'device.
- Thus sayeth the Lord. "
- Excuse me, Reverend.
But I believe you're readin'
the airplane safety instructions.
May we skip this part?
Hathaway had better have
a good excuse for not being here.
Quick, Granny, hurry.!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Can I see your invitations, please?
I'll handle this, Granny. Young man, have you
any idea with whom you're speaking?
I'd say one crazy lady
and another one with a bad wig.
Every strand of
this here hair is mine!
- Ow!
- Oh... Oh, Granny, no, no, no!
No, Granny, no! No, Granny, no!
We'll find another way.
"We are gathered here
to unite these two in holy matrimony. "
- Can we hurry things up, please?
- Yes, ma'am.
Come on. Come on, baby.
"If any one of y'all has one good reason
these two shouldn't be hitched... "
and it darn tootin'
better be a good reason...
"then speak now or forever
hold your peace. "
- All right, then. "I now pronounce you... "
- Please. Please. Please.
"man and... "
What in tarnation is that?
Charge!
- Come on, Granny!
- Who is that?
It is I, Jane Hathaway.
Hathaway,
have you lost your mind?
She's an impostor. She's marrying
Mr. Clampett just to steal his money.
- That sidewinder Tyler helped her!
- I'm ruined!
Milburn! Milburn!
Tyler. Let's set up the computer
and push the button.
If I can't have their money,
nobody should.
Quick!
Okay.
We'll send their billion bucks
bouncin'around so many banks...
- they'll never find it.
- It's all set.
All we got to do is push that button.
You rustic, nose-picking,
inbred yokels!
- You're all about to be poor again.
- Think again.
No, you don't,
you schemin'skunk.!
Wait'll I get my hands on you!
Oh, Pa, you must be
so disappointed.
A little.
But, Elly May, I was mainly
marryin' Miss Laurette...
'cause I thought you wanted her
for your new ma.
- I'm so sorry, Pa.
- Don't be sorry.
I love you
just the way you are.
I reckon I oughta raise you up
to be who you want to be.
Well, I don't need a new ma,
not as long as I got you and Granny.
Hot dog, Miss Jane!
You sure are a good shot.
Well, thank you, Jethro.
- Whoo!
- Got ya!
Well, folks,
I guess you can say...
things didn't turn out
quite the way we planned.
So, since there ain't
gonna be no hitchin'...
and we're all here anyway...
I say we have
one hellacious shindig.
Yeah.!
- Let go of me.!
- Here, boys. She's all yours!
Let go of my hand!
- Hey! Nobody treats my pa that way!
- Shut up!
How's that for ladylike,
you old money-grubber?
Come on, city boy,
let's dance.
All right, stand back!
You're under arrest
for kidnapping...
attempted embezzlement
and fraud.
Oh, right.!
It was all Tyler's idea.
I admit it freely.
It was all her idea.
I always fall in love
with the wrong kind of man.
- Clean up that cake.
- Don't step on the train.
I'll wait for you, honey.
Well, where was she? She... Oh.!
- Oh, well...
- Whee doggie!
Whoo.! Yeah.! That's good.
Thank you.
That's just about right.
Oops!
It's a shame they had to
file for bankruptcy.
I just hope my call to
the I.R.S. didn't have...
- Oh, I shouldn't open it. Sorry.
- No problem. We'll do it again.
But I got there...
That old lady is, uh...
That old lady is...
I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
- She's gettin' pretty old by now, I'll tell ya.
Still rolling.
- Okay. Give me a big smile.
- I can't get any bigger.
So, uh, what happened?
Actually, he slapped me.
Why don't you come up here?
Let me take a good look at you.
Jim. Jim? They're gettin'worried about you.
- Not even a bridesmaid.
- I gotta do this again.
Action.!
We've got... No,
we've got to get back.
I called, I told them
to postpone the...
- I lost my purse.
- It's right here.
- How did you get it?
- I don't know.
Jethro?
Come on down here.
Likely as not, there's
another family lives up here...
there.
Download GOM Player to experience
the highest video and audio quality!