When I first started safecrackina,
I used to rip into them.
Pour in the soup and blow the shit
out of them. It was like rape.
It had this sexual theme
runnina throuah it. I used to...
...blow them open and plunae riaht in.
Often, I was sexually
aroused at the time.
But as I became more proficient,
I learned to sneak up on them.
Ferret out their secrets.
I used to have them open
before they even knew I was there.
It was more like
seduction than rape.
The beauty of it was, I was fallina
in love with the whole thina.
ln love?
l take it you were fixating
on safecracking as a displacement...
...of normal sexual relations.
Tell me, how was your love life
at that time?
Just like any other guy.
l was looking.
Looking f or what?
-Love.
-Love. And what is love?
He was looking f or something
deeper, more lasting.
Something more than just nookie.
That's valid.
Time is getting short
and we've got a graduate.
Anderson is about to leave us
after ten years.
How does the group feel about that?
That's an outpouring of real feeling.
How do you feel about it, Duke?
-Are you sure you wanna know?
-Well, that's what we're here f or.
-Angry.
-Why is that?
-They grabbed ten years of my life.
-You knew the law. You took a chance.
Who are you angry at?
Those sons of bitches that cut
a piece out of this country every day.
Do you characterize their actions
as similar to yours?
Damn right. What's advertising
but a legalized con game?
What the hell's marriage? Prostitution
with a government stamp on it.
What is your stock market?
A fix ed horse race.
Some business guy steals a bank,
he's a big success story.
Some other guy steals
a magazine, and he's busted.
Well, f or my part
l feel deeply moved.
Knowing that he trusts me enough
to say things he really feels.
Saying those things, which l
as a prison official, could--
You can't do shit!
l'm not on parole, l'm finished here.
There's nothing you can do.
Deputy O'Connor, Deputy O'Connor
call your office, call your office.
Deputy O'Connor, call your office,
call your office.
Cell blocks six, seven, twelve
thirteen and fourteen...
...will have inspection
tomorrow at 0545 hours.
Repeat.: Cell blocks
six, seven, twelve...
... thirteen and fourteen
will have inspection--
Meyer, William.
Anderson, Robert.
Attention.: From now on water
will be available--
Spencer, Kurt.
Repeat.: From now on water
will be available from 2200 hours.
Anderson.
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
-Well, so long.
-Come on, get out of here.
Hey, come on. Kid.
Kid.
Take it easy. Easy.
-There you are, all right?
-Take it easy, Pop.
The f ree world and it's all yours!
-l don't like it.
-What do you mean, you don't like it?
You don't like the pretty girls?
You're not that old.
They look like whores.
Only not good whores.
-When did you go inside?
-1931 . l shot a cop.
You missed the Depression
and World War ll.
-You're lucky, you missed everything.
-Announcina the departure of bus 72.
-Well, didn't you get any mail?
-Who did you write to?
My sister, she was the last one.
She must've died, because the last thing
l got f rom her, an Easter card.
-l got that in 1948.
-Terrific.
l'll take a look, he must
have something here.
Charlie, check the mezzanine.
l think we got a 501 in progress.
-What do we do with him?
-How do l know?
Hey, what's this?
Okay, what is this?
Jesus, we almost didn't even
get out of the bus station.
Well....
-l got to go to the bathroom. So long.
-Yeah, okay, man.
America, man, you know,
it's so beautif ul l want to eat it.
You hang in there, man.
-l'd like to establish an account.
-Come this way, please.
Would you like our charge card,
good f or charging...
...at any one of thousands
of establishments?
Write your name here
as a sample signature.
Say ''cheese.''
Cheese.
-Right. You want a receipt?
-No, thank you.
Mister?
-Miss lngrid Everleigh, please.
-You a f riend?
Yeah.
-Who should l say wants her?
-Mr. Anderson.
Sign in, please.
Mr. Anderson.
Yes, ma'am.
You can go up, sir.
lt's apartment 2B.
-l haven't been laid in over 10 years.
-10 years.
Well, 10 years,
three months, eight days.
Shit.
I found it.
Peace of Mind lnvestigators.
Everleigh surveillance:
July 16th, 4:45 p.m.
Code E638549.
Voice actuated.
-ls it the 15th?
-Yes.
Okay, what happens now?
You've put on weight.
lt feels good.
What are you gonna do?
-Well, let's have breakf ast first.
-Are you gonna stay?
-Well, you haven't asked me, have you?
-Oh, my God, don't be coy.
-lngrid?
-Yes.
-What sort of people live here?
-A variety.
There's a f ag decorator upstairs
and a doctor downstairs...
...although they say he's
an abortionist. They're all loaded.
-Are you staying?
-Sure, l want to sleep with you.
All right.
A red hot woman.
lf l was a red hot woman,
you wouldn't want me.
You wouldn't have the feeling
you have f or me.
Poor Duke, too bad.
Mr. Gottlieb, please.
lngrid Everleigh.
You want what you can't have. You're
always hammering on that locked door.
Werner? lt's lngrid. l'm af raid
you can't come by anymore.
My boyf riend has come back,
and he's living with me now.
l'll see you one night a week
at your place. Werner. Werner!
Look, it's very simple, l just
like him more than l like you.
l want to thank you f or a marvellous
relationship and all the presents.
But it is my apartment.
For Thursdays with you
you can continue the upkeep.
lt's not a fight, it's a negotiation.
Kisses, darling.
Poor Werner. You know, he just
doesn't know who he is.
This coffee's going to take a while.
You want to make love to me?
lce cold.
What do you think? Can l get into
these flats? Would it be worth it?
-Here?
-Yeah.
l don't wanna know about it.
-l'd need your help.
-Do it, but don't tell me about it.
You know what l'm going to do?
l'm going to back up a van and steal
the guts out of the whole place.
Now?
-You're always so serious.
-l have no sense of humour. None.
You want a $1500 advance to finance
research, lay the caper out, et cetera.
-Let me explain what l'm going to do.
-Don't interrupt.
Don't talk to me like that.
l don't give a goddamn who you are now.
lt's all right.
Angelo is just in a hurry.
He's got a lot on his mind.
l'm sorry, Duke. Nick's right.
l got a lot on my mind.
Nick's riaht, I aot a lot on my mind.
They call him Duke Anderson.
He was telling these guys--
We don't care about him.
Who's the other guy?
l told you Treasury Department
guys 100 times.
Hat, the kid. His f ather was the Hook.
But when he was knocked over in Vegas,
the old man, Papa Angelo, adopted him.
l got a lot on my mind.
How's everything with lmmigration?
Ask him.
With the appeals and everything,
Duke's got at least nine months.
Duke's aot at least nine months.
-That's D'Medico, the lawyer.
-That's right.
Duke's got at least nine months.
What do we get out
of these apartments?
A f urniture van f ull of stuff.
From Picasso paintings to stones--
Oh, Christ.
-What do you want?
-Cash. Bills, that's what you want.
-There's cash there.
-Maybe l clear 25, 000.
Twenty-five.
-Do l hear 20?
-l think we'll do better.
-How much better?
-l'm counting on this to put me out.
-l want a stake.
-A stake f or what?
l want to be a sponge fisherman.
Up at 5:30, raw fish f or breakf ast.
Out in the boats by 6:00.
By 6:30, diving f or sponges.
Hey, what's sponges?
You are not a fisherman.
You're a goddamn burglar.
l want to be a rich burglar.
What do you think?
lt stinks. What are we screwing
around with stuff like this?
Even if he scores, it's less than one
week's take in our worst horse room.
l don't know.
He's a good dependable guy.
He saved Gino's life. l think
we owe it to listen to him.
This guy's more than muscle.
Every move is laid out.
lt's like a military operation.
Not like the old days.
Hey, the old days, huh?
You still think you can take me?
Come on, l'm in pretty good shape.
Hey, look at me, Vic.
l'm a businessman.
My gut is swelling.
My ass is dropping.
l got a wife and three kids.
l belong to f our clubs.
l worry about the crabgrass in the
lawn and worms in the goddamn poodle.
lt ain't right.
Man's a hunting animal.
-lt ain't natural to be an accountant.
-Here's your linguine, Mr. Angelo.
''An FBl request f or a wiretap
on the premises...
...of Antiques lnternational.''
-What the hell is that?
-An interior decorator's.
'' For investigations relating to
transport and sale of stolen property.''
2516 of the U.S. Code, Paragraph C
where it refers to section 2315.
Also section G, paragraph one.
The f ag that owns the joint is
buying antiques heisted in the Midwest.
Approved. Next case.
-May l help you?
-ls Tommy Haskins still here?
-Hey, Tommy, somebody here to see you.
-Oh, God, what is--?
Duke?
Duke.
You've come to tell me
you've had the operation.
Duke, look at you, dear boy.
You should be so lucky.
Don't get snippy with me, you bitch.
Come in the back.
-Can we talk?
-That's all you ever want to do.
Here, perch.
Some tea?
Tommy, l got a whole building
that l want combed out.
What? Of course you do.
lt's got a doctor's office.
Six flats, two to a floor.
l want schedules of services, hours
and names of maids, doormen. The works.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
You don't want one or two flats,
you want the whole thing?
That's right.
Five hundred f or now.
Well, Duke, l haven't seen it,
and l just don't like to rush into it.
Five hundred f or now.
Give me the address
and l'll figure out how to get in.
Five hundred.
Two sugars, right? l remembered.
When l see the size and shape
of it, and how to handle it...
...l'll let you know
what the price is.
lt's five hundred.
Everything you say sounds
like five hundred. How was prison?
Okay.
Hey, Tommy, the phones are all fix ed!
Oh, God, what do l know about that?
l hope you cleaned up after yourselves
like good little telephone men.
Meet anybody interesting
in your cell?
Kid.
Did l scare you?
You? No.
l got a caper laid out.
You wanna come?
You're one of those criminals
that corrupts younger offenders.
l need you to bridge burglar
alarms, open doors...
...cut some telephone circuits.
Now you can do that.
Your piece will set you up in business.
What? So some son of a bitch
can come steal me blind?
So you claim burglary insurance.
l don't know. l was in f or dope, see?
Some guys, you put them right out
of business, you rip off their stuff.
lf a guy's not smart enough
to get insurance...
...l'm just the hand of f ate.
He's gonna lose it anyway.
ls it right to steal
f rom insurance companies?
When you go rob a guy who's got
insurance, you're doing him a f avour.
You give him
a little ex citement, a story.
He becomes more interesting
because you robbed him.
The publicity gets people
to buy insurance.
You do the f uzz a f avour because you
prove they're deserving of a pay boost.
And you do yourself a f avour
because you need the dough.
-Do you believe that?
-lt's bullshit. lt's just dog eat dog.
-But l want the first bite.
-That's my man. Okay.
Hey, Kid, don't you want
to know what your cut is?
l trust you. You lay what
you can on me:
Okay.
'' Kid, don't you want
to know what your cut is?''
The other guy says, '' l trust you.
You lay what you can on me.''
We don't need the audio bug.
Let's pull it bef ore
somebody finds it.
lf the kid is still on narcotics,
the visual surveillance is good enough.
New York Narcotics Commission.
Hanson speaking.
House lnternal Security Committee:
Surveillance AD271T-41 .
3:34 p.m. Unidentified male Caucasian.
Six-f oot-three, brown hair...
...late 30s, early 40s...
...entered the rooms above
the subject premises...
...occupied by Edward Spencer,
a nonpolitical.
Hey, hey.
-Spencer?
-Who's that?
You don't know me, but I was
tiaht with Billy Maitland.
-Maitland is dead.
-l was there when they gave it to him.
l know you. l seen you
in the slam, five years ago.
l just got out.
-What did those bastards do to Billy?
-lt wasn't the screws.
A prison-yard scrap.
One of those things.
How's it going?
Don't sit down,
l'm on my way out right now.
-l got a job laid out.
-Yeah?
l need a good driver.
Let's take it f or granted
you need me, or you wouldn't be here.
l'm in demand.
Fella here last week
figuring a Brink's truck.
He spent months f ollowing that truck,
getting to know the driver, the crew.
Hell, he even laid the driver's
wife's sister, setting the thing up.
He walks out of here after talking
to me, and what happens?
The Brink's driver gets drunk,
beats up his wife...
...gets into a beef
with the cops and got fired.
So this chap is back to square one,
figuring it all out, but not with me.
What l'm saying to you is that
Spencer is laying very low...
...playing it very cool, because l got
the bread to wait f or the right thing.
l'll pay you a flat 2000
to drive f or me.
lf it's worth my time,
it's worth a percentage.
-How much do you figure to score?
-l don't know.
Enough to f urnish this place.
-Are you O'Leary?
-Yes.
l'm Sydney Brevoort.
Management has decided
to redecorate the halls.
-l'm here to survey the tenants.
-l don't know.
-Well--
-Hold it a second.
-What is it?
-Meter man.
-Here's my card.
-l don't know anything about it.
-Hold it! Hey, you!
-You talking to me?
-Yeah, where do you think you're going?
-l got a delivery of this f ur coat.
-Apartment 2B, Miss Everleigh.
-You come back here and wait.
l can only deliver to Mrs. Everleigh.
Don't give me any shit.
Stand over there.
-Come on, chief, let's go.
-What?
l'm sorry, but l only have
this afternoon to survey.
-The manager's got to clear it.
-But it's very simple.
You have my card, there's
the number, call the office.
l ask the tenants what colours
they want in their halls.
lt's not as if you don't know me.
l mean, you do have my identification.
-Afternoon, Antiques lnternational.
-One East 91st Street.
We got a guy here says
he's f rom your business.
-Yes?
-You got a Sydney Brevoort?
-What do you want to know?
-It's a matter of identification.
What does he look like?
-He's about 45, a little chunky, f ag.
-That's him.
Okay, thanks.
-All right, you can go up.
-Thanks, l'll start on the second--
Hey, hey.
-Hey, what's happening, baby?
-Let's see the invoice.
-'' Everleigh, Apartment 2B.''
-You got it. l think you've got it.
Hold it.
How do you do, Mrs. Horowitz?
l'm the decorator f or the building.
Oh, my God, you're not
putting that in dishwater?
-Do you have the rest?
-The rest?
lt's the old-f ashioned set that someone
who loves beautif ul things would have.
You know, Mrs. Horowitz,
jewellers just don't know.
They melt down these old settings,
and they end up in people's cavities.
You must come to my shop. l have
the kind of place where someone....
-Sorry, were you expecting this here?
-Everleigh, 2B.
They said you might want to try it on
in case it wasn't a good fit.
-Duke, did you do this?
-l thought you'd like it, so l got it.
Try it on.
-Thank you, O'Leary.
-l'll stay with him.
-ls it real?
-Sure.
What are you up to, you bastard?
-You didn't want to know.
-l don't. Can l keep it?
Sure, it was a necessary
expense anyway:
Sit down, l want to show you
how gratef ul l am.
-lt's your sweetness that gets me.
-You can always turn it down.
-Or l can send you a thank-you note.
-l never turn anything down. Never.
-lt's just another that l owe you.
-Don't keep count.
By now, things
can never be evened out.
-And what about them outside?
-What about them?
-l gotta keep that doorman up here.
-That's up to you.
-What if l make a noise?
-They'll think we're balling.
Make them happy.
Now we should be able
to match the hallway.
lf l could come in, perhaps we could
get an idea of the colours you prefer.
The management has sent me over
to see about redecorating your hall.
-l'll give you my husband. Carl.
-Yes.
-Sorry to disturb you.
-l'm Sydney Brevoort.
-Hi.
l've come to decorate your halls.
And not a moment too soon.
Thank you.
-You're gonna answer it, are you?
-Business bef ore pleasure.
Hello?
Yeah. For you.
-Hello?
-Hey, Duke, how are you?
-Who's this?
-Pop, I aot your number from the kid.
-Pop, how are you making out?
-Terrific, terrific.
Hey, Duke, could l come
and live with you?
See, l'm living with my sister.
She's got these f our kids...
...her husband's got this bad back.
Listen, are you okay f or bread?
-You aot a place to live?
-Yeah, don't worry about me.
I'll see you. The kid
knows where to find me.
Pop, hang on a minute.
-Something's up, are you interested?
-With you, Duke? Anytime.
-The tougher the better.
-Okay, look, I'll aet back to you.
Anytime. Everything's terrific.
l'm sorry about your sister. So long.
-Hello, Duke.
-Hi. How are you, Pat?
Not so good.
We're on them, loud and clear.
lnternal Revenue Service surveillance,
Pat Angelo, 8-12-70.
Case 642DZ713.
Subject with unidentified male, white.
How does it look?
100 percent.
My bird dog, he knows his stuff.
He says paintings
will go half a million.
There's a safe f ull of cash
held f rom tax es.
There's diamonds and jewellery that
they loan to museums.
l can do it. l need some muscle,
some technical help. And $1700.
-You've been away nine years.
-Ten.
The country's changed.
They got a new breed of cop.
People have alarms, guns. Dogs. They
breed Dobermans to tear you apart.
Realtors advertise these places.
24-hour-a-day armed guards.
You gotta sign in and out.
Some places got moats.
-Papa Angelo owes it to me.
-He owes it.
He owes you 20 years
f or saving his kid?
l've laid it out. Labor Day weekend.
People are away, the streets are empty.
You have got it worked out
pretty good.
On the way back f rom the f uneral,
l'll stop at Papa's and check it out.
Wait in the car. l'll talk
to the old man. He runs things.
-89 and he still calls the shots.
-l need $1700.
You never know, he's f ull of
surprises. 89 and f ull of surprises.
ls that you, Gino?
No, Papa, it's me, Angelo.
Gino's kid broke a tooth.
And l sent my doctor to Miami.
Gino's kid is 32 years old, Papa.
He's got kids of his own.
What are we gonna do, Papa?
This Anderson claims a debt of honour.
lt's too complex, too many people.
We don't need it.
We're in linen supplies, restaurants,
wholesale meat, everything.
lt's stupid, this bang-bang stuff.
What am l talking it down f or?
Maybe he can make it.
Why am l looking at the dark side?
Why can't l once say a positive word?
l'm always knocking.
That's not happiness.
This caper is so ex citing.
Papa?
Are you tired of living?
Would you like to die?
All right, so this Anderson caper
is gonna be a disaster.
How are you going to beat the police
on this thing?
lt won't hurt.
lt'll help maintain the image.
Let the businessmen and politicians
fear us, we're men who carry guns.
Will they argue a laundry contract?
Ref use a garbage-hauling contract?
l hope this thing f alls on page one,
and not page five.
Thank you, Papa.
Papa's sorry, he was all tied up.
He couldn't see you personally.
He okayed the deal.
We'll give you the money f or
the finance, we want 60I40.
50I50.
50I50. We want you to take one
of our boys along.
That's okay.
You don't know the whole deal.
We want you to burn him.
Burn him?
He's done his duty, he's sloppy.
He leaves bodies around.
We want him out.
The job is already complicated enough.
You came to me. l didn't ask you. lt's
a little negotiation, don't get sore.
Inarid.
lngrid.
Shut up.
You made it. Don't fight it anymore.
What was it like?
l don't know. l was scared.
What, during?
l don't know.
What were you scared of?
-l don't wanna talk about it.
-What?
l hated it.
l lost control and l hated it.
What are you so happy about?
Things are looking up.
The signs are good.
l hate being a woman. Men!
You're hairy, vain and overbearing.
l bet you think l'll crawl and beg you
to pet me like a drooly little dog.
l don't know why
l ever had to meet you.
To give me the chance to start
evening things up.
Okay?
For chrissake, what is this?
lt's hot in here.
Parelli? l'm Anderson.
l can't stay in here. lt's gonna take
the press out of my clothes.
Take them off.
You can get a towel outside.
You're out of your mind.
You suit yourself.
Any guy who wants to stay in here
with his suit on has got to be crazy.
-What is this--?
-You'll do this my way.
lf it wasn't f or Pat Angelo,
l would never be here.
Do you go armed?
Always.
Ever killed anyone?
Yeah.
lt doesn't bother you?
Well, you see...
...none of them was f riends.
ln f act, none of them
was even f rom my hometown.
What do you think?
l don't know.
We want you to snuff him quietly.
Why do you say ''snuffed, offed, knocked
out, rubbed out, deceased, passed on''?
Why not, '' kill him''?
ls it so hard?
Duke.
l like you, Duke, but l want to give
you some advice.
Parelli's tough and mean.
Unless you are very firm with this,
he's going to be ahead of you.
l would hate to have to explain to him
what happened, if he killed you.
You understand my dilemma.
-lf l don't, somebody else will, right?
-Right.
He's already dead.
l could look at it that way.
You could look at it that way.
The other guys, they'll just
have to go along with it.
Win or lose...
...it's a contract.
Okay, Pete.
3:45 p.m., unidentified male Caucasian
present at previous meeting at 8870.
At which matters of a nonpolitical
nature were discussed.
One unidentified male, sex deviate,
white, about 45.
One unidentified male,
white and in early 20s.
And one unidentified male,
black, in late 20s.
This is Jimmy l told you about.
Forget names.
We don't know each other, and won't.
-What a shame.
-That ain't his real name.
Okay.
He's the bird dog. He'll mark what's
valuable. All in a small bag.
Anything with an alarm, lock, safe,
whatever, the Kid will fix.
This is Socks.
Socks? l don't believe it.
You didn't say
there was gonna be no spooks.
No, no, on weekdays he's meek,
mild Clark Kent.
He don't need no socks,
he's got hair all over his feet.
Don't shoot me.
All right, cut it out! That's my name.
Show me a little respect.
All right, cool it.
What do we need him f or?
He's crowd control. Unless anyone acts
up, he'll keep his thing in his pants.
l'll be the judge of that.
l'm out.
l don't know if he'll
do what you tell him.
Socks, go get some beer and pizza.
Go fetch.
Or go tell Angelo you don't
want the job.
l don't like this neighbourhood.
l don't want to go out alone.
Jimmy, take him to the pizza joint
and don't let no spooks mess with him.
l used mob money to back the caper.
They gave us a schedule of all the
squad cars on the beat.
They're gonna help us fence the
stuff. They'll get a split and....
But they insisted that
we take this guy along.
Because they want him knocked.
Killed.
Oh, l'll do it.
l figured you ought to know about it...
...in case you wanted to get out.
lf you do, then do it now.
That was their price?
lf you want, l'll do it.
Violence, man. Maybe that's
what you're into. That's okay.
l wouldn't do that myself.
But if you think you should,
go right ahead.
ln f or a penny, in f or a pound.
-Inarid.
-Shut up.
You made it. Don't fiaht it anymore.
What was it like?
I don't know. I was scared.
For God sakes, Werner, turn it off.
Leave her alone. You can get any girl.
-Werner, will you--?
-Shut up, you f our-bit hooker.
l'm Werner.
l pay f or her clothes,
this place, and f or her time.
Maybe l got the price wrong,
but l know what to call her.
As l don't pay f or it,
naturally l see things different.
Will you turn that off?
l never stop hearing it anyway.
-Fighting over a woman. lt's crazy.
-Right.
-So we won't fight.
-Okay.
l know what you're doing.
l got it on tape.
lt's true.
So, what do l care about?
Miss Blue Eyes. But l don't rent by
the day or week. l expect ex clusivity.
What about her?
She's got the floor.
Say your piece, darling.
Do you know why she's coming with me?
Because she knows a contract's value.
She knows l'm cold, hard cash
on the line.
Security. Something you can count on.
Not ex citing, but rich in tax-ex empts.
lt sounds like he's blackmailing you.
What are you gonna do about that?
l don't know.
The signs don't look so good no more.
A whore, a convicted safecracker.
Calling a man trying to protect
his property a blackmailer.
lngrid...
...l'll quit.
l'll call the whole thing off.
What do you say to that, lngrid?
-l'm sorry.
-See? She's a whore.
l can't. l can't make it.
-What?
-I don't wanna talk about it.
-lt's okay. Take it easy.
-I hated it.
lt's gonna be all right. We'll hit
Hawaii, two weeks in the sun.
-Hey, Anderson.
-Yeah? What?
Don't worry about the tapes.
You want to raid this place, do it.
-Why?
-l don't know. Just f or the hell of it.
-What about the other guy who listened?
-Nobody says nothing.
lf they did, they'd be in jail.
--to pet me like a drooly little doa.
I don't know why I ever had to meet you.
To aive me the chance to start
evenina thinas up.
Come on, let's go.
-Okay.
-Go.
Look out.
Come on, Pop.
Where's Duke?
-You drunk?
-No.
O'Leary.
Leave him room to breathe.
Now you've got the TV here,
so you can see wherever we go.
lf someone comes in, anything goes
wrong, you call us on the house phones.
-Okay?
-Sure. Everything's gonna be okay.
Hey, Duke.
You looked swell on the TV.
Yes, can l help you?
l was transcribing tape recordings
of therapy sessions, when they came.
l thought it was a disturbed patient,
and l was dealing with it...
...when this shorter,
rounder one hit me.
-He hit you at that time?
-Yes! l was surprised.
-Parelli, f or chrissake.
-Just to keep him honest.
Okay, take some files.
Here, take the drug safe.
No, no, no! l have a key.
l have a key.
Did you move on your own? The tall one,
the leader. Did he make any threats?
He didn't touch me.
He was upset by the violence.
lf they moved you in fear,
it's kidnapping.
But you've got to be af raid,
or it isn't kidnapping.
Were you in fear of bodily harm?
Yes?
-What the hell is this?
-Mrs. Hathaway!
Shut up.
lt's a robbery!
-No, burglary. Robbery--
-Shut up.
-Don't talk to me like that.
We weren't expecting anyone.
lt was Labor Day weekend.
But the doorbell rang
and l answered it.
And this ape threw himself against the
door and burst into the room. l ran--
What did you--?
What are you--?
Get away f rom me.
Cool off. All right? No more.
Shut up! Sit down.
He won't hit him no more.
Socks.
-They called him Socks?
-Yes.
ls this the man?
l don't know.
He had a mask over his f ace.
Cool it!
Don't go in there,
you miserable creep!
l told you to stay away.
She hit me first.
She tried to give me a knee.
How'd you like it if she did
that to you?
This man likes to hurt people.
Just do what we say...
...and he won't hurt anybody.
For God's sake,
you've got to control him!
What have we got here?
They have a big coin collection.
The rest is useless.
l'll help you if you'll
just keep him away.
-Okay.
-Come on.
Don't touch him. He's a paraplegic.
He has asthma. He has to stay
in this air-conditioned room.
Who are they, Mom?
We're after the coin collection.
ls it yours?
What's the combination?
Tell him, darling.
lf they were any good,
they could do it the hard way.
Tell him to tell us.
-l won't.
-Mrs. Bingham.
-He knew your name?
-Yes, it was planned.
lt must have been. They put
us in the old lady's apartment.
These knives must weigh
a pound apiece.
Here you go.
Bell Telephone bonds dated 1877.
God knows what they're worth.
For God sakes, take them.
l'm tired of them.
Your f ather gave you those.
My f ather was one first-class
son of a bitch, as you well know.
Go take a look in her room.
Look at what she reads.
The Story of O. 73 years old and
all she's got to think about is sex.
Terrific!
lt was terrific! l didn't know you
could just snap them open.
l could show you men that could just
tease and tickle a safe open.
This is amateur stuff.
Leaving a mess like this. Look at it.
lt's the kids, they don't know nothing,
and they don't wanna learn.
What did you do then?
-That's it.
-Okay, Hathaway.
What can l do?
l can't move.
The windows are sealed shut.
-The phones are dead.
-Okay.
Oh, my God, double eagles!
-What's a double eagle?
-Oh, really.
This is WA2UYL in New York.
We are being robbed.
The address is 1 East 91st Street.
Please call police.
This is WA2--
lt's our first company since V-E Day,
when everyone opened their doors.
Then World War ll ended,
and no more visiting around.
l told Kaler to make tea.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Would it be all right
if l made some tea?
Mrs. Kaler, can l help?
Please, thank you.
Those homely words mean so much.
She talks like a letter to Dear Abby.
Police department.
I have a call for anybody from
Mr. Vincent Johnson in Wichita Falls.
-Who do you want to talk to?
-Anybody.
-ls he paid?
-Is he paid? No.
-Then he's collect.
-I said he's collect.
He's collect? From where?
-This is Wichita Falls, Kansas.
-Wichita Falls, Kansas?
-Are you a recordina?
-Who's calling?
Mr. Vincent Johnson.
For anybody.
Well, what's it about?
-What is it about, sir?
-Well, I think there's a--
I'm a ham radio operator and I aet
this messaae from Hawaii...
... that there's someone
robbina a house in your city.
-One moment.
-You accept the charaes?
-He isn't paid?
-He's collect.
We can't accept collect calls.
-For God's sake, operator, I'll pay!
-He's paid. Your party is on the line.
l'll put you through.
Long distance f or Emergency.
May l help you?
Release the elevator, please. Please
press the emeraency button and wait.
Tell Spencer the safe in 2A is ready.
Right, Duke.
Got you, Pop.
Got it.
What's the score?
Two's ready, three's done.
We just have the Longenes down the hall.
-lt looks good?
-Yes.
Check 4A and we get out.
If there is an emeraency...
...please press the emeraency button
and wait.
-Pop?
-Get the elevator!
-Who's at the elevator?
-Who is it?
He didn't say. Get that stuff inside!
Kid, you come with us!
Oh, my god.
Release the elevator.
You shouldn't play
with the tennis guy.
Your mother didn't
go f or any of this--
You're calling f rom where?
Are you paid?
Sergeant, it's another one.
Portland, Maine.
What have you got
in the 2-3, Jim?
lt's 2-3, George.
Respond to 1 East 91st Street.
-Possible burglary. Use caution.
-Roaer.
My God, that man's bleeding.
A squad car just went by.
-Did he stop?
-No, he just passed by.
Release the elevator, please.
Duke, l can't bear it.
ls everything okay?
Swell, Duke.
Shut that thing off, will you?
Release the elevator, please.
If there is an emeraency--
Hey, Duke, it's getting late.
l'll turn into a pumpkin.
Okay, let's get the Longene loot
and we'll cut out.
Hold it!
Kid, call Pop.
Tell him to ring the Longenes.
Hey, Pop, buzz the Lonaenes.
-They don't answer.
-He says he doesn't get any answer.
-Pop. The log says they're in.
-l don't get any answer.
-Maybe they're on to it.
-Don't panic.
Okay.
Hit it, Kid.
Patrolman Claire!
l borrowed this newspaper
f rom the driver of Car George 3.
Return it to him, and find out why
he had it in his car.
Personal...
...or duty.
lron Balls Delaney. Let's go.
Sergeant Everson and five men, sir.
l have a particular reason
in picking you f or this job.
Yeah, well, what is it
you want me to do, sir?
You know the 18-story building
adjacent to the subject structure?
Yes, sir.
That's the high ground.
Now your squad will take
the high ground.
Jump onto the roof
of the subject structure...
...go down ropes on the outside...
...drive the suspects
out of the building, into the street...
...and we'll be waiting f or them.
Yes, sir.
Who are you?
Then what did he do?
We tried to wake up my wife.
She's a sound sleeper.
They couldn't break into my safe.
lt's a marvellous safe.
They said to tell them the combination.
You tell them?
Hey, Tommy.
Everson, your job is to protect
private property...
...and preserve the safety
of the inhabitants.
l can't do it.
Son of a bitch!
Give me the numbers
or l'll bust your ass.
For God's sake!
How does that grab you?
Now give me those numbers!
Those things are museum pieces.
They're irreplaceable.
Now, you give me these numbers.
Help him up!
Push harder.
Put your hand under his f oot.
All right, feed me out, feed me out.
Okay, tie me off right there.
You're wasting our own loot.
He won't really hurt you.
Darling, it's all right.
Just hold on.
lt just hurts right now,
but you'll be all right.
You bastard! Tell him!
Be brave, be brave, darling.
lsn't it risky to stay on?
Get Socks.
Get the other hookup.
-Come on!
-Turn loose! Turn loose!
Good slide, man. Good slide.
Okay, let's go.
Him!
Good. Kill him!
Make him hurt.
Kill him!
Oh, him. l knew he'd kill me.
Let it go!
Shit.
Come on!
Let's go, let's go!
Take it away.
All right, now go toward the wall.
Drop the blue line.
Go on up there.
Go hand-over-hand on the rope.
That's it.
We-- We've done it.
Pop, no questions.
Go lock the stairwell door.
Take care of the second floor.
Blue Six, this is Jade Six.
Fuck! Testing, one, two.
Can you see anything
on the 91st Street monitor?
-Nothing.
-What about the basement?
Nothing.
Can't see anybody outside.
-But l know they're there.
-Crash through with the truck.
Okay, let's go.
What's the matter?
l can't make it.
When the cops come, put your
hands up and they won't harm you.
-Okay?
-Okay.
l'm sorry.
We got hostages.
We'll use them as shields.
Get the kid.
Get to those people!
Blue Six, this is Jade Six!
Everson!
The goddamn thing doesn't work!
Wait f or me!
Leave him, he's dead!
Look out!
The truck's moving.
Let it go!
Pull over here!
Get that man to a hospital.
Be caref ul!
Out of the way!
Sergeant!
Report!
This is everyone, sir.
There's a crippled kid upstairs.
-Who else?
-A stiff on three, named Parelli.
Why didn't you say so?
-Captain!
-What?
Me. l was part of it.
Please, captain, l'm ready to go back.
-Who else?
-You got us.
Me, the guy up on three,
he was the brains of it.
-He laid it out.
-Book him!
Thank you, captain.
Book him!
You take ten men
and go up on the roof.
You first seven men come with me. We'll
take the second and f ourth floors.
You take the rest of the men and
take the first and the third floor.
What the hell is this?
All right, Tony, go in there.
They didn't even touch this place.
That's f unny.
All right, let's clear out.
Take it easy.
Just breathe deep.
-Stand up slow, that's it.
-Here, under my hand.
Captain Delaney.
Who the hell put that thing there?
There'd better be a warrant f or this.
That's in the Everleigh flat, 2B.
Come on!
Come with me.
The rest upstairs.
There's a guy in the basement.
Take care of him.
Here, doc.
-Stand back!
-Keep those reporters out.
-ls he conscious?
-l don't know.
Let me get that microphone.
-Can you hear me?
-All right, clear the area.
You wanna make a statement?
Shut up, he's making a statement.
My God. She says...
-...l always hammer on locked doors.
-What's that supposed to mean?
Get him out.
l want a report on that tape.
An operation this size...
...you'd think somebody'd talk.
He won't fit, stand him up.
We gotta get him up.
One more. One, two, and....
Did you see the papers?
Didn't we have a Duke Anderson
on the Angelo tapes? Well, erase them.
We're the government.
We can't risk anybody finding those
tapes. They're illegal. Erase them.
The police will trace Anderson
and we get caught with illegal tapes.
Erase them.
Ripped by the wildbunch22
FKprod2003
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4cpgd
Help other users to choose the best subtitles