Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Now being admitted to the
practice of medicine
I solemnly pledge to consecrate my life
to the services of humanity
to help with the life of my patients
would be my first consideration
my colleagues would be my brothers
I will not permit consideration of race,
religion,nationality or social standing
to intervene between my duty
and my patients
whatever I shall see or hear
of the lives of men
which is not fit to be spoken
I will keep invariably secret
I will give no deadly medicine
to anyone if asked
nor suggest any such countenance
even under threat I will not use my
knowledge contrary to laws of humanity
these promises I make freely
and upon my honor
THE YOUNG DOCTORS
Subtitles by Seglora
Well Dr Coleman
-Did you have a good trip?
-Yes I did
You remember Dr O'Donnell,our Chief Surgeon
Glad to see you her,Dr Coleman
we need you here
Thank you
You really mattered when you said you
would be here this week,didn't you?
I didn't see much point in waiting
I got a fairly good impression of
the situation on my visit here last month
I am anxious to see the lab in operation
I want to see Dr Pearson again,of course
Hold on call for a moment
Husband of a patient
Mr Stresky
I am sorry Sir,I'll have the
treasury go over your bill
Good Bye Sir
People know that this hospital
doesn't make a profit
Not quite this time,claims  his wife
kept for a week too long
waiting for a pathology report
Now he has to go into debt to pay his bill
Now you want to see the rest of the place
He may as well know Harry
Surgical reports from Pathology
is sometimes pretty late getting back
and there are times when we hesitate
to discharge patients without
the final lab results
because those reports may effect the sort
of regimen the patient is placed on at home
And with bed-space as valuable as it is
I see.Well I imagine that is one
of the reasons I am here
Let's go
You want to see the end of bay
Regardless what you have heard Dr Coleman
Dr Pearson who has been in charge
of Pathology here for over 25 years..
..is a good man,done a great
deal for this hospital
You should have heard the wall
towering when he set up the blood bank
to salvage the hospital committee
This year we will do three times as
many tests as we did five years ago
He did some investigate research too
The cause and incidence of thyroid cancer
Most of it generally accepted now, but
few people remember it came from doctors..
Well we took the shortcut
with the hot one didn't we?
Tomaselli,are you telling me to go slow?
Make it easier for Dr Pearson
I did not realize that it
came out like that
I think in essence I am
Right this way,ladies,everybody
gets the front seat today
No hurry,ladies,no hurry
Star of the show is not going anywhere
Now,let's see
Which one of you is going to faint first?
This is a new class of nurses,I believe
I'll explain it,my name is Pearson
Pathologist for this hospital
Dr Howard who is resident
And Dr Shawcross who is in his fourth..
Am I right?
Quite right Doctor
Fourth year of surgical residency
And who will shortly be released
upon an unsuspecting public
You often here people ask
what does a pathologist do
Never hear anyone ask what a surgeon do
perhaps we all know what a surgeon do
A pathologist is the one who examines
the surgeon's mistakes when it is too late
He is the doctor who the patient
seldom sees,doesn't want to
Yet few departments in the hospital
have more effect in the patient's welfare
It is pathology which advises
the patient's physician on disease
Sometimes when all else fails,it is the
pathologist who makes the final diagnosis
That is a neat little abdominal scar,ain't?
Some surgeon realized that
pretty paupered one day
Thank you
Mr Tomaselli
Mr Tomaselli,could I see you for a moment
Just go down the hall and turn left and
Pathology I'll be right along
I draw your attention,young ladies,to some
words,you'll find in many autopsy rooms
"mortui vivos docebunt",
the death teach the living
The medical history of this man
shows three years ago
he suffered from the first coronary attack
and the second attack during this week
This man apparently died
of coronary thrombosis
I beg you pardon
Suddenly school..
I agree with you
-Who are you?
-I am a pathologist
Your first autopsy
And last I hope
Alas,with most things in in medicine
the first one is always the worst one
Go back in
-What?
-Go back in there
I'm intending to,but not
because you ordered me to
Now we have established
that in this specific case
the medical diagnosis was correct,
we move to the cranial area
I hold in my hand a human brain
And yet what do you see?
Only a mass of tissue
Only a few hours ago,this was
the thinking center of a human being
Human being.Not only the thinking center,
but the co-ordinator
of the senses,touch,smell,sight,taste
in her thoughts,hopes,dreams,memory
told the eyes to cry,the mouth to speak
This man was an engineer,this then was
the brain that used mathematics
understood stresses,devised constructions,
perhaps build houses,highways,dams
A cathedral,legacies from this
brain to other human beings
Starting out your medical
career,young ladies
it  is just as well to think about
these things once in a while
Because in this big impersonal machine
around here,this thing we call hospital
has one function,and only one,
to serve people
This human being,male,aged 53,was a person
A human being
I see you found your way
You may now,young ladies,be free to go
and forget everything I have said
Just as your predecessors
have done for the past 25 years
We go this way
Dr Pearson is entertaining
some student nurses again
It not was I say,but when
Dr Pearson sees those
He is going to pick you up and throw you..
That's fine,that's fine,just leave
those reports please
Good Morning Mr Tomaselli
Bannister,this is Dr Coleman
Bannister is Senior Lab Technologist,
been here almost as long as Dr Pearson
As long as Dr Pearson,
How do you do, Dr Coleman
We have been expecting you
Have you?
Sit down,sit down,there is a
terrible mess sometimes
We are busy,of course
we are almost always busy
You,young ladies should be congratulated
when a day no student faints
I am beginning to have some hopes for men
Thank you
Try some bicarbonate soda
And make sure you are going
out on a date tonight
Nothing like living
Sure forget dying
Good bye girls,have a nice lunch
Have a nice lunch
May never eat again
The eternal problem any hospital of course,
whose going to pay for the funds
-Oh there you are,Doctor,you remember
-I remember
You look younger than you did last month
Bannister we have to find something
for this young fellow to do
Now he is here
Your qualifications are good,
young fellow,on paper
Hope you can live up to it
Get him a lab coat,Bannister,
and show him around
Coffee
Don't let him see the  mark slides
you keep hiding away for your garden
I am late for a mortality review committee
make yourself at home
It is downright upsetting by taken by
a hug strong by your own wife
I have only one rule for a happy troika,
never hug off with your wife
Sorry
I am sorry for everybody.I had an autopsy
Impatient,impatient
Nowhere to go,we couldn't wait to get there
I used to be called for something
a doctor prescribed for his patients
Now an ordinary layman
can't  get near the first D without
pushing the doctors into the sand trap
First case Algernon Forbes,
male,white,58.Dr Rufus
The patient was referred to me February 10
with a suspected perforated ulcer
He had severe upper abdominal
pain and was in shock
Blood pressure was 70/40,he was ashen
grey and was in a cold sweat
The abdomen was rigid and
it was rebound tenderness
I ordered a transfusion to combat
shock and also morphine
No chest field X ray,Dr Rufus
It was my opinion that the patient
was too sick to go to X-ray
I agreed with the referring doctor's
diagnosis,obviously perforated ulcer
No doubts at all,Doctor
One always has doubts,Dr Pearson,
but I decided that all the symptoms
justified exploratory surgery
However,there was no perforated ulcer
I called Dr Jones for consultation but
before he arrived the patient died
Dr Pearson.Now is the time
for the autopsy findings.
No perforated ulcer,abdomen
entirely normal.
What was causing the severe pleuritic
pain was early development of pneumonia
Which could have been
discovered by chest X ray
It is very easy to have hindsight,
Dr Pearson loses no chance to remind us
I don't think Dr Pearson intended o..
Any man can make a mistake in medicine
but having been made that mistake
should serve as a warning
to others who can't see beyond the
area of their own surgical specialty
If Dr Pearson was conscientious
about his own department
as he is what's goes on at
the upper floors here,
Perhaps, we all get our surgical
reports from pathology in time
Gentlemen,I have repeatedly
requested more help
My department is
snowed down,I ask for technicians
Technicians.Instead the
staff of this hospital
Joe,Joe
The staff of this hospital decided a new
pathologist was needed to assist me
You now have that man on step,
and I have no doubts
That you'll now have your
surgical reports on time
But as long as I am head pathologist here
when I attend a mortality review
committee I intend to call the shots
as I see them, and when the time comes ,
when I do not attend this committee
it will be because I am no
longer member of this staff
Ah,Joe,you are taking all
this whole more seriously
And if I am not a member,it will
be that I have been kicked off
Because I have to be kicked out
since I have no intentions of resigning
Not until they roll me
down with my feet first
As there are no more surgical errors
to be discussed,I am sure you'll excuse me
Good Morning Gentlemen and the Lady
-Joe
-I know,I know
Patience,your hot headed idiot
Charlie,I have no place to
go,my lab been invaded
Invaded.You are acting downright senile
Listen,Beth shoul..
Beth.She wouldn't be proud of you
If Beth was alive she would
not be proud of you
What if we both getting older
Speak for yourself,Joe
-Charlie.You need a haircut
-No,I didn't..
Doctor,this is Mrs Alexander
Come right in,I am sorry
to keep you waiting
But sometimes these things take longer
in the hospital than we anticipated
I guess you know all about that
your husband is an intern here
Thank you Dr Alexander
Doctor,than I am perfectly healthy then?
Nothing to worry about is it?
Nothing whatever
The fact you strike me as
one of those rare young women
who can deliver her own child under a tree
And then plough 10 acre field
in the afternoon
Btw what did your first child die of?
Bronchitis,when she was a month old
I guess that this child is
doubly important to you
Yes.Yes very important.Why is it
something you haven't told me?
Oh,no.There is absolutely
no cause for alarm
Take that to the out patient lab
I am sure your husband,or the doctor..
who made that first blood test on
you some months ago must have told you..
that even if the blood test does
reveal antibodies in your blood
that only 1 child in 26 ever
develop erythroblastosis
and even if that happens
we can be prepared
We know that it is a possibility
All that depends on a
new blood test of course
In the end Mrs Alexander you are
going to have a normal healthy baby
Doctor Dornberger you are wonderful
I did not have anything to do with it
Elizabeth
Not yet
What took so long?
They haven't even taken a blood sample yet
Alec.Dr Dornberger is the
greatest doctor in the world
Oh,yes?
Except you,of course
Next to be,of course
Oh,I do not go on duty until 2 o'clock,Sir
Something you young
people will never learn
One thing leads to another
You start by stealing
a kiss in a hallway
pretty soon you will be having  baby
This way,Mrs Alexander
Thank you ,doctor
Come in,come in
Nobody stands in ceremony around here
Doctor Pearson
Civilization is strangling
itself in red tape
Doctor Pearson I have been here
in exactly 3 hours and fifteen minutes
If you want a coffee break take it
Is it your idea to have me sit around
here all day doing nothing
Until you can decide
what my duties would be
It is a hard matter to find time
You are fiery,aren't you?
I assumed that the very least there
would be an office ready for me
with clearly defined duties
Fiery.I picked you for one
Good.You want work.
Plenty work to be done
I am scientist not the administrator
You'll find work for your own level
Meantime why don't you take
over the autopsy room
Seems the engine is running
there to doctor Alywishes cue oil
I've always had a great interest and
a good deal of experience in serology
-I have been looking over the serology lab
-Serology
Why not
Thereafter you are in
charge of serology
-Anything else?
-Not right now
Thank you,Dr Pearson
-You are ready for the gros..
-No I'm not ready
I am ready as I ever be
She was not only a nurse,
she was a minister's daughter
The odds were all on my side
Put out that cigarette please
Good Morning Doctor Coleman,
I didn't see you there
There will be now smoking in the
autopsy room,Dr Shawcross
Not there
Dr Howard will you drape the patient
With a clean towel
Gentlemen,there is something
I need to remind you of
When we perform an autopsy we do
so with the permission of the family
of the one who has died.Our objective is
to advance medical learning
The family gives us the body in trust and
expect it to be treated with care respect..
..and dignity.And that's
how it will be treated
Thank you ,gentlemen,carry on please
We appeared to have been
skillfully taken apart
We sure have
Pardon me,my name is Alexander,Doctor
Alexander I am intern upstairs
Yes,Doctor
It is about my wife,we just arrived here
She is Dr Dornberger's patient
and we are expecting a baby
in a month and a half
Well,congratulations,doctor
It was you who supposed
to have a blood sensitation test today
I wonder if you have
any results on it yet
We probably wont even get
the samples until this afternoon
-Even if we do..
-This is very important
You see,she is Rh neg and I am Rh positive
How long does it take to
make the three tests
Not long
-Two tests,not three
-Two tests?
Yes,saline,high protein..
Don't most labs now make
an indirect Coomb's too?
Indirect what?
You don't even know what it is?
Look maybe you better
come back and see Dr Pearson
I don't know much about serology
but I have studied it up because of this
It has been proven that
some of the antibodies
in the blood of pregnant women can get past
both the saline test and high protein test
only the indirect Coomb test
Forget doctor,you are way of limits here
I have not got time to sit
around here the whole day
Listen,Mr,you are going to make time,
this is my wife and that baby
is very important to us
Dr Alexander I am Dr Coleman
Assistant Pathologist here
Certainly you must realize
I know that you will have
the results of the tests
tomorrow afternoon for
your wife's physician
if you are on duty upstairs I
suggest that you go back to it
All right,but I tell you one thing
my wife is going to get
every test available
Is there anything more ridiculous
than an expecting father
Yes.A serology lab without Coomb serum
What?
An indirect Coombs for blood sensitization
is elementary today,basic
Let's get some here in
time for Alexander’s wife
We can't just go out and
buy it like it was aspirin
You have to have a purchase requisition
Let me have one of the form
Dr Pearson always order the
lab supplies himself
I intend to have more authority here than
ordering 15 $ worth of rabbit serum
Well,when you get to my age the
best part of any day is the end of it
Are you going to leave this like,this?
Nudge me?
The only company we really get down
here
are all locked up in the ice
pack in the morgue
Bannister
Never failed,never
What's the trouble?
I'll tell you.It's the purchase orders
Do you think this is the Mayo clinic?
We got to have lab supplies
Yes but look at these.What do
we need Coomb's serum for
It is a blood sensitization test,
it is elementary,basic
-It's what?
-Dr Coleman ordered it
He signed the requisition himself.Look
So he did
Don't stand there looking for trouble
I put Dr Coleman in charge of
serology myself this morning
It is quitting time,go and wash
your hands,or something
You don't approve our order
how we keep our sera,Dr Coleman
I can't honestly say I do
Auto labs look spick-and-span,
glitter and clean
The only difference being we don't
care about manicures and haircuts here
We judge the lab and the man
with the practice of medicine
No time for the thrills
Any other suggestions,Dr Coleman?
Well,now that you ask I
do have one in particular
As many as you like,Dr Coleman
One way of speeding surgical reports
Who is talking to you
about surgical reports?
Have you ever considered
a tissue processing machine?
It should save at least a day compared
to the method preparing the slides by hand
Come in my office,Dr Coleman
Do you see these?
These are purchase requisitions
for equipment dating back years
Every time I put a bunch of these through
I have a battle with the administrators
He goes to the board and
have a battle with them
and then he comes back and say
we are spending too much money
You listen to me,Coleman
You are not here for my invitation,
you understand
They pushed you down my gullet
and I am choking on you boy
My patience is turning purple
trying to swallow you
but I'm going to do it
Let's get our policies straightened
out here once and for all
You got a job to do and so have I.
I am in charge of this department
We are going to do those jobs
We might get our wires
crossed everyday
but without interfering with our works
but I am still in charge here
You follow me?
I follow you
-Here are the purchase orders.
-All of them?
What? The requisition for Coomb's serum
I forgot all about that
We have been getting along with two
tests for blood sensitization for years now
We don't need it
Good Night Doctor Pearson
Dr Coleman
I thought I recognized you Dr Coleman
I want to apologize for
the way I acted today
-My wife and I..
-No need for apologies
As a matter of fact.You were right.
The Coomb's serum has been ordered
Your wife test will be made
in all three mediums
Thank you Doctor
No idea of the relief.Thank you very much
Turned your ankle?
-Hello
-What is the trouble?
Nothing.Nothing much.My knee just..
Sit over there.Come on.
-Thank you.
-Now let's take a look at it
-Don't be silly
-Don't you be silly.I am a doctor
Where is the pain?
It's about here
Dr Coleman.People are watching
How did you know my name?
The voices were very high.I guess that.
And the new ghoul in pathology
-Miss?
-Hunt.Cathrine
Miss Hunt.You are a phoney
Oh.Really
There is nothing that matters
with your knee,Miss Hunt
You think .That is the most conceited
egotistical thing I ever heard
Make up your mind,Mr
How much?
For you? 15 cents
No apologies please
I'm not apologizing.Where are you going?
I have exactly 3 hours and 10 minutes and
I am going to spend them with Marlon Brando
You wouldn't like
I'll have dinner with you
In a restaurant
with the wine
will be a good time
right out of town
Wine? And dancing?
If that’s been necessary
I know just the place
Sure you can dance with that bad knee?
Oh.I know I can.I am a phoney.You remember?
I have only three more years with lectures
Won't be long
As soon my internship is over
Take that look off your face
I hate you talking that way
I never heard my father discuss
money once,not once
Your father was one of the dying breed
He was old fashioned
practitioner in a small town
We always used jelly deserts
except when the cousins came
Nobody minded
My mind
You have to go to bed.And so is she
She is a strong little struggler isn't she?
There is only one way to get the best.
And that is to specialize
And the only place a man can
specialize is in a big town
Papa only called it one thing from the
Bible,I can't remember it exactly
Something about a man finding
himself and losing himself
I don't know anything about the Bible
Your father died owning nothing
He was rich,the richest man you ever know
everybody in that county loved him,
in the funeral there were so many cars
I loved him too but it is
different today,that's all
Yes.There is not a single
doctor in Richmond
You really would  like it,wouldn't you,
if I went back to Richmond
-..opened a little office
-Shut up
Will you please
Medicine is all of business
Shut up.Before papa turn over in..
Alec.
I love you
I always love you what you decide
Have our baby no matter how big,
or important or rich we are
You know I wish for you sake
that it was all over
Whoever invented this 9 month thing any way
It is not so bad,I went through it once
before,I don't care how bad it is
How hard Just it doesn't end the same way
Just to get away for a
little while sometimes
From all the pain and sickness
All the blood and the fear in their eyes
It gets to me too much sometimes
You begin to wonder where..
I have never said anything like
this to anyone before
-Sorry you did?
-No
That's what makes it all more confusing
Cathy,there isn't anyone in medicine
who hasn't felt the way you do
One time or another
But I felt it more and more lately
and I do not why I am talking about it now
when I feel so fine.
I really feel so delicious
I am so glad that I thought of
my plot to get a date of you
You know.If I was as honest
as you are,I have to tell you
that I really honestly despise the
strong silent type who just listen
From this let's talk about you for a moment
What made you decide to be a ghoul?
Pathology seemed the best way
to contribute to the war
The war?
Medicine is a war,creative,constructive war
Not many of us can be heroes
like Pasteur,Fleming or Salk
But sometimes there is
a spectacular advance
as in a war
when doctors rush to the new front
leaving lots of pockets of
knowledge behind to be filled in
Never heard anyone
talk about like that before
Make me feel like a trivial little idiot
I was wrong about you
You really are a good dancer
That Dr Pearson,do you know
what he advised me this morning
He said one way of get
rid of the taste of death
is by living and he was so right
I am two minutes early
Thank you for a lovely dinner
You don't have to pay any debt,Cathy
The man is not even human
Human
Why did not you think of it earlier?
Good Night
Yes Doctor we will send it up as
soon as we get the report
Everybody wants everything
the day before yesterday
Good Morning Bannister
What the devil is being going around here?
Don't look at me
I did not recognize the place
Where the magic can't find it
Now that is more like it
Mr Bannister
Dr Alexander.I just told Dr Dornberger
the blood samples only got
down here last evening
-What's all this?
-It's about my wife's blood tests,doctor
We have a possible Rh factor..
So don't you come barging in down here and
we show you a special favour
Perhaps we don't operate
that way in this department,Doctor
Alexander
You get the results in due time
and through Charlie Dornberger
Alexander!
Yes Sir
Call me in half an hour we
will have the result for you
Thank you Dr Pearson.Thanks a lot
Good Morning
Good Morning Bannister
Good Morning Dr Coleman
Some days just confuse me
Lung fibrosis,small recognizable nodules,
peptic ulcer just below the pyloric ring
Surprising thing about the human
body is not what finally kills us
but what we can have wrong
with us and still go on living
This woman should have
gone to a doctor in time
a simple operation would
have saved her life
Oh,Bannister
You've got to supervise the
histology section more closely
Your slice is sticking up
to look like a sandwich
Dr O'Donnell Surgery please
This place vacant?
Not yet.But if you don't
sit down it will be
-Last night you mentioned..
-Do you want to try some of this?
No thanks
Last night I'm afraid  I
mentioned too many things
Too many? Not enough
Aren't you hungry?
I'm starving
Will you listen to me for a second?
I am trying to find out to
get to know you better
I am not good at small talk
and flirting things like that
What I am saying is that..
How I am going to see more of you?
-You actually..
-No
Good.Then I know just the same
You two eating again
I am.Dr Coleman is on his diet
That seems to be the socially accepted
form of suicide these days
-Dr Pearson
-I'm coming.I'm coming
Don't say I never take lunch,Coleman
I am glad Dr Pearson is not on diet
These are reports for the coroner
on my desk I'll sign it
Joe
Accident case.Dead on arrival
Five years old
Charlie what's it all means
You want me give you a
philosophy of life and ten words
There is no philosophy,Charlie,impossible,
all chance,you never know what next
Life.Death
We are trying to fix some
of the accidents out of it
Now what about the Alexander girl
-Alexander?
-Rh factor
-Husband intern
-Oh Alexander ..
..I did the test myself sensitivity
negative no problems actually
I tell the boy
Oh,I already told him
-You?
-Kid nagged me what else could I do
Joe
Need a haircut
Did you break anything?
What did you have in mind
This one must known to the doctor
I bet you are the kind
that goes into convulsion
when you see somebody slip on a banana peel
I'm sorry
You are so dignified
and so sure of yourself
Just hold on,take it easy,and fly
Fly
Not my idea to be different Cathy
But we seen each every
day for more than a week now
And we are never alone,
there is always an audience
I didn't know you had anything
to say to me in private
I may look like a fool
and I feel like a fool
We are not teenagers,you know,
not them,we are adults
-If you had a car
-I'll get one.I rent one
I have Sunday afternoon off too
Just a wonderful country I could show you
Cathy are you hurt?
-This is my knee
-Where it did last week?
Oh,yes.I am a phoney.Remember?
Very tender isn't it?
How long have you had this Cathy?
A couple of,maybe a month.
Not serious Dr Grainger
Anything can be serious and not serious
I wouldn't be too concerned if I were you
We both want to know,
so I will arrange an X ray
OK Cathy
Killer Appendicitis Dr Rufus had a good..
-Do you want to see me?
-Yes.In your office,please,Dr.
Dr Pearson I have been running some
routine checks on the hot water system
The water temperature is not high enough
Exactly.Has anyone tried
to do anything about it?
You think that things run
poorly around here don't you?
As you keep asking.Yes I do
Young,green full of lofty ideas
I have been pleading for a new
hot water system for a year
It is too expensive project.
Anything else Dr Coleman?
No.I apologize
Full of vinegar I suppose.
Hear that you been laying
down the law in the autopsy room too
You asked me to take charge of it
No smoking I understand
Is that suppose to enthuse me?
Sign Read No Smoking
Are you laying down the law to me boy?
As I understand it,the hospital is to
be run for the welfare of the patients
Rules are set up for all,
there can be no law at all
Here or anywhere if there
are privileged exceptions
Shuffle of fancy ideas,
aren't you.All idea no blood
You've been here a week and
Bannister is ready to quit
Might be safer if he did
Three days ago I told the technicians
that I planned to make occasional
spot check on lab work
Yesterday I divided the blood samples
so the two tests would be runner
Schreck
Standard laboratory procedures
Bannister reached two
different results from the same sample
Everybody makes mistakes
There is no room for mistakes in medicine
When it comes to surgeons you yourself
You got your tummy boy,believe
me I have seen your kind before
You blood less hound,everything
spic-span,so sure of yourself
You learn that you are not
perfect one of these days,boy
It will be quite a shock,I hope I
will be around and see it that's all
And I will be around,because listen boy,
I am here to stay
You just shoving and pushing but I
am here to stay,don't forget it
If you don't like the ways
the things are run here
you are free to move boy,move on
I am not moving
I am staying too,don't forget that,ever
This is my home,you understand
I told you this before,I am in charge here,
you keep that fact straight
And I want no lab checks
without my authority
But lab checks is routine
I decide what is routine here
Pathologist,Pearson
Are you sure it is necessary Lucie?
All right.I'll be right up
Here is Dr Pearson
-Lucy
-This is Cathy Hunt
Oh,we have met,
sort of an informal way
Every time I see the young
lady she is giddy
Sure she doesn't have gout
A picture taken at a swimming
pool some time ago
Let me see both knees please
There was water in the pool I believe,
do you enjoy swimming? Do you?
Dr Pearson,Dr Pearson what do you think?
I try not to think,Cathy,anymore
than is absolutely necessary
X rays here?
Two sets,the first didn't show anything
Dr Dell corrected them to
show the soft tissue
and he confirms the
irregularity in the bones
Cathy you know what a biopsy is,don't you?
Usually to see that it is cancer
But not always Dr Grainger will take a
small piece of tissue from your knee
You won't even have to go to sleep
it is so simple and send it down to me
I'll study it under microscope
You wouldn't find anything
Doctor Pearson I felt too well
My knee only hurts once in a while
Of course if anyone find any..
You are an intelligent young woman
and surely you want to know
I told you already do know
Cathy it could be result of a swimming pool
accident
in which case nothing to worry about
Or it could be a bone tumor,
and even if it is there is every
likelihood that it is benign
Not cancer,you mean?
Not malignant,yes,but we do have to know
And if it is malignant?
Let me examine it first
-Then we..
-I know
I know you have to amputate,
wouldn't you Dr Grainger?
That's why I will not let you do a biopsy
Because even if it is malignant
I'd rather,anything,anything
than lose my leg
-Dr Pearson
-Yes
You won't mention this to anyone,will you?
Cathy
I think you should talk this over
with anyone who can make you realize
Promise,Dr Pearson.If you promise,
then I will think it over
By myself until Dr Grainger on Monday
Monday is day after tomorrow,
time is important
I'll think it over,I really will,
if you promise
All right,I won't mention it
to anyone we know
And if you use your head
I handled it before Joe
She has no family, she is of legal age,
and try to see the foolishness
of losing her leg
I am not good this Lucy,no good
Except more than she is right now
That's why I love this girl,
that's why we all do
We can't wait,the kid got no time to wait
You get that tissue sample down
to me Monday morning,first thing
Not a minute late,it ought
to be done tonight
Sound.Sunday Vespers
I remember when I was a
child in a very small town
I am glad that I'm not still a child
So am I
You do not care anything
about nature,do you?
You haven't even looked
Isn't it lovely?
Lovely is the word
Sometimes everything seems so unbelievable
So beautiful
I am sorry
I guess there must have been a
smell of fresh air after all I detect
I told you we get away
from people,didn't I?
Now you are stuck with me
Far enough away David?
A step in the right direction
What's the matter Cathy
I am sorry,David,I am sorry
It's not you it's me
I'm so tender everything can go on as if
David I don't want to know
what might have been
Cathy what is it?
Take me back to town,David
Take me back,please
All right,Cathy
Dr Dornberger may have said to walk
but it such a thing taking his advice..
-Hello
What's your name?
Elizabeth
My name is Elizabeth too
Take it easy
Alex,too soon.It can't be
You stay right here.I am going to get
a taxi and take you to the hospital
-I don't want
-Stay here
Emergency just telephoned,Charles
The patient arrived ,she is well advanced
This is a premature.Incubator ready?
Yes.It is on its way,Doctor
My kid is so small
It wasn't ready for this world,yet
Next 6 weeks would have
made a lot of difference
We'll keep an eye on him,you understand
his lungs are not fully developed
You see he has not
much of chance,aren't you?
No.What I am saying is,you never can tell
Some babies got the will
to live,fight for life
But I don't want to deny it
like some people.They just don't
You understand
Thank you doctor
Going up?
That was wrong.Thank you I am sorry.
Dr Pearson.Without disturbing her please
get word to Dr Grangier that I am here
I'll wait until I hear from her
Feeling a bit drowsy Cathy
This won't take long and
you won't feel a thing
Next please
Just stay relaxed,Miss Hunth,
this is just like having a tooth out
I always hated dentists
-Aching Cathy?
-I don't feel a thing
Good girl.Now we take a wedge
shaped sample of bone
Something between 2-3 cm should be enough
You made it in a hurry
Sorry to drag you out in
this time of the night
-Something important?
-A biopsy
I prepared the slides myself
I could not locate Bannister
He was probably somewhere else
pretending to be young
The case,difficult as they come
The surgeon suspects osteogenic sarcoma
What's the rush? Somebody's relatives?
No.It's not.Nobody's relative.
Just a patient
All right.Maybe we should work
this faster than every case
Not an easy one
Could be new bone formation
Osteoclastic activity with bands
of fibrous tissue in between
New bone formation could be the result
of regeneration after a fracture
I see now evidence of infection
No
No inflammatory cells in the bone spaces
Did you see any evidence
blood vessel invasion?
Oh No
Then we are back in the new bone formation
Borderline case
The man could only look in there some sort
of pattern would form of the absolute place
And the X ray?
Shadows and shadows
Radiology says it is up to us
Is this new bone forming
because it is a neoplasm?
Or is the bone proliferating as a natural
process in response to an injury?
Malignant or benign
Who wants power like this
This tumor is malignant as
soon as a surgeon amputates
Yes.And if we say it is malignant and we
are wrong
the patient loses a leg for nothing
But if it is actually malignant
and there is no operation
Who wants to play God
I had a professor who always warned us
the best we could give in cases
like these an educated guess
And what is your educated guess here?
I think it is benign
What is you opinion?
I think it is malignant
What about studying some past cases
It would take a week to take them out
-Take them out.What about the cross file?
-We don't have a cross file
Something I've been meaning
to set up for years
All right.We should have a cross file.
We don't.My fault
Scientific disagreement
Lucy.We always confer this
way in my department
You've met Dr Coleman
Oh yes of course
Well.This is one of those nights isn't it
I went home got to bed and
realized that I couldn't sleep
Here I am
Apologies
Lucy.We don't know,what it comes down to
all these years in medicine
and we don't know
Dr Pearson said malignant,
there is room for doubts
but I think the tumor is benign
I would not amputate if there
was any shadow of a doubt
Still I am worried about
the patient herself
Ordinarily I would have waited to morning
To perform a full med biopsy
But she was just permission tonight
so I had to take advantage of that
Now I just don't know how I dare choke at
it when there is any
doubt one way or another
I think I have a solution of sort,Lucy
There are two men who are experts
in this kind of pathology
The patients full name,Dr Grainger
She is one of our student nurses,
you may know her ,Dr Coleman
Cathy Hunt
Yes I know her
Dr Coleman,you have heard of Dr Collingham
in Boston and Dr Herenhart New York
We'll make two complete set of slides
get them off with air mail special delivery
and the next mail out of town
I'll be warning both doctors
saying it is urgent
and ask them to telegraph their
findings as quickly as possible
That will take time
Two days at the most
Every minute counts if you are
right every second counts
Anything I can do,Joe?
Being tight
How do you think I worked
my way through college?
Cathy?
Cathy,I was blind
I would have realized if
I had not taking up my self
Why didn't you tell me?
Why should I?
You are not involved
You should be sleeping
I can't
Not until I know what's going to happen
Dr Grainger promised to
let me know in a few hours
Dr Grainger won't know in a few hours
You mean.She promised..
She won't know for two days
I can't understand
Why,do you see,we..we,
can't always know for sure
And Dr Pearson thinks we should
get a few more opinions
Before
Cathy I feel sure the tissue is benign
Dr Pearson?
What does Dr Pearson think?
He,..he doesn't agree
I think
and I'm OK with anyone thinks
I don't care about medical opinion
All I know they are not
going to take off my leg
I won't let them
You have no right to
make a decision like that
Why not?
I can decide how I want to live
and how long
whether
Parents are dead it makes no
difference anyone but me
That's not true
That's no longer true,that's all
David
Please you don't need to..
I do need you
I don't understand it yet,
but I do need you
You only make everything more complicated
more confusing
Let's get this to post office
I like this time a man thinks about time
How much we got,
how much we think we got
Even if Lucy amputates,no guarantee
the girl will live only a year or two
or maybe until she dissolves
as I feel tonight,who knows
whoever knows,who has
any guarantee of time
Either one of us may slip
in the shower tonight
And we might drop a bomb accidentally
or otherwise
or a surgeon makes a simple single slip
during a routine operation
It happens,it happens
If we go along all the time
thinking we've got forever
Let us have while we have it
Let no anchor leave,
won't have it any longer
That won't be a second
I'm sorry I should have done that
Why so?Do you think
I would catch a pneumonia?
Well,let see it in this way
If I gave up the ghost tomorrow,
there is nobody in the world
that's get then solid damn
or as if you were to die
where the devil would that girl be
How long do you think we
have to wait for the answers
I'll phone Collingham and Herenhart
tomorrow morning,hurry them up maybe
You look like a fellow that
would do with a drink
I am not proposing we tie
one on,you understand
Once in a great while mild
anesthetic is clearly indicated
That's not a prescription,
Dr Coleman,that's an order
Dr Dornberger,what is it?
I don't think it is anything but
I want to double check
You suspect erythroblastosis don't you?
The symptoms are there,yes
Why didn't you do a exchange
transfusion at birth?
Dr Alexander,if the lab report on your
wife's blood test had been positive
we would have exchanged
the baby's blood at birth
The lab report was negative, an exchange
transfusion was not necessary
Doctor tell me about my wife's blood test
What's this delegation
We'll go on with this later
We just came from Alexander's baby
Could we get out the lab report,
I suspect that baby got erythroblastosis
Couldn't be Charlie
I remember you the young
fellow,the young fiery
Kicked up such storm around here
I just did dispose the test myself
Both tests
Dr Coleman,didn't you agree in
order to have an accurate
blood sensitization test three
tests were required
That's right,that's why
I ordered Coomb serum
I'll check with Bannister
Never mind
The indirect Coomb was
not done on my order
Do I understand you correctly
you mean Mrs Alexander may
have sensitized blood after all
This means that the baby
might have erythroblastosis
Could mean that
Bannister,we want a bilirubine every
six hours on Alexander baby at once
also is there any Coomb
serum in the hospital?
No Sir
All right.where do we get that half an hour
No time for that,we need to have
the test somewhere else
where the facilities,university hospitals
has the full lab
Get me the university hospital,
please and hurry
Also Bannister we need a blood sample
I will
Dr Fribe.This Dr Coleman,
Assistant Pathologist,Three Counties
Would you handle an emergency
Coomb test for us
we'll get the sample to you
right away,thank you
I would like to take the sample myself
Get it from Bannister take it
to the emergency ambulance
Could you get me to the
police department right away
May not be too late for an
exchange transfusion,Joe
This Dr Dornberger,we would
like a police car
to deliver an urgent blood sample
Doctor Alexander will be waiting
at the emergency entrance
Exchange transfusion should
have been done at birth
If it is not too late no credit to me
Joe
To best of my knowledge I have never
failed a patient to inadequacy or neglect
You made me part of my failure now
We've been friends for a long time,Joe
I've covered for you helped
you to battle upstairs
But this time,if this baby die,
so help me God
I'm going take you before the medical board
and I'm going to break you in two
Listen to me, son
Listen
Don't give up
It's worth living,it's worth it
This is your father and I love you
Don't give up
Dr Pearson
Oh,thank you
Connect me with Dr Grainger please
I am sorry,boy
Lucy I could not tell you on the phone
No,Joe
Here the two best men in the country
Are they definite?
Oh,yes,both of them,very definite
Dr Collingham Boston first specimen
definitely malignant
Dr Herenhart New York says the tissue
is benign no sign of malignant
Right back where we started
We are not,we lost time
It's the decision of the pathologist
Don't tell me use the decision
don't think I know
I am sorry,Lucy
For our training
All's there and we know nothing
That's not true,we do not know
everything,but we know a lot
More every year
-Joe?
-I know,I know
Doctor Coleman,on Sunday night
you said that in your opinion
the tumor was benign,do you have
any reasons to change your mind?
No,I have no reasons to change my mind
Doctor Coleman,you are in no position
to make an objective decision
Lucy,Doctor Coleman is the
assistant in this department,
the final decision is up to me
All right Joe,whatever you say
It is a malignant growth
Osteogenic sarcoma
And it is definite?
Quite definite
That's make it difficult,
I am not sure I can convince the
girl to allow the operation
Allow? She has to allow,
doesn't she realize..
That part is up to me
-This is a tough one
-They are all tough
They all already get the tough
I know
Cathy,whether you want it or not,
you must listen to me
I don't want to listen
I just want you to take me away,I mean it
Just the two of us now
I can't do that
If you love me,take me out of here
Don't let them come near me,please
No deal,Cathy,I love you,but no deal
I will not let them do it to me
Listen,you do not want to die,do you?
I am going to die anyway
We are all going to die some day
But soon.Soon if it spreads
Can you guarantee it not spreads,can you?
No
Can you tell me how long
even if I do let them
Nobody has no guarantee of time debit
Anyone of us could get killed tomorrow,
the next day crossing the street
For no what difference
Who has difference?
You are alive.That's the difference
You are alive now, and that's all you got
Only any of us can be surer
We can't be surer of anything else,nothing
Only that we are alive now
Alive and breathing,and we
better hang on to it
Hang on as long as we can
with whatever means we can
Hang on and live
That's why this whole hospital exist
That's what we are doing here
Keeping people alive because
we believe in life
It's good to be alive
Hope.That's what any poor human being has
that's all he has
And it's good
All right,David.
All right
In the aftermath
When it's over
Don't come back in here
Do you understand?
And hurry please
I am asleep
Dr Pearson,it is Alexander.
The blood test is positive.
Thank you.You hurry back here
Get me Dr Dornberger.
He is on the operating floor,quickly
Charlie,the Alexander baby
has erythroblastosis
The reticulocytes count is high
we haven't got the bilirubine yet
Never mind I know
-Is the blood warm?
-Yes ,Doctor
The hot water bottle in
the purpose position
On the table
It is important that this
exchange transfusion
that the blood is in the right temperature,
otherwise it is dangerous for shock
Only the ten sheet of calcium
Temperature
All right ready to start
I am cutting off the dry
portion of the umbilical cord
Not of the moist tissue
We have isolated the umbilical vein
and want to remove the blood clots
Venous pressure
16mm
We start going off with the blood
Do you want to send the
secretary in for that,Dr Pearson?
No thanks,Bannister
Any word yet on the baby?
Not yet
Lucy Grainger is taken the Hunt
girl back to her room for surgery
What about the Alexander baby?
Not a word
Venous pressure
57mm
Won't take just a little more
10cc artery
10cc again
Respiration up to 15 rather shallow
Breathing is very irregular now
How far are we?
50 cc is out 50 cc is in
We'll carry on
Skin feels cold,Doctor,I can't
count the respiration
He is not breathing well
Check the pulse
Set the artery pressure
Pulse is very weak,rate is over 180
Respiration is failing
He stopped breathing
Heart?
Very faint
Straight over the heart
My wife,what a temper,she
still says the bills too high
She blows her top,I tried to tell
her he is a specialist this Doc
After all Doctors are in
the business,ain’t it
Just like any other
What kind of doctor are you going into?
A general practice in my home town,
there is no doctor there now
Not get rich that way,pal
No,I'm not get rich
Get the oxygen over the tube
Pulse is stronger
I get it at 140
We'll go out of the transfusion
Thanks Bannister
Pathology Doctor Coleman
Doctor Dornberger tell Joe
that the Alexander baby survived
the transfusion prognosis is good
Thank you ,Dr Dornberger
The Alexander baby is going to live
No thanks to me
You are not resigning?
You are forgetting who is
in charge around here
Why I am not resigning cause
they won't ask me too hard
You are needed here
Not any more
Boy,don't change on me
We got sharp eye,sharp mind
We both knew the minute you
walked in here this day was coming
I never intended to..
Of course you didn't
I have been trying to figure
out what I have against you
Other than your compounded
personality of course
I used to think I was
scared this day coming
I wasn't that.You made me feel guilty
Like a fig.I didn't mean"Shut up and listen
you might learn something"
You made me feel like a fig,
because you reminded me of
was myself 30 years ago
cocksure and full of ego nothing
is too good for medicine
no room for error,negligence
I was right then and you are right now
We both know that now,don't we
Maybe I am not up to it yet
Don't waste time being humble
You are good,it won't be easy though
Your phonery,budgets,over
budget,committee,meetings
Troubles in the lab which
needs to be smooth over
The doctors coming in and out
asking for this and that
and the salesman with
the unbreakable test tube
another,another
The end of the day you will
ask what happens to him
All the fine things we set out to achieve
Research,study
The end of the year,all the other years
Listen to me boy
Don't let it happen to you
This would be the advice from
the best friend you ever have
Listen. Don't let that happen to you.
Get away from the phones,the files,
the paperwork and keep yourself upto date
Lock yourself in a closet if you have to
But do it,do it
You follow me?
Yes,Sir I follow you
A boy, a girl up there by herself
she will be waking up soon
She doesn’t want to see me
Why? For ill judgment?
She is lying.
Women don't even know when
they are lying sometimes
They got to do it
To keep idiots like you
and me for understanding
She knows as well as you do
that compassion is a part of love
She is not worried about herself,
how she is loved
or why,she is worried about you
She is going to be a cripple
the rest of her life
She is trying to spare you
Listen,all she is thinking of is you
and all your thinking is of her,right?
You tell me why
What's love? If it is not thinking of
somebody else more than yourself
I can't get through to her
You'll be there when she wakes up
just be there,that will get through to her
-Joe
-Yah
I've just examined the tissue.
You were right.It was definitely malignant
Dr Grainger hadn't operated she
would not live six months
Thanks,David
What are you doing
staying around here?
Look,son,you don't have forever,you know
You just think so,because you are young
Thank you,Joe
Doctor Grainger
It's me,Cathy
And I'm staying
Subtitles by Seglora
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org