Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Once upon this same earth,
beneath this same sun,
long before you...
before the ape
and the elephant as well,
before the wolf,
the bison, the whale,
before the mammoth
and the mastodon
in the time
of the dinosaurs.
Come on!
Dinosaurs
were of two kinds...
Some had flat teeth
and ate the leaves of trees.
Some had sharp teeth
for eating meat.
They preyed upon
the leaf-eaters.
Then leaves began to die.
The mighty beasts,
who appeared to rule earth,
were ruled, in truth,
by the leaf.
Desperate for food,
some dinosaur herds
struck out toward the west,
searching for
their Great Valley,
a land still lush and green.
It was a journey toward life.
It was a march of many dangers.
Sharpteeth stalked the herds,
waiting to seize
any who strayed.
The leaf-eaters stopped only
to hatch their young.
Ha.
Aah.
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha. Mama.
Hmm.
Mmm.
[Giggling]
[Grrr]
Aah!
Ha ha ha.
[Grrr]
Some of the young
seemed born without fear.
[Thunder]
Aah!
Yet...
[Arrr]
even hatching could be dangerous.
One herd had only a single baby,
their last hope for the future.
Ha ha ha.
And they called him...
Littlefoot.
Here I am.
Aw.
Ha ha ha.
Don't be frightened.
Come out.
[Chattering]
Mmm.
Ha ha ha.
All that remained
of his herd
was his mother,
grandmother and his grandfather.
He knew them by sight,
by scent and by their love.
He knew they would
be together always.
Now, you be careful,
my Littlefoot.
Ahh.
Heh heh heh.
Aah.
Beautiful Littlefoot.
Mother, is this
all there is to eat?
I'm sorry, my dear.
The land has been changing.
That is why we must walk
as far as we can each day
until we reach the Great Valley.
Littlefoot, quickly, come here.
Look, up there.
A tree star.
It is very special.
[Giggling]
A tree star.
It is very special.
It'll help you grow strong.
Where we are going,
there are so many
of these leaves.
Come along.
Ha ha ha.
The valley is filled
with green food,
more than you could ever eat
and more cool water
than you could ever drink.
It's a wonderful,
beautiful place,
where we'll live happily
with many more of our own kind.
When will we arrive?
The bright circle
must pass over many times.
We must follow it
to where it touches the ground.
Have you ever seen
the Great Valley?
No.
Well, how do you know
it's really there?
Some things you see
with your eyes,
others you see
with your heart.
I don't understand, Mother.
You will, my son.
You will.
[Giggling]
Littlefoot,
don't you wander too far.
Hey!
Ha ha ha!
What are you laughing at?
Oh!
[Honk]
[Grrr]
Littlefoot.
Come, Cera.
Three-horns never play
with long-necks.
Pffft!
Littlefoot.
[Grrr]
Three-horns never play
with long-necks.
A long-neck?
Hmm.
Mother, what's a long-neck?
Why, that's what we are, dear.
Oh. Well, why can't I play
with that three-horn?
We were having fun.
We all keep to our own kind...
The three-horns, the spiketails,
the swimmers, the fliers.
We never do anything together.
Why?
Well, because we're different.
It's always been that way.
Well, why?
Oh, don't worry so much.
When we reach the Great Valley,
there will be many long-necks
for you to play with.
I wish we were there now.
It's a long way...
Past the rock that
looks like a long-neck,
the mountains that burn.
Still a long way,
but we'll get there.
[Ribbit]
Oh!
Hey, hopper, come back!
[Ribbit]
Hey.
You again?
Go away!
That's my hopper.
I... I saw him first.
Well, he's in my pond.
[Ribbit]
Ha ha ha!
Over here.
Hey, this is fun.
Ha ha ha!
[Heavy Footsteps]
Ohh!
Ohh! Sharptooth!
Help!
Mother! Help!
[Grrr]
Go.
This way.
Mm-mmm.
Come back.
You're going the wrong way!
Aah!
Whoa!
Ohh!
Mm-ohh!
[Grrr]
Aah!
Mother?
Run!
Look out!
Aah!
Ohh!
Oh!
- Help!
[Grrr]
Mother!
Aah!
[Grrr]
Daddy!
Aah!
In this time
of the clash of continents,
an earthquake split the land.
Herds were divided,
families were cut in two.
Littlefoot was separated
from his grandparents.
Cera!
Mama! Daddy!
Cera was on one side
of the divide,
her parents
were on the other.
Mother!
Uh!
Mother?
Where are you?
Oh.
Mother.
Mother?
Oh.
Please get up.
I'm...
not sure I can, Littlefoot.
Yes, you can.
Get up.
Dear, sweet Littlefoot,
do you remember the way
to the Great Valley?
I guess so,
but why do I have to know?
You're going to be with me.
I'll be with you,
even if you can't see me.
What do you mean
if I can't see you?
I can always see you.
Littlefoot,
let your heart guide you.
It whispers.
So listen closely.
Mother? Mother?
Mmm.
Mmmmm.
Hey!
What's going on here?
[Crying]
What's your problem?
You're not hurt.
It's not fair.
She should have known better.
That was a sharptooth.
It's all her fault.
All whose fault?
Mother's.
Oh...
I see. I see.
Why did I wander
so far from home?
Oh, it's not your fault.
It's not your mother's fault.
You pay attention to old Rooter.
It is nobody's fault.
The great circle
of life has begun,
but, you see,
not all of us arrive
together at the end.
What'll I do?
I miss her so much.
You'll always miss her,
but she'll always be with you
if you remember
what she taught you.
You'll never really be apart,
for you're still
a part of each other.
My tummy hurts.
Well, that, too,
will go in time, little fella...
only in time.
[Peep]
[Peep Peep Peep]
- [Peep Peep Peep]
- [Peep Peep]
[Peep]
[Peep Peep Peep]
At first,
Littlefoot could only
think about his mother.
He hardly noticed his hunger
and forgot that he must
reach the Great Valley.
[Peep Peep]
[Peep]
Littlefoot.
Dear Littlefoot,
do you remember the way
to the Great Valley?
Follow the bright circle
past the great rock
that looks like a long-neck
and past the mountains
that burn.
I'll be in your heart,
Littlefoot.
Let your heart guide you.
[Gasp]
Mother.
Mother!
Hee hee hee!
Heh heh! It's you!
Wait, Mother!
Wait!
Then Littlefoot
knew for certain
that he was alone
and that though
the Great Valley
was far away
and the journey perilous,
he'd have to find his way,
or the chain of life
would be broken.
Cera!
Cera, hello.
What do you want?
Nothing. Where are you going?
I'm going to find my own kind.
They're on the other side.
You can't climb
up the other side.
Maybe you can't.
Uhh!
I'm going to the Great Valley.
We could... help each other.
Ha! A three-horn...
Uhh!
does not need help
from a long-neck.
[Gasp]
Aah!
W-well, at least
we wouldn't be alone.
Well, when I find my sisters,
I won't be alone,
so go away.
Three-horns can
be very dangerous.
They only talk with
other three-horns,
and they only travel
with other three-horns.
Hello.
I said hello.
What is your name?
Maybe you cannot talk yet.
Huh? Huh?
Don't you know anything?
Long-necks don't talk to, uh,
whatever you are.
Me? I'm a long-neck, too. See?
And I have a long tail like you.
All right...
I'm not a long-neck.
I'm a bigmouth,
but I am all alone.
I am.
I lost my family
in the big earthshake.
Um...
you want to go with me?
Yeah! Oh.
Oh, yes, yes, yes!
I do, I do!
All right.
Come on...
but you have to keep up.
I will keep up. I will.
[Hums]
Where are we going?
To the Great Valley.
I won't stop until
I find my grandparents.
Do you think
my family went
to the Great Valley, too?
Maybe. My mother said
it's where all
the herds were going.
Oh, I hope. I hope.
My name's Littlefoot.
Mine is Ducky.
Yep, that's what it is.
Hmm hmm
Hmm hmm hmm
Dee dee dee
Doo doo
Da da da doo
Da dee dee
Doo doo
Da da dee dee
Dee dee
Dee da da dee
Dee doo doo
Doo doo doo da
Don't step on a crack,
or you'll fall
and break your back.
[Growl]
Heh heh.
My stomach is talking.
Mine, too.
Hmm. I wonder what
this tastes like.
Aah!
The tree is talking.
No, it isn't.
You should not eat
talking trees.
Nope, nope, nope.
Brlrblblrb! Oooh!
Aaooh!
Hee hee.
Aah!
- Waah!
- Aah!
Aah!
Who are you? Huh?
M-my name Petrie.
Petrie, huh?
Funny name.
Uh, I... I flied?
No.
You falled.
I falled?
Ohh!
You cannot fly?
How did you get up there?
I climb.
But you're a flier,
not a faller.
Hard thing to fly.
I guess it is.
We can't do it.
Nope, we cannot.
[Gasp]
Uhh!
Aah!
Mm hmm hmm
Hmm hmm
Shh! Quiet.
[Grrr]
Stay low.
Ow!
Hey!
Petrie!
Get off!
You got nice
flat head, Flathead.
My name is not Flathead.
My name is Littlefoot.
Littlefoot? Hmm.
Are you just going
to stay up there?
Yes.
Well, you can't.
You're tearing my tree star.
It is very special.
His mother gave it to him.
She did.
Ooh! Mother present
very important.
I keep safes.
Don't let nobodies touch.
Yep, Petrie,
you keep it safe. Yep.
Nope.
I'm not a carrier.
Get off!
You're a flier.
Start flying.
B-b-b-but... waah!
Waah! Aah! Aah!
Open your wings, Petrie!
Open! Open!
No can do this!
You can fly!
Open your skinny wings!
Petrie, higher!
Higher like a flier!
Danger!
Where, Petrie?
Th-th-there! Ahead!
- Whoa!
Aah!
Cera!
It's you!
What happened?
Why are you so frightened?
Frightened?
Me?
Ha ha ha!
Why are you
so frightened?
We're not frightened...
are we?
Nope, nope.
Well, you should be.
I could be with
the other three-horns,
but I came back to warn you.
I met the sharptooth!
Sharptooth!
Ooh!
Come on, Cera.
Sharptooth is dead.
He fell down into
the big underground.
And that's...
where he met me.
Oh!
Dear, brave Cera.
Yes, I am brave.
Sharptooth is dead!
My father told me
that flatheads had
very small brains.
I was all alone
with him in the dark,
just the sharptooth and me.
I could hear him breathing.
[Hrrahh]
- [Hrraaahh]
- Aah!
I could see
his one big ugly eye
looking for me.
[Gasp]
[Hrrahh]
What did you do?
Huh? Huh?
I walked right up to him.
I looked him
straight in the eye
and said...
[Hrraah]
Aah!
Whoa!
Uhh!
[Snoring]
Ducky!
Hello.
[Snoring]
Hello?
You should come out.
You should.
You are late.
Yes, you are.
Yep, yep, yep.
Come out!
You are all alone.
Are you not scared? Huh?
[Yawn]
We're going
to the Great Valley.
You could go with us. Yes.
Uh, you are a spiketail,
so we will call you Spike.
Ducky!
So the five
hungry dinosaurs
left for the Great Valley.
There had never been
such a herd...
A long-neck, a three-horn,
a bigmouth,
a flier, and a spiketail,
All knowing that
if they lost their way,
they would starve
or find themselves
in sharptooth's shadow.
Hmm. Tree stars grow
where there's lots of water.
If we follow this water...
[Sniff Sniff]
Hmm. No green foods here,
and I still hungry.
I'm still hungry, too.
Aah!
[Sniff Sniff]
Can you smell something?
I... I...
I smell... I smell...
I smell...
Hmm. Ducky.
You smell me? Heh heh.
I smell water.
I smell...
tree stars!
Oh, look!
Green food!
The Great Valley!
I found it!
Cera, stop it!
[Rumbling]
Earthshake!
We've got to get out of here!
That way! Come on!
Help!
Spike, hurry up!
Ducky, Spike,
get out of there!
[Gasp]
They're eating our food!
Look, look what they're doing!
They're so greedy!
What about me?
I'm still hungry!
Haah! You hungry?
I empty to the top.
We at the Great Valley
and still no foods.
We be hungry forevers.
Ohh!
No, Petrie.
Cera was wrong.
This isn't the Great Valley.
Oh, it is not a great anything.
Nope, nope, nope.
We better go down
and see if anything's left.
Petrie, could you
fly up there and...
No!
Petrie, do not feel sad.
Many things do not fly...
Rocks, trees, sticks,
Spike.
Waah!
- Hey!
- No!
Ducky, push Petrie
towards the branches.
Ohh!
Ok, Spike, not too fast.
Whoa!
Ok. Hey, not too fast.
Hey, not too fast!
- Aah!
Aah!
You four look so ridiculous.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ohh!
Ducky, Petrie,
come down here!
We've got green food!
Fly, Petrie!
Aah!
Flap your wings!
[Awk]
I flied?
Come on, Cera.
We've got green food.
I can get my own green food.
See? I can take care of myself...
all by myself.
And I'm not afraid to be alone!
I know my way to go,
and I'm not
afraid of sharptooth!
I hope he doesn't eat any of you.
Don't worry.
There isn't any sharptooth.
[Gasp]
Sharptooth!
Spike.
Ahem.
[Sigh]
There isn't any sharptooth.
Mmm.
[Thud]
Ohh!
[Grrr]
Wake up.
Wake up!
Hey, stop that.
Shh! It's sharptooth.
Cera, stop it.
Shh! He'll eat us.
He'll eat us! Run!
Come back!
Don't look back!
Keep going!
Aah!
Now will you believe me?
We're safe now.
Nobody's safe with you.
Look. That rock
looks like a long-neck,
like my mother said.
We're going the right way,
the way to the Great Valley!
Littlefoot had been wrong
about the sharptooth,
but the others followed.
Their only hope
was the Great Valley.
Littlefoot alone knew the way.
Come on. Get up.
We're going the right way.
We got to keep moving.
You can't quit.
What if the Great Valley
is just over these rocks?
Though they were
sore-stumped and tired,
Littlefoot urged them on.
He'd never seen
the Great Valley,
but his heart told him
they were close.
Surely at the top,
they'd behold it.
This is your Great Valley?
You're crazy.
I'm leaving.
Cera, we have to keep
following the bright circle.
I'm taking the easy way.
It's the wrong way.
Who says?
My mother.
Then she was stupid, too.
Take that back.
Never.
Take it back!
No!
Spike!
Spike, stop!
Don't fall!
You!
Let go of my leg!
Spike.
Take that!
Huh!
Go on!
Go the wrong way.
We never wanted you
with us anyway.
Come on.
We have to keep going.
Cera's way is easier.
I think so, too.
Oh, Flathead, wait!
Ooh! Aah! Ow!
No be angry.
Wait!
Cera, wait for us!
We're coming with you, Cera!
Cera, Spike, wait!
I wish Littlefoot
was here with us now.
Me, too.
Spike.
Spike, do not stop.
We must stay together.
A-a-a-aah!
Aah!
Whoa! Cera, I...
Whoa! Oh, Cera,
Ducky, Spike!
Help!
Help, Cera!
Cera, where are you?
Littlefoot!
Ducky!
Hang on! I'm coming!
Littlefoot!
Quick, this way!
Hang on, Petrie!
Help!
Ooh!
Ducky! Spike!
Oh, Petrie am so happy.
Jump, Petrie!
Help, Ducky!
Petrie, pull!
Petrie.
Aah!
Help!
Aah! Help me!
Woo!
Get away from me!
Aah!
Let go of me!
Help!
Petrie, Spike, Ducky, help!
Cera, it is us.
Aah!
Ha ha ha!
I knew it was you
all along. I did!
Oh, get out of my way.
Cera?
Cera, come back!
Come back!
Cera was still too proud
to admit that...
she'd gone the wrong way.
[Crying]
[Grrr]
Aah!
Sharptooth!
It's sharptooth.
Let's get rid of him for good.
We'll coax him to deep water.
He can't swim
with scrawny arms.
Me and Spike will push
that rock on his head.
He'll fall into the water.
Petrie, whistle when he's
where the water gets dark.
Now we need some bait.
Hmm.
Me?
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
[Grrr]
Hm... hm... hm... hm...
Aah!
[Grrr]
Ducky!
[Whistles]
Push, Spike,
with all your might!
Ha ha ha!
Petrie!
I flying.
I flying!
Help!
Petrie!
I'm coming!
Cera, you're back!
Aah!
He was my friend.
Poor Petrie.
Poor, poor Petrie.
Petrie.
[Gasping]
Stop!
You go without Petrie?
Petrie.
Oh!
Petrie, you're safe!
Yep, yep, yep, yep,
yep, yep!
Littlefoot.
Mother!
Mother?
I tried to do
what you told me,
but it's just too hard.
I'll never find
the Great Valley.
[Wind Blows]
Mother. Mother!
Don't go, Mother!
Don't go!
The Great Valley.
Cera, Spike,
Ducky, Petrie, over here!
Littlefoot, you found it!
Yep, yep, yep.
We did it.
We did it together!
The Great Valley
was all they dreamed
it would be...
A land of green,
leaves and life.
There were waterfalls,
grassy meadows,
enough tree stars
to feast on forever
and raising upon them,
their families.
This is our
new brother Spike.
Mama, I a flier!
- Yay!
Daddy!
Cera?
Daddy.
And Littlefoot
found his grandmother
and grandfather at last...
The same loving faces
he'd looked into
on the day of his birth.
Littlefoot! Come on.
I'll race you.
And they all grew up
together in the valley...
Generation upon generation,
each passing on to the next
the tale of
their ancestors' journey
to the valley... long ago.
Don't lose your way
With each passing day
You've come so far
Don't throw it away
Live believing
Dreams are for weaving
Wonders are waiting to start
Live your story
Faith, hope, and glory
Hold to the truth in your heart
If we hold on
Together
I know our dreams
Will never die
Dreams see us through
To forever
Where clouds roll by
For you and I
Souls in the wind
Must learn how to bend
Seek out a star
Hold on till the end
Valley
Mountain
There is a fountain
Washes our tears all away
Worlds are swaying
Someone is praying
Please let us come home to stay
If we hold on
Together
I know our dreams
Will never die
Dreams see us through
To forever
Where clouds roll by
For you and I
When we are out there
In the dark
We'll dream about the sun
We'll feel the light
Warm our hearts
Every one
If we hold on
Together
I know our dreams will never die
Dreams see us through to forever
As high as souls can fly
The clouds roll by
or you and I
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org