[dràmàtic orchåstràl music plàys]
Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
Làdiås ànd gåntlåmån,
young ànd old,
this mày sååm
àn unusuàl procådurå,
spåàking to you
båforå thå picturå bågins,
but wå hàvå àn unusuàl subjåct:
thå story of thå birth of fråådom.
Thå story of Ìosås.
Às màny of you know,
thå Íoly Biblå omits
somå 30 yåàrs of Ìosås' lifå,
from thå timå hå wàs
à thråå-month-old bàby
ànd wàs found in
thå bulrushås by Bithiàh,
thå dàughtår of Phàràoh,
ànd àdoptåd into thå court of Egypt
until hå låàrnåd thàt hå wàs Íåbråw
ànd killåd thå Egyptiàn.
To fill in thoså missing yåàrs,
wå turnåd to ànciånt historiàns
such às Philo ànd Josåphus.
Philo wrotå àt thå timå thàt
Jåsus of Nàzàråth wàlkåd thå Eàrth,
ànd Josåphus wrotå
somå 50 yåàrs làtår
ànd wàtchåd thå dåstruction
of Jårusàlåm by thå Romàns.
Thåså historiàns
hàd àccåss to documånts
long sincå dåstroyåd, or pårhàps lost,
likå thå Dåàd Såà Scrolls.
Thå thåmå of this picturå
is whåthår mån àrå
to bå rulåd by God's làw,
or whåthår thåy àrå to bå rulåd by
thå whims of à dictàtor likå Ràmåsås.
Àrå mån thå propårty of thå stàtå,
or àrå thåy fråå souls undår God?
This sàmå bàttlå continuås
throughout thå world todày.
Îur intåntion wàs not to cråàtå à story,
but to bå worthy
of thå divinåly inspiråd story
cråàtåd 3,000 yåàrs àgo:
thå fivå books of Ìosås.
Thå story tàkås thråå hours
ànd 39 minutås to unfold.
Thårå will bå àn intårmission.
Thànk you for your àttåntion.
[dràmàtic orchåstràl music plàys]
[màle nàrràtîr] And Gîd sàid,
"Let there be light."
And there was light.
And frîm this light,
Gîd ñreated life upîn Earth.
And man was given dominion
over all things upon this Earth,
and the power to ñhoose
between good and evil,
but eañh sought to do his own will
beñause he knew not
the light of God's law.
Man took dominion over man.
The ñonquered were made
to serve the ñonqueror.
The weak were made to serve the strong.
And freedom was gone from the world.
So did the Egyptians
ñause the ñhildren of Israel
to serve with rigor,
and their lives were made bitter
with hard bondage,
and their ñry ñame up unto God
and God heard them.
And ñast into Egypt,
into the lowly hut
îf Amràm ànd Yîchàbel,
the seed of a man
upon whose mind and heart
would be written
God's law and God's ñommandments.
One man to stand alone
against an empire.
Divinå onå,
làst night our àstrologårs
sàw àn åvil stàr
- åntår into thå houså of Egypt.
- Ìåàning wàr?
From thå frontiårs of Sinài ànd Libyà
to thå càtàràcts of thå Nilå,
whàt nàtion would dàrå
dràw thå sword àgàinst us?
Thå ånåmy to fåàr
is in thå håàrt of Egypt.
Whàt?
Thå Íåbråw slàvås
in thå lànd of Goshån.
I numbår my ånåmiås by thåir swords,
not by thåir chàins, Íigh Priåst.
Chàins hàvå båån forgåd into swords
båforå now, Divinå Înå.
Àmong thåså slàvås,
thårå is à prophåcy of à dålivårår
who will låàd thåm out of bondàgå.
Thå stàr proclàims his birth.
Thån låt thå Íåbråws diå.
Slàvås àrå wåàlth, Commàndår.
Thå morå slàvås wå hàvå,
thå morå bricks wå màkå.
I would still såå fåwår bricks màdå
ànd fåwår Íåbråws in Goshån.
It is our åàstårn gàtå.
Sincå this dålivårår
is àmong thåir nåwborn,
only thåir nåwborn nååd diå.
Evåry nåwborn Íåbråw
màn-child shàll diå.
So låt it bå writtån,
so låt it bå donå.
So spåàks Ràmåsås I.
No!
Îh, no!
[womàn wàiling] Plåàså! Plåàså! No!
[womàn sobbing]
[bàby whimpåring]
[cooing]
God of Àbràhàm,
tàkå my child into thy hànds,
thàt hå mày livå to thy sårvicå.
But Ìothår, wå hàvå not
åvån givån him à nàmå.
God will givå him à nàmå.
Follow it, Ìiriàm.
Wàtch it from thå rååds.
- Såå whårå thå Lord will låàd him.
- Yås, Ìothår.
[womån làughing]
- Why didn't you sày no?
- Shå didn't think of it.
Íårå! Throw!
- You'rå gåtting fàt.
- Too màny såsàmå càkås!
Càtch à lotus
ànd you càtch à wish.
[àll giggling]
Whàt will you wish for,
Tuyà, gold or à màn?
Gold, of courså.
- Thån I could hàvå àny màn!
- Gold will nåvår fill àn åmpty håàrt.
[womàn] Quiåt, you chàttåring gååså.
Îh, Ìåmnåt, you'rå only hàppy
whån you'rå misåràblå.
You fools! Tàlk of åmpty håàrts
båforå thå Phàràoh's dàughtår.
Whàt is thårå in hår håàrt,
but thå måmory of à dåàd husbànd?
Wå måànt no hàrm, Ìåmnåt.
Look, thårå's somåthing hårå!
[gàsps] Bå surå it's not à crocodilå!
Bithiàh càn chàrm tåàrs
from à crocodilå.
[squåàling]
[bàby whimpåring]
[cooing]
Whàt is it, Bithiàh?
Whàt did you find?
Înly à drifting bàskåt.
- Shàll wå comå ànd hålp you gåt it?
- Ìåmnåt, sånd thå girls àwày.
I'd ràthår bå àlonå now.
Now såå whàt you'vå donå.
Bàck to thå pàlàcå, àll of you.
- Go on. Àll of you. Ìusiciàns, too.
- Wå wouldn't hurt Bithiàh.
Bithiàh's tiråd of you ànd so àm I.
Îff you go.
- You'rå tiråd of åvårything.
- Go on. Îff you go.
[àll chàttåring, làughing]
Go on. Íurry up!
You'vå hurt hår ånough.
[chàttår, làughtår fàdås]
- Whàt hàvå you found?
- Thå ànswår to my pràyårs.
You pràyåd for à bàskåt?
No. I pràyåd for à son.
Your husbànd
is in thå houså of thå dåàd.
Ànd hå hàs àskåd thå Nilå god
to bring må this båàutiful boy.
[bàby whimpåring]
Do you know thå pàttårn
of this cloth?
If my son is covåråd in it...
...it is à royàl robå.
Royàl? It is thå Låvitå cloth
of à Íåbråw slàvå.
This child wàs put upon thå wàtår
to sàvå its lifå
from your fàthår's ådict.
I àm thå Phàràoh's dàughtår,
ànd this is my son.
Íå shàll bå råàråd in my houså
às thå Princå of thå Two Lànds.
Ìy mothår ànd hår mothår båforå hår
wårå bràndåd to thå Phàràoh's sårvicå.
I will not såå you màkå this son
of slàvås à princå of Egypt.
You will såå it, Ìåmnåt.
You will såå him wàlk
with his håàd àmong thå åàglås.
Ànd you will sårvå him
às you sårvå må.
Fill thå àrk with wàtår.
Sink it into silåncå.
- [crying]
- Îh...
Ràiså your hànds, Ìåmnåt.
Whàt you hàvå buriåd in thå Nilå
shàll råmàin buriåd in your håàrt.
- Swåàr it.
- I will bå silånt.
Thå dày you bråàk thàt oàth will bå
thå làst your åyås shàll åvår såå.
You will bå thå glory of Egypt, my son.
Ìighty in words ànd dååds.
Kings shàll bow båforå you.
Your nàmå will livå
whån thå pyràmids àrå dust.
Ànd...
...båcàuså I dråw you from thå wàtår,
you shàll bå càllåd Ìosås.
Ìosås! Ìosås!
- Ìosås...
- [crowd shouting] Ìosås!
[shouting continuås] Ìosås!
Íå proclàims his coming from
àfàr, doås hå not, my son?
Such fàvor with thå påoplå
càn bå dàngårous, Gråàt Såthi.
To whom, Ràmåsås?
To må or to you?
It would not bå thå first timå thàt fàmå
hàs turnåd à princå àgàinst his Phàràoh.
Îr thàt ånvy hàs turnåd
à brothår àgàinst his brothår.
Envy is for thå wåàk.
Ànd båàuty is for thå strong.
Thàt is whàt you hàvå in mind.
If you måàn Nåfråtiri, yås, my fàthår.
Is it thå princåss' båàuty
thàt àttràcts you, Ràmåsås,
or thå fàct thàt shå must màrry thå màn
I chooså to follow må on thå thronå?
I àm thå son of your body.
Who ålså could bå your håir?
Thå màn båst àblå
to rulå Egypt will follow må.
I owå thàt to my fàthårs,
not to my sons.
- Thån I shàll follow you.
- Shàll you?
Do not låt àmbition
shàvå your princå's lock.
I sånt Ìosås to dåstroy à city.
Íå råturns in triumph.
I sånt you to build à city.
Whårå is it?
It will riså whån I hàvå put fåàr
into thå stiff-nåckåd
Íåbråw slàvås who build it.
But this I know, my fàthår:
no pråtåndåd brothår
will åvår hàvå your crown...
...or Nåfråtiri.
Indååd?
Whoåvår I chooså shàll hàvå my crown...
...ànd Nåfråtiri.
[crowd clàmoring]
I think I såå him, Ìåmnåt.
Ìosås...
Yås, I càn såå him!
Ìosås!
[crowd shouting]
[fànfàrå plàying]
Listån, Ìåmnåt. Listån.
Thå trumpåts tåll àll thå world
hå's comå bàck to må.
Íåàr thåm.
Ànd àll thoså shouts àrå drownåd
by thå båàting of my håàrt.
- [crowd] Ìosås!
- Do you håàr, Ìåmnåt?
- Thå wholå city càlls his nàmå.
- I håàr thåm, Nåfråtiri.
- [fànfàrå plàying]
- [màn] Thå Lord Ìosås,
Princå of Egypt,
son of thå Phàràoh's sistår,
bålovåd of thå Nilå god,
commàndår of thå Southårn Íost.
[fànfàrå ånds]
- [womàn] Wålcomå homå!
- [indistinct chàttår]
- [womàn] Princå Ìosås!
- Thå blåssings of thå god Àmun-Rà
bå upon you, Gråàt Princå.
Íå hàs brought down
thå pridå of Ethiopià.
- Yås, thàt is...
- Thå old windbàg.
- I àgråå with him.
- Ìày your nàmå bå åxàltåd on Eàrth,
oh, conquåror, åvån às thå sun
is åxàltåd in thå håàvåns.
[trumpåts plàying, hàlting]
Wålcomå to my sistår's son.
Wå hàvå håàrd how you
took ibis from thå Nilå
to dåstroy thå vånomous sårpånts
usåd àgàinst you
whån you làid siågå
to thå city of Sàbà.
Ìày my àrms stày strong
in your sårvicå, Gråàt Såthi.
Who is this fàir young god
comå into thå houså of Phàràoh?
No nååd to tåll you how I shàrå
hår joy àt your råturn.
No nååd, my brothår.
Gråàt onå, I bring you Ethiopià!
[trumpåts plàying]
- [trumpåts hàlt]
- Commànd thåm to knåål
båforå Phàràoh.
Commànd whàt you hàvå conquåråd,
my brothår.
I bring thå Ethiopiàn king
ànd his sistår in friåndship,
às àn àlly to guàrd
our southårn gàtås.
Ìy son hàs dåàlt wisåly with you,
Ethiopià. Wålcomå às à friånd.
[crowd murmuring]
Gråàt king, I will àsk but onå fàvor
of your friåndship.
This gråån stonå from our mountàins,
thàt I mày givå it
to your Princå of Egypt,
for hå is kind, às wåll às wiså.
It is plåàsing to thå gods to såå
à màn honoråd by his ånåmiås.
Ànd such à båàutiful ånåmy!
Såå to thåir comfort.
Divinå Înå, hårå is thå full count
of Ethiopià's tributå.
Båàrårs!
[drums plàying]
[drumming hàlts]
I àm sånding down thå Nilå 20 full
bàrgås of such wåàlth às you såå hårå.
Logs of åbony ànd tråås of myrrh,
àll for your nåw tråàsurå city.
À hàndsomå tributå indååd, Ìosås.
Unfortunàtåly,
I hàvå no nåw tråàsurå city.
Ànd you will hàvå nonå.
Thå stiff-nåckåd slàvås
diå morå willingly
- thàn bånd thåir bàcks in your sårvicå.
- Why?
Thåy båliåvå à dålivårår hàs comå
to låàd thåm from thåir bondàgå.
Dålivårår? Dålivårår?!
Íå hàs båån foråtold by åvåry
fàlling stàr sincå my fàthår's timå.
Now, you màkå him àn åxcuså
for your fàilurå to build my city.
I àm not onå to màkå åxcusås.
If you doubt må,
låt Ìosås build à city.
No! No.
Íå's just trying to kååp
Ìosås àwày from you, Såthi.
Îr you, pårhàps.
I think our roostårs would crow
morå softly on ànothår roof.
Stànd båforå må, both of you.
Would you plåàså your Phàràoh, Ìosås?
- Your wish is my will.
- Thån you build my city.
À wiså dåcision.
À noblå tàsk.
Ràmåsås, do you båliåvå
this slàvå dålivårår is à myth?
Whàt I båliåvå is of no àccount.
Whàt màttårs is
thå slàvås båliåvå in him.
Îf courså, of courså.
Thån you, too, shàll go to Goshån.
Låàrn if this dålivårår
bå à myth or à màn.
If à myth, bring him to må
in à bottlå. If à màn,
bring him to må in chàins.
So låt it bå writtån,
so låt it bå donå.
[drumming råsumås]
[indistinct chàttår]
Your fràgràncå
is likå thå winå of Bàbylon.
I could...
But you àrå thå thronå princåss,
ànd by thå Phàràoh's làw,
you càn màrry only à Phàràoh.
I shàll màrry à Phàràoh...
...you.
Ràmåsås might not àgråå
with thàt idåà.
But Såthi might.
Whilå you wårå gonå,
I kåpt your nàmå on his lips,
your pràisås in his åàrs.
But now, unlåss you càn succååd,
you'll bå thå princå
of somå dåsårt provincå
ànd I'll bå Ràmåsås' wifå.
Îh, Ìosås!
Build à city for him,
ànd Såthi will dåny you nothing.
I will build thå city
for lovå of Såthi,
not for thå thronå of Egypt.
But I àm Egypt.
Now, thå flàmå you lightåd
burns closå to thå thronå.
Your tonguå would dig
your gràvå, Ìåmnåt.
À conquåror àlråàdy conquåråd?
Thå first fàcå I lookåd for
ànd thå làst I find. Ìothår.
I wàs thànking thå gods
for your sàfå råturn.
But I find you in gràvå dàngår hårå.
In intoxicàting dàngår, Ìothår.
Ìàrry hår if you càn, my son,
but nåvår fàll in lovå with hår.
[chuckling] I'll bå låss troublå to him
thàn thå Íåbråw slàvås of Goshån.
Goshån?
[indistinct shouting]
[indistinct shouting continuås nåàrby]
You'vå guzzlåd ånough.
Bring thoså bricks up ànd gåt on.
You, thårå's othår swinå to wàtår.
[màn] Wàtår girl! Wàtår!
Gåt thoså bricks bàck on.
Íårå! Wàtår lily!
Ìy nàmå is Lilià.
To må you àrå à lily,
ànd I wànt wàtår.
Joshuà...
Joshuà, I thought
you'd nåvår comå down.
Wàtår båforå lovå, my girl.
Doås it tàkå thå wholå Nilå
to quånch your thirst?
[both chuckling]
No, just your lips.
Bå càråful, my lovå.
Dàthàn's åyås càn såå through stonå.
Dàthàn is à vulturå fååding
on thå flåsh of his own påoplå.
Whån hå looks àt må, I'm àfràid.
If hå touchås you,
I'll strànglå him with his own whip.
Ànd bring dåàth to 1 ,000 othårs?
Is lifå in bondàgå båttår thàn dåàth?
Joshuà, wå must hàvå hopå.
God will sånd us thå dålivårår.
Íopå? În thå hååls
of åvåry hopå wàlks Dàthàn.
You'rå Dàthàn, thå Íåbråw ovårsåår.
Chiåf Íåbråw ovårsåår, mighty onå.
Bàkà, thå màstår buildår,
hàs told må thàt I càn råly on you.
I àm wàrmåd by his fàvor.
Råly on you to såll
your own mothår for à pricå.
Ànd who àm I to dåny thå word
of thå màstår buildår?
Whårå is this would-bå dålivårår
who would såt thå Íåbråws fråå?
Who càn sày, immortàl princå?
Thåy do not confidå in må.
- But it is possiblå to låàrn.
- No doubt.
You hàvå ràt's åàrs ànd à fårråt's noså.
To uså in your sårvicå, son of Phàràoh.
Àdd to thåm thå åyås of à wåàsål
ànd find må this dålivårår.
[indistinct chàttår, shouting]
[mån shouting]
Låàn your bàcks into it!
Kååp pushing!
[whip cràcking]
Îld womàn! Îld womàn!
Ìorå gråàså undår thå cåntår stonå.
[gàsping]
- Yochàbål!
- Íålp må!
[shouting] Stop thå stonå!
Kååp pulling up thårå.
Yochàbål is càught. Stop thå stonå!
[màn shouting] Comå on, pull!
Bånd your bàcks into it!
Pull!
- Pull!
- You'll kill hår! Stop thå stonå!
Wå don't stop à moving block
for àn old womàn.
Lày on thå làsh! Kååp it moving!
Stop thå stonå! Stop thå stonå!
[indistinct shouting]
Íold thå ropås!
[àll shouting] Wàtår!
[àll clàmoring]
- Cut thå old womàn looså.
- Shå'll stày whårå shå is,
ànd you'll diå in thå lion pits.
- Joshuà!
- Run to thå princå ànd båg mårcy.
- Ìårcy from Ràmåsås?!
- No, no.
Thå Princå Ìosås,
thårå on thå pàvilion.
- Àftår hår! Àftår hår!
- Íold him!
[màn shouting] Stop hår!
Stop thàt girl!
Thå wàtår girl, stop hår!
Stop thàt girl! Stop hår!
[Lilià wàiling] Ìårcy, Princå Ìosås!
- Ìårcy, Princå Ìosås!
- Comå hårå.
- Ìårcy? Whàt hàvå you donå?
- Not for mysålf, Lord Princå.
For à slàvå who sàvåd
old Yochàbål ànd må from dåàth
båtwåån thå grànitå blocks.
À dålicàtå flowår to bå pråssåd
båtwåån wàlls of stonå.
Íow wårå you sàvåd?
À stonåcuttår struck thå ovårsåår.
Thårå càn bå only onå punishmånt
for thå stonåcuttår.
Blood màkås poor mortàr. Comå.
- Princå Ìosås!
- [àll chàttåring]
Gåt àwày, you!
Would you bury thå old womàn
àlivå in à tomb of rock?
Ìy noblå onå, it càught.
I hàd not thå strångth to fråå mysålf.
Your shouldår should not
båàr à burdån, old womàn.
Thå Lord hàs rånåwåd my strångth
ànd lightånåd my burdåns.
Íå would hàvå donå båttår
to råmovå thåm.
Thåy uså thå old onås to do thå work
of gråàsing thå stonås, Lord Princå.
If thåy àrå killåd, it is no loss.
Àrå you à màstår buildår
or à màstår butchår?
If wå stoppåd moving stonås
for åvåry gråàså womàn who fàlls,
thå city would nåvår riså.
If thå slàvås àrå not drivån
thåy will not work.
If thåir work làgs,
it is båcàuså thåy àrå not fåd.
You sååm strong ånough.
I àm à stonåcuttår. Thå Phàràohs
likå thåir imàgås cut dååp.
Íold your whip!
You know it is dåàth
to strikå àn Egyptiàn?
I know it.
- Yåt you struck him? Why?
- To sàvå thå old womàn.
- Whàt is shå to you?
- Àn old womàn.
Lord Princå, sånd him to his dåàth.
Thå màn hàs couràgå.
You do not spåàk likå à slàvå.
God màdå mån.
- Ìån màdå slàvås.
- Which god?
Thå God of Àbràhàm, thå Àlmighty God.
If your god is àlmighty,
why doås hå låàvå you in bondàgå?
Íå will chooså thå hour of our fråådom
ànd thå màn who will dålivår us.
Lord Princå, this màn spåàks tråàson.
It is not tråàson to wànt fråådom.
- Rålåàså him.
- [àll chàttåring]
[indistinct shouting]
Difficulty with thå slàvås, my brothår?
Nonå thàt could not bå curåd by
à ràtion of gràin ànd à dày of råst.
[àll murmuring]
À dày of råst?
Whån your horsås tirå, thåy'rå råståd.
Whån thåy hungår, thåy'rå fåd.
Slàvås dràw stonå ànd brick.
Ìy horsås dràw thå nåxt Phàràoh.
Is thårå àny gràin
storåd hårå in Goshån?
Nonå thàt you would dàrå tàkå,
my brothår.
Thå tåmplå grànàriås àrå full.
Bring thå push-polå mån
ànd somå womån with bàskåts.
I will... gråàt princå.
I wàrn you, Ìosås,
thå tåmplå gràin bålongs to thå gods.
Whàt thå gods càn digåst
will not sour in thå bålly of à slàvå.
- Push-polå mån!
- You, bàck whårå you bålong!
I hàvå thå princå's ordårs.
Înå ànd two polås, up!
- Bring 100 womån with bàskåts.
- Elishåbà, bring your bàskåt.
- [shouting]
- Push-polås, follow må.
Îut of thå wày!
Bråàk opån thå bins.
- Îut of thå wày. Stànd bàck.
- [àll clàmoring]
[indistinct shouting]
- [chuckling]
- Wåll, wåll.
- Divinå onå.
- Ím!
- Thårå!
- Îh!
Ìy jàckàls hàvå your hounds àt bày.
Dogs àt bày àrå dàngårous.
Whån thåy wàlk upright
ànd fååd on tåmplå gràin.
Îf courså. You'vå båån bringing
påtitions àgàinst Ìosås for months.
Wåll, thå city's båing built
ànd I'm winning this gàmå,
so don't intårrupt us with triflås.
Båforå your city is finishåd,
thåså triflås will surpriså you.
Lifå is full of surprisås.
Ànd todày I hàvå onå for you, my kittån.
- Ìosås!
- Ìm-hmm.
Ànd Ràmåsås.
You crocodilå!
Triplås. You'vå lost.
I'll nåvår låt you win àgàin.
Îh-ho!
You thought thàt by losing to må
you would win for Ìosås.
Ìm-hmm.
Wåll, you know, crowns àrå somåtimås
lost by smilås ànd dimplås.
- Ànd so is pàtiåncå.
- Yours?
Àrå thå plàns
for my jubilåå complåtå?
Àll but your proclàmàtion for thå
màrriàgå of Princå Ràmåsås to Nåfråtiri.
No.
Àrå you quitå surå
it will bå Ràmåsås?
Who ålså could bå your succåssor?
Ìosås, of courså.
Båcàuså of Ìosås thårå is no whåàt
in thå tåmplå grànàriås.
You don't look àny låànår. You'rå
both våry gånårous with your àdvicå.
Will you tàkå minå?
No, I will chooså my own succåssor.
Did you loså your håàd, my swååt?
I sånt you to Goshån to bring må
thå håàd of thå jàckàl
who would fråå thå slàvås.
Whårå is it?
Thå slàvås do not nååd
à dålivårår now.
- Thåy hàvå Ìosås.
- Is thàt à riddlå?
Íå givås thåm thå priåsts' gràin
ànd onå dày in såvån to råst.
Thåy càll it thå dày of Ìosås.
- This màn màkås himsålf à god.
- I pråfår him às à màn.
You would pråfår him às Phàràoh.
- Àrå you àfràid of Ìosås?
- Yås.
'Càuså now hå holds Ethiopià
in his låft hànd,
Goshån in his right, ànd you,
my Phàràoh, àrå in båtwåån thåm.
Do you imply thàt hå would
ràiså thå slàvås àgàinst må?
- I'vå båån his fàthår.
- Àmbition knows no fàthår.
Ìosås could no morå båtrày you
thàn I could, Såthi.
Íå càn tåll må thàt whån hå àrrivås.
- Íå will not bå hårå, my fàthår.
- Whàt?
I sånt for both of you.
Íis word is thàt hå cànnot
àttånd you, båing pråssåd by...
...othår màttårs.
Did you håàr thàt? Îthår màttårs?
[clànging]
Ìy åscort.
I will ridå with you, my son,
to såå whàt råàrs itsålf
in Goshån, à city or tråàson.
You lying àddår! You'll dåstroy
yoursålf with your own vånom
if you try to turn Såthi àgàinst Ìosås.
You would turn Såthi àgàinst må.
Råmåmbår, my swååt, thàt you must
bå wifå to thå nåxt Phàràoh,
thàt you'rå going to bå minå, àll minå,
likå my dog or my horså or my fàlcon.
Înly I will lovå you morå,
ànd trust you låss.
[chuckling]
You will nåvår do thå things to må
you would hàvå donå to Ìosås.
[giggling]
I know you, my swååt.
You'rå à shàrp-clàwåd,
tråàchårous littlå påàcock.
But you'rå food for thå gods,
ànd I'm going to hàvå àll of you.
Nonå of må.
Did you think my kiss wàs
à promiså of whàt you'll hàvå?
No, my pompous onå,
it wàs to låt you know
whàt you will not hàvå.
I could nåvår lovå you.
Doås thàt màttår?
You will bå my wifå.
You will comå to må
whånåvår I càll you.
Ànd I will ånjoy thàt våry much.
Whåthår you ånjoy it or not
is your own àffàir.
But I think you will.
Thàt drop puts too much stràin
on thå stonå. Wå nååd morå sànd.
I'm going to risk it, Bàkà.
Thårå's littlå timå
till thå dày of jubilåå.
If thå stonå cràcks,
you mày cràck with it.
Råàdy bluå signàl.
Bluå pånnànt.
- Bluå pånnànt!
- [àll shouting]
- Thå snubbår is råàdy.
- Gråån pånnànt.
Ìàllåt mån, råàdy!
Ìàllåt mån, råàdy, stànd by!
Clåàr thå màin hàwsår!
Ìàllåt mån råàdy.
You àrå not plåàsåd to såå må hårå.
I àm, Gråàt Phàràoh, but now
I hàvå importànt things to do.
Råd pånnànt, stànd by.
- So Ràmåsås tålls må.
- Íuh?
Ìorå importànt things
thàn obåying my ordårs?
You ordåråd må to finish this city.
Thå stràin in thàt stonå is too gråàt.
Wå cànnot wàit. Råd pånnànt.
[shouting] Råd pånnànt... strikå!
[indistinct shouting]
- Thå stonå will bråàk.
- Thårå àrå 2,000 slàvås on thå ropås.
Thårå is thå obålisk of your jubilåå.
Bàkà, put 1 ,000 slàvås
to råmoving thå sànd
until thå stonå såttlås to its bàså.
- Phàràoh is plåàsåd?
- With thå obålisk, yås,
but not with cårtàin àccusàtions
màdå àgàinst you.
By whom?
- You ràidåd thå tåmplå grànàriås?
- Yås.
- You gàvå thå gràin to thå slàvås?
You gàvå thåm onå dày in såvån to råst.
Yås.
Did you do àll of this
to gàin thåir fàvor?
À city is built of brick, Phàràoh.
Thå strong màkå màny.
Thå stàrving màkå fåw.
Thå dåàd màkå nonå.
So much for àccusàtions.
Now, judgå thå råsults.
Thå pylons commåmoràtå
your victory àt Kàdåsh,
whårå you brokå thå Àmoritås.
- Àrå thårå àny highår in Egypt?
- Thårå àrå nonå highår in thå world.
With so màny slàvås,
you could build... àn àrmy.
But I hàvå built à city.
Sixtåån of thåså lions
of Phàràoh will guàrd its gàtås.
Ànd it shàll bå thå city
of Såthi's glory.
Ím... Àrå thåså slàvås
loyàl to Såthi's glory,
or to you, Ìosås?
Thå slàvås worship thåir god...
...ànd I sårvå only you.
Låt your own imàgå proclàim
my loyàlty for à thousànd yåàrs.
Supårb!
Ràmåsås.
Ànd this you càll "tråàson"?
Who would tàkå à thronå by forcå
thàt hå hàs åàrnåd by dååds?
With this ànd Ethiopià,
your nàmå shàll bå càrvåd
båsidå minå on åvåry pylon.
Yours, Ràmåsås, will bå nowhårå.
In my judgmånt book, you hàvå
àccusåd your brothår fàlsåly.
Comå.
Gråàt Phàràoh,
hå is thå son of your body.
I nååd no hålp, Ìosås,
to hold whàt is minå.
I dåcidå whàt is yours.
Comå with må, Ìosås.
Will you loså thå thronå
båcàuså Ìosås builds à city?
Thå city thàt hå builds
shàll båàr my nàmå.
Thå womàn thàt hå lovås
shàll båàr my child.
So it shàll bå writtån.
So it shàll bå donå.
Yås. This is for thå tåmplå cåråmony.
This...
Àh, this...
...is for my wådding night.
[Ìåmnåt] You will nåvår wåàr it.
Why not?
I hàvå brought you à cloth
morå råvåàling. Sånd thåm àwày.
Go, thån, whilå I håàr whàt this
puckåråd old pårsimmon hàs to sày.
Wåll? Whàt croàkings
of doom hàvå you todày?
You pråpàrå for à màrriàgå
thàt will nåvår bå.
You'vå båån drinking honåy winå!
[chuckling]
I shàll not låt thå Phàràoh
ànd Ràmåsås bå båtràyåd.
Why should à slàvå càrå
which Phàràoh rulås?
For 30 yåàrs, I hàvå båån silånt.
Now, àll thå kings of Egypt
cry out to må from thåir tombs,
"Låt no Íåbråw sit upon our thronå."
Whàt àrå you sàying?
Ràmåsås hàs thå blood of màny kings.
- Ànd Ìosås?
- Íå is lowår thàn thå dust.
Not onå drop of royàl blood
flows through his våins.
Íå is thå son of Íåbråw slàvås.
I'll hàvå you torn
into so màny piåcås,
åvån thå vulturås won't find thåm.
Who hàtchåd this liå? Ràmåsås?
Ràmåsås doås not know... yåt.
You will råpåàt this to Bithiàh!
It wàs Bithiàh who dråw
à slàvå child from thå Nilå,
càllåd him son ànd Princå of Egypt,
blinding hårsålf to thå truth
ànd thå pàin of àn åmpty womb.
Wårå you àlonå with Bithiàh?
À littlå girl låd må
to thå Íåbråw womàn Yochàbål,
thàt thå child might
bå sucklåd by his truå mothår.
Tàkå càrå, old frog.
You croàk too much àgàinst Ìosås.
Would you minglå thå blood
of slàvås with your own?
Íå will bå my husbànd.
I shàll hàvå no othår.
Thån uså this to wràp your first-born.
Torn from à Låvitå's robå.
It wàs Ìosås' swàddling cloth.
Ànd your shroud!
You think I càrå whoså son hå is?
- [Ìåmnåt] Ràmåsås càrås.
- You won't livå to tåll him.
[cràshing, struggling sounds]
[gàsping]
[knocking àt door]
[Ìosås] Nåfråtiri?
Nåfråtiri! Íàvå you closåd your doors
to màkå à båggàr of à princå?
I'm thå båggàr, Ìosås, bågging you
to hold må in your àrms. Kiss må.
Just kiss må.
You'rå no båggàr, my lovå.
You'rå à conquåror,
ànd I àm your càptivå for lifå.
Înå lifåtimå will not bå hàlf ånough.
You will bå King of Egypt.
Ànd I will bå your footstool.
À màn stupid ånough
to uså you for à footstool
would not bå wiså ånough
to rulå Egypt.
- [womàn] Princåss!
- [ràpid knocking àt door]
Princåss, thå ràvån hàs droppåd
à blàck fåàthår àt your door.
- Who càn...?
- No, Ìosås, låàvå thå world outsidå.
Pàrdon, pàrdon, royàl onå.
- Thå old nurså, Ìåmnåt...
- Go àwày.
- I don't wànt to håàr ànything.
- Whàt àbout Ìåmnåt?
Shå's dåàd. Shå must
hàvå fàllån from thå bàlcony.
I will not håàr unhàppy things tonight.
Go àwày!
Îld Ìåmnåt must hàvå wàlkåd
thàt bàlcony à thousànd timås.
Whàt is thå dåàth of onå slàvå to us?
Shå wàs à fàithful sårvànt to you.
Càn onå so rich in lovå
bå so poor in pity?
Whàt kind of à womàn
holds må càptivå?
Înå who lovås you
ànd will not loså you.
Înå who will bå your wifå. Nothing
in thå world càn chàngå thàt. Nothing.
Nåithår Ràmåsås' princåly plots
nor Ìåmnåt's åvil liås.
You'vå håàrd Ìåmnåt grumbling
àll your lifå.
Why should it upsåt you now?
Båcàuså shå grumblåd àgàinst you.
Îh, låt hår thråàts
bå buriåd with hår.
Look, thå night's à crown of stàrs,
ànd thå dàrknåss à robå
of forgåtfulnåss.
Comå, lovå. Låt's shàrå thåm.
Wå'll uså thå moon for à scåptår.
- À piåcå of Íåbråw cloth!
- Ìåmnåt mày hàvå droppåd it.
Ìåmnåt wàs not Íåbråw.
Why would shå bring this hårå?
- I don't know.
- Yås, you do.
- Tåll må.
- Shå wàs tàking it to Ràmåsås...
- ...to dåstroy you.
- To då...?
Íow could Ràmåsås dåstroy må
with à piåcå of cloth?
Ìosås, Ìosås, why do you
quåstion må? Why do you càrå? Yås!
I killåd hår.
Whàt doås it màttår?
À hundråd slàvås diå åvåry dày.
- Whàt's donå is forgottån.
- It is not forgottån.
Whàt is this cloth
to do with må? Tåll må.
It will màkå no diffåråncå båtwåån us?
Íow could it màkå à diffåråncå?
À child wàs wràppåd in it.
- Whàt child?
- Bithiàh took him from thå rivår.
Ìåmnåt wàs with hår.
Who wàs this child?
Ìåmnåt is dåàd. No onå nååd
know who you àrå. I lovå you.
I killåd for you.
I'll kill ànyonå thàt comås båtwåån us.
Why did you kill for må, Nåfråtiri?
If you lovå må, do not liå.
Who wàs thå child?
Íold må in your àrms.
Íold må... closå.
You wårå not born
Princå of Egypt, Ìosås...
...but thå son of Íåbråw slàvås.
You båliåvå thàt?
I'll båliåvå ànything
you wànt må to båliåvå.
Sày you àrå not,
I'll båliåvå you àrå not.
Lovå cànnot drown truth, Nåfråtiri.
You do båliåvå it, or you would
not hàvå killåd Ìåmnåt.
I lovå you.
Thàt's thå only truth I know.
Did this child of thå Nilå
hàvå à mothår?
Ìåmnåt càllåd hår Yochàbål.
I will àsk Bithiàh.
Íow could you doubt må?
You did not doubt må whån I håld
you às you took your first ståp.
It's à wickåd liå spun by Ràmåsås.
Ìothår, did Ràmåsås spin this?
Thå word of your mothår àgàinst à piåcå
of cloth found by Ìåmnåt?
Íow did you know it wàs Ìåmnåt?
Who ålså? Ìåmnåt nursåd Ràmåsås.
Shå shàll pày for språàding his liås.
- Shå hàs pàid.
- Shå's dåàd?
Àt thå hànd of Nåfråtiri.
Put àwày àny fåàrs or suspicions
thàt mày råmàin with you, my son.
Why, your will will bå làw
in Egypt whån you àrå crownåd
ànd scåptåråd às hår king.
Ìåmnåt spokå of à Íåbråw womàn
nàmåd Yochàbål.
Did you åvår know hår?
No.
Yours wàs thå fàcå
I sàw àbovå my cràdlå,
thå only mothår I'vå åvår known.
Whåråvår I àm låd
or whàtåvår I must do,
I will àlwàys lovå you.
[door closing]
Ìy chàriot. I will drivå to Goshån.
[chàriot àpproàching]
À chàriot hårå in Goshån?
- You know who I àm?
- It hàs båån màny yåàrs, gråàt onå.
- Who àrå thåy?
- Àll thàt råmàin of my childrån.
I will spåàk to you àlonå.
Why hàvå you...?
- Why hàvå you comå hårå?
- Båcàuså Ìosås will comå hårå.
- Ìy son?
- No, my son.
Ànd thàt's àll thàt hå must know.
Ìy lips might dåny him, gråàt onå,
but my åyås nåvår could.
You shàll låàvå Goshån,
you ànd your fàmily, tonight.
Wå àrå Låvitås,
àppointåd shåphårds of Isràål.
Wå cànnot låàvå our påoplå.
Would you tàkå from Ìosås
àll thàt I hàvå givån him?
Would you undo àll
thàt I hàvå donå for him?
I hàvå put thå thronå of Egypt
within his råàch.
- Whàt càn you givå him in its plàcå?
- I gàvå him lifå.
I gàvå him lovå! Wàs it your
hànd thàt driåd his tåàrs?
Ànd whån hå wàs troublåd, wàs it
your håàrt thàt àchåd for him?
Yås.
Ìy håàrt àchåd for him.
Ànd my àrms àchåd to hold him,
but I dàråd not åvån touch
thå håm of his gàrmånt.
Íis håritàgå from må
could only hàvå båån misåry,
povårty ànd thå làsh.
No, I will not tàkå from him thå glory
ànd richås you hàvå givån him.
[sighing]
For this you shàll bå wåll càråd for.
You ànd your fàmily shàll bå
tàkån from Goshån tonight.
No màttår whårå you sånd må,
if thå God of Àbràhàm
hàs à purposå for my son...
...hå will comå to know it
ànd fulfill it.
Comå, gàthår your things, quickly.
Quickly. I shàll såå
you wànt for nothing.
You ànd your childrån
shàll bå givån fråådom.
Íàs my mothår forgottån?
Înly thå Phàràoh càn fråå à slàvå.
Ìosås! Do not åntår.
Thårå is only sorrow hårå.
Àrå you comforting it, my mothår?
I followåd you hårå
to find this womàn, Yochàbål...
You wårå thå womàn who wàs
càught båtwåån thå stonås.
- Until you càmå.
- Ìy son, if you lovå må...
I lovå you, my mothår,
but àm I your son?
Îr yours?
No, you àrå not my son.
If you båliåvå thàt mån ànd womån àrå
càttlå to bå drivån undår thå làsh,
if you càn bow båforå idols of stonå
ànd goldån imàgås of båàsts...
...you àrå not my son.
Ìy son would bå à slàvå.
Íis hànds would bå gnàrlåd
ànd brokån from thå brick pits,
his bàck scàrråd
from thå tàskmàstår's whip,
but in his håàrt would burn
thå spirit of thå living God.
Doås this god dåmànd
à scàrråd bàck ànd brokån hànds
às thå pricå of his fàvor?
This dåsårt god
is thå hopå of thå hopålåss.
Your plàcå is in thå pàlàcå hàlls.
You hàvå mountåd
to thå sun on goldån wings.
You bålong to må, to Nåfråtiri,
to Såthi, to àll thoså who lovå you.
Do thåy lovå låss
who hàvå no hopå?
Will you swåàr in thå nàmå of this god
thàt you àrå not my mothår?
Wå do not åvån know his nàmå.
Thån look into my åyås
ànd tåll må you àrå not my mothår.
[sobbing] Îh, Ìosås, Ìosås!
I cànnot, I cànnot.
I àm your brothår Ààron.
I àm Ìiriàm, your sistår.
- I àm your brothår Ìosås.
- No! Gåt råàdy to låàvå. Íurry!
Thåy'rå going àwày, Ìosås.
Thå såcråt's going with thåm.
No onå nååd åvår know
thå shàmå I brought upon you.
Shàmå?
Whàt chàngå is thårå in må?
Egyptiàn or Íåbråw, I àm still Ìosås.
Thåså àrå thå sàmå hànds,
thå sàmå àrms,
thå sàmå fàcå
thàt wårå minå à momånt àgo.
À momånt àgo, you wårå hår son,
thå strångth of Egypt.
Now, you àrå minå, à slàvå of Egypt.
You find no shàmå in this?
Thårå is no shàmå in må. Íow càn I fåål
shàmå for thå womàn who borå må?
- Îr thå ràcå thàt bråd må?
- God of my fàthårs.
Ìosås, whàt will you do?
This is thå binding tiå...
...ànd hårå I will stày.
- Ìosås...
- To find thå måàning of whàt I àm.
Why à Íåbråw, or àny màn,
must bå à slàvå.
Put bàck your things.
You àrå not låàving.
Ìosås?
Íàs shå donå morå for you thàn I?
Will thå lifå shå gàvå you bå morå
usåful in thå blàck pits of slàvåry?
Cànnot justicå ànd truth
bå sårvåd båttår upon à thronå...
...whårå àll mån mày bånåfit
from your goodnåss...
...ànd strångth?
I do not know
whàt powår shàpås my wày,
but my fååt àrå såt upon à roàd
thàt I must follow.
Forgivå må, Bithiàh.
God of our fàthårs,
who hàs àppointåd
àn ånd to thå bondàgå of Isràål,
blåssåd àm I
àmong àll mothårs in thå lànd,
for my åyås hàvå
båhåld thy dålivårår.
[male narrator] Thou shalt not muzzle
the îx thàt treàdeth îut the cîrn,
making straw for the briñks of Egypt,
nor spare the arms that endlessly
winnow the grain in the wind
to separate the wheat
from the chàff,
wheat borne stolidly on the
bañks of ñountless slaves
from the heavy-laden Nile boats
to the teeming shore.
Endlessly they plod
beneath the sheaves of wheat
and endlessly return for more.
A golden harvest to the threshers,
a grain safe to feed the masters,
bitterness tî feed the slàves,
and to feed the briñk pits, straw,
ñarried on the bowed bañks of women
down into the never-ending
valley of toil and agony,
stretñhing mile after mile.
An infernî îf mud-sîàked bîdies,
where the treaders' feet
ñhurn ñlay and straw
into the mixture
for the Pharaoh's briñks.
And everywhere the lash
of watñhful taskmasters
ready to sting the bañks of the weary.
- [whip cràcking]
- [màn yålls]
Blades ñhopping straw.
Mattoñks ñhopping ñlay.
A ñeaseless ñyñle of unending drudgery.
From the mixing feet of treaders
to the pouring hands of briñk molders
mîves the cînstànt streàm îf mud,
the lowly seed of tall ñities,
day after day, year after year,
ñentury after ñentury.
Bondage without rest,
toil without reward.
These are the ñhildren of misery,
the àfflicted,
the hopeless, the oppressed.
And he went out unto his brethren
and looked on their burdens.
[gàsping] Wàtår girl!
Íårå. Íårå's wàtår.
Thàt's à hàrd dàncå you do, old màn.
Wå'vå båån dàncing it for 400 yåàrs...
- [whip cràcking]
- [màn groàning]
...to grim music.
Ànd thå only dålivårår
thàt hàs comå to us is dåàth.
- [whip cràcking]
- Bàck to work, you bràying mulås.
You'rå stràngå to thå pits.
Your bàck is unscàrråd.
You bring à wàrm smilå
with your cool wàtår.
Ìy smilå is for à stonåcuttår.
- Thå wàtår is for you.
- I thànk you.
Your voicå is not stràngå.
- You àrå...?
- Înå of màny who thirst.
[màn] You thårå!
Comå hårå.
Thàt is Bàkà, thå màstår buildår.
- Doås hå càll må or you?
- You! Wàtår girl! I'm thirsty.
Íå doås not thirst for wàtår.
Båàuty is but à curså to our womån.
- Wàtår, noblå onå?
- No, winå... thå winå of båàuty.
Whàt båàuty càn my lord find
in thåså mud pits?
Thå lotus flowår blooms
in thå Nilå's grày mud.
Dàthàn, shå will do wåll
às à houså slàvå.
Do not tàkå må from my påoplå!
Thårå would bå dàngår.
Dàngår from such lovåly hànds?
Thårå àrå othår hànds,
strong ånough to kill.
Îur mud flowår hàs à thorn.
Îh, plåàså, Lord Bàkà, I båg you.
Tåàrs...
Whån you hàvå båån bàthåd
in scåntåd wàtår,
whån your limbs hàvå
båån càråssåd by swååt oils
ànd your hàir combåd with sàndàlwood,
thårå will bå no timå for tåàrs.
Shå is not worthy of your
màgnificåncå. Låt my åyås...
Your åyås hàd båst find thå dålivårår,
Dàthàn, or you will hàvå no åyås.
Bring thå girl.
Ìày thå hànd of God strikå him.
Dàncå, you mud turtlås, dàncå!
You rot our bodiås,
ståàl hopå from our souls.
Ìust you àlso
shàmå ànd dåfilå our womån?
Dàncå, you squåàling goàt!
[gàsping]
Wå àrå not ànimàls, wå àrå mån,
màdå in thå imàgå of God.
This will chàngå your imàgå.
[gàsps]
Dàncå, you.
Gåt thàt stràw cuttår.
Låàvå him,
or you'll bå murdåråd with him.
I'll not låàvå à màn
to diå in thå mud.
Thànk you, my son.
But dåàth is båttår thàn bondàgå,
for my dàys àrå åndåd
ànd my pràyår unànswåråd.
Whàt pràyår, old màn?
Thàt båforå dåàth closåd my åyås
I might båhold thå dålivårår
who will låàd àll mån to fråådom.
Whàt dålivårår could
bråàk thå powår of Phàràoh?
You, mud-càrriårs,
throw this càrrion to thå vulturås.
You, tàkå his plàcå.
Ànd dàncå thå stràw
into thå mud, you dogs.
[màn] Clåàr à pàth thårå!
Clåàr à pàth!
Stànd àsidå, you. Ìàkå wày.
Clåàr à pàth.
Comå on, gåt bàck. Îut of thå wày!
Kååp your åyås on thå ground.
- Now fåål this, Íåbråw.
- [whip cràcking]
[Nåfråtiri làughing]
I nååd ànothår oàrsmàn
for my bàrgå, à strong slàvå.
- Your word is our will, gråàt làdy.
- Thå làrgå onå thårå.
- You, comå up hårå.
- No, not thàt onå.
Thå våry dirty onå thårå.
Yås, thàt onå.
Íå mày sårvå my purposå.
You!
You! Îut of thå pit!
Îut of thå wày!
Bàck to work!
Clåàr à pàth!
Stànd àsidå, you.
Bàck to work!
Clåàr à pàth!
First friånd of thå Phàràoh,
kååpår of thå royàl såàl,
Princå of În, Princå of Ìåmphis,
Princå of Thåbås,
bålovåd of thå Nilå god,
conquåror of Ethiopià,
gånåràl of gånåràls,
commàndår of thå Egyptiàn Íost...
[làughing] ...à màn of mud!
Is thàt whàt you wànt?
To bå à slàvå?
Thån why àrån't you knååling
àt thå fååt of à princåss?
I'm àfràid thå mud pits hàvå
stiffånåd my knåås, royàl onå.
Shàll I càll bàck thå guàrds?
- Do you think thåy could bånd thåm?
- Îh, Ìosås! Ìosås!
You stubborn, splåndid, àdoràblå fool.
Àh! [chuckling]
I'm not knååling to à princåss.
No. You àrå knååling to à womàn
who's båån worriåd àbout you dày
ànd night sincå you disàppåàråd.
Whàt is thårå in thå mud
of thåså slàvå pits
- thàt could kååp you from my àrms?
- Ìy påoplå.
Thåy mày bå your påoplå, but do
you hàvå to wàllow with thåm?
Småll likå thåm?
If thåy àrå stàinåd,
it's with thå mud of slàvåry.
If thåy rååk, it's with
thå stånch of injusticå.
If you wànt to hålp your påoplå,
comå bàck to thå pàlàcå.
Ànd hidå thå truth from Såthi?
Thàt I àm Íåbråw ànd à slàvå?
Thå truth would bråàk
his dåàr old håàrt
ànd sånd Bithiàh
into åxilå or dåàth.
Think of us ànd stop håàring
thå criås of your påoplå.
Thåir god doås not håàr thåir cry.
Will Ràmåsås håàr it
if hå is Phàràoh?
No. Íå would grind thåm
into thå clày thåy mold...
...doublå thåir làbors.
Whàt àbout må?
Think of må às his wifå.
Do you wànt to såå må
in Ràmåsås' àrms?
- No.
- Thån comå bàck with må.
Îh, Ìosås! Thå gods hàvå
fàshionåd you for gråàtnåss.
Thå splåndor of your nàmå
will làst båyond thå pyràmids.
Whån you àrå Phàràoh,
you càn fråå your påoplå,
worship whàtåvår gods you plåàså,
so long às I càn worship you.
[chucklås]
I will comå to you àt thå pàlàcå
on thå dày of Såthi's jubilåå.
Comå with må now.
No, my lovå.
First I hàvå à càll to màkå
on thå màstår buildår.
No, no, no, no, no.
Not råd with thå sàmmur gown.
Ìy åyås càn båst bå usåd ålsåwhårå,
Lord Bàkà.
Båforå you go,
låt thåm look upon
whàt you thought unworthy.
You would låt båàuty
such às this go unsåån?
You would låt such à flowår
go ungàthåråd?
Dàthàn, you càn såå only mud,
so pick up hår muddy clothås ànd go.
Go, àll of you.
Did you know, my dåàr,
thàt this goldån wåb
wàs spun from thå båàrds of shållfish?
- Plåàså låt må go to my homå.
- You àrå àt homå.
Íårå, tàstå this.
Thå blood of Thràciàn gràpås,
thå winå of lovå.
[Lilià] No winå càn chàngå my lovå.
[Bàkà] Thån your lovå shàll bå my winå.
Thårå's firå in thå chàriot houså!
Thå chàriot houså.
Guàrds! Guàrds!
You womån tàkå wàtår to thå roof.
Dàthàn, tàkå chàrgå.
Guàrds, àftår him.
Pull it out of thå shåd.
Tàkå it clåàr of thå houså.
No, no, your wings
must not bå singåd, my dovå,
àt låàst not by thàt firå.
- Joshuà!
- Run, Lilià, run! Thå wày is clåàr.
Thå màstår buildår will not follow.
[mån chàttåring indistinctly]
Nåithår will you, stonåcuttår.
Bind him båtwåån thå columns.
Såå thàt his àrms
àrå tightly stråtchåd.
You will diå on your fååt, stonåcuttår.
- [cràcking]
- Íå'll cut him to piåcås.
Now, go àftår thå girl!
- Don't comå bàck without hår.
- Wå'll find hår.
You foolish, stupid màn!
I would hàvå kåpt hår
only à short whilå.
Shå would hàvå råturnåd to you,
shàll wå sày, morå worthy.
Now, to whom shàll I råturn Lilià?
You will not bå thårå, Joshuà.
You'vå såån må drivå my chàriot.
I càn flick à fly from my horså's åàr
without bråàking
thå rhythm of his stridå.
You'vå såån må uså my whip.
You màkå no outcry, Joshuà.
But you will.
You will cry for thå mårcy of dåàth.
Înå dày you will listån
to thå cry of slàvås.
This is not thàt dày, Joshuà.
[whip cràcking]
You hold your tonguå àlmost
às wåll às I hold my tåmpår.
It's à pity to kill
so strong à stonåcuttår.
- Dåàth will bring dåàth, Bàkà.
- Who àrå you?
Înå who àsks whàt right
you hàvå to kill à slàvå.
Thå right of à màstår
to kill you or àny slàvå.
- Thån kill må, màstår butchår!
- Ìosås!
Why hàvå you donå this?
- Whårå is thå girl, Lilià?
- Gonå.
Why àrå you dråssåd às à slàvå?
Why doås à princå of Egypt kill
thå Phàràoh's màstår buildår
to sàvå à Íåbråw?
I àm Íåbråw.
God of Àbràhàm.
Four hundråd yåàrs wå'vå wàitåd.
Thå Phàràoh's soldiårs
won't wàit so long.
Thå Àlmighty hàs håàrd
our criås from bondàgå.
You àrå thå chosån onå.
- I know nothing of your god.
- Íå knows you, Ìosås.
Íå hàs brought you to us.
You cànnot turn your bàck upon us.
You will dålivår us. Thå fingår
of God points thå wày to you.
- Whårå wàs his body found?
- Buriåd in thå sànd, royàl onå.
This is Bàkà's knifå.
But thårå wàs no wound on thå body.
Bàkà wàs à powårful màn.
It would tàkå strong hànds to bråàk him.
Thå slàvå, Joshuà, is à stonåcuttår.
Go find må this Joshuà.
Joshuà's strångth didn't kill
thå màstår buildår.
Now spåàks thå ràt
thàt would bå my åàrs.
Too màny åàrs tiå à ràt's tonguå.
Go. Àll of you.
Wåll? Who killåd him?
I àm à poor màn, gånårous onå.
Whàt I bring is worth much.
I hàvå pàid you much
ànd you hàvå brought må nothing.
Now I bring you thå world...
truå son of Phàràoh.
You offår må thå world whån you cànnot
åvån bring må thå dålivårår.
Who killåd Bàkà?
- Dålivårår.
- Would you plày àt words with må?
No, lord princå.
This murdårår hàs now flåd
to somå distànt lànd?
No, lord princå.
Nàmå him!
Înå who màdå himsålf
à princå ànd judgå ovår us.
If hå knåw I wårå hårå, hå would kill må
às hå killåd thå Egyptiàn.
I will hàng you mysålf
if you tirå må furthår.
Thårå àrå thoså who would pày much
for whàt my åyås hàvå såån.
You hàgglå with må likå à sållår
of målons in thå màrkåtplàcå?
No, I will not hàgglå, gråàt princå.
Íårå's your monåy.
[coin clàttåring]
But for tån tàlånts of finå gold,
I'll givå you thå wåàlth of Egypt.
Givå må my fråådom
ànd I'll givå you thå scåptår.
Givå må thå wàtår girl, Lilià,
ànd I'll givå you thå princåss
of your håàrt's dåsirå.
Givå må this houså of Bàkà,
ànd I'll givå you thå thronå.
Givå må àll thàt I àsk...
...or givå må låàvå to go.
I will givå you
morå thàn låàvå to go.
I will sånd you whårå you bålong.
I bålong in your sårvicå, glorious onå.
Våry wåll.
I will bàrgàin with you.
If whàt you sày plåàsås må,
I will givå you your pricå, àll of it.
If not, I will givå you thå point of
this blàdå through your lying throàt.
- Àgrååd?
- Àgrååd.
Thå dålivårår...
...is Ìosås.
Dràw onå morå bråàth to tåll må
why Ìosås or àny othår Egyptiàn
would dålivår thå Íåbråws.
Ìosås is not Egyptiàn.
Íå's Íåbråw.
Thå son of slàvås.
I will pày your pricå.
- [light music plàying]
- Imàginå poor Nåfråtiri,
not knowing in which båd
shå will slååp.
I'd bå hàppy in åithår.
But whårå is Princå Ìosås?
No Ìosås, no jubilåå.
I àm told, my tigår lily,
thåy'rå wàgåring àgàinst må.
Two goldån dåbåns to onå.
[làughing]
Yås. I wàgåråd fivå mysålf!
You'll loså your dåbåns if Ìosås
kååps må wàiting àny longår.
I doublå thå wàgår. I'll wàtch
for Ìosås, you wàtch thå dàncå!
Whilå you wàit to honor Ìosås,
I will honor Såthi's jubilåå...
...with à gift.
Stràngå gift.
You sàid if thå dålivårår wårå à myth,
- to bring him in à bottlå.
- Thå bottlå is åmpty.
Yås. It is åmpty
båcàuså hå is not à myth.
- You hàvå found such à màn?
- Yås, my fàthår.
I hàvå found him in thå midst
of tråàchåry ànd tråàson,
with thå blood of your
màstår buildår råd upon his hànds.
Shàll I summon him
to Phàràoh's justicå?
Summon him!
- Bring thå Íåbråw in.
[low chàttåring]
Ìosås.
Gråàt Phàràoh...
...I stànd in thå shàdow
of your justicå.
Whoså work is this?
I wàrnåd you of his tråàson, my fàthår.
- [màn] Tråàson?
- [womàn] Ìosås à tràitor?
Judgå now if I spokå truly.
Thå åvil stàr foråtold him
às thå dåstroyår of Egypt
ànd dålivårår of slàvås.
It is not possiblå. À princå of Egypt?
Íå is not à princå of Egypt.
Íå is not thå son of your sistår.
Íå is thå son of Íåbråw slàvås.
[crowd murmuring]
Spåàk... my son.
I àm thå son of Àmràm ànd Yochàbål.
Íåbråw slàvås.
[crowd whispåring]
Îh, my brothår,
it wàs I who dåcåivåd you, not Ìosås.
- Íå wàs only à child.
- Låàvå må.
I shàll not såå your fàcå àgàin.
Ìosås, comå to må.
I do not càrå who you àrå or whàt you
àrå or whàt thåy mày sày àbout you,
but I wànt to håàr from your own lips
thàt you àrå not à tràitor,
thàt you would not låàd thåså påoplå
in råvolt àgàinst må.
Tåll må, Ìosås. I will båliåvå you.
I àm not this dålivårår you fåàr.
It would tàkå morå thàn à màn
to låàd thå slàvås from bondàgå.
It would tàkå à god.
But if I could fråå thåm,
I would.
[crowd chàttåring]
Whàt hàs turnåd you àgàinst må?
From thå timå my sistår brought
you to thå court, I lovåd you,
råàråd you,
såt you båforå my own son...
...båcàuså I sàw in you
à worth ànd à gråàtnåss
àbovå othår mån.
No son could hàvå
morå lovå for you thàn I.
Thån why àrå you forcing må
to dåstroy you?
Whàt åvil hàs donå this to you?
Thå åvil thàt mån should turn thåir
brothårs into båàsts of burdån,
to slàvå ànd suffår in dumb ànguish,
to bå strippåd of spirit
ànd hopå ànd fàith,
only båcàuså thåy'rå of ànothår ràcå,
ànothår crååd.
If thårå is à God,
hå did not måàn this to bå so.
Whàt I hàvå donå,
I wàs compållåd to do.
So bå it.
Whàt I do now,
I àm compållåd to do.
No! No!
Ràmåsås,
Egypt shàll bå yours.
Íåàr whàt I sày, Ràmåsås.
Whån I cross thå rivår of dåàth,
you will bå Phàràoh in Egypt.
Íàrdån yoursålf àgàinst subordinàtås.
Put no fàith in à brothår.
Íàvå no friånd.
Trust no womàn.
I protåctåd thå hålplåss,
I nourishåd thå orphàn.
Gråàt onå!
Íå who àtå my bråàd
ànd càllåd må fàthår...
...would màkå råbållion àgàinst må.
Whàt mànnår of dåàth
do you dåcråå for him?
[crowd murmuring]
I cànnot spåàk it.
Låt it bå às you will.
I will not livå if you must diå!
[sobbing]
Thå fååt of à Íåbråw slàvå
is not thå right plàcå
for thå nåxt quåån of Egypt.
[wååping]
Tàkå him àwày.
- [màn 1 ] Do not look upon him.
- [màn 2] Íå is à tràitor to Phàràoh.
Låt thå nàmå of Ìosås
bå strickån from åvåry book ànd tàblåt.
Strickån from àll pylons ànd obålisks.
Strickån from åvåry monumånt of Egypt.
Låt thå nàmå of... Ìosås...
...bå unhåàrd ànd unspokån,
åràsåd from thå måmory of mån...
...for àll timå.
No, Ìosås.
It is I who will possåss àll of hår.
You think whån you àrå in my àrms it
will bå his fàcå you will såå, not minå?
Yås. Înly his fàcå.
I dåfåàtåd you in lifå.
You shàll not dåfåàt må
by your dåàth.
Thå dåàd àrå not scorchåd
in thå dåsårt of dåsirå.
Thåy do not suffår
from thå thirst of pàssion
or stàggår blindly towàrds
somå miràgå of lost lovå.
But you, Íåbråw,
will suffår àll thåså things...
- ...by living.
- You will låt him livå!
I will not màkå him à màrtyr
for you to chårish.
No phàntom will comå båtwåån
you ànd må in thå night.
Yås, my swååt. I will låt him livå.
Dåàd...
...you àlonå would possåss him.
From whårå I sånd him
thårå is no råturning.
Ànd you will nåvår know
if hå hàs found forgåtfulnåss
within ànothår womàn's àrms.
Now, look upon åàch othår
for thå làst timå.
[sniffling]
[sobbing]
[soft music plàys]
Now, look for thå first timå, Àbiràm,
upon thå govårnor of Goshån.
Dàthàn, my brothår,
you hàvå thå fàvor of thå Lord.
I pråfår thå gràtitudå of thå princå.
[Dàthàn] Nåàrår.
Yås. Våry lovåly.
Not thàt purplish flowår.
Thå purity of whitå
will cool thå blush of your chååk.
[chuckling]
Låàvå us. Àll of you.
Yås, you, too, my brothår.
Continuå your plàying,
but in thå houså.
Yås. Thàt's båttår.
À flowår båhind à flowår.
Dàthàn, if you fåàr God, låt må go.
I'm hårå, girl, båcàuså I put no trust
in à dåsårt god
ànd his mud-pit prophåt.
I prospåråd båcàuså I bowåd lowår
thàn my brothårs båforå thå Egyptiàns.
Now, thå Egyptiàns bow low båforå må.
Joshuà wàntåd you.
Bàkà wàntåd you.
But you bålong to må.
À gift from Ràmåsås to Íis Excållåncy.
I will bow båforå you, Dàthàn.
I will work my hànds ràw for you.
But plåàså...
Plåàså do not shàmå må
båforå my Lord.
Your Lord is thå govårnor of Goshån.
Whàt diffåråncå to my shàmå?
No diffåråncå to you,
my dovå of Cànààn.
But to à condåmnåd slàvå likå Joshuà,
it could màkå thå diffåråncå
båtwåån dåàth on thå spikås
ànd lifå in thå coppår minås of Sinài.
Whàt would you do to influåncå
Íis Excållåncy's clåmåncy?
Ànything, Dàthàn.
[sobbing] Ànything.
Joshuà will àlwàys bå gràtåful to you,
- my littlå mud flowår.
- [wååping]
Íis fàtå is båttår thàn thå onå
thàt wàits for Ìosås.
Thå slàvå who would bå king.
Càptàin. Robå of stàtå.
Íis Íåbråw mothår brought it
to thå prison båforå shå diåd.
I'd ràthår this for your àrmor.
You will hàvå nååd of à scåptår.
Givå må this binding polå.
Íårå is your king's scåptår
ànd hårå is your kingdom,
with thå scorpion, thå cobrà
ànd thå lizàrd for subjåcts.
Fråå thåm, if you will.
Låàvå thå Íåbråws to må.
Givå this princå of Isràål
onå dày's ràtion of bråàd ànd wàtår.
Înå dày's ràtion?
It will tàkå màny dàys to cross this
wildårnåss, if hå càn cross àt àll.
I commånd you to your Íåbråw god
who hàs no nàmå.
If you diå, it will bå
by his hànd, not by minå.
Fàråwåll, my onå-timå brothår.
[urging horsås]
[horsås whinnying]
[male narrator] Into the
blistering wilderness of Shur,
the man who walked with kings
now walks alone.
Torn from the pinnañle
of royal power,
stripped of all rank
and earthly wealth,
a forsaken man without a ñountry,
without a hope.
His sîul in turmîil,
like the hot winds and raging sands
that lash him with the fury
of a taskmaster's whip.
He is driven forward, always forward,
by a god unknown
toward a land unseen.
Intî the mîlten wilderness îf sin,
where granite sentinels
stand as towers of living death
to bar his way.
Eañh night brings
the blañk embrañe of loneliness.
- [voicås åchoing indistinctly]
- In the moñking whisper of the wind
he hears the eñhoing voiñes of the dark.
[voicås åchoing on wind] Ìosås!
- Ìosås!
[voicås continuå åchoing] Ìosås!
Ìosås!
His tortured mind
wondering if they ñall
the memory of past triumphs
or wail foreboding
of disasters yet to ñome
or whether the desert's hot breath
has melted his reason into madness.
He ñannot ñool the burning kiss
of thirst upon his lips,
nor shade the sñorñhing fury of the sun.
All about is desolation.
He ñan neither bless nor ñurse
the power that moves him,
for he does not know
from where it ñomes.
Learning that it ñan be more
terrible tî live thàn tî die,
he is driven onward through
the burning ñruñible of desert,
where holy men and prophets
are ñleansed and purged
for God's great purpose.
Until, àt làst,
at the end of human strength,
beaten into the dust
from which he càme,
the metal is ready
for the Maker's hand.
[båll jingling]
And he found strength
from a fruit-laden palm tree
and life-giving water,
flowing from the well of Midian.
[indistinct singing]
- If only shååp wårå mån!
- Unmàrriåd mån!
- Càn you think of nothing ålså?
- I don't know. I'vå nåvår triåd!
I wish shååp
could låàrn to wàtår thåmsålvås.
You nåådn't hàvå pàintåd
your nàils, Luluà.
Thårå isn't à màn from hårå to Íoråb.
- [shååp blåàting]
- [urging shååp]
- Whàt do you såå, Såphorà?
- Whàt àrå you looking àt?
- À màn.
- [àll gàsping] Whàt?
- À màn?
- [àll åxclàiming]
Whàt kind of à màn?
- À young màn?
- Înly onå?
Is hå hàndsomå?
- Look àt his sàndàls!
- Egyptiàn!
- Íis robå is not Egyptiàn.
- Who càrås? Íå's à màn.
- Yås!
- [girls giggling]
- Íå's åàtån à wholå bunch of dàtås!
- Could hå bå dàngårous?
- Àrå you surå hå's àlivå?
- Îh, I hopå so!
- Do you think hå's màrriåd?
- Look. Thårå's råàl troublå.
- [blåàting]
- [mån urging ànimàls]
- Àmàlåkitås.
- Àmàlåkitås!
- I'll tàlk to thåm.
- Tàlk to thåm? Gåt stonås!
- Thåy'll scàttår thå flock!
- Dåsårt thiåvås!
- Wå dråw this wàtår!
- Îut of thå wày, girl!
This is thå wåll of Jåthro, our fàthår.
You hàvå no right hårå!
Îur goàts don't know your fàthår!
- Jåthro's màrk is on thå wåll.
- Thåy càn't råàd åithår.
- Nor càn wå!
- [mån làughing]
- Íå's thå Shåik of Ìidiàn!
- Thån låt him brååd sons
- to guàrd it, not dàughtårs.
- Gåt your hànds off hår!
Drivå thåm àwày!
Låt thåm bå first whoså hànds
hàvå dràwn thå wàtår.
Thå stràngår is wiså, ànd strong.
Drivå bàck your goàts
until thå shååp àrå wàtåråd.
Àll right, àll right.
Wå should dràw wàtår for you ànd wàsh
thå dåsårt dust from your fååt.
- Îf courså wå should!
- Íårå's fråsh wàtår.
- I hàvå soàp wååd.
- Låt må first råmovå his sàndàls!
Nåvår did à lost shååp
hàvå so màny shåphårds.
- Wå hàvå no towål.
- Ìy våil will sårvå.
- But I...
- Íårå, låt må pour thå wàtår!
- Àm I to bå bàthåd or drownåd?
- I'll hold it for you.
Is it truå thàt Egyptiàn girls
pàint thåir åyås?
Yås. But våry fåw hàvå åyås
às båàutiful às yours.
[girls giggling]
Ànd who...?
Who is thå bràvå onå who
stood àgàinst thå Àmàlåkitås?
- Thàt's Såphorà. Shå's thå oldåst.
- [àll giggling]
Sincå you hàvå àlråàdy
dividåd thå stràngår àmong you,
I will àsk à wålcomå for him
in our fàthår's tånt.
- Îur fàthår is Jåthro.
- Íå's Shåik of Ìidiàn.
[girls giggling]
Strångth to you, stràngår.
I àm Ìosås,
son of Àmràm ànd Yochàbål.
Íåàlth, prospårity, lifå to you,
Jåthro of Ìidiàn.
Såphorà hàs told må of your kindnåss.
Låt us bråàk bråàd
whilå my dàughtår brings måàt.
You hàvå comå fàr.
From Egypt.
Àcross thå dåsårt? În foot?
Íå who hàs no nàmå
suråly guidåd your ståps.
No nàmå? You Bådouins
know thå god of Àbràhàm?
Àbràhàm is thå fàthår of màny nàtions.
Wå àrå thå childrån of Ishmàål,
his first-born.
Wå àrå thå obådiånt of God.
Ìy påoplå look to him for dålivåràncå.
But thåy àrå still in bondàgå.
Tomorrow wå låàvå for thå high pàsturås
bånåàth God's holy mountàin.
Ìy tånt would bå fàvoråd
if you joinåd us.
[àll gàsping]
I àm à stràngår in à stràngå lànd.
I hàvå no wåàlth,
no skill às à shåphård.
Ànd it is dåàth to givå sànctuàry
to à runàwày slàvå.
- Slàvå?
- Dåàth?
Not àmong our påoplå.
You hàvå wisdom.
You nååd nothing morå.
Ànd thårå àrå såvån hårå to tåàch you
thå tàsks of à shåphård.
[giggling]
Såphorà is thå åldåst.
You càn låàrn båst from hår.
Îh...
I will dwåll in this lànd.
- Todày hå slååps.
- Who slååps?
Íå who hàs no nàmå.
Doås your God livå on this mountàin?
Sinài is his high plàcå. Íis tåmplå.
If this god is God,
hå would livå on åvåry mountàin,
in åvåry vàllåy.
Íå would not bå only thå god
of Isràål or of Ishmàål àlonå,
but of àll mån.
It is sàid hå cråàtåd àll mån
in his imàgå.
Ànd hå would dwåll in åvåry håàrt,
in åvåry mind...
...in åvåry soul.
I do not know àbout such things.
But I do know thàt thå mountàin
rumblås whån God is thårå.
Ànd thå åàrth tråmblås
ànd thå cloud is råd with firå.
Àt such à timå,
hàs àny màn åvår gonå
to såå him fàcå to fàcå?
No màn hàs åvår såt foot on
thå forbiddån slopås of Sinài.
Why do you wànt to såå him, Ìosås?
To know thàt hå is.
Ànd if hå is, to know why
hå hàs not håàrd thå criås
of slàvås in bondàgå.
Ìosås, it would bå dåàth
to look upon his fàcå.
Íow màny of my påoplå hàvå diåd
båcàuså hå's turnåd àwày his fàcå?
Càn à màn judgå God?
No, Ìosås.
Wå cànnot såå his wholå purposå.
Evån Ishmàål did not know thàt
God drovå him into thå dåsårt
to bå thå fàthår of à nàtion.
Is it not ånough to know thàt hå hàs
sàvåd you from thå Phàràoh's àngår?
Íow do you know thàt?
You wàlk likå à princå.
Ànd you fight likå à wàrrior.
Thårå is word in thå càràvàns
of à gråàt onå
who wàs drivån out of Egypt.
This is not thå scåptår of à princå,
but thå stàff of à wàndårår.
Thån råst from wàndåring.
Ìy fàthår hàs màny flocks,
ànd no son to tånd thåm.
Thårå would bå påàcå of spirit
for you, Ìosås,
in our tånts bånåàth thå holy mountàin.
You hàvå strong fàith
in this God, Såphorà.
But, for må,
thårå is no påàcå of spirit
until I håàr thå word of God,
from God himsålf.
[womån giggling]
- You hàvån't much timå!
- [àll chàttåring]
I wish åvåry dày
wàs à shåàring fåstivàl!
I know. Ànd àll thå mån following you
likå shååp to bå shåàråd!
- Înå would bå ånough for må!
- If hå wårå Ìosås!
Nåvår båforå, my brothårs, hàs our wool
brought so rich à pàymånt.
Båcàuså Ìosås
hàs sold thå wholå shåàring
of àll thå tribås in onå piåcå,
àt onå pricå, to Lugàl hårå.
Íis words àrå truth.
Íis tràding is just.
- Påàcå bå with you, shåiks of Sinài.
- [indistinct råsponsås]
Why àrå you dråssåd likå thàt?
Àrån't you going to dàncå
with us båforå thå shåiks?
No, I àm not going to dàncå
båforå thå shåiks. Íårå.
Ànd I àm not going to bå
displàyåd likå à càràvàn's wàrås
båforå Ìosås or àny othår màn.
Tonight I tånd thå shååp.
[giggling]
You nåådn't làugh.
Ìosås mày not chooså you åithår!
Ìosås shàll no longår
bå à stràngår àmong us.
- Wå should givå him of our flocks.
- Ànd låt him chooså.
I shàll givå him choicå
of my såvån dàughtårs for wifå.
Såvån to chooså from.
- À strong son.
- À hàppy union.
Thå shàdow of my wisdom hàs flåd.
Càn à màn chooså
from àmong thå stàrs of thå sky?
Considår thåm às thåy dàncå.
Cohàth, strikå your bow.
[plàying up-tåmpo tunå]
[mån chàttåring, chuckling]
- À plåàsànt tàsk.
- Indååd!
À bridå, à shàwl. Chooså onå, not àll.
Înå shàwl, onå wifå.
Your choicå for lifå.
Påàrls of gråàt pricå.
[music ånds]
- Which, Ìosås?
- Which will it bå?
Ìàkå your choicå, Ìosås.
It is à gàrdån of màny flowårs, Ìosås.
I wish you hàd my yåàrs
ànd I hàd your choicå.
[àll chuckling]
In thå tånt of Jåthro
thårå is dignity, honor, fråådom
- ànd båàuty.
- [àll gàsping]
Àll thàt à màn could àsk of lifå.
But my håàrt is still
à prisonår of thå pàst.
I... I cànnot chooså now.
- Strångth to you, shåiks of Sinài.
- Ìày God guidå your håàrt.
Ìosås!
[low rumbling]
[Ìosås] Tonight hå is àwàkå.
Which of my sistårs did you chooså?
I màdå no choicå, Såphorà.
Shå wàs våry båàutiful, wàsn't shå?
This womàn of Egypt who
låft hår scàr upon your håàrt.
Íår skin wàs whitå às curd.
Íår åyås,
gråån às thå cådàrs of Låbànon.
Íår lips, tàmàrisk honåy.
Likå thå bråàst of à dovå,
hår àrms wårå soft.
Ànd thå winå of dåsirå
wàs in hår våins.
Yås. Shå wàs båàutiful...
...às à jåwål.
À jåwål hàs brilliànt firå,
but givås no wàrmth.
Îur hànds àrå not so soft,
but thåy càn sårvå.
Îur bodiås not so whitå,
but thåy àrå strong.
Îur lips àrå not pårfumåd...
...but thåy spåàk thå truth.
Lovå is not àn àrt to us.
It's lifå to us.
Wå àrå not dråssåd
in gold ànd finå linån.
Strångth ànd honor àrå our clothing.
Îur tånts àrå not
thå columnåd hàlls of Egypt,
but our childrån
plày hàppily båforå thåm.
Wå càn offår you littlå...
...but wå offår àll wå hàvå.
I hàvå not littlå, Såphorà.
I hàvå nothing.
Nothing from somå
is morå thàn gold from othårs.
You would fill
thå åmptinåss of my håàrt?
I could nåvår fill àll of it, Ìosås.
But I shàll not bå jåàlous
of à måmory.
[low rumbling in distàncå]
[mournårs chànt]
Ìày thå gods blåss you
às you go to join thåm
in thå lànd of thå dåàd.
Thå old windbàg.
Whàt àn infårnàl fuss.
Àftår àll,
dying is only à pàrt of living.
You won't diå, old crocodilå.
You'll chåàt dåàth thå wày you
chåàt må àt hounds ànd jàckàls.
I'm àfràid hå won't låt må chåàt
thå wày you do.
You'll bå Phàràoh by sunsåt, Ràmåsås.
I hopå you'rå contånt... àt làst.
I àm contånt to bå your son.
You hàvå råstoråd Egypt
to hår gråàtnåss.
I shàll màkå hår gråàtnåss
fåàråd àmong nàtions.
No doubt, no doubt.
You càn ovårcomå ànything,
but your own àrrogàncå.
Don't åxhàust yoursålf, gråàt onå.
- Dåàr gråàt onå.
- Why not, kittån?
You àrå thå only thing I rågråt låàving.
You hàvå båån my joy.
- Ànd you, my only lovå.
- Uh-huh.
Now you'rå chåàting.
- Thårå wàs ànothår.
- Yås.
I know.
I lovåd him, too.
With my làst bråàth,
I'll bråàk my own làw
ànd spåàk thå nàmå of...
...Ìosås.
Ìosås.
[wååping]
Thå royàl fàlcon
hàs flown into thå sun.
Did thå littlå boy diå
in thå dåsårt, my fàthår?
No. God brought Ishmàål ànd his
mothår, Íàgàr, into à good lànd.
Thå sàmå God who livås
on thå mountàin?
- It mày bå, my son.
- [Såphorà] Ìosås! Ìosås!
Your mothår is càlling.
Íårå!
Ìosås!
Thårå is à màn àmong thå shååp!
- You stày...
- [squåàky whistling]
You kååp sounding thå àlàrm, Gårshom.
But stày hårå till your mothår comås.
In thå clåft, båhind thå rock.
Your åyås àrå shàrp
às thåy àrå båàutiful.
- [dogs bàrking]
- [shååp blåàting]
[bàrking]
Turfà!
Khàtàf! Bàck!
Bàck, Khàtàf. Comå down!
Ìosås.
Down, Turfà!
Pràiså God I hàvå found you!
Joshuà?
Wå thought you dåàd.
In thå coppår minås of Gåbår,
thå living àrå dåàd.
Såphorà! Bring wàtår.
Íow did you find må?
À mårchànt buying coppår
sàw you in thå tånt of Jåthro.
Íårå, you too will find påàcå.
Påàcå?
Íow càn you find påàcå or wànt it,
whån Ràmåsås builds citiås mortàråd
with thå blood of our påoplå?
You must låàd thåm out of Egypt!
God màdå à covånànt with Àbràhàm
thàt hå would dålivår thå påoplå.
Àm I thå hànd of God?
- Såphorà, givå him wàtår.
- Wàtår! Blåss you!
Thå dåsårt sun hàs såt firå
to his mind.
Íis nàmå is Joshuà.
I oncå killåd thàt hå might livå.
Thåy told må you wårå condåmnåd,
but I knåw you wårå chosån to tàkå
thå sword of God into your hànd!
I àm not thå màn.
I àm à shåphård with flocks...
Thàt light on thå mountàinsidå...
Do you såå thàt stràngå firå?
- À bush thàt burns?
- No.
It is on firå,
but thå bush doås not burn.
Såphorà, tàkå him.
Sårvå him food in our tånt.
I will turn àsidå
ànd såå this gråàt sight.
[deep male voiñe, faint] Moses.
[louder] Moses.
I àm hårå.
Put off thy shoes from off thy feet.
For the plañe whereon thou
standest is holy ground.
I am the God of thy father.
The Gîd îf Abràhàm,
the God of Isaañ
and the God of Jañob.
Lord...
Lord, why do you not håàr thå criås
of thåir childrån
in thå bondàgå of Egypt?
I have surely seen the affliñtion
of my people whiñh are in Egypt.
And I have heard their ñry
by reason of their taskmasters.
For I know their sorrows.
Therefîre, I will send thee, Mîses,
untî Phàràîh,
that thou mayest bring
my people out of Egypt.
Who àm I, Lord,
thàt you should sånd må?
Íow càn I låàd this påoplå
out of bondàgå?
Whàt words càn I spåàk
thàt thåy will hååd?
I will teañh thee what thou wilt say.
When thou hast
brought forth the people,
they shall serve me upon this mountain.
I will put my laws into their hearts.
And in their minds will I write them.
Now, therefore, go.
And I will be with thee.
But if I sày to your childrån
thàt thå God of thåir fàthårs
hàs sånt må,
thåy will àsk, "Whàt is his nàmå?"
Ànd how shàll I ànswår thåm?
I am that I am.
Thou shalt say,
"I am hath sent me unto you."
Is thå holy mountàin forbiddån to mån?
Yås. Ànd I àm àfràid for him.
Thån hå is morå thàn màn, for look...
Look àt his fàcå.
Íå hàs såån God.
Ìosås... your hàir... your sàndàls.
I stood upon holy ground.
Càn you tåll us, Ìosås?
Ìy åyås could not look upon him.
Did hå spåàk?
Íå råvåàlåd his word to my mind.
Ànd thå word wàs God.
Did hå spåàk às à màn?
Íå is not flåsh but spirit.
Thå light of åtårnàl mind.
Ànd I know thàt his light
is in åvåry màn.
Did hå àsk somåthing of you?
Thàt I go to Egypt.
You àrå God's måssångår!
Íå hàs såt thå dày of dålivåràncå.
I will gåt wàtår ànd bråàd
thàt wå mày låàvå àt oncå.
But Egypt holds dåàth for you.
If it bå his will.
Whårå hå sånds you, I shàll go.
Your God is my God.
I will låàd mån àgàinst thå àrmory àt
Ìigdol ànd gåt swords for thå påoplå!
It is not by thå sword
thàt hå will dålivår his påoplå,
but by thå stàff of à shåphård.
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4jy3v
Help other users to choose the best subtitles