Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
I'm looking for Darby Reese.
Does he know you're coming?
No, he doesn't.
Darby.
Someone's mom's here to see you.
Yeah, all right.
All right. Yeah. Who'd you say you are?
Margaret Hall.
He'll be right down.
How about this?
- Mother of Beau.
- Mr Reese.
You're younger than I expected. Please, sit.
I wantyou to stay away from my son.
Does Beau know you're here?
- Where are your sneakers?
- Don't know.
Please find them. You'll catch a cold.
Oh, Jack! I'm sorry.
Margaret, where on earth
is that damned remote?
I don't know. Broken, isn't it?
Didn't Dylan step on it last night?
For the love of Pete.
Try the one in the study. I think it'll work.
- And where is Mr Dylan?
- He's in the driveway.
Dylan.
- Sweetheart, where's your brother?
- In the driveway.
- I mean Beau.
- He took off in the boat.
Mad about something. I don't know.
Been gone a while, kiddo.
- I went to Reno today.
- I know. He called.
I'm going upstairs.
May I come in?
- I need to talk to you.
- You talk to everybody lately.
- Please don't be glib.
- Like I told you, he's my friend. That's all.
Well, he may not be the friend you think he is.
He's just a guy, all right? Just a place.
- You've got to talkto me about the drinking...
- I shouldn't have been driving. I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have been
visiting nightclubs...
- Are we through?
- No!
You could have been killed in that accident.
I know you're having difficulty...
If you're having feelings...
I don't know what it is you think I feel, but
you're blowing this thing out of proportion.
He offered to stay away from you.
- What?
- For money.
He said if I paid him, he'd stay away.
$5,000.
- I don't believe you.
- It's true.
- He said you'd tell me things.
- Beau, stop. Would I lie to you?
- Was Darby with you Friday night?
- Just let it go.
- I don't want you seeing him.
- Do we have to talk about this now?
I don't want you going into Reno. We can
put the music lessons on hold for a while.
Margaret, it's Tom.
Yes. Tom, it's Margaret.
It's good to hear you, too.
Everything's fine. We're all fine.
What?
I can't hear you.
Yeah. Dylan's helping me.
He's making Xs on the calendar.
Don't you disappoint him.
Beau?
Well, hold on a sec. He's right here.
Hi.
I'm fine. Yeah, the same stuff.
Yeah, school, water polo, you know.
No, no. No answers yet.
Wesleyan lost my transcripts.
Yeah.
I'm not playing as much as I'd like,
but I'm enjoying the classes.
No, the drive's been fine.
I miss you, too.
Are you crazy? That's my mother's room.
- It's me.
- Yeah, I can see that.
- You wanna have some fun?
- No!
- Go away. You're gonna wake everyone up.
- Come on!
Just go away. Someone's gonna see you.
Hey, I came all the way from Reno.
- Come on.
- All right.
Quiet. Just be quiet.
I'll be right down. Don't move.
Make a sound,
I'm gonna drown you in the lake.
Come on.
Whatever you say, lover.
Light a match or somethin'.
Yeah. Much better.
I'm sorry about my mother.
I thought I was your little secret.
Imagine my surprise.
She knew I was at the club
Friday night, that's all.
- She doesn't really know...
- She knows, believe me.
- Why are you saying that?
- Poor Beau.
She's a mother, not a moron.
Shut up.
She was bound to find out.
That's the way things work.
I just don't want you
talking to her any more, OK?
- Or to anyone else.
- All right!
No one. I'm serious. It's my business...
Whatever you want, precious.
What did you talk to her about?
What did you say to her?
Nothing. Well, not much.
You gotta relax, beauty.
Why? What did she tell you?
Did she ask you to stay away from me?
- I believe she did.
- And?
And I...
All right, I...
I told her I might be amenable
to a little negotiation.
Friendly to an offer.
Beau...
To stop seeing me.
Of course I was lying. You knowthat.
I know what? Thatyou tried
to steal money from my mother?
- It's only money. Don't take it so personally.
- Get off me.
Look, I need money.
Haven't you noticed? I tend to overindulge.
I said don't touch me.
That hurt, you little fuck.
Hey, come on, come on.
- Look, I'm sorry, all right? I'm sorry.
- Get off my arm.
Beau, Beau...
Jesus. You're not being a very good host.
- Get out. Get outta here.
- Easy, tiger.
- Get the fuck outta here.
- That hurt.
Beau, Beau, come on.
Beau.
Jesus, Beau.
Beau!
Sweetheart, what happened?
Beau?
I thought I was the only one up.
- You're sure I shouldn't go?
- Yes, I'll be right back.
- Problem?
- No, just the wind.
Did I hear Beau earlier?
No, I don't think so.
Why don't you get to bed? It's late.
Margaret? Is thatyou?
- You're up early.
- Trouble sleeping.
- Going for a swim?
- Too cold.
Just a walk. Maybe I'll run a little.
Where have you been?
I lost my mitt. I can't find it.
- It's around. We'll find it.
- Were you out in the boat?
- Is Paige ready to go?
- You been AWOL quite a while, Maggie.
- Did you look under your bed?
- I thoughtyou were out in the boat.
Go look under your bed.
Paige, the Lloyds are here!
- Is Beau up?
- Beau? No, I haven't seen him.
So, you took a spin on the lake?
Paige, slow down, please.
- Hey, hey. Gangplank.
- Honey, the Lloyds are waiting.
- Where were you all morning?
- Mom, I can't find it.
Dylan, please. It's time to go - now.
You'll just have to borrow a glove
from someone. It won't be so bad.
- You can't just borrow a mitt.
- Course you can.
Who's gonna let me borrowtheir mitt?
You'll work it out, Dyl.
People like to share. Go on.
- Running late?
- Yes, sorry. Lost track of the time.
Do you mind picking up?
I have a tennis thing I can't get out of.
- If you can't...
- No, I'll manage. It's not a problem.
Great. Bye-bye.
- What happened last night?
- Wesleyan wants another music sample.
I'm being considered for a grant.
I need $50 for the session.
All right. So what happened last night?
Can you give me a ride?
Cos I'm late for water polo already.
Beau.
What do you want me to say?
Thatyou were right?
Fine. You were right, OK?
- I just wanna know what happened.
- Look, I'm already late.
You're bruised and scraped.
Something happened
and you've got to tell me...
Oh, there you are!
I thought we were gonna
take that skiff out for a spin.
I just got back. Beau needs a ride to school.
Will you be all right for a little while?
I was out on the dock.
I couldn't see you there.
Found this, anyway.
On the beach in the sand, plain as day.
I'm surprised you didn't see it
this morning on your walk.
No. No, I didn't.
What happened to your face?
You're not gonna say anything to Dad?
You know, about last night?
No.
All right. I'll find a ride back. Bye.
I think boy ballerinas just don't look right.
They look so funny.
I perfectly agree with you.
You know, he put on
his tights the wrong way.
I think it's very funny.
Hey, are you sure you're not getting a crush?
You know I was just kidding.
Yeah.
Hey, look!
- What's going on? Did somebody drown?
- Keep movin'.
Yes, I'm trying to get through
to Captain Thomas Hall.
The USS Constellation.
His wife Margaret.
Please don't put me on hold again.
I need to speakto him today. Right now.
I realise they left port. I told you I'm his wife.
Well, no, it's not exactly an emergency.
His wife, Margaret.
All right.
No, no message. Thank you.
He's dead.
Darby's dead. He was killed Monday night.
- That night he was here.
- Beau.
It's in the paper. Look.
- Did he know other people in Tahoe?
- How should I know?
He knew everybody.
The police are saying
someone murdered him.
Did anybody else know he was coming?
Did anybody know you were friends?
Does it matter? Mom, he's dead!
I don't know. Do you think
the police will want to speak with you?
I don't know. I don't know.
Must be a real relief to you though.
- I mean, him being dead.
- Beau, please.
That's gotta have some appeal.
Can't bother you, can't bother me.
- Stop it, for Christ's sake.
- You know, you were right, Mom.
He was a loser. Now it's just in the paper.
Mom! There's a man downstairs.
He wanted to talkto Dad, but I told him...
- Who'd he say he is?
- He didn't.
All right, I'm coming.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah. I came to see Tom Hall.
- He isn't in.
- I can wait. I told that to the girl.
I'm his wife.
- When will he be back?
- He won't be. Not today.
What exactly is ityou want?
I came to talk about
Darby Reese and your son.
Dylan.
I need you to play somewhere else.
- Why?
- I need to speak with this man.
- Promise you won't touch the computer?
- Yes, I promise.
I think you know Darby Reese.
So, you must know he is dead.
Murdered.
Your son's been spending
a lot of time with Mr Reese.
Special time. Sort of intimate.
Forgot my fish book.
Dyl, Dyl. No more interruptions.
You understand?
Sorry.
We know Darby was coming here
Monday night to see Beau.
- The night he was killed.
- "We"?
- Yeah, I have a partner.
- Partner?
- Beau's done nothing wrong.
- Maybe.
- I said he's done nothing wrong.
- So why haven't you gone to the police?
- Why don't they know that your son and...
- Is there a point to this?
We think your son is mixed up
in a murder. That's the point.
I think you should go now.
Have you been listening to me?
- No, I think you should go.
- Will you shut up? What's wrong with you?
You think this is a game? That I've come
to chat, to offer advice? To warn you?
Does it work, your video machine?
- Put this in.
- I...
I said put it in the machine.
It belonged to Darby. He owed us money.
We thought it worthless, but not now.
Now it has value.
Now we are sure it has value.
- So play it.
- It's playing.
Like movies?
- Please shut it off. Please.
- 40 minutes of a budding sexuality.
$50,000 by tomorrow,
or there'll be a copy with the Tahoe police.
Where do you expect me
to get $50,000 in 24 hours?
- That's not our problem.
- And how do I knowthat's the only copy?
You don't. That's the position you are in.
Come up with the money, you own the tape.
You don't want the police involved
any more than they are now.
Margaret! For the love of God, you must
talkto those cleaners about these stains.
Oh, sorry. I didn't realise.
- Jack Hall.
- Alek Spera.
Jack...
Mr Spera has helped Tom with some things.
Spera? From the air station?
Please don't come back here. I'll meetyou
in town. Just not here, not around my family.
All right.
- The post office?
- Yes, OK, that's fine.
OK. Tomorrow, 5 o'clock.
And remember, Mrs Hall, $50,000.
4.  4 o'clock. I have the kids.
OK. 4 o'clock.
Mom.
I'm not going to practise today. I just can't.
Could you call the school and let them know?
I don't wanna talkto anyone. Not now.
Well, my husband is, as I explained to you,
in the navy, he's on a boat,
he's somewhere in the middle
of the North Atlantic.
It's just not possible for me
to get a signature from him.
Well, you cosigned the mortgage,
so you and your husband would both
have to sign on any future encumbrance.
If it isn't possible to reach
your husband by fax, perhaps we...
I need the money tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Hello!
- Here you go.
- Thank you. You're the best.
Yes. I'm sorry. Of course
I'm talking about a current balance.
No, that's 30-155.
Account number
48-74-39-20-11-79-22-91.
No, I'm trying to determine my credit limit.
The available credit, please.
37-83-54-96.
No, no. 330-155...
Jack, I didn't know you... Can you hold on?
Your laundry, Jack.
Damn tweezers. I thought I might
have my lunch early today.
I'll bring it up.
Well, can we do it on the phone,
as an advance?
All right. Goodbye.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- You OK, Beau?
- Can we just start it again?
- Relax, kiddo. They're gonna love ya.
Oh, my God! So ugly.
No, I have to have it immediately. 00...
Today. 197-734...
I just wanna know how quickly
we can have the cash.
H-a-l-I. I'll hold.
Yes. Hall.
No, the cash, not credit.
Please don't transfer me...
Please...
Can you say that again?
Thank you.
Hall. H-a-l-I.
No, I have to have it immediately.
Mine? November 5th 1960.
Margaret.
I can't reach him.
Account number 601...
3163.
I can't get a signature.
No. 0097...
56...
My mailing address is 7087 Lakeshore...
11...
Tahoe City, California.
961...
No, don't bother calling back.
Because we won't need it at Christmas.
Thank you.
Jack! Leave that for Beau.
He'll be home soon.
Oh, don't be silly. It's just a bottle of water.
Well, thanks.
It's good for the back, I think.
Jack, can I talk with you about something?
Surely.
I have a problem.
I need some money.
- I knowthis is awkward.
- Don't be silly. How much?
No. That isn't...
Well?
The thing is...
Well, come on, Maggie. Spit it out.
My back's tightening up.
The thing is I'm not really sure.
Why don't I go and check my purse again?
Here. Take...
Take 80.
And if you need any more, let me know.
All right, Jack.
This is the last one.
Jack, I really don't think you should...
Jack?
Jack!
Jack! Jack!
Can you hear me, Jack?
- Do you wanna see my mom again?
- Yeah, I do.
Come in. Mom!
2, 3, 4
Dylan. Call 911.
Go. Tell them we need an ambulance.
2, 3, 4, 5
Jack!
Use more strength. Press harder.
Do you know howto do this?
Can you do this?
Tilt his head back. One breath when I hit 5
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
1, 2
Mommy, they said they're coming,
5 minutes.
Dylan, I need your help. Can you go upstairs
and get me a pillow? Dylan, please.
5, go!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
Jack... Jack...
Jack, can you hear me? Jack...
Margaret...
Just lie still. Everything's fine.
Everything's fine.
- Mom?
- It's OK, Dylan. Everything's fine.
Mom, are you there? Pick up if you're there.
Where are you?
Well, I'm at Amber's. She needs a ride
to tomorrow night's ballet. I hope that's OK.
And I'm gonna stay here for dinner. OK?
All right. Bye.
Hello?
- Where's my mother?
- She's...
Your grandfather, he had a...
You should call the hospital.
Who are you?
I'm...
I know your father.
I'm a friend of your father's.
And I was...
leaving.
I've been trying your cellphone all day.
Why haven't I heard from you?
I had nothing to say.
Right.
You should've called. Where's the money?
Why?
- I'll go back tomorrow.
- Why tomorrow? Why is tomorrow different?
Because it is. I couldn't get it today.
Of course you could.
You could, but you didn't.
- Look. I want that money.
- Yeah.
And so do you. You do understand?
- I said I'd take care of it.
- All right, fine.
I trust you, Alek, like I trust myself.
You say you're gonna get the money,
you get the money.
But goddamn it, you'd better get
that son-of-a-bitch fuckin' money.
This is a good piece of business
and I'm not gonna walk away from it.
I don't know what the fuck's
goin' on with you.
All right. Tomorrow, Al, right?
I'm trustin' you.
And if you can't carry through, I will.
Yes, Jack Hall. I'm his daughter-in-law.
No, we just came from the hospital.
He said sometime in the next 2 days.
All right. Will someone call?
Please, tonight. Thank you.
Mom!
- Did you talk with the hospital?
- Yes.
- How is he?
- I don't know.
I'll be right back. I have to
speak with someone outside.
- I did mean to come yesterday.
- I waited almost an hour.
- I'm sorry about that.
- You were not coming, Mrs Hall.
- You were here, you saw what happened.
- You were not coming!
- Did you get the money?
- No.
- I'm not sure you understand.
- We don't have the money.
You have to get the money.
Is that not clear enough?
It's $50,000. It is not the kind of thing
that everyone can just go out and get.
- Have you spoken with your husband?
- He can't be reached. He's on a carrier...
This is truly none of your business.
What about the old man?
Well, you have to try harder.
- Try harder?
- I don't think you're really trying.
- Really?
- Yes.
Well, maybe you should explain
"really trying" to me, Mr Spera.
Tell me. How would you be
"really trying" if you were me?
Butyou're not me, are you?
You don't have my petty concerns
to clutter your life and keep you from trying.
You don't have 3 kids to feed,
or... worry about the future
of a 17-year-old boy,
who nearly got himself killed
driving back from some kind of a nightclub
with his 30-year-old friend
sitting drunk in the seat beside him.
No, these are notyour concerns. I see that.
But perhaps you're right, Mr Spera.
Perhaps I could be trying a little harder.
Maybe sometime tomorrow, between
dropping Dylan at baseball practice
and picking up my father-in-law
from the hospital,
I might find a way to try a little harder.
Maybe I should take a page from your book.
Go to the track,
find a card game...
Maybe I should blackmail someone.
Or maybe you have another idea.
I mean, maybe you have a better idea
of how I might try a little harder
to find this $50,000
you have come here to steal from me.
You're right. I'm notyou.
I don't...
This is only a business opportunity.
That's all.
What kind of a heartless man are you?
Do you ever get away
from your family, Mrs Hall?
I'll talk to Nagle about the time.
- Maybe he will listen.
- Mom!
I'm sorry. You don't know
what kind of a man Nagle is.
Please go. Leave my family out of this.
- It's getting late. Paige needs to go.
- Thank you, sweetheart.
- Is everything OK?
- Yes.
- I'll get it.
- Dylan! Mom...
Hall residence. Dylan speaking.
One minute, please. It's for you.
Mr Spiro?
I'll take it upstairs.
OK, Dylan. Hang up, please.
- Why are you calling me here?
- I need to speak with you.
I'm sorry. Please listen.
You only need to raise 25,000.
I told Nagle I won't take my share.
I don't want it now.
If I could make him go away,
stop bothering you, I would.
I wish I could go back, but I can't.
He wants that money and he'll make things
ugly for you if he doesn't get it, I promise.
Do you hear me? It's not so much now.
- Why are you doing this?
- Please just do as I say. Just get the money.
Are you there?
- Do you understand?
- Yes. I think so.
Meet me in Reno tomorrow, 3 o'clock.
- Harrah's, outside.
- All right.
- Can you find it? Harrah's Casino?
- Yes.
Tomorrow. It's not much time, I know.
No.
- If you keep giving it gas, you'll flood it.
- Paige, can you do something?
Where are you going?
- The car, sweetheart. I'm late.
- OK. Pop it.
- Problem?
- It's nothing. My daughter'll fix it.
Make somebody a great husband someday.
- Can I help you?
- Hope so.
Talkin' to the residents about the murder
at Buck's Cove. You heard about that?
- OK, try it, and don't...
- I know.
OK!
Yes, we heard about it.
Seems the victim was killed
with an anchor. Pierced his lungs.
We were thinkin' maybe that anchor could've
come from one of these houses around here.
Well, our dinghy doesn't have an anchor.
We tie it to the dock.
- Always?
- Yes.
All right. Like I said, just checkin'.
If you think of anything, give us a call.
OK.
I'm stumped. What did he want?
- You can't fix it?
- I don't know.
No, I guess not. You probably
clogged the fuel lines.
- You know, Beau's car...
- I'll call a taxi.
- Where are you going, anyway?
- Some errands. I'll be back before dinner.
- Well, how am I supposed to get to ballet?
- Sue's stopping by.
7087 Lakeshore Court.
Tahoe City.
Yes. I'll wait outside. Thank you.
You look nice. What's going on?
Nothing. Just some errands in town.
- You're taking a taxi?
- Yeah, the Jeep won't start.
I could drive you.
No, I'd prefer to be alone.
You sure you wanna hock this stuff?.
- Yes. How much do you think?
- I could go to 8500.
Maybe 8600.
Well, I was hoping
that you could give me more.
8600 is more.
Margaret, stop!
- Where's your car?
- It wouldn't start.
I don't have all the money. I could
only raise 12,000. A little more than 12.
Here. Please say it's enough.
- I need to talk to you. Just for a minute.
- Jack's waiting to be picked up. I'm late.
- I'll drive you back to Tahoe.
- No, thank you.
- Would you help me find a cab?
- I need to talk to you, please.
Things have changed.
The seat belt is above the door.
- The hospital, not the house?
- Yes.
No, thank you.
I took you for a smoker.
They arrested someone for Darby's murder.
- That's impossible.
- It's more than possible.
- Who is it?
- It doesn't matter.
Who is it?
His name is Donnelly. Martin Donnelly.
- He didn't do it.
- Like I said, it doesn't matter.
Nagle's lost the advantage, but he'll make
a deal with you. He'll wanna make a deal.
Donnelly didn't kill Darby.
- What?
- I know that.
- You don't.
- I do.
- How?
- It's not important.
How?
Darby...
Darby came to our house
that night to see Beau.
I had gone to his nightclub earlier in the day.
Beau had been in a car accident.
He'd been drinking with Darby.
You see... My husband...
He won't understand as it is, his son being...
I don't know howto talk to him about it.
He's away at sea so often.
It's not that...
I must sound very silly to you.
I just wanted him to stay away from Beau.
But I failed.
He came to the house that night.
They fought in the boathouse.
I don't know why.
I heard these noises and I came down.
Beau had run back in.
I met Darby on the dock.
We argued. I pushed him
and he fell through the railing.
- You pushed him?
- Yes.
And?
The railing just gave way,
and he fell onto the anchor.
- And I moved the body.
- You?
Yes. In the boat, in the morning.
- Alone?
- Of course alone.
I don't believe you.
I don't care what you believe.
It is what happened.
- And I have to tell them.
- Tell them what?
- That you killed a man?
- Yes.
This is crazy. Whatever happened that night
is over. Done. It can't be undone.
Not undone, but I can put an end to this,
to Nagle's threats, to all of this!
Stop it! Just stop it!
It's too late for that.
Whatever happened, it's too late.
Listen to me. You have
your family to think about.
The life of your family, not Donnelly.
Forget all of this. Forget Donnelly,
forget Nagle and me.
Go home. Put all this behind you
as if it never happened.
Do you hear me, Margaret?
Margaret...
You've reached the Halls. Leave us your name
and number and we'll get back to you.
Thanks for calling.
Hi, it's Mom. I'm running late.
If the hospital calls, just...
Never mind. I'll be home soon.
Hi. I got a call that my grandfather
was waiting to be picked up.
- Name?
- Jack Hall.
My mother was supposed to
come and get him. Is he...?
Great. Thanks.
- Sure you don't wanna keep the wheelchair?
- Don't be ridiculous.
It's bad enough they saddle me with this.
This thing's a wreck.
Can I take your cane? I can put it in the back.
No.
- How will you get home?
- I'll get a taxi.
You know, I never thanked you
for your help with Jack.
I was there, that's all.
His heart had stopped.
It happens.
Nagle. It's Alek.
I don't know. Columbia sent back my tapes,
and Wesleyan just asked for another one.
- What about Annapolis?
- I didn't apply to Annapolis.
Shame. It's a fine school.
Just lie down.
I think he was in 313.
- You already told me that.
- Well, he can't have disappeared.
Take a breath.
He was checked out to a Beau Hall.
It's time to stop this, that's all.
She came up with 12. There is no more.
No. The husband's on a boat somewhere.
It won't happen for him.
We got what we could. Let it go now.
Battleships.
I never liked carriers.
Who was the guy who used to give us
those helicopter rides, in Virginia?
- No one ever gave you helicopter rides.
- Don't you remember? The tall guy?
- That's hogwash.
- I'll be right back.
And no helo rides. Not on my watch.
So explain it to me again. Maybe I'm stupid.
I already told you.
Donnelly will be out by tomorrow,
in which case we have what we had all along.
You got most of what you wanted.
It's over. It's enough.
I don't want "most". I want "all".
Why is it so hard for you to understand that?
I'm warning you, Carlie. Don't be greedy.
It's not your place to warn me.
You should know that. It's not your place!
Jesus. What the hell is she doing
in a taxi in Tahoe?
I asked you to handle this. You did not.
I don't know why, I'm confused.
But I'm gonna do this now.
- Who are you?
- I think you know my partner.
Please go. I can't talkto you, not here.
You'll talkto me.
- What do you want?
- Just the money. I just want the money.
- I gave it to Alek.
- Part. You gave him part. I don't want part.
- He said that Donnelly...
- He didn't kill Darby. It's idiotic.
- The police will know soon enough.
- Just get out of my house.
This is the problem
and I would like to resolve it now.
I'll try and be clear.
I think you've lied to Al.
I think you've put ideas in his head.
I think you have the money.
I think you haven't been altogether
straight forward with us...
if you wanna know the truth.
What kind of a fool do you think I am?
- Would I risk anything if I had the money?
- Maybe.
Where's your husband?
I'd like to talk with him, because
I don't want this going on any longer.
I can't seem to get any kind of
straight answer from you.
Carlie.
Alek, go away.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- I told you not to come here.
- That was not your right.
- You lost control.
- That's not important.
Al, please. Please go. Go away.
- This woman's made a fool of you.
- Think what you want.
A stupid, stupid fool. A weakling.
- You've behaved like a stupid weakling.
- Shut up.
Are you fucking her? Is that what's going on?
Is that it? You're fucking her?
- I said shut up.
- Don't talk to me that way.
Get out of here.
- Don't push this, Al.
- Get out!
Alek.
Alek, I...
Alek...
Be quiet.
Please, I beg you, don't.
I'll go to the police.
I'll tell them about Darby. I'll tell them
you killed Nagle in self-defence.
I'll go to the police, Alek.
I'm sorry.
It shouldn't have come to this.
Alek, Alek...
Alek...
We have no choice now.
Please... You gotta let me tell 'em.
Please.
Listen to me. Go inside.
No one can be near the windows.
Think of something, anything.
Just keep your family away.
Meet me in the driveway. We'll go together.
Take my car keys. In my coat, on the right.
I'll drive Nagle's car. You follow in mine.
Butyou must go inside.
I'll wait in the driveway.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
No.
No...
Mom?
What's going on?
- Your lip! Jesus...
- Beau, I need you to help me.
- Where are you going?
- I can't drive this. The shift...
- I need you to drive the car. Please.
- Mom...
Please. We need to leave now.
Can you help me?
Just... Please, just help me.
It's a grey car. Did you see it in the driveway?
No.
There. Is that it?
He shouldn't have left like that.
He should have waited.
- It's not what you think.
- How do you know what I think?
- He's a friend.
- Yeah.
That's all. He's just a friend.
Did you see that?
Beau, Beau! Please, call for help.
- Alek! Alek!
- You shouldn't have followed me.
- Jesus! Jesus!
- Why did you follow me?
You didn't wait. Why didn'tyou wait?
I lost control of the car, Margaret. My arm.
Margaret, stop. Stop!
Margaret, stop.
Stop!
- I'm gonna get you out of here.
- No, no!
Just leave.
- Someone will come.
- Oh, Alek.
They'll think he died here in the crash.
- Please go.
- I can't leave you.
Butyou must.
They can't find you here. Think!
Please, no.
Margaret, the tape and the money.
Look for them.
They were on the seat. Can you see them?
Get them out.
- I can't see where...
- Just try.
- Now go.
- No, Alek.
I can't.
Please go.
I'm sorry, Margaret.
I'm sorry for all of this.
Margaret...
Yes?
I think...
I'm not...
Alek...
Mom?
Do you want me to call somebody?
No.
Can you just be here with me?
All right.
I'm here.
I don't know how...
I don't know what to say.
So don't.
I don't need to know.
It's not important.
I love you, Beau.
Yeah.
Me, too.
Mom, it's Dad. Can you pick up?
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/4yr9s
Help other users to choose the best subtitles