Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
~~
[Female Singer]
~ Whoa, love ~
~Is a burnin'thing ~
~And it makes ~
~ The fiery ring ~
~Now my wild desire ~
~I fell into
a ring of fire ~
a burning ring of fire ~
~I went down, down, down
and the flames went higher ~
~Burn, Burn ~
[Birds Chirping]
[Man] I bet you've been
gettin'a lot of, uh...
Churchills, probably Mandela.
Some de Gaulles.
I'd have to go with, uh...
Anwar Sadat.
Anwar Sadat?
- The former Egyptian president.
- Right.
No, no. Two years at the paper,
I never heard that one.
I'd have to say Sadat.
Talk about standing up to
political and popular pressure.
I'd like to think
that I had those kind of balls.
There's a guy who did not die
in vain. He died for peace.
Any ideas you'd die for,
Governor?
Obviously I'd die
for this country.
- I served, you know,
not in Vietnam but Desert Storm.
- Right. The Bronze Star.
There wasn't a lot of shit
to get into there, but I was in it.
What I meant was,
would you take a bullet...
to advance abortion rights, flat taxes,
things you've been behind for years?
I'd like to think
that I'd die for civil rights.
- [Tires Screeching]
- Jesus!
Jesus Christ! What the...
Governor! Governor!
Governor Hathaway!
Christ! What the...
Governor! Governor! Jesus!
~~[Garbled Music]
~Ring of fire ~
Yes! No... A car...
[Stammering]
I'm under a br...
~~[Garbled Music Continues]
~I fell into
a ring of fire ~
a burnin'ring of fire ~
~I went down, down, down
and the flames went higher ~~
Somebody's obviously in the car.
The governor is in the water.
Yes, Governor Hathaway
is in the water.
You gotta send
somebody out...
No, no, I want to see the car
come out of the water.
- Back it up.
- Rewind!
[Indistinct Chatter]
- You okay?
- I don't know about this, Fiona.
Governor, excuse me.
Bottom line. You put your ass on the
line out there. This guy from the Post...
Paul Smith is his name.
He's describing what you did as if
you should get the Medal of Honor.
That isn't the reality, is it? She died.
In the end, that's the reality.
There's one reality here,
Governor.
The people have given you
Reagan-like approval numbers.
- Last week were in the 50s,
today you were at 82.
- Look at it this way.
That girl died.
That's a tragedy.
But you did everything
you could possibly do to save her.
They couldn't save the Alamo, either,
but everyone who died there's a hero.
- We're at a commercial.
You're almost up, okay?
- Okay.
Show your remorse,
but don't be broken.
You're a national leader now.
Think that way.
- Is Bert on our side?
- Absolutely.
- Three, two, one.
- This is it.
[Fiona] After this,
everything will be on our side.
He has long been considered
at the top of President Evans's list...
to fill the vacancy left by the death
of the vice president three weeks ago.
But after the heroics that have become
the stuff of national legend...
Governor Hathaway has become
the nation's choice...
to take on the post of
the heir-apparent to the presidency.
- Governor, thank you for joining us.
- Thank you, Bert.
That's a nasty bit of business,
what happened on that river. Nasty.
It's a damn shame you were
the unlucky bastard in that spot.
Six and a half years in the White House,
press still hasn't gotten wind
of these bastards.
Yeah, pretty, uh...
pretty heroic,
what you tried.
Just like everybody's
been saying, very, uh...
- Pure Audie Murphy.
- Thank you, sir. I only wish...
If it was me, I don't know if
I would've dove in there.
Might have.
But honestly, I don't know.
[Sighs]
Well...
At least for once, the press
is turning one of us into a hero.
What was it like?
It was...
It was cold.
Oh, sure, this time of year. You were
risking your life saving that woman.
- The cold alone could've
snapped you like a twig.
- It was dark under the water.
The headlights were on.
So were the interior lights.
I could see her face.
She was very pretty. Young.
-She was terrified.
- Wow.
It was like
she was being buried alive.
She looked at me.
And then she had
this look of helplessness.
l, I tried to pull
at the door, but, uh...
I needed air, you know?
I couldn't...
No. By the time I got back down
to the car, she was dead.
Her face was frozen in that look.
She carried that look of terror...
right into her death.
You did more
than most men would.
I wonder.
Look, Jack, it's just not gonna happen.
I can't nominate you.
I can't put you up.
We can't have
another Chappaquiddick.
- I tried to save her.
Kennedy ran away, remember?
- You failed.
Nobody's saying
it was your fault, but you failed.
[Evans]
It's a bad beef, Jack.
You're one of the leaders
of this party, a rising star...
but you've got
a Republican-heavyJudiciary.
They're not gonna give
a rat's ass about that.
They're not gonna care
about your years of service
or what you've done for education.
This would be it.
A girl died and...
- This administration needs
a smooth confirmation.
- You let it happen.
We had a rocky time
over the crime bill.
Can't have any more obstacles
put in front of us.
Well, I appreciate you
telling me personally, Mr. President.
I'll, uh...
I'll support
whoever you select, of course.
I know that.
You're the future
of the Democratic Party...
and you always will be.
Well, there's a boatload
of press out there.
I don't think
you should avoid them.
Take it easy, Jack.
I don't understand this, Kermit.
Six years ago I was the best man for
the job, and I'm still the right guy.
- I have a great relationship
with Runyon...
- Listen to me.
- Isn't there something
we can do about this?
- Believe me, I've tried.
He's made up his mind. Filling this slot
may well be his swan song.
Wants to be careful with it.
Let's not push it.
Why not keep
in his good graces?
You're a good man, Jack.
Want to see the governor out?
- Jerry, you want to come in?
- Yes, sir.
Mr. President,
Jerry's here.
That was as rough as it comes.
Never seen anybody look so defeated.
- Yeah, poor son of a bitch.
- Mr. President?
Saw the governor out there. Looks like
he had the shit kicked out of him.
If I have any more caffeine,
I'll be voting for the flat tax.
I got this tea
from the Greek ambassador.
Go on, sit. Never thought of Greece
as a tea-producing country...
but, Jesus Christ,
if this isn't the tea to end all teas.
Well, looks likeJack Hathaway's
had a shitty week.
So Hathaway, he's out?
That's solid?
That leaves us
with Malloy or Hanson.
It's gotta be Hanson.
Malloy's out.
- Now, Mr. President, I think you know...
- It's Hanson.
You know how I feel. Hanson
may have turncoated our way,
but a turncoat's a turncoat.
We've had a vacancy for three weeks. The
nation's moved from mourning to anxiety.
I need a vice president. And I need a
person who's gonna reflect my politics.
- Fill it with Frank Malloy.
- No, no. Malloy's got
an inflammation of ambition.
He won't be doing his job.
He'll be preparing to do mine.
He's not even my second choice.
If it doesn't work with Hanson,
we're gonna go back to Hathaway.
- Do you think Hanson's a team player?
- Senator Hanson is gonna work.
And it's the job of you two to make sure
that confirmation gets through.
- I need to know I can count on you.
- Of course you can.
The president and I discussed several
issues, including the vice presidency.
-[Man] Did the president
offer you the position?
- I asked him to withdraw my name.
-[Phone Ringing]
-[Woman Moaning]
Don't answer it, please.
-[Ringing Continues]
-[Man] I gotta get it.
It's the red line.
[Woman]
No, no, no, no.
- Hanson here.
-[Giggling]
Yeah, of course I'll hold.
Shh. Quiet.
Hello, sir!
I'm great, sir, thank you. Yes.
-As a matter of fact,
we're watching him on C-SPAN now.
- No names were discussed.
Yes, she is.
One second, sir.
It's the president.
He wants to talk to you.
You wanna speak to him?
Hello, sir.
This is Senator Hanson speaking.
Oh, Christ.
That's what the prick said to you?
"We can't have another Chappaquiddick."
No, not Evans. Newman said
the thing about Chappaquiddick.
What the fuck
is that supposed to mean?
That doesn't even make
any sense, Jack.
You weren't some drunk
who drove your car...
off a bridge and abandoned the whore
you were fucking to die.
That's what I told them.
Not in those words.
This is the second time
they fucked us over.
- Did he say who he was going with?
- No.
- It's gonna be Malloy.
Fucking Frank Malloy.
- That's what I'm hearing.
Jack, he isn't worthy of...
- This isn't happening to me.
- You can go.
You're gonna take it up the ass.
Want to bend over and make
their job a little easier?
You understand
what's going on here?
This is it.
The whole fucking plan, Jack,
everything, was to get to this point.
We have one shot at this,
and it's gone!
And you're gonna mope around
like some 12-year-old girl
who can't get a date to the dance?
"Frank Malloy,
that's what I'm hearing."
- What would you like me to do?
- I'd like you to give a shit.
I'd like you to call Shelly Runyon back
and get this fucking thing fixed!
- Why not?
- You've already gone over it.
It's done, ancient history.
I don't feel reconciled
about it yet.
[Indistinct Chattering]
- I'll think about it.
- No, I think it's fine.
Okay, I'm not convinced.
Thanks.
You sure you want
to have alcohol on your breath
the first time you meet the president?
- No, you're right.
- No offense. Just wondering.
I'm married
to the vice president, huh?
Whoa, whoa.
I haven't been confirmed yet.
I haven't even been asked yet.
You know what we gotta do pronto?
We gotta start working Runyon.
- Runyon's gonna be a problem.
- Why is Runyon gonna be a problem?
- 'Cause he's head ofJudiciary.
- But the Senate takes care...
Everything but the vice president.
Twenty-fifth amendment
doesn't specify...
who runs the show
on that confirmation.
Rumor has it that the House
has advise and consent on this one.
- Runyon lobbied just hard enough
to get his committee the gig.
- Yeah, I think he did.
I know his number-two guy, Ted Baker.
We went to college together.
I'll phone him.
- I'll start pummeling him.
- No, no, no.
Don't say anything to him yet.
- Why?
- Let's get it on our own merit for now.
You know what?
I'm not gonna argue with you.
Not only are you right,
but you're about to meet the president,
and you look great.
- Doesn't she look great?
- Yeah, she looks great.
What do you think, Stevenson?
I'd go for the number six,
slightly right of center, sir.
That's what I was thinking.
[Evans]
How's your average?
- One forty-five last time out, sir.
- That's not bad.
No!
That's what I get
for my leftist tendencies.
- Senator Hanson
and her husband are here.
- Bring 'em in.
Yes, sir.
- I'm gonna need some time
with the senator.
- Yes, sir.
- Senator!
- Mr. President.
- You remember my husband.
- Will Hanson. The McMahon campaign.
We tried to steal your husband away.
He runs a hell of a campaign.
You gave me nightmare visions
of having to return to my law practice.
- Hi. Jackson Evans.
- Lewis Hollis.
- What was the first name?
- Hollis.
- No, Lewis is my first name.
- Lewis. Welcome, Lewis.
So, have you guys
been down here before?
- [Together] No.
-Johnson, he, uh...
built it in '65.
Right now some terrorist camp in Libya
is being spared a bombing raid...
because I'm obsessed
with beating my 150 average.
- You guys bowl?
- Once in a while.
What's your average?
- Seventy.
- I don't have one.
Hungry? You want some lunch
before we speak?
No, thank you, sir.
[Evans] I saw this movie once
where the president...
is just tickled that anything he wants
to eat he can get in a moment's notice.
Here. Turns out, it's the perk
of the century.
- Otto?
- Yes, Mr. President?
Sorry for the late notice. For lunch,
could you arrange coq au vin...
with a side of penne?
-[Otto] Spicy or mild?
- Spicy.
And, uh... Oh...
- Hazelnut pudding for dessert.
- No problem, sir.
One day I'll catch him napping.
- Anyway, how much
did we win that one by?
- 61 to 33, sir.
It's pretty easy
getting over things when you win.
I guess Sudan is where the press
will make its first hay.
I think if we announce,
the press might have
other things on its mind.
But you know,
Sheldon Runyon and Jack Hathaway
have been friends for years.
And Runyon is going to come after me
with all guns blazing.
Senator, why do we have to worry
about Shelly Runyon's guns
when I control the atomic bomb?
We'll introduce you
to the Cabinet in one hour.
I'll make the announcement then.
- That's fine, Mr. President.
- That's the wayJerry Ford
did it with Rockefeller.
I always thought it was pretty damn
classy. Have we notified the networks?
Oh, yes. All the pundits
are in a guessing feeding frenzy.
Box of Malomars says
they've already anointed Malloy.
- You look great, by the way. Just great.
- Thank you, sir.
Okay, guys, one hour,
the Cabinet Room.
Off to the races!
- Senator, is this
what you're gonna wear?
- She looks fine.
- No, she does.
- You look beautiful, Senator.
- Thank you.
- Very becoming.
I think it works.
Let me explain
how this is gonna work.
In a minute, POTUS is gonna come in,
make an announcement...
- Introduce you
to the vice presidential designate.
-Jerry.
We hear the president's decision
is Malloy. Can you confirm this?
In ten seconds you're gonna have
your answer. So calm down.
All right. Then after he's made...
Dave. [Whispers]
I'm gonna give you guys
20 minutes for questions and answers.
So keep them short
and, hopefully, sweet.
And you can roll starting now.
I'll introduce him
in five... thousand...
four... thousand,
three... thousand, two.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the president of the United States.
Welcome. Good afternoon.
Please.
- Thank you for coming here
on such short notice.
- Laine Hanson, from Ohio.
As I embarked on the task
of selecting a vice president...
I was driven by the emotion
of wanting to make a choice...
that would've made Troy Ellard,
my friend, proud.
Senator Laine Billings Hanson
of Ohio is that person.
[Toliver]
Sherri, you are first.
Ms. Hanson, do you feel being
a woman played any type of role
in the president's decision?
Well, l, uh...
First I would like to say...
what an honor it is to be here
before you in this position.
And I hope to serve up to the
standards which President Evans
set for me in that introduction.
Thank you so much, sir.
To answer your question...
- First rate, Mrs. Hanson.
- Thank you. I learned
a lot from Will.
Ah, yes, Will.
You, sir, are gonna have
to make yourself scarce.
- No, of course.
I'll give you your privacy.
- No, I mean scarce.
During the confirmation period,
I want you out of sight.
- Pardon me?
-A wife there behind her husband...
is perceived as supportive.
A husband following around behind
his wife is perceived as a puppeteer.
- But I think...
- No, honey. I think
Mr. Newman's right on.
Let Hollis handle
the day-to-day...
- And I'll be the man behind the curtain.
- Where do we go from here?
The FBI's gonna have to do
an extensive background check.
- Director Friend
will handle the investigation.
- Yes, we made sure of that.
Just about every aspect of your life
will be uncovered.
Your bank accounts,
your medical reports.
- What am I forgetting?
- Correspondence to
government agencies, speeches...
When Nelson Rockefeller was confirmed,
they had over 300 agents working on him.
They had a lot more life
and cash to investigate, huh?
We'll do our own background
check in case anything falls
through the cracks, to be safe.
- At the same time,
the House will... Come in.
-[Knocking At Door]
The House will put together
its bipartisan subcommittee...
of theJudiciary to interview you and
advise and consent to your nomination.
Shelly Runyon's
running the show there.
Cheyenne, Wyoming, you're on with
Vice President Designate Laine Hanson.
- [Man] Larry, how are you?
- I'm fine. Thanks for calling.
I just wanted to say
to the senator that...
all of Cheyenne is with her.
We think she's absolutely great for
the country and this administration.
- Congratulations.
- [King] What's the question, sir?
I wanted to ask the senator, if she
could pick one person from history...
to serve as her model for how to behave
in office, who would that be?
-[Knock At Door]
-[King] Good question, Senator.
Hey, guys.
Nice to see you.
-Sorry to barge in on you.
- No, no, no, no.
I'm just watching your girl.
- First female prime ministers?
- They were great leaders.
Would you put Thatcher
in that category?
No, I don't think so.
- You know what? I would
have to say Thomas Jefferson.
- [King] A man?
-She's something, isn't she?
- I don't really know her.
We served together
a few years ago, and, I guess...
we just ended up
in different company.
- Take a seat.
- Congressman, the president
asked us to come down here.
He'd like to let you know
he'd appreciate your support
in the senator's confirmation.
- Really?
- He asked me directly, Shell.
But the president didn't consider it
important enough to ask me personally?
You know it's important.
It's the old man's swan song.
Putting a woman in office
means something to him.
Laine Hanson's
the absolute best choice.
You don't believe that.
Come on. You're too smart.
Look, I don't mind
she's a woman...
but I'm not confirming a woman
just because she's a woman.
Laine Hanson
has an extra burden.
She's has to come on the world stage
with perfect credentials.
Margaret Thatcher didn't have perfect
credentials. The world respected her.
The world accepted Margaret Thatcher
because they knew she had to answer
to Ronald Reagan.
A woman better be pretty damn qualified
to have nobody to answer to...
and Laine Hanson
is not that.
Look me in the eyes
and tell me...
that Laine Hanson is your first choice
for the vice presidency.
Laine Hanson
is my absolute first choice.
I'd so want you
in my poker game.
Country needs
a smooth confirmation.
The president needs
- The country needs
a competent vice president.
-[Cell Phone Ringing]
Excuse me a minute.
There's only one person in the world
that has that phone number.
So who's the second choice?
We haven't really settled
on anybody yet.
Tell me, if Laine Hanson were
to be hit by a flying car...
who would the president
then select?
[Sighs]
I think the president
still likes Jack Hathaway, Congressman.
You know...
Jack Hathaway, there's a good man...
for a Democrat.
[Laughs] There's a man
I would say would have...
a smooth confirmation.
- Jack Hathaway?
- Smooth as a baby's ass.
- He's already taken himself
out of it, so...
- Right.
Right!
Well, who the hell knows?
Perhaps Lainey
will shock the world...
by pulling out
her brilliance...
and erudition at the hearings
that none of us know she has.
So, Shelly, can we ask
for basic fairness?
- Fifty-fifty, Democrat and
Republican at the hearings?
- Of course you can.
Congressman! Congressman!
Mr. Runyon.
Just wanted to steal you
for a second. I'm Reg Webster.
- Oh, you're one of Stoney's boys?
- Uh, no.
You staff or intern?
Actually I'm a representative.
Reginald Webster of Delaware.
Oh, fuck me. I'm sorry, Webster.
What can I do for you?
- I'm running late.
- I was hoping I could grab
your attention for a second.
- What's the skinny?
- Well, uh...
- I'm late, Mr. Webster.
- I understand a chair's
opened up in the committee...
and I'd like
to put my name forward.
I believe you'll find me
industrious and hardworking.
TheJudiciary's
for senior members.
Wheeling was in for five terms
before we let him in.
My hands are tied.
There's nothing I can do.
Shelly, I've been trying
to reach you for five days.
- I left you 3 2 messages.
- Well, leave me a 33rd.
- Where you from?
- Delaware.
Oh, yeah, you were...
You knocked Emory Bettis out.
Emory used to be
in the Thursday night game.
He was always good
for a few hundred bucks.
I guess he ran his campaign
like he played poker.
I take it you have
a predisposition.
- About the confirmation, I mean.
- No. Actually, I'm 100% objective.
- Mmm. Do you have
a dictionary, Mr. Webster?
- Yeah.
Take a Magic Marker,
cross out the word "objectivity."
Your constituents want you
for your opinions, your philosophy...
for your subjectivity.
Laver has to duck
out of the way of that one.
One that Laver can't get.
He's still trying to recover.
And he zings another
powerful forehand past Laver.
See that, Tim-Tim?
Know what we call that?
- We call that topspin.
You know how we get topspin?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah? Tell me.
- 'Cause BabyJesus made topspin.
What?
- BabyJesus gave it topspin.
- Jesus?
Ah! Why do you say that?
- Because BabyJesus made everything.
- Yeah? Who told you that?
Miss Moyer in kindergarten,
and Mommy says...
- I have to listen Miss Moyer.
- Wow, this is news to me.
I gave up my career
trying to strike that nonsense
out of the public school system.
Maybe I ought to put him
in public school, then.
Remember what I told you
about moving your grip down...
- And to the left?
- Uh-huh.
- Go see if Dad's found
his bathing suit yet.
- Gimme a hug.
Yeah. Thanks, champ.
- They are paid to teach, not...
- To preach.
I know, but he's six years old, and he
also believes in the tooth fairy...
- And that George Washington
never told a lie.
- Well, it drives me crazy.
- Mary, wanna turn the ball machine off?
- Yes, Mr. Governor.
Thanks for seeing me, Dad.
- Why wouldn't I see you?
- Partisanship.
I gotta love
at least one Democrat.
You know, Dad, I'm getting some reports
that you might not be ready to back me.
That you're opposed
to my confirmation...
- You've heard quotes?
- No, I haven't heard.
Just that we should expect
to be reading of your opposition.
Pardon my Swahili, but you're being led
a line of pure bullshit.
- I haven't said a word.
- Maybe it's just that.
Maybe you've been quiet.
- I hate the press.
- I know, Dad.
- When I left the mansion,
I swore I would never talk to them.
- I remember.
- I suppose you're gonna force
my hand on this, huh?
- You wouldn't have to say much.
- Just a little something.
- Okay, okay.
l, uh...
I'll call back
Joe Glynn at the Times.
He's okay.
He'll write it up well.
I once leaked him
some shit about Buchanan.
Damn near won him the Pulitzer.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Sure.
Thanks.
What would you do,
or have done, in my case?
Well, when your president
asks you to jump...
it's hard not to jump,
that's for sure.
But you remember what Ben Franklin
said about the vice presidency.
What did he say?
I didn't talk to him this week.
He said he ought to be addressed as
"Your Superfluous Excellency."
In the past ten years,
I've enjoyed the kind of power
the vice presidency can't offer.
Why would anybody want
to give that up? Am I crazy?
Baby, power is
where power goes.
- Think you can beat me?
- Uh, yeah. Okay.
Hey, Tony!
Foul!
Can't trust
those fuckin' people.
Speaking of which, Mr. Webster,
it turns out you're a Democrat.
l, uh, wasn't keeping it
a secret.
Sad to say, I don't think I can
bring you aboard the committee, son.
Ray Spies makes all the decisions
regarding the other party.
- It's a courtesy.
- But not a requirement.
- It's not, that's true.
- If Ray Spies interviewed me...
he'd refuse to put me
on the committee even for a minute...
because he'd find out that
when it comes to Laine Hanson...
I went to my dictionary
and crossed off the word "objectivity."
Are you suggesting Mrs. Hanson may not
be your first choice for vice president?
I'm suggesting that Laine Hanson
has stricken our party
with policies and attitudes...
that are best served
across the aisle from where she came.
I take it, like most
members of your party...
your selection would be
Governor Hathaway.
Governor Hathaway's a great man.
He's a visionary,
a bona fide hero.
- But he withdrew his name
from consideration.
- Minds can be changed.
- How much discretion
can I count on from you?
- A hundred percent, sir.
- Even from your own leadership?
- I said a hundred percent.
Good. Good man.
Good man.
I think if I make the rounds,
do the Sunday morning talk shows...
raise the level of the game a bit,
outtalk her on the issues...
Issues? What kind of fucking campaigns
are they running in Virginia?
Not the kind I'm used to.
Jack, this whole thing
with the girl drowning...
It's bullshit!
- I was there, Shelly.
The president told me himself.
- It's an excuse.
Jackson Evans has chosen to make
putting a woman in office his swan song.
Laine Hanson is the only
reasonable choice in your party.
He's not going with Boxer.
She's too liberal.
He's not going with Jones
because she's older than he is.
- There's Winslet.
- She's not coming off
the Supreme Court.
Laine Hanson is attractive.
She's a looker.
The mere fact that she was
a Republican means that she
can't be too far to the left.
It's a perfect pedigree.
We can't get you in by convincing him
you're the right man for the job.
We have to convince him that
she's wrong. Once we do that, you're in.
And Toliver,
he's as much as told me...
I'm not going for a low blow.
It's not my way.
You won't have to.
We have to go after her. We have
to make her wade in her own blood.
- Who did you say you were?
- I'm Makerowitz.
- Makerowitz.
- I'm sorry. That doesn't
mean much to me.
- Web got somebody...
- A friend of the Hathaway campaign.
Who is footing the not-too-unimpressive
bill of Mr. Makerowitz.
Private citizen wants to do
their own investigation...
What exactly are you trying to find out?
Campaign irregularities, bribes?
- Isn't that the FBI's responsibility?
- Yes, it is.
But the FBI would not
find anything. All of her money
is tied up in blind trusts.
The kind of improprieties
you're talking about,
I think that only helps her.
Personally, I think the nation
would be relieved to know that
just because she's a woman...
-it doesn't mean she can't be
as ruthless as the rest of us.
- Governor?
You ever stabbed a man
in the navel? You?
Me? No, I haven't.
Stab a man in the navel,
and that's all she wrote.
Bleeding is so swift and severe,
it wouldn't matter ifJesus put
His healing hand on the wound...
the bastard is dead.
We have to gut the bitch
in the belly.
We all have to understand,
we're going to obliterate her life...
but it will get you
the vice presidency.
- Hey, Dog!
- Lewis, how you doin'?
- Wow, that's a plate of food!
- [Laughs]
You didn't have
to dress up for me.
I had to accompany the senator
to the Gridiron Lunch.
lfJohn Q. Public could see
the money that the knuckleheads
that run this country...
spend on these lunches,
there would be a second revolution.
I'm telling you, there is some money
spent on these stupid lunches.
- What is this?
- It's the reason you're here.
You can't let anybody know
where you got this from.
If Runyon found out
I gave this to you...
he'd fire me,
and I don't want him as an enemy.
That's Lainey Hanson
getting gang-banged.
Looks like something
out of Hustler.
[Sighs]
That's her for sure.
I know it's hard to tell with her...
her face in someone's crotch...
but that's her, man.
Why are you showing me this?
I will not be party
to an ambush.
Why are you
showing me this, Ted?
Okay.
I want out of Runyon's office.
And I thought maybe you could
get me on staff...
This is the best you could
come up with? This shit?
This is shit.
Read the deposition
of the LaVamere lady.
[Woman's Voice]
She was putting on a sex show.
- How long did this go on for?
- It was hours.
- How many hours?
- Three or four.
[Man]
Which one? Three or four?
[Woman]
Three, I guess.
In her defense,
she was drunk.
To be honest, once she finished fucking
and sucking those two assholes...
she was carried into another room, and
boys were going in and out of there...
but I don't know
if she was fucking them.
When she came out,
she was covered in cum. It was awful.
Excuse me, Counselor.
l, um...
- May I?
- Of course.
Just to clarify, why exactly
was Mrs. Laine Hanson...
Strike that.
Laine Billings involved in this, uh...
appalling and disgusting behavior?
- That's... That's what's important.
- Exactly.
Thank you.
It's great to see you guys.
- [Applauding, Cheering]
- There you go.
Thank you so much
for your support. Thank you.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hey, Madam Senator.
- How you doing?
- I'm okay.
I wish you'd heard the speech.
That line you gave me about...
"If we can put a man
on the moon, then why can't we
put all men on the moon?"
It was perfect.
It really broke the ice.
- Great audience for that, huh?
- Yeah, it was great.
- [Sighs]
- What's goin' on?
Uh...
well, it looks like Runyon
or somebody close to him...
has been running
a little private investigation...
Iooking for stuff that the Feds
wouldn't even touch.
- It's, um...
- Yeah?
What is it?
What...
[Phone Ringing]
- He doesn't know anything about it.
- You're asking me to step down?
I'm asking you to do what's in
the best interest of the party...
and this president.
Well, I'm sorry.
I can't do it, not over this.
He's not going to allow me
or himself...
to get shot down over what would've
been a private sexual encounter.
- Some swan song for the old man, huh?
- It's fuckin' awful.
The senator got a little wild
when she was 19. What is the big deal?
Let me explain
the big deal to you.
The people of this nation
can stomach quite a bit.
But one thing they can't stomach
is the image of a vice president
with a mouthful of cock.
You don't have to use... Look.
Let's use the word "alleged. "
They got photos! They got witnesses!
They got the "alleged" slut...
Hey! Let me tell you something.
I'm her husband first.
I don't tolerate talk like that.
- Will, calm down.
- You better get used to it, Will.
Especially when not even your wife
will defend herself.
Give me something, Laine.
Anything.
Hell, just deny it.
Why don't you just deny it?
It is simply
beneath my dignity.
Dignity! Right.
We'll just have to make this all
not worthwhile for Mr. Runyon.
What have you got on the
distinguished gentleman from Illinois?
Some pretty good stuff.
- S.E.C. investigation, 1985.
- You got stocks?
I want something embarrassing!
Something sexual!
Little boys, midgets,
that sort of thing.
- Cows! I don't give a goddamn!
- Come on, Kermit.
If we do that,
we're no better than he is.
We are no better than he is.
There's nothing there.
He got married when he was 2 1.
There's no evidence
he ever cheated on his wife.
Too bad we're not running in France.
We could really nail him on that one.
When do you have
your lunch with him?
With Shelly Runyon?
I'm not having lunch with him.
Friday, 1:00.
It's scheduled tomorrow.
It's automatic.
He's committee chairman.
It was set up. S.O.P.
- Laine.
- Shelly.
I'm sorry I started.
You were late.
- I'm not too late, I hope.
- A minute or two.
- Were you tied up with anything?
- No, sorry. I'm just late.
- Hi, Clem. You too.
- Senator, nice to see you.
- I ordered you the porterhouse.
- No, I don't eat meat.
- I'll have the penne.
- You should really... Mmm.
- Try the steak. Ask Hugo
to burn it on the outside.
- No, thank you.
I really don't eat meat.
I'll just go ahead with the penne.
- Spicy?
- Yes, please. Thanks.
So, how are...
Will and the boy?
Let's forego
the small talk today, Shelly.
- It'll make me feel cheap.
- Let the big talk begin.
Have you seen this?
That's my... That's my file
on you, Senator.
- Mm-hmm.
- How did you get it?
Have you read it yet?
How did you get it?
Have you read it?
- What do you have to say for yourself?
- With all due respect...
um, Senator...
- It doesn't matter what
I have to say for myself.
- Oh, it doesn't?
It seems to me, Mr. Chairman,
all you can claim about me...
claim,  is that I had sex...
- Deviant sex.
- Who says it was deviant?
I do.
And what I say, the people will believe.
And you know why?
Because I'll have a very big microphone
in front of me.
Wow, you must
really hate me, Shelly.
I don't hate you.
It's not possible to hate you. You're...
What the hell was it that Reynolds
called you the other day?
Groovy.
You're a groovy chick.
No, what l, um, do detest
is your selfishness.
I have served this nation
without regard for personal
income for over ten years.
You are selfish because you want to take
on a job that positions you to assume...
a mantle of gigantic
responsibility...
and you do it full well
with the knowledge...
Of what?
What?
Greatness is
the orphan of urgency, Laine.
Greatness only emerges
when we need it most...
in times of war
or calamity.
I can't ask somebody
to be a Kennedy or a Lincoln.
They were men
created by their times.
What I can ask for
is the promise of greatness.
And that, Madam Senator...
you don't have.
Well, then...
I just wouldn't be using sex
as leverage...
if I were you, Sheldon.
Because there's one thing
you don't want.
It's a woman with her finger
on the button who isn't getting laid.
Will that be the argument the senator
offers up before the committee?
[Laughing]
Sir? Can I get you
something to drink?
- Uh, no, I'm fine. Thank you.
- You sure?
No, great.
Thanks a lot.
- Ah, Mr. Webster.
- Mr. President.
- Good to see you.
- It's an honor, sir.
- I've been meaning to have you
up here for some time.
- Really?
Excuse me. Willie?
Thank you, Willie.
Yeah, you betcha. You unseated
that old bastard Bettis.
He must've voted against me
70 percent of the time.
You know what this is?
That's a shark steak sandwich.
Fucking shark steak.
- You want half?
- Uh, no, thank you.
- Are you a vegan? Had lunch?
- No. Uh...
So you choose not to break bread with
the president of the United States?
[Laughs]
Thank you.
When I was in the Senate, Bettis
could always be counted to leave
half a grand at the poker table.
Always stayed in, never folded.
Always wanted that miracle card.
- That's good, isn't it?
- Mm-hmm.
Now, Truman,
he was a poker player.
Damn fine one,
as I understand it.
Son, I understand you may be
making a mess of our plans...
to put Laine Hanson
into the vice president mansion.
Right now, sir, I cannot see
supporting Laine Hanson.
- How old are you?
- Me, I'm 28.
And at that age and experience,
you think you're the one
to sit and judge Mrs. Hanson?
Well, that's the whole point,
isn't it?
I am, sir.
Mr. Webster,
I'm asking you to lay off...
as a personal favor.
It's one thing to break ranks
and vote against my candidate...
but to actively attack her
from the bench, that's another.
Mr. President, I just don't believe
in Laine Hanson...
especially when we have
at our disposal Governor Hathaway.
He's a party loyalist
and genuine hero.
And I cannot and shall not vote for a
candidate simply because she's a woman.
I am nothing if I do not
follow my heart, sir.
I envy you.
I do. You know why?
Because someday, years from now, you're
gonna come in here with your family...
and you're gonna look up
at my painting...
and you'll be able to say to them,
your kids and grandkids...
"Way back then
I defied my president.
It cost me my reelection,
kept me out of politics forever.
I was on the track
to maybe one day end up here...
destined to make the kind of changes
in this country...
that only great men, given the right
time and place, can make...
and I have none of that now,
but that's okay...
because I did
what was in my heart."
The heart, it can never be wrong,
can it, Mr. Webster?
Mmm. Delicious.
You got a little...
Hi.
I'm Jack Hathaway.
How are you?
Hi, sir. Um...
Ow. I'm Special Agent Willomina.
Sure is good of you to meet me.
It's a pleasure.
How can I help you?
I know you're busy, so this
will be as routine as it gets.
- Did my girl offer you coffee
or something to drink?
- Oh, yes, she did.
She was very nice, your girl.
Yes, she is.
She's very nice.
So like I said, I just want to cross
a couple ofT's, little stuff.
It's all just part
of the process.
By the way, sir, I was real impressed
with your graciousness...
- On the whole Senator Hanson thing.
- Oh?
You know, in supporting her.
Real gracious.
Well, as you know, I withdrew my name
from consideration.
Right. Right.
And I think she's a real fine choice.
Anybody that knows her knows that.
How long have you known her?
- Oh, well, actually, I don't really...
- I'm sorry.
When you said,
"Anybody that knows her"...
- I know people who know her.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm happy to give you
their names, if you'd like.
- Great.
I don't really know her, but I've
seen her several times at functions...
and, uh, I think
she'll do a real good job.
Sir, can I just say that...
I was really hoping
you'd go for the position...
especially after what happened
on the Apachaway.
I think people would think,
in the back of their minds...
"This here's a guy who takes risks
when the right thing's at stake."
- Lifesaver?
- No, thanks.
Anyway, some real bad luck,
your being right there.
Not if I'd been able
to save her.
No, no, in the crabbing area.
It's just that
you were fishing for bass, so...
- That probably explains why
we didn't catch anything.
-[Laughing]
You fish in the Apachaway
a lot, so I thought that
you would know that, but...
I don't fish a lot.
- I thought your equipment
was pretty sophisticated, but...
- There's a difference...
between wanting to fish
and having time to fish.
Tell me about it.
-And he freed the slaves
and won the Civil War.
- That's right!
He was probably
our greatest president.
- Even greater than George Washington?
- It's a running debate.
- Laine Hanson.
- Oh, Mr. President.
And you must be
one Timothy Hanson.
- Timothy Muskie Hanson.
- [Chuckles]
Well, Timothy Muskie Hanson, how would
you like a great big cookie? Any kind.
- No, thank you.
-Any kind at all.
Oatmeal, white chocolate...
Actually, we just had dinner,
but thanks.
In that case, shall we have
our picture taken, young man? Hmm?
- How do I look?
- Your tie's a little crooked.
Well, can't take a picture like that.
Will you straighten it for me?
Your mommy tells me you know more about
the presidents than most grown-ups.
- I like to study them.
- Mmm! Me too.
I think we're ready
for business, Dennis.
- Sir.
- You must be very proud of your mom.
Yeah, being the vice president
is better than being the president.
Oh, I'm sure you're right.
'Cause nobody wants to shoot
the vice president.
So, you must be feeling
pretty excited about now. Please sit.
- Hmm?
- Well, I think I'm a little nervous.
Well, good! Good.
Night before a confirmation hearing.
Anything else,
I would've withdrawn your name.
- What about this Webster, sir?
- Ah, one second. Anybody here hungry?
- No, thanks.
- No, sir, I'm not. Thanks.
Otto, could you whip up some
Kung Pao chicken, but with walnuts?
[Otto Over Intercom]
No problem, sir.
Ah, the kid. Met him. You know
this young congressman, Webster?
No, sir, I don't.
No matter. He reminds me of me
when I was his age. That's bad.
K, you need to put out word
that no matter what this kid does...
nobody's to give him
a hard time.
He's misguided, but he's got something.
And one day, who knows?
All right, sir. I'm sure the senator
can handle Mr. Webster.
There is one concern
we need to...
[Evans]
Oh, right, concern. Laine?
K told me about your little
sexual romp in college.
Shit. Tomorrow is the 17 th.
- Glenda?
- [Woman] Yes, sir?
Tomorrow is Jacobson's birthday.
Have you got something
for the son of a bitch?
Yes, sir. You got him
a leather-bound Don Quixote.
Oh, good. Good gift.
Metaphorical gift.
He'll be trying to figure out
why I got him that forever.
Ah, were you married
at the time?
Uh, I was a freshman in...
You know, sir, I'm just not going
to comment on the whole thing.
It's beneath me
and it's beneath the press.
That's the way to go. Fuck the press.
Senator Hanson does not kiss and tell.
- It's perfect.
- Maybe I was too rough
on Shelly in Hartford.
Then this would all be moot,
'cause you wouldn't be president, sir.
You know what?
Married, unmarried, One guy, two guys,
the whole football team.
Who the fuck cares?
You just look those bastards
in the eye and tell them exactly that.
These guys,
they're gonna confirm you.
But they want to embarrass you
in the process.
They want to send you into
this administration as a virus.
So you have only one choice.
- Yes, sir?
- Don't... be embarrassed.
[Runyon]
Two hours, gentlemen.
It is now up to us
to light the spark...
which will result in a moral uprising,
so that we may have...
a new birth
of national honesty...
and decency.
And sometimes in this process...
you will question
even yourselves.
And that's good,
that's healthy.
For what are we
if we are not what we believe?
Laine Hanson...
is a cancer.
A cancer of liberalism.
A cancer of disloyalty.
Her nomination itself is the cancer
of affirmative action.
What we will sing
with voices stentorian...
is that she is the cancer
of virtuous decay.
Clausewitz said that war
is the natural extension of politics.
But politics is also
the extension of war.
They are one and the same.
In this war,
there will be casualties.
But so help me God...
not among us.
[Reporter]
Senator, could we have a word?
[Chattering]
The president canceled
his golf game with me.
- He always cancels his golf game.
Don't worry about it.
- Not with me.
- Kermit, can I talk to you a second?
- We'll talk later.
[Hollis] They're home,
they're watching, they're proud.
-[Gavel Banging]
- Lewis, this is it. Thank you.
Order. Order.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my name is Sheldon B. Runyon
from the great state of Illinois.
It is my privilege
and my honor...
to serve as the chairman
of these special hearings.
We are here today for only
the third time in our history...
to ensure the proper implementation
of the 25th amendment...
and for the first time...
the House has taken on
that responsibility.
Myself and my esteemed
colleagues are determined...
to ensure that this very
important matter be handled with...
expedition and dignity.
We are proud to welcome
our friend and colleague, Laine Hanson.
Madam Senator,
I welcome you.
Thank you, Mr... .
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Will the "gentlelady"from Ohio
please rise and raise your right hand?
Madam Senator,
do you swear to tell the truth...
the whole truth and nothing
but the truth, so help you God?
- I do.
- Please be seated.
Mr. Chairman, point of order.
The Chair recognizes
Mr. Webster of Delaware.
Mr. Chairman, I direct
your attention to page 16...
tab C-25 of the ledger,
a transcript of the Q-and-A session...
between the nominee and several students
from Harvard University.
- Page 16?
- Page 16 at the bottom of the page.
You'll see the following remarks
in reference to a question...
regarding the separation
of church and state.
The nominee said, and I quote,
"The separation exists...
because we cannot have a fairy tale
govern a nation."
What, sir, is the point?
The senator just swore an oath
to an entity she does not believe in.
Madam Senator,
you understand...
that you have promised
to be truthful to this committee?
-And that lying to this body
is perjury, punishable by law?
- Yes, I do understand that.
Well, I think
we're all agreed...
that even though the senator
has shown a disdain...
for religion
and those practicing it...
which is her constitutional right...
that does not necessarily,
Mr. Webster, make her a liar.
I'm confident we can proceed.
- Madam?
- Yes?
For the record, would you
state your name and address?
Yes. My name is Laine Hanson.
My address is...
[Woman] You can just do that,
pull phone records?
[Willomina] I work
for a pretty powerful guy.
[Woman] Yeah, we're close,
we were close for a while.
That's till recently, of course.
Our career paths sort of went
in different directions.
At least you have your life.
There's nothing sinister going on here.
At this point,
we just need...
to look at every aspect of her life
and find everyone that knew her.
You never know
what you're gonna find.
- Did you find anything?
- No, no, not really.
Not really?
You mean...
A little bit, actually.
I did speak to other classmates,
and they told me she was pretty wild.
Wild? Yeah, she was wild.
Wild enough you can be sure the tabloids
are gonna have a field day.
Have you spoken to them?
Um, me? No.
But somebody somewhere's gonna talk.
- But not you.
- Uh-uh, no.
- It's okay if you have.
We're not gonna lock you up.
- No, I haven't.
So no one like,
maybe, the National Enquirer...
or one of those
silly television programs...
- That show, um... Access...
- Confidential?
No, no, no.
I don't know anything.
The last time I talked to her it
was just, "The kid this, the kid that."
According to our records,
you spoke to her on the 15th.
- Three weeks ago?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that makes sense.
l... She was going to Vegas.
Oh, is that right? Vegas?
She asked me to go along with her.
It was gonna be her treat.
I couldn't go
because I had to work.
We were gonna stay at one of those
ritzy new places. The, um, Bellage...?
- The Bellagio? Right.
- Yeah.
- With the contortionist.
- I've never been.
You've been going through my desk.
It never crossed my mind
when I was a younger woman...
that I'd be this age
and not have kids.
Somehow in my mind, kids.
Raising them,
making them good people.
That's what I wanted.
Then I met you,
and I realized that I'd be...
trading my dreams
so that we could live yours.
We sacrificed all of that
so we could do good.
We have done good.
I was never prouder
when you fought to make hate crimes
a capital and federal offense.
You stood so tall,
defying the world, and you won.
It was then that I realized that all
of our sacrifices were not in vain...
that you were a good man.
And now, everything you have
ever achieved will be eliminated...
because, with this horrible filth...
you'll go down
as a second-rateJoe McCarthy.
Your problem, Shelly, is that
you have no sense of history.
She's no good.
[Laine Indistinct Over TV]
Come on!
Come on.
See, Daphne? This is
how you get to the top.
Lew?
[Runyon] I have an issue to speak of,
and I'm most gravely concerned.
If this body will indulge me,
I have before me...
a perfect example of the need
for this institution...
to pass the Internet Libel
Protection Act.
In the Nichols Report piece...
posted to 40 million
Internet subscribers...
it is claimed that you,
Senator...
were involved in a sexual imbroglio
while in college.
That is...
trading favors...
with several partners in exchange
for entry into a sorority.
Though I will not waste
the committee's time with such...
nefarious and sleazy innuendoes...
I will not deny the senator
her right to respond.
Mr. Chairman,
I have nothing to...
I will not respond
to this article.
I say "Bravo"to you, Senator.
Bravo to you.
First let me state...
that I encourage
every American...
and every citizen
on this planet to boycott...
the Nichols Report.
This is the type of filth
and degenerate pornography...
that should not see
the light of day.
I can only assume, Senator,
that you will...
not only bring suit
against the perpetrators of...
www.nicholsreport.com...
but also against
the remarkable look-alike
who appears in these disgusting photos.
And when you do file suit, know that it
comes with my full support.
Your refusal to deny this report
of sexual deviance...
will not have an effect
on this committee...
on whether or not it votes to advise
and consent to your nomination.
Mr. President, do you have
a comment on the allegations
made on the Internet today?
I'm not gonna discuss any allegations,
especially those on the Internet.
But, sir, the sexual allegations
were made very public today
by Congressman Runyon.
- And I'm sure he quite regrets that.
- [Everyone Chuckling]
Sir, if you agree with the allegations,
or agree the allegations are accurate...
do you think that Senator Hanson
is morally fit to take office?
I'll tell you what.
I'm sure that
President Mateo and I...
would both welcome the votes
of only those people...
with sexual indiscretions
in their past.
We'd be landslide victors
every time.
Hey, Sheila.
- They've been waiting for you
for about ten minutes.
- Okay. Hey.
- Henry, I gotta talk to you
in five minutes, okay?
- Okay.
[Chattering]
How about "Her involvement
in prostitution"?
No, no. You gotta couch it
like it's something...
for the FB...
the AG to investigate.
- Hi, Reggie.
- Hi.
Well, how about,
"How embarrassing it is...
- That the..." No, no, no.
- Who...
- What?
- Where's Gilmore?
- Gilmore.
- Um, Idaho? Iowa?
Can I interrupt for one second?
We're all set with America Live.
What are you guys
talking about?
We're just going over
our statement...
in response to
The Washington Post story.
- What story?
- The one that says the secret
investigation is ongoing...
to determine whether
she accepted money...
for her activities
in college.
I didn't hear about this.
Well, it's, uh...
It's, um...
It'll be in...
tomorrow afternoon's edition.
Just in time for the congressman
to make his statement...
and just in time for it to stick in
the minds of Americans over the weekend.
Wh... What's the source?
Where'd they get the story?
- Unnamed sources
close to the investigation.
- I see.
Al.
- Al!
- Yes?
We can, um... Let's...
Let's dot the I's, cross the T's
on this one later.
All right, thank you.
l, uh...
I think I have some self-righteous
indignation coming my way.
Well, is there any truth
whatsoever to the story?
- There will be an investigation.
- She's gonna have the truth on her side.
- She's gonna deny it and
make us all look like fools.
- Let her.
Let her deny just that part
of the story.
- Hold here.
- What? Oh.
That's all right.
I can do that myself. Yeah.
Thank you.
-America Live is not in
the circus business.
- Pete's always fair.
[Laine]
Should I hear anything in this?
You're gonna be vice president.
- You'll talk about
legitimate issues of concern.
- Right.
Where is the senator's monitor?
There is no monitor for her.
She'll hear Pete in the earpiece.
That is a piece of shit.
We talked about this, Ray.
If Peter's gonna be able to see her,
she has to be able to see him.
- He's got a sensory advantage over her.
- You wanna pull her?
I'm not talking about pulling her.
I'm just saying it's bullshit.
She was just great in the hearings
today. Cool and collected.
- Steve Poullet.
- Hi.
[Chattering]
Should I hear anything?
Oh, I got it. Okay, great.
Oh, it's that one.
Yeah, I know.
Can't hear...
Yeah, right, got it.
Okay, I've got
the intro now.
Thank you for having me, Peter.
Sure, that'd be fine.
Well, it has been
a taxing experience...
but if we're forced to take
the voters out of the equation...
I think that the vetting system
by simple necessity must be arduous.
Mmm.
I have to plead motherhood
on that one, Pete...
but I not only served
on the Foreign Relations Committee...
I sponsored the Hanson-Fineman Bill
which readjusted the War Powers Act...
to allow the executive to respond
to state-sponsored terrorism...
like that of Iraq, Libya,
North Korea, for instance.
But rather than boring you
with my rsum...
I'd rather answer your questions
on specific issues of foreign policy.
I suppose I could ask you, Mr. Crenshaw,
how you'd feel in the same situation.
Why would I answer that for you?
Sorry. It's simply a privacy issue.
Look, I won't address issues
of sexuality in a hearing room...
or on national television
or anywhere else for that matter.
- Where's the control room
for America Live?
- Down the hall.
Excuse me.
The control room for America Live?
- Where is the fucking control room?
- Right down there.
Fuck!
Down here, down here, down here!
Don't tell me
we're gettin' sandbagged!
We're getting sandbagged! I knew
you couldn't trust this fucking guy!
Senator Hanson,
do you recognize Mr. Poullet?
Un, no. I don't have a monitor,
so I can't see him.
[Poullet] The truth is,
Lainey and I had that one incident.
I don't believe we ever
saw each other again after that.
To her credit, she was very drunk
when she had sex...
with my friends,
uh, my brothers and I.
A sandbag is what it is.
He's fucking your friend.
He has obviously infiltrated
your show.
Mrs. Hanson, you still have not taken
a stand on the accuracy of this report.
It's very accurate,
and those photos are accurate too.
We had them on the frat house
bulletin board for months.
We called that
"Life in the Sex Laine."
- What are we gonna do now?
- We're gonna sue him.
I will not dignify those remarks
or your questions with a response.
Good evening.
The guy's a jerk. We're never gonna
put our people on that show again.
Some asshole called in
and made this idiot claim.
Hell, they've gotta investigate.
The whole situation's
a son of a bitch.
I would like to start
by saying...
that much has been made of the reports
in the press of an investigation...
into the possible...
possible,  I say again...
criminal behavior
on the part of the nominee.
This committee will wait
for a report from the FBI...
before taking this matter up.
However, I'll once again afford
the nominee an opportunity to respond.
l, too, will wait for the FBI report
before responding.
Madam Senator.
Tell us a little bit about your family.
You have a son.
Mm-hmm. Yes, I have
one six-year-old boy, Timothy.
That's a very nice age.
Now, I see here
that when you...
had Timothy,
you were absent from your duty...
for a few months'
maternity leave.
- It's the right of every mother
to be able to take maternity...
- Paid maternity leave.
Yes. I don't believe we should penalize
our citizens for having children.
I think I'm on safe ground saying that
valuing motherhood is quite nonpartisan.
- [Gallery Chuckling]
- Um, were you to get pregnant again...
do you plan
to take maternity leave?
Um, I've not given that
any consideration.
No? Are you still able
to bear children?
Yes, I am...
I believe, yes, I am.
Yet you have not given
this matter any consideration.
Perhaps that means...
No, strike that.
Madam Senator...
let us assume you ascended
to the presidency...
and you were to have a child
during your term.
Would you cede your duties
to your vice president and for how long?
Mr. Chairman, would the chair
expect to have the designate
assure this committee...
that she would have her tubes tied
before she assume office?
- Mr. Chairman, I humbly
request a point of order.
- You will be afforded one.
- With all due respect...
- You will be afforded one
when I am finished.
The truth is that while we have
not put a seal on the concept
of having another child...
my husband and I practice
birth control.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I would
now like to...
enter the arena of loyalty.
Loyalty is a revered quality
among vice presidents. Would you agree?
- Yes, very much so. Yes.
- Yet you chose to officially move...
from the Republican to the
Democratic party when you left
the House to run for the Senate.
I view switching parties as a testament
to my loyalty to my country.
I felt that the Republican party
had shifted from the ideals that
I cherished through my youth.
As a Republican,
did you ever...
vote along party lines
but against your own beliefs?
No, never.
- You still believe in
every vote you made?
- Yes.
- Including your vote
to impeach President Clinton?
- Yes, I do.
That was an issue of fairness.
The president,
as commander in chief, stood by...
while several military officers,
including candidates for the
chairman of theJoint Chiefs...
were prosecuted for adultery
or were not permitted...
to advance their careers.
I am opposed to making adultery,
or even lying about it,
a crime in our armed forces.
But while it is a law,
it should be enforced
without consideration of rank...
even if that rank
is commander in chief.
Perhaps the senator is unaware
that commander in chief
is not actually a military rank.
I am aware of that.
What I think we can say
of President Clinton is that he
was not guilty but responsible.
[Gallery Laughing]
"Not guilty but responsible."
I am...
I like that.
[Laughing]
l, uh, l-I may, uh... I may use that.
- If you wish, you can go ahead.
- Thank you.
When... [Clears Throat]
When considering you
for the vice presidency...
we must also consider your worthiness
as commander in chief.
- Would you agree?
- Yes, I do.
In that case, given your feelings
on the matter...
have you ever
committed adultery?
- No, I have not.
- No?
You're quite sure? Madam Senator, you
understand that, uh, you are under oath.
Yes, I understand that, between the two
of us, I'm the one that's under oath.
When you guys go before
the Antitrust Committee,
don't you want Hank on your side?
Sure, but not at any price.
Last time we spoke,
you were sitting where you are now.
Hank was sitting where Len is.
You started telling him
what a shame it would be...
if the refrigeration systems
on the trucks went out.
Hank's a hothead,
and he took that as a threat.
If we were threatening him,
he'd know it.
That's what I thought,
but now we have some massaging to do.
Hank's gotta be treated
with kid gloves.
-Senator Hanson?
Congressman Webster's here to see you.
- Sorry. Yep?
- Guess we got our ten minutes.
- Okay, send him in.
No, I want to resolve this.
I do. Just give me a few minutes.
If you want something to drink,
Jerry will take care of you.
- We're gonna get back into this?
- We will. We will.
Senator, you want me to sit in?
Make sure the congressman's
clear on everything?
We'll be fine. Won't we, Mr. Webster?
We'll be all right. Thanks.
Proud of yourself?
So, what can I do for you,
Mr. Webster?
I'm sure you're wondering
why I'm here.
I think you're here because you want
to know why I'm not fighting back.
Because despite it all, you've got
some odd sense of fair play.
You're kicking my ass.
It's gone from feeling like
easy pickings to out-and-out bullying.
I feel like there should be
some back and forth between us,
you and the committee.
I'll give you back and forth on Social
Security, relations with Israel...
on the Dow Jones, the census,
almost everything, but not this.
No, not my personal life.
It's just nobody's business.
That's not what the people
will tell you; the people will
tell you it is their business...
that you're setting standards
of morality for their children.
Especially their girls.
Have you ever heard
of Isaac Lamm?
- Isaac Lamm? No.
- He was the first one
to come before HUAC...
the House Un-American
Activities Committee.
He was also the first one to name names,
first to cooperate with the government.
The dominoes fell from there.
Careers crushed,
families destroyed.
Just imagine, Mr. Webster,
if Mr. Lamm had just said,
"Fuck you," to the committee.
Imagine how much harder
he would've made it for them.
Are you accusing the committee
of sexual McCarthyism?
Well, it's not necessary
to make the accusation.
Oh, I just can't respond
to the committee's lightly
veiled accusations...
because it's not okay
for them to be made.
Or maybe you can't respond
because the answers you have
to give are too embarrassing.
You know what?
You're young.
That's okay. That's okay.
I'm gonna choose to be amused
by your navet, give you
the benefit of the doubt.
I'm gonna spell it out
for you even more clearly.
If I were a man,
nobody would care...
how many sexual partners
I had in college.
And if it's not relevant for a man,
it's not relevant for a woman.
Jerry, send the folks back in, please.
I gotta finish this up.
[Mrs. Runyon]
He's not a bad man.
He believes in what he's doing.
There's an odd sort
of integrity there.
But in this business,
with so much at stake...
it's not enough to believe
in yourself, you have to be right.
This is an ideological rape
of all women.
- Timmy, that's a little too high.
- Okay, Mommy.
Thank you, sweetie.
Well, then I'll survive it
for all of us.
Tomorrow morning Congressman Marshall
is gonna ask you questions.
He's going to hit you
with abortion.
I promise you that Shelly will find
some way to call you a baby killer.
We're ready for him.
Our position papers are first-rate.
- Every one of them.
- You let him finish.
Then you look him in the eye
and you ask him...
"Mr. Runyon, 20 years ago
your wife Maggie had an abortion.
Do you think her a murderer?"
He's a hypocrite.
No, he's not.
Shelly has no idea.
Are you saying you would appoint
a Supreme Court justice...
based on his being pro-choice?
Mr. Marshall, the vice president
does not appoint Supreme Court justices.
Should you succeed the president
or even advise the president?
I would be inclined,
though not without flexibility...
to disregard any man or woman who is
pro-life from serving on the High Court.
So you would allow a personal political
belief to enter into such a decision?
Abortion isn't
a constitutional issue.
The fine ladies and gentlemen
who serve on the Supreme Court...
which is now stacked
with right-wing appointees...
have no business deciding whether women
have to resort to back-alley abortions...
You mean they have no business
deciding whether women have
a license to commit murder.
[Runyon]
Mr. Marshall, your time has expired.
Sir, if the distinguished "gentlelady"
from Ohio would answer the question...
I think the lady has made clear
her propensity for abortion.
- Come on, Mr. Runyon!
- Mr. Lewis, you do not
have speaking privileges.
Mr. Chairman, I find your term,
"propensity for abortion"...
misrepresentative of my position.
I have a propensity
for a woman's right to choose.
- To abort a child!
-A fetus.
To kill a baby
as it grows in the womb.
Personally, Senator...
I do not believe that it is
the right of our citizens...
to... to butcher
a defenseless human being simply...
simply as a matter of choice.
At the risk of my own future,
I tell you this:
If you support the right...
of a woman to choose,
you are supporting...
nothing less than
a-a-a holocaust of the unborn.
Mr. Chairman,
are you calling me...
I believe my position
on this issue is clear.
Yes, madam,
it most certainly is.
God, I love this game.
[Chuckles]
[Coughing]
When she tries to tell me
how to do it, I do it my way.
Then she comes back and changes it
afterwards, and that way...
Jeez.
[Coughing]
Good one, sir.
You're an all-weather golfer,
I see.
What kind of stick
you using there?
- It's a putting stick.
- Right, putting stick.
When I asked for you last week,
they said you were in Vegas.
- Business, sir.
- Vegas is business?
I did blow
a roll of quarters.
Will you excuse us?
- How's that cough doing?
- Aah.
That's her casino account balance.
She offered to take her sorority sister
to Vegas, her treat.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth and nothing
but the truth so help you God?
I do.
Please state your name
for the record.
Cynthia C-H-A-R-L-T-O-N Lee.
Thank you.
Please be seated.
We will start the questioning
with Mr. Skakle.
Mr. Skakle, the five-minute rule
is in effect.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Miss Lee.
Miss Lee, hello. I'm over here.
Thank you for joining us.
Now, you are under subpoena,
is that correct?
Yes.
- Miss Lee, could you speak
directly into the mike?
- Yes.
I understand you're nervous, but believe
me when I tell you you're among friends.
Miss Lee, you are not married.
No... No.
- No, I'm not.
- But you once were.
I was married
to William Hanson.
- Who is now married to the nominee.
- Yes.
He married Laine after our divorce.
It was about seven years ago.
Divorce. Right.
I've read your divorce papers.
Ladies and gentlemen,
that by the way is tab 76.
They cite
irreconcilable differences.
Could you tell us, what were
those irreconcilable differences?
I can't really pinpoint them.
- Was your husband
physically violent to you?
- No.
Did you have financial
disagreements or disagreements
over how to raise your kids?
We didn't have children.
- Were there infidelities?
- Yes. There was one.
Is it safe to say that this infidelity
precipitated the divorce?
Miss Lee, please answer
the question verbally. Was that a yes?
Yes, it was.
It was a yes.
- Did you, ma'am, have the affair?
- No.
- It was your husband then?
- Yes.
Will...
Will was in charge...
of Laine Billings's
first senatorial campaign.
He was with her all the time.
Are you suggesting the senator,
the nominee, had an affair
with your husband?
- Once again, Miss Lee...
- I'm sorry. Yes. Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Did the nominee know
Mr. Hanson was married?
Laine was my friend.
My good, good friend.
Miss Lee, would you explain
to this committee as you
did in your deposition...
how you discovered
that the nominee was involved...
in an affair
with your husband?
Yes. Um...
On the night of the elections,
I was at home.
I had the flu.
I was watching TV, watching Laine
about to make her acceptance speech.
I was very sad
that I couldn't be there.
It was a triumph
for Laine and my husband.
She was up at the podium.
Will was by her side.
He was holding her hand
in victory.
On the other side
of Laine...
she was just sort of clasping
that person's hand.
But with Will...
their hands were interlaced.
It was odd
that I noticed it, but...
Um, my doorbell rang.
I answered the door,
and there was a gentleman there...
dressed very nicely,
he had a yellow tie on.
He had papers for me.
- Papers? I'm sorry.
- Separation papers.
Since the committee
chose to humiliate a private woman
in the most public possible setting...
I would like to apologize
to her alike...
and I will also do so privately
when she allows me to do so.
Um, what I did to Miss Lee
was wrong.
It was not done out of malice.
Indeed the opposite.
Um...
Iove is an involuntary reflex,
and I fell victim to it.
Um, I deeply regret
causing Cynthia pain...
and it is especially saddening
for me because...
of how close we once were.
And whether or not the affair
that Will and I had...
should have any bearing on my assuming
office is for the committee to decide.
I dare not assume that I have
the objective wisdom to make
that determination. Thank you.
- Senator,
are you suggesting the public...
- Okay, she's had a long day.
You know what she's going through.
Come on, come on.
She was your best friend.
Runyon deposed Will's
ex-wife today, and, uh...
she stated that Will and I
had had an affair...
She saw her fucking holding hands,
interlocked fingers with this gal...
and she knew
that she'd been fucking him.
That's what she said.
- I'm sorry.
-[Newman] It's a bad beat.
I'm not sure that I get
the point of all this.
- You said under oath
that you never committed adultery.
- That's right.
- You perjured yourself.
- I didn't commit adultery.
- You were fucking Will
when he was married.
- All right.
Even the most loose definition
of committing adultery
would not include that.
Goddamn it, she's right.
You're right.
In order for it to be
committing adultery, she'd have
to be married at the time.
You're nitpicking
in reverse now.
Your husband may have been
an adulterer. You're not. Fine.
What you are is a sex-crazed,
home-wrecking machine.
The female Warren Beatty.
Runyon knows
that you're clean of the perjury...
but he's got the world thinking you're
something out of a bad soap opera.
You've goddamned crystallized
the difference between being
guilty and being responsible.
Are you asking me
to step down, sir?
No, it's not gonna be
that easy for you, and it's not
gonna be that easy for them.
They caught you being
a human being. That's all.
I'll die before Shelly Runyon
checkmates me.
I think the president's trying to say
the Sitting Bull routine isn't working.
- The Sitting Bull routine?
- No!
Fight back.
Show them Laine Hanson isn't gonna take
their shit. Take the fight out of'em.
- What's the process?
- Confess.
- Confess?
- Yeah, confess.
- Confess.
Confess to the gang-bang.
Confess to all of it.
-[Evans] Look what it did
for Clinton with Flowers.
- Play it any way you want.
It didn't hurt his numbers.
It improved his numbers.
Show indignation about how a man
would never have to go through
hell for having done this.
Confess and demonstrate
to the young women of America...
how such sexual impropriety
can ruin their lives.
Confess and preach about the dangers
that alcohol can bring to you.
For God's sakes, just confess!
I understand, Kermit, truly.
I understand, and you know what?
It's really nobody's business.
Well, it is
our fucking business!
Listen, Laine...
I don't care who you fucked...
and how many times
in how many positions...
as long as it doesn't threaten
the administration.
You can be cavalier
on your own dime.
Mr. President.
[Sighs]
I am fully prepared
to step down...
but my personal life...
and my past...
are just that.
But I will do
whatever you say.
Show them why Laine Hanson is my nominee
with your closing statement.
Mr. Chairman...
ladies and gentlemen
of the committee:
Uh, remarkably enough, it seems
that I have some explaining to do.
So...
let me be absolutely clear.
I stand for a woman's right
to choose.
I stand for the elimination
of the death penalty.
I stand for a strong
and growing armed forces...
because we must stomp out genocide
on this planet...
and I believe that that
is a cause worth dying for.
I stand for seeing every gun
taken out of every home. Period.
I stand for making
the selling of cigarettes
to our youth a federal offense.
I stand for term limits
and campaign reform.
And, Mr. Chairman, I stand for
the separation of church and state...
and the reason that I stand
for that is the same reason that
I believe our forefathers did.
It is not there to protect religion
from the grasp of government...
but to protect our government
from the grasp of religious fanaticism.
I may be an atheist...
but that does not mean I do not
go to church; I do go to church.
The church I go to is the one
that emancipated the slaves...
that gave women
the right to vote.
It gave us every freedom
that we hold dear.
My church is this very chapel
of democracy that we sit in together...
and I do not need God to tell me
what are my moral absolutes.
I need my heart,
my brain and this church.
Get in there, get in there.
Oh, shoot!
Come on, come on, come on!
- Senator? Oh...
- Hello, Freshman.
Senator, I just wanted
to steal a couple of seconds.
What? See what whores do
on their time off?
Listen,
I know the things I've done.
They may not have been nice
or considered politically savvy...
but they have served the greater good
and they have been honest.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
Look, I know
you're not a whore.
- I'm not gonna talk about it.
- I know. You're not talking about it.
Somebody else
has come forward.
Somebody else from the night
of the incident sent me this letter.
They didn't send it to me.
They sent it to the committee.
I just happen to be in charge
of all the correspondence.
I don't think you can keep quiet
about what's in there.
Mr. Runyon has a copy,
and now so do you.
I beg you, Senator,
to deal with this.
- How long is this flight?
- About an hour and 40 minutes.
POTUS is scheduled to address
the American Legion on the third.
- American Legion? Who approved that?
- I don't know.
- I thought he had
the D.A.R. dinner that night.
- We have a five-hour window.
- Hey, Chuck.
- Hey, Kermit.
Did you get the AP reports?
- What's that?
- POTUS's poll numbers are down 23%.
- And Hanson's in the low 30s.
- Get in there.
I'll talk to you in a minute.
- Are you Willomina?
- Yes, sir.
You asked to see me?
- Is this your handiwork?
- Yes, sir.
- How many people have seen this?
- I gave it only to the director.
- And who have you talked to about this?
- Nobody.
Not a husband? Boyfriend?
- Grandma in Kalamazoo?
- No, sir. Nobody.
- Keep it that way.
- Yes, sir.
You did a good job,
Special Agent.
Sir! Uh, sir, I just... I just wanted
to ask, ask you. Um, well...
Are you gonna dump her?
Sir, this may be really,
really inappropriate...
but if that's what you guys
are thinking...
Please, you can't do it.
She's hope.
Hope that the standards...
That there is no double standard.
Hope that the goals
can be the same.
You know what?
You're goddamn right.
That was absolutely inappropriate.
Robertson.
[Runyon]
I wouldn't take it too hard.
It's not exactly fair
when six foxes and one chicken...
are voting on
what to have for dinner.
[Evans] Well, that's not
playing fair. I'll give you that.
You want an oatmeal cookie?
- Trevor?
- I'm getting them, sir.
I find these giant raisins...
Well, you'll see.
Taste like grapes.
Shelly, you really made
a mess of things for me.
You sure did clobber me.
Isn't it possible, sir,
that I was... that I was acting...
- In the best interests
of the United States?
- No.
It's not possible.
That's what pisses me off. It's all
about retribution for Hartford.
Thank you, Trevor.
That'll be all.
- Go ahead. Try this. It's wonderful.
- No.
I may have taken the presidency
from you, but you one-upped me.
You took away my legacy.
I look at her and I see someone who
has proven the capacity for disloyalty.
Or the capacity
for seeing the light.
We're both sticking
to our guns.
The difference is...
mine are loaded.
Look, it doesn't matter, does it?
She's not being confirmed.
We can talk for days
about greatness and leadership...
but Laine Hanson
will not be confirmed.
I have seven from your side
who are giving her the ax.
Oh, indeed, the ax?
We can go through
the process of a vote.
You can waste time...
and suffer the humiliation,
or... or we can just move on.
- There's a lot of good folk
to choose from.
- Who?
Who can I be certain
you'll confirm?
The man you wanted in the first place:
Jack Hathaway.
Shelly.
Good man.
Okay, Shelly...
I'll give you GovernorJack Hathaway,
but I wanna make damn sure...
-you'll give him a smooth ride.
- My word. There's a reason
they call me Honest Shell.
Irony, Shelly.
I want an insurance policy.
I want a piece of the rock.
I wanna make sure...
you're not gonna pull
some kind of baloney out of your hat...
and make a mockery
of my administration again.
Listen. This is
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna ask Mrs. Hanson and
Mr. Hathaway up to the Oval Office...
before the D.A.R. banquet
tomorrow night.
I want you there as well,
but, Shelly...
before then, I need you
to marry yourself to this guy.
I need you to make a public statement
that makes his sinking your sinking.
- Otherwise...
- But I'm not sure I can...
Let's make this confirmation
fast and furious.
- Help me save face on this one.
- Okay.
Oh, man. Mr. Runyon,
prefer I take you around back?
- No, I'll be fine.
- Yes, sir.
How do you respond to the rumors
that Mrs. Hanson has withdrawn her name?
That is a rumor
I've not yet heard.
Have you heard about the possibility
of Governor Hathaway...
- Returning to the list
of vice presidential...
- Governor Hathaway is a fine man.
Will he have a smoother ride
than Mrs. Hanson?
Let me go on record
as saying...
that in my opinion there is
no man alive... no Democrat alive...
who could bring...
more integrity
to the office of the vice presidency.
I would stake my career...
on Governor Hathaway's, uh,
smooth and efficient confirmation.
[Runyon]
As for Laine Hanson...
- Got everybody, Glenda?
- Yes, sir. He says you can
go in whenever you're ready.
- Great. Hello, Jack.
- Kermit.
- Fiona, you're looking
particularly fetching this evening.
- Thank you, sir.
- I believe this is the first one
of these affairs for you, right?
- Yes.
- My 37 th.
- You look great.
- Hello, Shelly.
- Newman.
Everybody would understand if you
wanted to delay for two weeks.
I'm not sure I could stomach
another two weeks.
Oh, Jack.
- Jerry. Good.
- How are you?
Mr. Hanson.
-[Evans] Gentlemen. Jack.
- Mr. President.
There he is! Shelly!
Hello, Mr. President.
Uh, you know what?
Before we get started...
I can't stomach the idea...
of touching that chichi food we always
get served at these state dinners.
- Glenda?
- Yes, sir?
Could we put together a grilled
cheese sandwich? Muenster on rye.
Right away.
Oh, sorry. Where are my manners?
You guys want anything?
- No, thank you, sir.
- Shelly?
Jesus, uh, Shell,
those were some...
very nice things
you said aboutJack.
Jack, there. I understand
that you two have never met.
- Laine Hanson, Jack Hathaway.
- It's a pleasure.
- I'm quite in awe of you.
- Thank you.
[Glenda]
Mr. President?
- Yes, Glenda?
-Sir, the kitchen's
all out of Muenster.
Really? Wow.
Well, um, let's get on that.
We don't want the wheels
coming off the wagon.
This is, uh...
This is quite an event.
Here we are. Quite a sad event.
- Mr. President, if I may?
- Yes, please.
A short while ago,
you told me that you thought
I might be the future of the party.
I know that these
are tough times...
and the future is uncertain...
but I'm very pleased to think
that I might be able to help
make things a little smoother.
The future, yes.
Well, there is one thing...
quite certain
about the future.
- What's that?
- [Coughs] Sir?
- You have the right to remain silent...
- Fred.
- I have to read him his rights.
- Fred, the governor,
he knows his rights.
You know your rights, right, Jack?
You don't have to humiliate him.
You fucked up, buddy.
- The girl, do you know what she was?
- What girl?
- The girl in the river.
- She was a paralegal.
- Before that.
- She was military. Fourteen Golf.
We found the money that you put
in her account at the Bellagio.
- Two hundred thousand dollars.
- And that ad in...
- Soldier of Fortune.
- Yeah,  Soldier of Fortune.
I don't mind confessing,
I am at a total fucking loss.
Shelly, he paid her
to go off the fucking bridge.
He paid her to save her.
Jesus Christ.
- Shelly, maybe l...
- You shouldn't say anything.
- Jack, look, we respect...
- You're going to have
to come with me now.
Fred. We respect you.
We're trying to make this go
as smoothly as it possibly can.
I know you meant no harm.
- Hell, I don't even know...
What would the charge be?
- Negligent homicide.
Oh, negligent homicide.
Sir.
- Good luck, Mrs. Hanson.
- You too.
Who doesn't want
a shortcut to greatness?
Oh, it's a goddamn shame
about the Muenster.
Mr. President.
Yeah, Shelly?
You set me up.
Just this once.
For the record, sir...
I find what you did
to be manipulative...
Mr. Chairman, let's just say...
"I'm guilty
but not responsible," hmm?
Shelly, you needn't worry
about us exposing the fact...
that you leaked all that horrible
material about Laine on the Internet.
We know that you were
just following your heart.
Yeah, Hartford,
it was a tough one.
But... Well, it doesn't
make a difference.
- She still is who she is.
- Yes, she is.
And you are who you are.
You're still coming
to the banquet, aren't you?
Because I'd love to see you.
Is your wife in town?
May I introduce
tonight's honoree, Miss Barr?
- Congressman Webster.
- Honor, madam.
And, Congressman,
you know the senator, of course.
We go about two feet back.
I asked them to have you seated
at my table tonight.
- If you want to break bread with me.
- Absolutely.
- Don't eat all the hors d'oeuvres.
- Shark steak sandwiches?
Yeah. Save me some.
Last time I shared one of these,
it was with the president of Russia.
Or maybe it was the kid
who won Wimbledon for the second time.
I'm honored, sir.
[Coughing]
You're not supposed to inhale.
Maybe that's the first thing
you should've told me.
Recognize this affidavit?
Where'd you get that, sir?
Where you got yours.
Where Shelly Runyon got his.
From Mr. Webster.
He may not know
his right from his left...
but apparently
he does know right from wrong.
I understand you
even less now, Senator.
- You are an enigma wrapped in a riddle.
- Wrapped in a riddle.
Watch your step, Senator.
What if I told you that I'm just
busting at the seams...
to know what exactly
happened that night...
to hear the truth
from your own lips?
Totally off the record.
Not between the president
and the senator, but between
the president and Laine.
Better than that.
Between Jackson and Laine.
Well, I had just turned 18
when I got to college...
and I had never been
away from home, not really.
And I was immediately...
I was immediately lonely.
And that's when
the sorority kicked in.
I wanted them,
they wanted me.
I was the daughter of the governor,
for chrissake.
- True blue catch.
- I guess so.
And like any other sorority,
they have an initiation, a rush.
And they have this girl, this woman
that Runyon deposed, Patty LaVamere.
She runs the sorority,
and she gives it to me straight:
If I wanna be in, I have to go to
their brother fraternity and have sex...
with two boys.
What a coup for them, huh?
Daughter of a big-time Republican
doing a frat house?
But I say,
"There's no chance."
- The whole thing was pretty hairy.
- I bet.
But six beers later,
I'm talking a different tune...
so off we go
to the frat house.
Half the girls were there,
about a zillion boys.
They're cheering my name.
"Laine! Laine! Laine!"
And I'm just stumbling around.
Eventually I just say,
"I'm gonna go for it."
If getting laid is a common initiation
for boys in the frat...
then why not for us, right?
- You're asking me?
- No, I'm not.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry. Go ahead.
That's okay.
So they send me
into this room.
It's dark and dim.
There are these two guys.
They both have towels
wrapped around their waists.
And the first guy,
he slips his towel off.
And I see his thing, and...
I take it in my hand...
and I say...
- It was the first thing
that came into my head.
- What did you say?
I said,
"I'm sorry, I don't smoke."
[Both Laughing]
And then I just got
the hell out of there.
You okay, sir?
Oh, no, I'm just thinking what I'd pay
to be back in college again.
The next day, the campus
was rampant with word...
that I had been
the center of a gang-bang.
I mean, the governor's daughter.
Let me tell you.
That's one hell of a bell to un-ring.
- What about the photographs?
- Not me.
I never took my clothes off.
Even if I had, I've got
this big birthmark on my right thigh...
that the lady with the lovely physique
in the photo lacks.
- No witnesses?
- Pure urban legend.
A little bit of wishful thinking
thrown in, I think.
You know, Laine...
you could've looked those pricks
in the eye and told them the truth.
Under oath. Told them
they were full of shit.
And barring that,
you could've at least told me.
But see, it really wasn't any of your
business either, and it still isn't.
There's something about
almost puking on a Havana...
that just turns a girl...
to blush.
This letter from Jack Bennet...
and Larry Bellows, affidavit, I guess,
that you got from Webster.
It pretty much says
that nothing happened that night.
- They're ready
to come forward to be deposed.
- That's very good of them.
So, that's it. The end.
Good guys win.
I'm gonna call a press conference
tomorrow, read that letter...
and damn it if you don't have
the fastest confirmation on record.
No, sir.
"No, sir"?
What, "No, sir"?
I would prefer that we not
have the press conference, sir.
Laine, maybe you've been out
of law school too long.
- This is what they call
exculpatory evidence.
- Yes, I realize that.
- This is your ticket to wherever
history is gonna take you.
- Yes.
But principles only mean
something if you stick by them
when they're inconvenient.
If I ever did
answer the questions...
you know,
even to exonerate myself...
that would mean that it was
okay for them to have been
asked in the first place...
and it isn't.
- You would sacrifice your reputation?
- Yes, I would.
People have sacrificed
a lot more for a lot less.
[People Chattering]
- We've got him! We have Goliath.
- Sir, are you all right, sir?
- It's okay, guys. Busted.
- POTUS is secure.
[Radio Announcer]
Of course, the president addressing
a joint session of Congress...
is always unusual,
always an event.
This speech is scheduled
to begin momentarily.
We understand the president
has arrived at the U.S. Capitol.
[Laine] I don't care if I never
see any of these guys again.
[Radio] Sources in the White House
have told us that the president...
- It's gonna be okay.
- Does intend to withdraw the name
of Senator Laine B. Hanson...
I still have a year and a half on
my term. That's a long time to recover.
- Then there's always...
- Given the stunning charges
made against Governor Hathaway...
- Laine, honey, it's gonna be fine.
- Those on the inside are suggesting...
- It's gonna be okay.
- The president will designate...
-Ambassador Francis J. Malloy
as his number two.
- Yeah, thanks.
Pace me at five to ten, okay?
[Radio Announcer]
... after the greeting
of the president of the United States.
Mr. Speaker, the president
of the United States of America.
Thank you.
Napoleon once said,
when asked to explain the lack
of great statesmen in the world...
that, "to get power...
you need to display
absolute pettiness.
To exercise power,
you need to show true greatness."
Such pettiness and such greatness
are rarely found in one person.
I look upon the events
of the past weeks...
and I've never come so to grips
with that quotation.
So, ladies and gentlemen
of this Congress...
it pains my soul to tell you
that you have brought blood
and shame under this great dome.
Your leadership has raised
the stakes of hate to a level...
where we can no longer separate
the demagogue from the truly inspired.
And believe this,
there are traitors among us.
And I'm not talking about those of you
who sided against your party leadership.
I'm talking about those of you
who were patriots to your party...
but traitors
to the necessary end result:
that of righteousness,
the truth...
the concept of making
the American dream blind to gender.
And you know,
I am not free of blame.
Right from the start
I should've come down here...
pointed a finger your way...
and asked you,
"Have you no decency, sir?"
Yesterday...
I met...
Mr. Runyon...
you may walk out on me,
you may walk out on this body...
but you cannot walk out
on the will of the American people.
Americans are a good people,
they're a just people, Mr. Runyon...
and they will forgive you,
but they will not forget.
Hate and ego
have no place residing...
in what my good friend Laine Hanson
calls the chapel of democracy.
So, let me make one thing clear.
You come at us with whatever weapons
that you have in your arsenal...
but there is
no weapon as powerful...
as that of an idea
whose time has come.
A woman will serve in the highest level
of the Executive. Simple as that.
Yesterday...
I spoke with Laine Hanson.
I told her that she could decide
her own destiny.
If she wanted to continue
her fight for confirmation...
that I would stand beside her.
She has asked me
to allow her to step aside.
She told me that she wanted
my administration to end on a note...
of triumph
and not controversy.
Understand, those of you who worked
to bring Laine Hanson down...
that she asked to have her name
withdrawn from consideration...
not because she isn't great,
but because she isn't petty.
Because those two
conflicting leadership traits...
could not live as one
within her body or her soul.
Greatness.
It comes in many forms.
Sometimes it comes in the form
of sacrifice. That's the loneliest form.
Now, it turns out
that Laine Hanson is a woman...
an American
of devout principle...
and she has inspired me
to act alike...
and I cannot accept
Senator Hanson's withdrawal.
And I'm now calling for an immediate
vote of confirmation of Laine Hanson.
And, Mr. Speaker...
I would like to make this
a live roll call.
I want to see the faces
of those of you...
who would eliminate the possibility
of greatness in American leadership...
because of half-truths,
lies and innuendoes.
I will not be deterred
by partisanship.
by misogyny.
I will not be deterred
by hate.
You have now come face-to-face
with my will.
Confirm my nominee,
heal this nation...
and let the American people
explode into this new millennium...
with the exhilaration of being true
to the glory of this democracy.
Thank you.
How's that for a swan song?
You're back, Laine.
Yeah, I know.
Download GOM Player to experience
the highest video and audio quality!