Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
[ Indistinct Voices,
Creatures Roaring ]
[ Mechanical Whirring ]
[ Creaking ]
[ Birds Twittering ]
[ Man Narrating ]
From a secret island
in the South Pacific,
the courageous Tracy Family
run an organization called...
International Rescue.
When disaster strikes
anywhere in the world,
they are always
first on the scene.
They go by the name they gave
their incredible machines--
The Thunderbirds.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one,
Thunderbirds are go.!
But in this family ofheroes,
there is one son left behind.
[ Woman ]
So, gentlemen, we all know that
A-squared plus B-squared equals...
[ Students ]
C-squared.
C-squared. That's right.
But what happens when we bring in
Leonardo da Vinci's ''E, '' ''F''and--
- [ Teacher ] Mr. Tracy.!
- Alan.
Alan!
How kind of you to come back
from outer space, Alan.
I trust reentry wasn't too rough.
[ Chuckles ]
Here on Earth, we've been discussing
the Pythagorean theorem.
Did any of that happen to sink in?
I-I was just--
Apparently not.
''Thunderbirds are go.''
Well, I hope you aren't going
anywhere special over spring break, Alan.
Because I expect a 1 0,000-word paper
on my desk the day you get back.
That should keep you busy.
- [ School Bell Ringing ]
- ''That should keep you busy.''
You can take your 1 0,000 words
and stick 'em right up your--
Alan!
[ Alan ]
Headmaster.!
Mr. Tracy.
Miss Garrett.
[ Huffs ]
You got to be more careful, Alan.
Why can't I just tell them
I'm a Thunderbird, Fermat?
Because, technically,
you're not a Thunderbird yet.
And if your identity
was discovered,
it'd be a di-di--
[ Boy Shouting ]
It could be very bad.
I know. I know.
It's the Thunderbirds!
They're gonna be on Tv!
Let's go!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Where are they?
They're in Russia
at an oil rig fire!
Great. I'm stuck at school,
and my brothers are on
another cool mission.
Wanna watch?
Yeah!
We're told the super rig is now
in danger of total collapse.
And there is real concern
for the lives of six men
who remain trapped onboard.
An emergency call went out
to the Thunderbirds just a few minutes ago.
They should be here any moment now.
And here they are!
[ Cheering ]
[ Pilot #1 ] Thunderbird 2,
this is Thunderbird 1 .
I have visual, south column.
They're trapped on an inspection platform.
- [ Pilot #2 ]
F.A.B. We'll take it from here.
- Come on! Come on!
- Scott, get out of there!
That tower's coming down!
- Got it.!
- [ Students Gasp ]
-[ Pilot #2 ] Thunderbird 1 , any damage?
- Negative, Dad.
- Come on. Come on.
Swing around.
You can't get close enough
taking that approach angle.
[ Pilot #2 ] Approach angle's no good.
I'm gonna have to swing around.
[ Scott ]
Watch the wind shear, Thunderbird 2.
Scottie, I was watching for wind shear
when you were still wearing diapers.
Come on, Dad.
- Whoa! Hold on!
- Who needs the diapers now, Dad?
- What do they do now?
- Probably drop the rescue platform
from Thunderbird 2.
Open 'em up.! Here we go.!
Rescue platform's on its way.!
[ Pilot #2 ]
Virgil, how's it goin'?
[ Virgil ] It's lookin'good, Dad.
- Come on!Jump!
- [ Grunts, Groans ]
Okay, I've got a visual.
Hold it there!
[ Beeping ]
[ Virgil ] Target's locked.
Firing rescue lines!
Come on, guys.! Hook 'em up.!
We got to get you out ofhere.!
- Hoist away!
- Let's haul 'em out of there!
- Commencing reverse thrust.
- [ Newsman ]
The Thunderbirds are actually rescuing--
[ Pilot #2 ]
Okay, let's bring 'em home.
- [ Man Shouting ] Look out!
- [ Grunting ]
Okay, we got to get 'em out fast.
The rig's gonna blow.
- [ Pilot #2 ] Hang on.!
- [ Collective Gasp ]
[ Pilot #2 ] Whoa.! Sorry, boys.!
Hold on tight.! Here we go.!
- Come on, virgil.
- [ Virgil ] Hold on, guys.!
- [ Pilot #2 ] How ya doin; Son?
- [ Virgil ] Never better.!
[ Pilot #1 ] Thunderbird 1 ,
commence knockdown procedure.
F.A.B., Thunderbird 2.
- [ Bell Chiming ]
- [ Scott ] Lining up target.
[ Scott ]
Fire.
Yeehaw.! Bull's-eye.!
Outstanding shot.!
[ Scott Chuckles ]
[ Pilot #2 ] All right, boys.
Let's take these babies home.
[ Woman Reporter ] As you can see,
the fire has been extinguished.
The rocket fired from Thunderbird 1 has
robbed it of the oxygen it needed to burn.
Amazing! The Thunderbirds
have done it again, Chuck!
[ Cheering ]
[ News Anchor Chattering ]
That was great work, Lisa.
Thanks a lot.
[ Sarcastically ]
Ooh, I wish I could be
a Thunderbird one day,
Thunder-turd.
[ Students ''Oohing'' ]
That's another good one, diaper boy.
[ Students Laughing ]
- Tracy!
- [ Newscast Continuing ]
There's someone here for you.
Hello, boys.
Lady Penelope Creighton-Ward
at your service.
Alan, darling, your father's been
unexpectedly detained, and he's asked me
to pick you up. Is that all right?
Sure beats the bus.
- Definitely.
- Fantastic.
Now, will any of these
gorgeous young things be joining you?
[ All Shouting ] Me! Me! Me!
Just...
- Fermat.
- Quite right.
Lady Penelope. Why are you in America?
Are you on a mission for my father?
Alan, shh.
I am an undercover agent,
so please try to be discreet.
[ Lady Penelope ]
Here we are.
Hi, Parker.
Good afternoon to you,
Master Hackenbacker.
[ Bones Cracking,
Fermat Groaning ]
Hi, nosy.
Less of that attitude,
Ooh! Ah!
or I shall be obliged
to deliver the Parker haymaker.
Okay.
Bring it on, big guy.
[ Lady Penelope ]
Try not to run over any children, Parker.
Very good, milady.
Come on, Parker, chop-chop.
[ Alan ]
All right.!
[ Fermat ] Whoa.!
[ Alan ]
Yes.!
Yeah!
Oh, look, Parker.
Pink is the new black this season.
I'm very glad to hear it, milady.
And hemlines
are going up.
That is good news, milady.
- Oh, and apparently England
won the football last night.
- Yes! England!
[ Lady Penelope ]
Calm down, Parker.
Yes, milady. Sorry, milady.
[ Sighs ]
[ Sirens Blaring ]
[ Woman ] Come on, Daniel.
Come on, baby. Out you jump.
Wait till your father
hears about this.
Panhead!
[ Vehicle Hovering
Overhead ]
Aliens!
[ Loud Whirring ]
[ Boy ]
Even better.!
It's the Thunderbirds!
- Okay, lock it up.
- [ Woman ] Okay, people, let's move it.!
- Okay, let's go! Let's move it!
- [ Man ] You'd better go slow with the steps.
- Hey, we need some help over here.!
-[ Woman ] Here you are.Jump down.
Mission complete.
- Thunderbird 1, we are good to go.
- F.A.B.
- [ Overlapping Chatter]
- [ Mechanism Whirring ]
[ Computer Voice.'Male ]
Tracking device activated.
Ah, the chariot of the gods.
Having dallied with the mortals,
they return to Olympus.
So I follow.
Pardon me, milady.
Approaching Tracy Island.
And radar indicates
we have some company.
[ Vehicle Zooming Past ]
Now, that's showing off.
I wish that was me.
[ Man ]
I'm about to run postflight checks,
Mr. Tracy.
Anything I sh-sh-sh--
Anything you want to tell me?
Brains, I noticed
a build-up of vibration
on Thunderbird 2,
followed by illumination
of number-five engine out light.
Okay, Mr. Tracy, I'll ch-ch--
study flight data in the guidance processor.
Dad!
Alan.!
Pop!
Let me look at ya!
Oh, man!
Uh-oh, look out.
Hey, sprout!
- Hey, buddy.
- Dinner's ready. Come and get it.!
Onaha, it smells delicious.
I am starved.!
So, Dad, I saw the mission on TV.
It looked pretty dangerous.
Saving lives
is a dangerous business.
But it's what we do.
[ Alan ] Do you think the fire
was causing thermal updrafts?
I mean, that would explain...
the whole thing.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Enough shop talk.
I wanna hear about school.
School is boring.
Plus, I've been thinkin'.
I mean, maybe I could be home educated now.
That way, I could sit in on a mission
from time to time?
What do you think?
No shortcuts, Alan.
No school, no rockets.
- Say, why aren't you wearing your retainer?
- [ Brothers Chuckling ]
So, I'm getting this reading,
telling me the wind is blowing 60 knots,
right up my keister.
No kidding?
Did you try readjusting the flaps?
Well, that's the first thing I did, sprout.
It's not my first day on a Thunderbird,
you know?
- Try and keep up.
- Don't you have homework to do?
- Unless he's blown up this school
like that last one.
- [ All Laughing ]
- [ Scott ] Yeah, keep Alan away
from the ships. He's a hazard.
- Okay, that's enough. Pass the salad.
[ Virgil ] Man, I haven't seen
that much fire since that volcano in Fiji.
[ Scott ]
That wasn't Fiji.! That was Istanbul.!
[ Virgil ] Istanbul was the earthquake.!
[ Scott ] Yeah, well,
nothing compares to Argentina.
Dad, I'm not really hungry.
- Come on, Fermat. Let's go.
- But, you-- Uh--
I'm not done! Okay.
Kyrano, have you seen Lady ''P''?
By the pool.
Of course.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
Parker.
We're not supposed to go in there.!
We could get in trouble.!
Aw, you worry too much.
[ Door Lock Beeping ]
Where'd you get the access code
for Thunderbird 1 , anyway?
Fermat, my friend,
what you don't know
can't hurt you.
I'll be right there.
- It seems the fire
at the oil rig was no accident.
- Any suspects?
Not yet,
but I'll keep you posted.
Thanks for bringing
Alan home.
My pleasure.
Any excuse to visit paradise.
[ Girl Humming ]
- Tintin!
- Hey, Mr. Tracy.
Hello, Tintin.
Good evening, Lady Penelope.
- Did you know Alan's home?
- Alan's back?
I mean, ''Oh, Alan's back.''
Hey, Dad.
When are those two
gonna get along?
When Tintin decides
the time is right.
Girls are always far ahead
of boys with that sort of thing.
What sort of thing?
Romance.
Alan and Tintin?
I didn't see that one coming.
No, you wouldn't.
Have a safe flight home, Penny.
Thanks,Jeff.
Okay, Fermat.
Run preflight checks.
Right,
Hydraulic systems... are green.
Commence
main engine sequence.
F.A.B., Alan!
Couldn't hurt
to just fire up the instruments.
- [ Beeping, Twittering ]
- No, wait, Alan! That's the...
- wrong switch!
- [ Computer Voice.'Female ]
Warning-- engine sequence breach.
- Oh, God!
- Warning-- engine sequence breach.
[ Engine Whirring ]
- [ Instruments Beeping ]
- Oh, could this day get any worse?
Alan, my office... now.
- It just did.
- [ Sighs ]
I can't believe it.
We're so b-b-busted.
Look at this.
What is it?
Looks like some sort of...
gallium electrolyte compound.
We've got to get out
of here.
Dad, I know you're mad.
I shouldn't have been in the ship,
but if you just give me a minute--
You're damn right!
You shouldn't have
been in there!
But nothing happened, Dad.
I had it under control.
''Under control''?
You have any idea the importance
of secrecy in our operation?
You fired up a Thunderbird
without activating
the anti-detection shield.
You put everyone in danger
when you act selfishly.
You want to be part of the team?
You have to play by the rules.
You understand?
Do you?
Yeah, I understand.
I understand you don't want me
to be a Thunderbird.
You don't want me to do anything.!
You won't even listen to me when I'm
trying to tell you something important.!
I've heard enough.
You're grounded
for the rest of spring break.
But, Dad!
Bottom line, Alan--
- You need to grow up.
- Then let me.
Please.
[ Phone Ringing ]
Hey,John.
I was just about to turn in.
What can I do for you?
I could sure use a pizza.
You know a place that delivers?
[Jeff]
Thirty minutes or it's free, right?
Anything else on your mind?
Well, got a forest fire in Vladivostok,
a typhoon heading for Singapore.
- What's happening on Planet Tracy?
- Alan's home for spring break.
Yeah. I thought I could see
a storm brewing in your region.
Teenagers.
Well, we've all been there.
And, Dad, you've done a great job
since Mom died.
Thanks,John.
Keep an eye on that typhoon for us,
and, uh, I'll call vladivostok
and see if they need any help
with that fire.
F.A.B., Dad. Sleep tight.
[ Panting ]
Morning, Dad.
Hey, Son.
There's something
I'd like to sh-sh-sh--
Here. Take a look.
[ Device Buzzing ]
The neural-net control system?
It's great to have you back.
[ Chuckles ]
I'll bet you didn't think
spring break was gonna be
this wo-wo-wo-- fun.
Watch this.
[ Whirring ]
And the tiny phone lifts up.
[ Whirring Continues ]
Perfect.
Dad, it--
- [ Loud Bang ]
- [ Thud ]
[ Whirring Stops ]
[ Gasps ]
Uhh, ne-ne-ne--
Almost perfect.
There's something I wanted
to talk to you about, Dad.
Oh, right. Oh.
O-Okay. Right.
Having problems with--
with a ga-ga-ga-ga--
ch-ch-ch-- wo--
female?
N-N-No. No.
Alan and I found
some sort of gallium compound
on the nose cone of Thunderbird 1.
W-We should check that out
st-st-st-- immediately.
Oh, that'd be
goo-goo-goo-- swell!
- The island is in sight.
- Transom, I need you.
[ Woman ]
Yes, sir.!
Sir, our cloaking devices
evaded their detection systems.
We have a positive visual
from the tracking solution
from Thunderbird... 1.
- Mullion.
- Sir!
Sir, armed and ready.
Shall I target the main structure?
Why would I want to destroy
what will soon be mine?
One of the principal tenets
of Eastern martial arts...
is to use your opponent's
strength against him.
This is ridiculous!
It would be almost impossible...
to force the Thunderbirds
to leave their island.
On the other hand,
it requires no effort at all
to let them go.
The Thunderbirds' purpose is to rescue.
All we need to do is give them a victim.
- Commence targeting.
- Straightaway, sir.
Target acquisition
ofThunderbird 5... is locked.
- Fire.
- [ Display Whirring ]
[ Alarm Sounding ]
[ Computer ]
Red alert.!
- What the--
- Warning--impact imminent.
Thunderbird 5 to Tracy Island!
Mayday! Mayday!
-[ Computer ] Red alert.!
-[ Klaxon Blaring ]
Red alert.!
[ Brains ] Switching
to command and control center.
How bad, Brains?
Thunderbird 5,
major damage sustained.
Possible mm-mm-fu--
Possible strike by a mm--
Meteor.
Yep.
Thunderbirds are go.
Check retros.
[ Scott ]
Go.
[ Rockets Igniting ]
[ Computer ]
Guidance systems green.
[Jeff]
Go to maximum thrust.
There goes the cavalry.
But who will rescue the rescuers?
Alan.! Tintin.!
[ Panting ]
Thunderbird 5 has been hit!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Don't panic! Don't panic!
On the other hand--
[ All Shouting ]
Run!
[ Whirring ]
- We made land.
- Cut them off.
Activating
communications blackout.
[ Computer ]
Warning--intruder alert.
Communications failure.
What the he-he--
devil is going on?
Communications failure.
Mr. Tracy, do you copy?
Warning--intruder alert.
Thunderbird 3,
please respond.
[ Instruments Chirping, Buzzing ]
How did they find the island?
Do you think it was what I did
in Thunderbird 1 ?
Do you think
I ruined everything?
No!
That compound we found could have
some sort of transmitting capability.
We have to do something.
My dad's in the control room,
but...
how do we get there now?
The vents.
Let's go!
We have to get a message
to my dad!
[ Computer ]
Emergency power to 1 0%.
I'm losing all power!
Repeat--
Hold on,John!
We're coming in!
[Jeff] Gordon, prepare
for immediate docking.
[ Gordon ] You got it, Dad.
Reverse main thrusters
on my mark. Three, two, one.
Easy. Watch the roll.
Roll index angle,
minus two degrees.
[ Computer ]
Initiate docking sequence.
We're locked on.
[Jeff]
Nice work.
[ Computer ]
Docking sequence complete.
Tunnel hatch secure!
Emergency packs, boys!
Let's move!
[ Computer ]
Air lock pressure equalized.
[ Panel Beeping ]
- We're in! Let's go!
- [ Air Hissing ]
John!
Scott, tackle that fire!
Am I glad to see you guys.
Easy. You're hurt.
virgil, take care of your brother.
Gordon, give me a damage assessment.
- Come on! Hurry!
- [ Device Whining ]
[ Twittering ]
One-inch steel plate...
with sequential
titanium locking mechanism.
[ Neck Bones Cracking ]
I love a challenge.
[ Fermat Whispering ]
Watch out for the guards.
[ Alan ]
Get in! Get in!
♪♪ [ Whistling ]
Who-Who-Who-Who--
What's going on?
So this is Mount Olympus.
And these are the Thunderbirds.
I should've guessed--
JeffTracy,
the billionaire ex-astronaut,
of course.
Isn't he the one who lost
his wife in an accident?
Avalanche, wasn't it?
How tragic.
[ Alan Whispering ]
Just keep going straight ahead.
Okay.
Professor Hackenbacker?
We met at last year's
international conference
on nanotechnology.
I thought your thesis
on neutrinos was...
extremely... stimulating.
- Transom, concentrate!
- Sorry, sir.
[ Device Twittering ]
The command control
switch is here.
Fingerprint recognition system.
Professor! Please!
- Activate the control switch.
- Nuh-nuh. Nuh, nuh--
- You must be kidding.
- Professor, you and I share
an interest in the science of the mind.
The difference is,
I was born with my powers.
Trust me when I tell you,
you've barely touched the surface.
Even the strongest minds
can be broken.
- It would be a pity to break yours.
- Fu-Fu--
- No way.
- Activate the control switch, Prof.
[ The Hood ]
Like a puppet on a string.
[ Maniacal Laugh ]
[ Straining Grunts ]
- [ Device Humming ]
- [ Groans ]
[ Computer ]
Activating command and control.
[ Beeping, Whirring ]
[ Klaxon Blaring ]
- [ Gas Hissing ]
- [ Whirring ]
[ Hissing ]
We have control.
Get up!
Sorry, Professor.
Nothing personal.
[ Buzzer Buzzing ]
- We got a constant warning light
on our E.P.S. system!
- Attempt manual override!
No! That's negative!
- [ Alan Whispering ] That's it.
- Okay. This one.
Back to Thunderbird 3 now.
John, got to move.
[ Groans ]
[ Electronic Chirp ]
The locking mechanism's jammed!
Attention, Thunderbird 5.
As you can see, I have taken over
your facilities.
- You no longer control
your operational systems.
- [ Image Beeps Off]
[ Alan ]
They've taken over.
Warm them up, Transom.
[ Transom ]
Increasing temperature to maximum.
- Who's the bald freak?
- You?
-[ Mind Waves Oscillating ]
- [ Grunts ]
- Dad!
- [ Groaning ]
They've got... my dad.
[Jeff]
Okay. You have our attention.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Oh, how rude of me!
You can... call me The Hood.
Now, listen, Mr. Tracy
We won't be negotiating.
I'm going to use the Thunderbirds
to rob the largest banks in the world,
starting with the Bank of London.
The world's monetary system
will be thrown into chaos
and the Thunderbirds held responsible.
- [ Scott ] You'll never get away with it!
- Why the Thunderbirds?
- An eye for an eye, Mr. Tracy.
- ''An eye for an eye''?
Perhaps you've forgotten me,
but surely you remember
saving the life of my brother,
- Kyrano.
- [ Gasps ]
I'm sorry, Mr. Tracy.
- [ Kyrano ]
I thought he was dead.
- [ Laughs ]
- Take them away.
- [ Mullion ] Yes, sir.
Whoa.
That makes
The Hood my uncle?
[ Whispering ]
Every family has a black sh-sh--
Black sh--
[ Loud Sneeze ]
[ Clears Throat ]
These vents
are murder on my allergies.
You left me to die that day.
You may have broken my body,
but you've no idea how powerful
my mind has become.
Now, you will suffer,
as I suffered...
waiting for a rescue that will never come.
- Wait!
- [ Power Whirs Off]
Scott, status report.
CO2 levels are rising.
All right. Wire the oxygen scrubber
to the emergency batteries.
- Clean the air.
- How long will that give us?
About four hours.
[ Fermat Gasping ]
- [ Partially Muffled Sneeze ]
- [ Mullion ] Someone's there.
- [ Fermat Gasping For Air ]
- Time to go!
[ Gasping Continues ]
[ Fermat Cries Out ]
- [ Snarling ]
- [ Hand Bones Crunching ]
[ Agonized Scream ]
[ Tintin ]
Run.! Run.!
[ Alan ] No.!Jump.!
You can get through to the silos.
[ All Yelling ]
Apparently,
the island is not as secure
as you thought.
Children.!
Did you find any children?
Here they are.
Thunderbird 2 silo,
in the loading arm.
- Seal them in.
- [ Controller Squealing ]
- [ Alan ] Hold on!
- [ All Yelling ]
- [ Tintin ]
The doors,you guys.! Let's go.! Come on.!
- [ Fermat ] Go! Go!
[ Doors Crashing Shut ]
This way!
[ Fermat ] No!
[ Tintin ]
They've got us trapped.
[ Tintin ] What do we do now?
[ Fermat ]
If we can get to Thunderbird 1 silo,
we can escape
through the service tunnel.
But we need
a plan, Alan!
I'll use
the Thunderizer on the door.
- [ Computer ] Elevator active.
- [ Alan ] You guys
get the goons with the Firefly.
Alan.! This equipment
is only to be used in an emergency.!
- I guess this qualifies.
- Yeah.
- [ Grunts ]
- Here they come!
- Fermat, can you drive this thing?
- Uh, no.
- [ Grunts ]
- Hey, watch it!
I took microbiology,
not driver's ed!
- Set the pressure to maximum.
- Got it.
Retreat!
- [ Computer Squealing ]
- [ Yelling ]
Whoo.!
[ Henchmen Yelling ]
- [ Yelling Continues ]
- Let's move it!
[ Beeping, Twittering ]
That's it.
- [ Rapid Beeping ]
- Time to Thunderize.
- Yes!
- [ Groaning ]
- Come on! Let's go!
- [ Grunting ] Get 'em!
[ Alan ]
Where's Fermat?
Fermat!
Coming.!
[ Alan ]
Hurry up.!
[ Grunting ]
What were you doing
back there, Fermat?
I had an nuh-nuh-- idea.
Just try and keep up, okay?
I'll open the tunnel.
We got to keep moving.
[ Keypad Beeping ]
[ Computer ] Access denied.
Go back.
Yell when you see them coming.
- [ Beeping ]
- Access denied.
Alan.
You can run if you want.
[ Takes Deep Breath ]
Were you surprised to hear
what your father did to me?
It is frightening when we realize
our parents aren't perfect.
But perhaps you already suspected
that about your father.
Why did he build
these magnificent machines?
Do you suppose it was guilt?
Because he let your mother die.
Open the door, Alan.
[ Chuckles ]
Open... the... door.
We can't go this way!
[ Sobs ]
He's there.
[ Door Whirs Open ]
No! Ow!
What are we gonna do, Alan?
[ Alan ]
I don't know. I'm thinkin, okay?
[ Whimpering ]
Keep backin' up.
I've got an idea.
[ Stone Ricochets ]
[ Chuckling ]
- That's your idea?
- It's not me you're angry at, Alan.
It's not you I'm aiming at.
- [ All Screaming ]
- Get them!
- Transom, fire up Thunderbird 1.!
- [ Whirring ]
- And set to broil!
- [ Screaming ]
[ Screaming, Yelling ]
[ Blipping, Twittering ]
[ Transom ] No sign of them.
[ Mullion ] Of course not.
The little brats went up
like firecrackers.
Pop! Pop! Pop!
- [ Laughing ]
- [ Enraged Blubbering ]
-Don't...
- [ Grunts ]
give him the satisfaction,
Professor.
[ Brains Groaning ]
This has taken too long.
Pick out the equipment you need...
to get into those banks
and load it into Thunderbird 2.
- No more delays.
- Yes, sir.
[ Coughing ]
[ Fermat ]
How about a little warning
before you pull a stunt like that?
Relax, Fermat.
It's just a little water.
I could have drowned.
[ Gagging ]
You mean you can't swim?
[ Coughs ] I repeat--
I could have drowned!
[ Alan Grunts ]
I said I was sorry, Fermat.
Let's just put this behind us, okay?
Got to watch
each other's backs.
Nice drawers.
Thank you.
Boo! Whoo!
- No! Come on! Tintin, stay there!
- You're worse than a couple of girls.
Hurry up and get dressed.
Those are nice drawers.
[ Giggles ]
[ Fermat ]
Data from Tracy Island is sent
to Thunderbird 5 via satellite, right?
Right.
So there's
a minuscule possibility...
that if we reach
the island satellite station,
we could--
Blow it up.
No, we could hack into it...
and give control
back to Thunderbird 5.
Good thinking, Fermat.
Thank you.
All right, let's do it.
[ Groans ]
Here's the plan.
We're here, right?
So we go along the shore,
around the base of the mountain
to the access road here.
And then up to the transmitter.
So what do you think?
Good. Except that
we're here, not there,
And the transmitter is there
and not here.
We have to go through the jungle.
But that's for-for--
off-limits.
It's gonna be dangerous.
I'm in.
[ Alan ]
We got to get up there fast.
All our folks are in trouble,
and ifThe Hood gets off the island--
Actually, he's not going
anywhere for now.
[ Laughs ]
This is the guidance processor
for Thunderbird 2.
It can't take off without it.
Fermat, you're a genius.
How'd you get this?
Alan, my friend, what you
don't know can't hurt you.
[ Cell Phone Ringing ]
[ Lady Penelope ]
Parker.
Milady.
- We have an emergency.
- [ Watch Twitters ]
What a charming fellow.
[ Knocking ]
Come in.
Have a look at this, Parker.
He and this woman--
poor girl--
both work for this man,
known as The Hood.
Sounds like an alias to me, milady.
Quite right, Parker.
Real name Trangh Belagant,
assumed dead
when his illegal diamond mine
collapsed in the jungles of Malaya.
Oh, perfect, Parker.
The Thunderbirds rescued over
500 mine workers in the collapse,
including Mr. Belagant's brother.
Milady, that's Mr. Tracy's
loyal manservant, Kyrano.
How's my schedule for today, Parker?
Eh, you have clay pigeon shooting
with Lord Marlborough,
a benefit gala
for the Institute of the Blind,
and, incidentally,
there's a typhoon
bearing down on Singapore.
I suppose that's urgent.
Yes, milady.
There is also
a bridge collapse in Buenos Aires
and a volcanic eruption in Jakarta.
- The Thunderbirds still haven't responded?
- No, milady.
And the media is awash in speculation
vis-á-vis their whereabouts.
Over the Lisa Lowe.
Chuck, disaster after disaster
around the world today...
and still no sight
of the Thunderbirds.
Typhoon Jago hit land
in Singapore just one hour ago,
and thousands
have been left homeless
by a volcano in Jakarta.
Only the Thunderbirds have
the incredible machines to carry out--
[ Report Continues ]
I think it's time to send out
the emergency signal, Parker.
I fear you're not wrong, milady.
- Lisa Lowe. Back to you, Chuck.
- [ Bell Chimes, Buzzer Buzzes ]
[ Buzzing Continues ]
[ Footsteps Sloshing ]
[ Alan Grunting ]
I'm telling you, Fermat.
It was-- It was like The Hood
was inside of my head back there.
- What do you mean, Alan?
- [ Fly Buzzing ]
Maybe he can read minds or--
or control minds or something.
Don't be silly, Alan.
Everything can be explained
by science.
I'm just trying to figure out
his weakness. Everybody has
an Achilles'heel, right?
Well, my Achilles' heel
is actually my Achilles heel.
It's got a blister
the size of a basketball.
[ Chuckles ]
Tintin.!
- Can we s-s--
- Stop?
- Yes!
- No!
[ Sighs ]
Okay!
[ Grunts ]
No more cheeseburgers
for you, Fermat.
Any word?
Nothing, milady.
Right. You'll have to tell Lord Marlborough
that I've broken my shooting arm.
We shall send the Institute
of the Blind a dozen guide dogs.
- And bring the car around.
- Yes, milady.
The Thunderbirds
appear to be in a spot of trouble,
and I don't like that.
Let's go, Parker.
Ready for launch.
We'll use this to get into the vaults.
Subtle as usual, Mullion.
I didn't realize we'd be
getting points for style.
We're robbing banks, remember?
Don't worry.
You'll get your money.
Transom, initiate preflight diagnostics.
- [ Buttons Clicking ]
- [ Turbines Whining ]
- [ Rattling ]
- [ Alarm Wailing ]
- What's going on?
- [ Button Clicking ]
[ Computer ]
Guidance processor error.
- It's the guidance processor!
- [ Mullion ] What's wrong with it?
- There isn't one.
- [ Groans ]
Clever, Alan.
It's the children.
They have it.
No way.
They're dead.
No one could live through
something like that.
I did.
Get them, Mullion.
Take whatever you need.
And make sure you get
the guidance processor
before you lose your temper.
[ Fermat Whimpering ]
Alan, don't you think
Tintin is blossoming?
''Blossoming''?
What's that supposed to mean?
Come on, Alan.
You have a cr-cr-- crush on her.
You got to be kiddin'!
I mean, she's--
She's not that bad,
I guess.
Okay, guys, take five!
[ Fermat ]
Five isn't gonna do it.
[ Alan, Fermat
Breathing Heavily ]
Guys?
[ Groaning, Panting ]
- Don't move.
- [ Grunts ]
What is it?
Androctonus scorpion.
- Is that dangerous?
- Point-025 milligrams of its venom...
is fatal.
So, dangerous is, in fact,
an understatement.
[ Fermat ]
Watch out.!
- Tintin, what was that?
- Let's get going.
Hey! She has the same powers
as her uncle-- The Hood.
Do you think?
It must run in the family.
[ Alan ]
Did you do that?
Just drop it, okay?
Still think everything
can be explained by science?
Not girls!
[ Alarm Wailing ]
[ Groaning ]
- [Jeff] Scott! Gordon! You all right?
- [ Gordon ] We're okay! [ Coughs ]
The heat exchanger's blown!
[ Coughing ]
You don't say.
Come on!
Those brats are in here
somewhere!
- How we doin', Fermat?
- Don't rush me, Alan.
This is very d-delicate equipment.
[ Cries Out ]
Which is now... b-broken.
Can you fix it?
Ye-Ye--
Maybe but...
I'll need something
to solder with.
We're in the middle of nowhere, Fermat.
Where are you gonna find
something like that?
What?
[ Scream Echoing ]
Ow!
[ Groans ]
Perfect.
Gee, Alan, I never would have
figured you for a crybaby.
- [ Muffled ]
I'm gonna kill you.
- What'd he say?
- I think it was some sort
of an apology.
- [ Crunch ]
Mm.
I think that's-- I got it. Yes!
You're the m-m-man, Fermat.
Okay.
- [ Device Beeps ]
- The first step is to establish contact
with Thunderbird 5.
-Dad.!
- [John ]
It's Alan!
- Alan! Where are you? Are you safe?
- I'm at the satellite relay station
with Fermat and Tintin.
Fermat's gonna hack into
the main computer system and
give control of Thunderbird 5 back to you.
- We're standing by.
- Okay. We're almost there.
[ Gasps ]
Goodness me, Professor.
You're so good-looking
without your glasses on.
I think you may find that's another thing
we have in common.
Pretty?
[ Computer ]
Unauthorized transmission.
Oh, now that's not fair!
[ Alarm Beeping ]
Just when things
were starting to sizzle.
Unauthorized transmission.
A burst of transmission
from the island satellite station.
- Should I jam it?
- And give Mullion the coordinates.
[ Transom, Over Radio ]
Take the main track southeast.
Then head up Satellite Hill.
[ Device Beeping ]
They're onto us!
We're being jammed!
- Can you finish?
- I'll try.
- Alan, what's happening?
- Hang in there, Dad.
One more minute, okay?
-[ Beeping Continues ]
- It's not going to work, Alan.
The signal's too weak
for data transmission.
[ Transmission Static ]
Dad, can you hear me?
They're jamming this signal.
We're gonna lose you. Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
That's a negative.
It's too dangerous.
Follow emergency procedure.
Wait for Lady Penelope
at the rendezvous point.
Alan, can you read me? Al--
- Dad! Dad!
- Alan, we're losing you! Alan!
[ Breath Quavers ]
Well.
[ Fermat ] No!
[ Alan ]
Useless!
You--
It is now.
I'm sorry, Alan.
This is hard on all of us.
No. It's okay.
I'm fine.
You don't have to be
such a tough guy, Alan.
I'm worried about my dad too.
I'd do anything
to be with my parents right now.
But The Hood knows
we're alive now.
We have to go.
Even worse.
They know exactly...
[ Engine Roaring ]
where we are!
Come on!
[ All Screaming ]
Oh, great! More water.
Tintin!
Can you slow 'em down?
I'd be delighted.
Then do it,
and meet us at the junkyard.
Come on, Fermat!
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
This'll get us outta here.
- There! Come on!
- [ Buzzing ]
[ Branch Creaks ]
Straight ahead.
[ Grunts ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Buzzing ]
It's gonna make this thing
hard to control, you know.
No problem.
You really must be careful not
to exceed four bars of boost or else--
I said no problem.
[ Tintin ] Guys, let's go!
We gotta get outta here!
What is this?
It's a hoversled.
It's our ticket outta here,
unless you've got a better idea.
- Yeah. Let's wait for Lady Penelope,
like your dad said.
- Here.
Great plan. Let's sit here
and wait to get caught.
I say we have to do something--
now. Right, Fermat?
Actually, I agree with Tintin.
I don't think this is s-s-safe.
You don't think anything
is s-s-safe.
Just because I s-s-stutter...
doesn't mean that I'm wrong.
If we're a team,
we should make decisions
as a team.
Do you guys wanna sit here
and take a vote, or do you
wanna get outta here?
'Cause I'm going.
You can be a real jerk
sometimes.
- [ Engine Starts ]
- [ Tintin ] Yeah!
[ Growling ]
[ All Whooping]
Go! Go!
[ Continue Whooping ]
[ Tintin ]
Oh, no!
Come on! Faster!
Alan! You're going too fast!
-[ Fermat ] Alan.!
- I need more speed
to get above the trees.
- Hang on!
- [ Fermat Yelling ]
[ Both Whimpering ]
[ Both Grunt ]
[ Buzzing ]
What'd I tell you guys?
Oh, no.
[ Hoversled Zooms ]
[ Fermat Struggling ]
[ Tintin ]
What are you doing?
Oh, no!
Not the fridge!
Tintin.
- That's it, Son.
- Sweetheart, are you okay?
- I'm fine, Dad.
Cool off, kid!
[ Laughing ]
Tracy Island approaching, milady.
Switching to aqua mode.
Isn't life fun sometimes?
Rib-ticklin', milady.
- [ Beeping ]
- [ The Hood ] What is it?
We have an unidentified craft
approaching the island
at high speed.
Lady P.
Hoo! Somebody roll down a window.
It's gettin' a little hot in here.
Reentry into Earth's atmosphere
in 37 minutes.
Oxygen's out at 30,
so we won't feel a thing.
Stop it.
Come on, Dad.
- The situation's hopeless.
- No, it's not. There's still time.
We've got people on the ground
working for us.
- Alan? He's just a kid.
- He's a Tracy.
[ Electrical Burst ]
This doesn't look good, Parker.
No, milady.
That bougainvillea
is absolutely parched,
and someone should do something
about that hideous hammock.
[ The Hood ]
Whom do we have here? Mullion.
I must warn you...
that I know judo, krav maga...
and tae kwon do.
And I know Parker.
Milady.
[ Groans ]
You've broken my nose.
Yes. That was very much
the intention of the maneuver.
- [ Transom Yelps ]
- One tries so hard in life...
to sort things out
on an intellectual/conversational level.
- But sometimes, it's just... not... possible.
- [ Yelping ] Oh!
[ Transom ]
Ow! Ohh!
- [ Mullion Grunts ]
- Shall I bring the car around, milady?
Parker, have a bit of a lie-down.
- Excuse me, milady.
- [ Grunts ]
[ Growls ]
Ah.
[ Applauding ]
Lady Penelope.
- Of course. He has his palace.
Why not his princess?
- Flattery will get you nowhere.
Ow. Have you any idea
what a manicure costs these days?
Ow!
[ Crashes ]
- Boo!
- [ Yells ]
Coming through, milady.
[ Both Yelping ]
[ Parker ]
Duck, milady.!
He's weak.
Using his power
makes him weak.
[ Growling ]
- Whoa!
- You're a formidable opponent,
Lady Penelope.
- More than a match for most men.
- That's not saying much then, is it?
[ Grunts, Screaming ]
[ Straining ]
I suggest you let us pass.
Don't try your parlor games on me,
you sad, little man.
- [ Mocking ] Oh.
- You committed a serious crime
trespassing on this island.
And in about... four seconds,
I'm going to get
quite cross with you.
[ Straining ]
How are you, Alan?
[ Groaning ]
I hope you don't think
I'm going to chase you.
[ Groaning ]
You can make it stop, Alan.
- Ohh!
- You have something
that belongs to me.
Really, sir, don't mind me.
This isn't the first time
my head's been pulverized,
and it's never done any real harm before.
- [ Screaming ]
- Stop! Stop! I'll give it to you.
Fetch.
You made a match of it, Alan.
I'll give you that.
Put them with the others.
[ Mullion ]
You're comin' with me.
[ Struggling ]
Put me down.
This outfit is couture.
[ Breathing Deeply ]
Don't go to sleep.
John! Look at me.
Keep your eyes open.
- [ Mullion ]
You need to cool off,lady.
- Lady Penelope!
Big oaf!.
Right. That's quite enough losing
for one day.
[ Shuddering, Teeth Chattering ]
So, how does it feel
to be right all the time?
Not b-b-bad actually.
[ Laughs ]
I'm so sorry, Fermat.
We make quite a pair.
It's hard for me to t-t-talk.
It's hard for you to l-l-listen.
Parker, I have an idea.
Excellent, milady.
Brains.
- How long doJeff and the boys have?
- [ Shuddering ] I... can't think.
I'm too col-ol-ol--
- [ Computer ]
Guidance processor installed.
- The guidance processor has been installed.
Engine sequence complete.
Thunderbird 2 is ready for takeoff.
[ Computer ]
Begin launch sequence.
What is our E.T.A.?
Under an hour.
Bank of London,
here we come.
[ Computer ]
Thunderbird 2 preparing for takeoff.
[ Alan ]
We've gotta be quick.
The Hood's gettin'away.
- In position, milady.
- Here we go.
[ Computer ]
Launch sequence, stage two.
- Yes!
- Good shot, milady.
Come on, Parker.
Let's give the bad guys
a good thrashing.
[ Computer ]
Hydraulic systems green.
Guidance systems green.
Launch sequence, stage three.
[ Tapping ]
This seems to be a straightforward
six-lever mortise, milady.
- I love it when your checkered past
comes in handy, Parker.
- Thank you, milady.
Unfortunately, I fear
I shall need a piece of wire
to access the mechanism.
- Oh. [ Clears Throat ]
- [ All ] Oh.
[ Sproing ]
Ah. Will this suffice, Parker?
Most certainly, milady.
I didn't actually need it anyway.
Of course not, milady.
- [ Lock Beeps ]
- [ Fermat ]
Quick! They're getting away!
[ Alan ] It's okay.
Everyone get to the control room.
Your hat.
[ Alan ] Get in there quick, Fermat,
and save my family.!
Then we'll get The Hood.
- Good luck.
-[ Computer ]
Access to mainframe denied.
Looks like they slipped a back-door key
into the access codes.
I'll follow your lead, Son.
Thunderbird 5, come in.
[ Alan ]
How long have they got
before reentry?
[ Fermat ]
Ninety seconds, and counting.
- [ Computer ]
Access to mainframe confirmed.
- I'm in!
[ Alan, On Monitor]
Good job, Fermat.
Okay.
I just need someone on their end
to confirm the access protocol.
Thunderbird 5, come in.
[ Alan ]
Dad, come on.
Are we comin' through?
[ Brains ]
Mr. Tracy, can you hear me? Come in.
[ Lady Penelope ] Thunderbird 5, come in.
- [ Alan ] Dad.! Come on.!
- Mr. Tracy, can you hear me?
Come in.
- [ Keyboard Clattering ]
- Dad.!
- Thunderbird 5, come in.
- [ Alan ]
How long have they got?
- Forty-five seconds until reentry!
Damn it,Jeff!.
Wake up!
[ Monitor Beeping ]
[Jeff] I think that's the first time
you've ever called me
by my first name, Ray.
- Thanks for waking me.
- Dad!
Alan. Well done.
Mr. Tracy, confirm access protocol.
Confirmed.
We're back online.
Gravity is restored.
Put Thunderbird F-F--
your craft into geostational orbit
immediately.
- F.A.B., Brains.
- [ Computer ]
Geostationary orbit reestablished.
- Looks like we're good to go.
- [ Kids Cheering ]
- Dad, are you all right?
- We're fine. We still have a job to do.
- Where's The Hood?
- He's in Thunderbird 2, Mr. Tracy.
He's headed for Lo-Lo-Lo--
London.
- She's right.
- He's got them all on board.
Looks like Thunderbird 3
lost a booster, Dad.
We'll never get there in time.
Let me go after The Hood.
He'll destroy everything you've built,
everything the Thunderbirds stand for.
Negative. I'm sorry.
It's too risky.
I can do this.
You know I can.
What am I saying?
We can do this.
Okay, Alan.
We'll meet you there.
- Thunderbirds are go!
- F.A.B.!
Okay, boys, we are outta here!
[ Tintin ]
Are we really going?
[ Alan ] Yep.
[ Tintin ]
Oh, boy.!
You ready, Fermat?
Nuh-Nuh--
[ Sighs ]
I guess.
[ Computer ]
Engine sequence activated.
- [ Fermat ] Flight controls are green.
- [ Computer Voice Continues, Indistinct ]
Hydraulic systems are good.
Right.
Set primary fuel pumps.
- Main engine start.
- [ Spaceship Rumbling ]
Don't boys just love their toys.
[ Computer ]
Engine sequence complete.
Launch sequence initiated.
[ Alarm Sounding ]
[ Computer ]
Launch sequence complete.
And off we go.
[ Kids Cheering ]
Get the bridge up!
[ Radio Beeping ]
[ Punches Keypad ]
- Thunderbird 1, come in.
- Roger, Brains.
Situation update. Thunderbird 3
is about to initiate separation.
[ Both ]
F.A.B.
Boys, Thunderbird 2
is in final approach to London.
I know The Hood's weakness, Fermat.
I can stop him if we get there in time.
Stand by.
We're going to maximum thrust.
[ Fermat, Alan ]
Whoa.!
[Jeff]
Gordon, heat 'em up.
[ People Screaming, Shouting, Indistinct ]
We're getting reports
of some kind of incident in London
involving the Thunderbirds.
Lisa, are you there?
[ Alarm Blaring ]
I'm here in Jubilee Gardens
where Thunderbird 2 has made...
an impromptu landing,
causing total panic
in central London.
As far as we know, there has
been no emergency call
from this area,
so it's unclear
why Thunderbird 2
would be active here at all.
[ Thud ]
I don't know
if you can see this, Chuck,
but Thunderbird 2
seems to be unloading
some kind of machine.
Set a course for the vault.
[ Crowd Moans ]
[ Crowd Chattering ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Transom ] Sir, if we
continue on our present course,
we'll sever the monorail's
subterranean supports.
Shall I correct our position?
Stay on course.
But, sir,
we'll cause a major disaster.
No, we won't.
The Thunderbirds will.
[ Child Whimpers ]
- Let's get her down, boys.
- Initiate landing, Fermat.
- Right.
-[ Computer ]
Three-point landing sequence initiated.
Retros to 75.
- Flaps to 1 6.
- F.A.B.
[ Alarm Beeping ]
[ Computer ]
Danger. Landing-sequence error.
- You're going too fast!
- Thanks.
Retros to 90.
- [ Loud Thump ]
- [ Fermat ] It's down!
- Textbook, boys.
- [ Kids Gasping ]
Activating electromagnetic pulse
to disable the bank security systems.
[ Mullion ]
E. T.A., one minute.
- Parker, meet me at the Bank of London.
- [ Over Phone ] Yes, milady.
- Ride it out, boys.
- [ Teeth Chattering ]
The Hood's getting away.
Those people can't hold on
much longer.
- What are you gonna do, Alan?
- We're the Thunderbirds.
Our duty is to save those people.
Brains, we're going
into the accident zone.
F.A.B., Thunderbird 2.
And good luck.
- [ People Screaming ]
- [ Gasps ]
Brains! The monorail is down!
Repeat! The monorail is down!
- [ Punches Keypad ]
- I'm going underwater in Thunderbird 4.!
[ Computer ]
Automatic pilot.
You have the bridge.
- Me? Fly Alone?
- Fermat, the Thunderbirds
need you right now.
I need you.
[ Exhales ]
F.A.B., Alan.
[ Punches Keypad ]
- [ Computer ]
Manual Control.
- [ Exhales ]
- Brains, come in. What's the situation?
- The Hood has caused
a major disaster with the Mole.
The mono-mono-mono--
one-track railway is down in the Thames.
- Where's Thunderbird 1?
- It's on the ground.
- The ki-ki-kids are in Thunderbird 2.
- F.A.B. We're right behind 'em.
- [ Mullion ] Look at all this gold.
- [ The Hood ] Stay focused, Mullion.
Nine more banks to go.
Fermat. Deploying Thunderbird 4
in three, two,
one.!
Thunderbird 4 is go.
I can see the monorail.
- [ Screaming, Muffled ]
- Mommy!
[ Shouting, Indistinct ]
- Don't panic, guys.
- [ Shouting, Muffled ] Help me!
[ Computer ]
Extending magnetic claw.
Fermat, I'll hold the monorail in place.
Can you get a line on that stanchion
and lift it up?
I can't get a clear fix
on the target.
- I might hit the passengers.
- I'll go and fix it myself.
- What, you mean swim?
- Get me as close as you can.
[ Whimpers ]
How we doin' on that line, Fermat?
Just look out your window.
Come on, Tintin.
Come on.
You can do this.
[ Laughs ]
Opening the air lock.
[ Computer ]
Contact magnets activated.
Okay, Fermat, we need a lift.
[ Fermat ]
F.A.B., Alan.
Commencing reverse thrust.
[ Whimpers ]
What's that?
That was amazing, Tintin.
Thank you.
[ Alan ]
Nicejob, Fermat.
Nothing to it really.
Easy does it.
[ All Chattering ]
Hold on.
[ Sirens Wailing ]
- [ Scott ] There they are!
- [ Everyone Cheering ]
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Way to go, Alan!
I'm glad you could
finally join us.
Don't go getting cocky
after one mission.
We still have
a dangerous situation here.
I need you boys
to close down this accident scene.
Tintin, go get Fermat.
Meet us at Thunderbird 1.
Alan, you come with me.
We gotta get to the Bank of London fast.
Lady Penelope went after The Hood.
I know.
She may need our help.
Ashes to ashes.
Diamonds to diamonds.
Lady Penelope.
What an unpleasant surprise.
Don't be rude.
I can't tell you what a pleasure it would be
to use my little finger to pull this big trigger.
- Now don't move.
- Mullion.
- Oh! That's not cricket!
- I'm sorry!
The only part of sport
I ever liked was winning.
How ghastly. Oh!
Hey, Dad, that stuffThe Hood said
about you leavin' him to die.
[ Punching Keypad ]
He was lying, right?
No.
You see, you can't
save everyone, Alan.
It doesn't matter how hard you try
or how brave you are.
It doesn't even matter
if it's someone you love,
someone you'd give up your life
in a second to save.
You just can't save everyone.
What was Mom like?
She was a lot like you.
Come on.
We got a job to do.
Finish her off, Mullion.
Shame on you.
I always despise a man
who delegates the importantjobs.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh! Dream on, sad act.
[ Chortling ]
[Jeff] Good timing, Parker.
Good afternoon, Mr. Tracy.
Come with us!
My pleasure, Mr. Tracy.
[ Laughing ]
The Thunderbirds.
They're here.
Kill them all.
Alan, you guys stay here
with Parker.
- I'm gonna go find Lady Penelope.
- But what about The Hood?
Look out, Parker!
- Master Tracy.!
- Oh, look out, Parker!
All right. That's enough of that.
Don't move.
-Go on then.
- No, sorry. I can't hit a lady.
- Allow me.
- Oh!
I've been waiting
to get my hands
on you little brats.
And I've been waitin'
to get my hands on you.
[ Knuckles Crack ]
[ Groans, Gasping ]
Now that was a punch.
Parker, can you wrap this up?
What did you have in mind,
Master Hackenbacker?
Well, strategically speaking,
the best odds of success
lie with the Parker haymaker.
- I concur.
- [ Groans ]
- Penny.
-Jeff, no!
Did you save them all
this time,Jeff?
Or did you leave
someone behind?
I didn't make you what you are.
It's not me you have to convince.
- You leave my son out of this!
- [ Lady Penelope ]Jeff!.
- Dad!
Look, out, Dad! Dad!
I'm disappointed in you, Alan.
I thought we were kindred spirits.
Well, we're not.
I'm JeffTracy's son.
Yes, you certainly are.
[Jeff] No.!
Alan, no! Don't!
- [ Grunts ]
- Alan!
[ Mutters ]
Come here,you little minx.!
Oh!
[ Groans ]
- Bye-bye.
- Oh.!
[ Murmurs ]
Alan, stay back!
You want so desperately
to walk in daddy's footsteps.
[ Out Of Breath, Choking ]
[ Choking ]
[Jeff]
Let him go.!
Did you really think
you could challenge me?
-[ Alan ] Let him go.! Please.!
-[ Lady Penelope ] Let him go.!
-[ Continues Choking ]
-[Jeff] Please.! Let him go.!
- [ Lady Penelope ]
Alan! Alan, are you all right?
- [ Alan Coughs ]
Alan! Get out! Run!
-He's getting weaker.
He can't last much longer.
- Neither can you.
[Jeff]
Alan, no.!
Look out.!
Alan!
I'm glad you could be here
to see this,Jeff.
[ Groaning ]
- [ Gasps ]
- Good-bye, Alan.
[ Groaning ]
- No!
- [ Gasps ]
Ha!
Oh.
Ah.
[ Sighs, Gasping ]
Leave me, Alan.
Leave me to die--
[ Gasps ]
like your father did.
I don't want to save your life.
[ Gasps ]
Ah.
But it's what we do.
[ Laughs ]
[ The Hood Sighing ]
[ Spacecraft Zooming ]
See you soon,Jeff.
Now, that was definitely
showin' off.
[ Policemen Chattering ]
[ Mullion ]
Get off of me!
[ Policemen Shouting, Indistinct ]
[ Chattering ]
[John ]
That was a nice catch.
[ Gordon ] Hey, Scott.
[ Gordon, Laughing ] Get him.!
[ Lady Penelope ]Jeff, what
did you put in these margaritas?
It's a Tracy secret.
[ Laughing ]
- [ Laughing ]
- [ Out Of Breath ]
That's my boy.
[ Grunts ]
One more week, and you're
gonna be swimmin' like a fi-fi-fi--
dol-dol-dol-- sh-sh-sh--
aquatic creature.
Good job, Ferm.
Thanks.
So, what do you think?
He's gettin' there.
Whoa. Tintin.
You'rejust really, um,
blossoming.
-Eww! Did you say ''blossoming''?
- [ Triangle Clanging ]
Gather around, everybody.
I have an announcement to make.
Tonight is a special night.
We're all together because of
three very special people--
Fermat, Tintin, Alan.
The world needs Thunderbirds,
and the Thunderbirds need you.
[ Gasps ]
Mr. Tracy.
- Thank you, sir.
- [ Sniffling ]
Congratulations, Alan.
No shortcuts.
You earned it.
You all did.
I'm not usually an emotional man,
but sometimes
even the toughest nut must crack.
Way to go, sprout!
That's my boy, Alan!
That's my brother!
[ Whooping, Yelling ]
- [ Laughing ]
- [ Chattering ]
-[ Cell Phone Beeping ]
-[ Gordon ] Come on, Alan.!
Yes, Madame President.
I see. Of course. Straightaway.
Boys. Sorry, Penny.
Duty calls.
Of course it does.
And quite right too.
Thunderbirds are go!
Fast as you can, Parker.
Certainly, milady.
♪ Weapons underground
keeping our planet safe and sound ♪
♪If someone evil's coming 'round
they should be frightened ♪
♪Frightened ♪
♪ 'Cause now the boys are back in town ♪
♪No strings to hold them down ♪
♪Down ♪
♪Don't be mad
Please stop the hating ♪
♪Just be glad that they'll be waiting ♪
♪Friends we have are ever-changing ♪
♪ You know
now the lid's about to blow ♪
♪ When the Thunderbirds are go ♪
♪ The kids are learning fast
They know the T-birds kick some ass ♪
♪Be sure that there's no comin'last
if you're on their side ♪
♪ Their side ♪
♪It always looks so cool
when spaceships come out of the pool ♪
♪ You know that you'djust be a fool
to be a bad guy ♪
♪Bad guy ♪
♪ 'Cause now the boys are back in town ♪
♪No strings to hold them down ♪
♪Down ♪
♪Don't be mad
Please stop the hating ♪
♪Just be glad that they'll be waiting ♪
♪Friends we have are ever-changing ♪
♪ You know
now the lid's about to blow ♪
♪ When the Thunderbirds are go ♪
♪♪
♪ Thunderbirds are go
go, go, go, go, go, go ♪
♪Don't be mad
Please stop the hating ♪
♪Just be glad that they'll be waiting ♪
♪Friends we have are ever-changing ♪
♪ You know
now the lid's about to blow ♪
♪ When the Thunderbirds are go ♪
♪ Thunderbirds are go ♪
♪ The Thunderbirds are go ♪
♪ Yeah, the Thunderbirds are go ♪
♪ Thunderbirds are
Thunderbirds are ♪
♪ Thunderbirds are go ♪♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org