Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
♪
Anybody home?
( knocking )
Walter?
Newscaster: ...complete
with emergency vehicles
from as far away as Oakland.
Fire crews from Union City
have joined Newmont detachments
from all seven stations,
and although the fire
is contained,
it still burns fiercely
inside the food court itself.
Now, early reports
point to a gas main
ruptured by a PG&E repair crew
as the cause of the explosion
in the food court, but
this has yet to be confirmed.
Oh, my God.
Once again, there was a tragic
explosion earlier this evening
at the Newmont shopping mall.
Ten lives have been lost,
and the list of the injured
continues to grow.
Yup.
This is Michelle Gould
reporting live from Newmont.
Hungry?
Yeah.
My princess,
I bring you
savory shish kebabs
made by authentic
savage Pakis.
I wanted fried chicken, Ali.
But this is better.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Is Walter home?
No.
Let me just check.
Just a sec, just a sec.
Voicemail: Hey, it's Walter.
Leave a message.
He's not picking up.
Let me check the machine.
Okay.
( beeping )
Walter: Hey, Mom, Dad.
My phone died, again,
and this was the only number
I could remember.
Anyway, I'm going over
to the mall.
Can one of you pick me up?
I'll just hang in the
food court. See you later.
( alarms wailing )
I'll call you.
Man: Excuse me, ma'am.
It's dislocated!
Please, I just-- No, no.
I've got to go in.
I've got to get--
I think my kid is in there!
Ma'am, please step back!
Excuse me, I have a real
reason to go in there.
My son was at the mall today,
and I haven't been able
to reach him, so I--
Look, lady, nobody
is getting in here tonight!
There must be someone who can
tell me if he's in there or not!
Talk to the officer
out by the front entrance.
He has a number
that you can call.
Reporter: At approximately
4:15 P.M., a gas line exploded
near the north side
of the building.
We have to stress that
we do not have confirmation
as to the exact nature
of the blast.
Eddie?
No. No,
we're almost home.
Okay. We'll let you know
as soon as we hear
from him.
Thank you.
I need a smoke.
Munsif?
Oh, hello.
I'm inspector Kalkowitz.
You must be
Mrs. Pelletier.
Please have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
White tip Jasmine.
I'm sorry about your son.
Don't.
Okay, I'll get to the point.
These days, you know,
somebody sets off
some firecrackers
in their backyard,
and we get about a thousand
calls for a terrorist alert.
What do you mean?
I thought it was a gas leak.
Well, let's say it was
a gas leak for now, okay?
The point I'm trying to make
is that there's a bunch--
I don't give a shit
about any of that.
You keep interrupting me.
Just get to the point!
You don't want to make
an enemy out of me,
because if you did,
you'd be losing
a very important friend.
Shall I tell you why?
Because I lost my son
in Iraq.
So let's talk about Eddie.
Here are your son's ashes.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Take as much time
as you need.
( man praying in Urdu )
( gasping )
Sorry to make you folks
keep coming down here.
When will you know
what caused the gas leak?
Well, we're doing everything
we can, Mr. Munsif.
I need to use
the restroom.
Um...
I'm Lea.
I'm Maryam.
You lost your son.
Me, too.
Have you been
to the memorial?
Yeah.
I've been wanting to go,
but I just--
I just haven't
been able to.
I could take you.
Ready?
Who is she?
One of the mothers.
( knocking on door )
( knocking )
What do you want?
I need to talk to you.
I shouldn't have had
to find out
that my son died
from the news.
Jesus Christ!
Come on, Lea.
I had a right to know.
You had a right.
You had a right?
Eddie had a right
to a father
to a father who spent
time with him.
Eddie had a right
not to live like this!
Don't forget, Lea,
I didn't divorce you.
You divorced me.
You pushed me away!
You kept me from him!
I divorced you.
Not Eddie.
That doesn't mean
you stop caring about him,
stop supporting him!
I never stopped caring
about him, ever!
I should've been
at his funeral.
Is that why you're here?
Is that why you came?
You don't think
you're a good Christian
because you missed
the funeral.
Is that what this
is about?
Oh, Saint Charles,
you might be damned
like the rest of us!
That's not what this is about.
That's not why I'm here.
Well, why are you here?
Because I didn't think
that either one of us
should go through this alone.
I should go.
Yeah.
He's handsome.
What was his name?
Eddie.
He just turned 15.
Walter just turned 16
last summer.
All he wanted was a car
for his birthday.
But my husband
wanted him to wait
until he went off
to college.
Tell me more about Eddie.
What was he like?
He was always a good kid.
Sweet kid.
I tried to give him space,
but I should have
picked him up the day...
And afterwards she told me
how her husband became
an evangelical,
and they couldn't do
the things they used to.
They couldn't even
put on masks
and go trick or treating.
We know all about
that kind of fanatic.
Mm-hmm.
Yammi?
Hmm?
We still have
each other, don't we?
Walter is... gone.
We could have another--
I can't do it.
Hello?
Oh. Oh, God. Again?
Hi.
Do you know
what they want?
I have no idea.
Mrs. Pelletier,
Mrs. Munsif,
You both brought
recent pictures
of your sons, right?
If I could have them for
a moment, I'll make copies.
Can you tell us
what this is about?
I'll have them back to you
before you leave.
Mrs. Pelletier,
you can come in now.
I'll see you at 3:00.
I'll pick you up.
Oh, okay.
Ms. Pelletier,
I'm Special Agent Reese,
and you should know
some things have happened
to change the nature
of this case.
Case? What do you mean?
I didn't know
there was a case.
Remember I told you
about the firecrackers
in the backyard?
Well, one of them went off.
The ATF has found
evidence that there were
two explosions
at the food court that day.
The first one was a bomb,
which then set off
the gas main explosion.
What?
Your son was killed
by a bomb.
Oh, my God... A bomb.
We're sorry.
We're very sorry.
What happened?
Well, that's what we're
trying to figure out, okay?
Did your son, by any chance,
know this kid Walter?
Walter Munsif?
No.
Do you know
the Munsifs at all?
Well, I met her here
the other day.
Do you have any reason
to suspect that her son
could've had anything
to do with it?
The bombing?
My God!
You think Maryam's son
had something to do with it?
That is horseshit!
Well, how can you
be so sure
if you only met her
a few days ago?
I don't know.
I can just tell,
just like I can tell
you're an FBI bitch,
and you should not be calling me
with this kind of crap.
Okay, all right. Lea, we--
Mrs. Pelletier,
I've got a bomb
and a Pakistani kid,
so I'm sure
you can appreciate
where we're going
to have to go with this.
Can I go?
Don't tell them shit.
There were hundreds
of people there,
but you assume Walter
did it.
Mrs. Munsif, you were
born in Pakistan?
Yes,
but I'm an American citizen.
I've been here for 18 years.
And your husband, Ali.
He was born there, too?
Yes, he also is
an American citizen.
It says here that
your husband was brought in
for questioning
in December 2001,
in connection
with an investigation
into the Logan Street Mosque.
Does it also say there
that he was kept there
for 3 days,
and that he didn't
have a lawyer,
and that his family
had no idea
what was happening to him
and was terrified?
And then
you let him go,
a case of
mistaken identity.
No apology, nothing.
Yeah, it does.
So, how did you feel
after all that?
How would you feel
if you were us?
We're American citizens.
We pay our taxes,
we follow all the rules,
and then you come and
take us away for no reason,
other than
we look different?
How would you feel?
I'd be angry.
I'd be furious,
and maybe if I'm young
and impressionable,
like any 16-year-old,
and I get mixed up
with the wrong people,
then maybe I'd want
to take some revenge.
We were not angry like that.
We were upset
like anyone would be
if they were treated
wrongly or unfairly.
Is that about it,
Agent Reese?
Yeah, that's it.
We'll call you when we need
to see you, Ms. Munsif.
Kalkowitz: Thank you.
Maryam: They said
it was a bomb.
What?
That killed Walter.
They're starting
an investigation.
They mentioned
the Logan Street Mosque.
It's starting again.
Walter didn't do
anything wrong.
We need to get a lawyer.
Ali, let's just wait!
They'll see Walter
is innocent.
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm just
going out with Lea.
I'll stop by the restaurant
after we're done.
Maryam, be careful
what you say to her.
Why?
Because you don't know her.
You don't know
what she could do.
Ali, she lost her son,
too.
So, tell me about the time
Walter was arrested
for fighting
at the movie theater.
Do you know why
he got into that fight?
No. Tell me.
Because the other boy
was saying
horrible things to him,
racist things.
Did Walter often
behave like that?
Impulsive? Hotheaded?
Walter was a quiet,
regular boy.
He loved reading history.
He loved playing
the guitar--
Oh, come on, Mrs. Munsif.
He broke that kid's jaw
at the fight
at the movie theater.
You made a terrible mistake
accusing my husband.
Don't do the same
with my son.
Was Walter involved
in any significant way
with the Logan Street
Mosque?
No.
Well, what if I told you
We have photos of him
entering the Mosque
on at least two occasions?
Maybe there was some kind of
celebration or something, but--
So, Walter wasn't involved
with any radical groups,
jihadists,
people with anti-American
or anti-Western ideologies?
No. Walter loved this country.
We love this country.
Which is why I'm sure you're
going to be totally cooperative
with us.
What happened, Maryam?
They have pictures
of Walter
outside Logan Street
Mosque.
Was he going
to the mosque?
What would he
go there for?
I don't know.
I don't know what
to believe anymore.
What are we going to do?
I think we should move back.
Back?
It's only going to get worse.
And leave everything
we've built and crawl back?
I talked to Yusuf's Uncle.
His cousin Tazim
is going to buy my share
of the restaurant.
I think it's a good idea.
This is not happening, Ali.
We're not going back there.
You're talking
about our homeland,
where our families
come from.
Sure, we have our madmen.
Sure, we have
20 million people
shitting in the streets,
but at least we're not
circling the world
dropping bombs
at everything we don't like!
What do we have here that's
so goddamn precious anyway, huh?
Give me a mud hut
on a dusty street.
Give me biryani
on a filthy plate
in the middle of a stinking
market, with an open sewer
running through it.
At least we'd have our son!
I didn't mean it.
You did.
( door slamming )
( reporters shouting )
Man: Mrs. Munsif,
Mrs. Munsif!
Woman: We just need
a little bit of your time.
How do you feel
the police
are handling
this investigation?
Mrs. Munsif!
Was your son involved
in the blast?
in the blast, Mrs. Munsif?
Hi, Janet? This is Maryam.
Yeah, I just wanted
to let you know
that we've got
some great new listings.
Yeah, and the condo
we looked at last week,
the one you really liked...
Yeah, well, they've just
dropped their asking price.
So, um...
Oh. Okay, okay...
Yeah, I do understand,
but, you know,
it's a good time to buy.
Okay. Yeah, okay.
Just call me
when you're ready.
Yeah. You, too.
( humming )
Sorry I haven't come by.
I wasn't sure.
I thought you might
want to be alone.
Yeah, that's okay.
I feel so bad. I just
don't know what to say.
There's nothing to say.
I mean, who could do
such a thing?
What could have possibly
been going through
that Muslim kid's head?
They don't really know
what happened.
Come on.
You saw the article.
Angry Muslim kid,
always fighting
with American kids.
Father was a suspect
during 9/11.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Did my husband let you in?
Why are you in my house?
Excuse me, ma'am. You can't
go in there right now.
Don't tell me what
I can do! This is my--
Sorry, ma'am. We have
a search warrant.
Mrs. Munsif, please
wait downstairs.
You have no right
to be here.
Don't make this any harder
than it has to be.
Harder than it has to be?
That's my son's room!
We're done checking
the bedroom, ma'am.
Anything?
A couple of transmitters.
These are my son's toys.
They're ordinary toys!
Here's a copy
of the search warrant.
Our suspect,
a Pakistani-American juvenile,
claimed he was being harassed
with racial insults
by group of teenagers.
An altercation ensued,
and the suspect broke the jaw
of a 14-year-old boy.
Where are you going?
( tires screeching )
Oh, my God.
Call the police.
What for? They think
we are terrorists, too.
So we do nothing?
Wake up, Maryam.
We're going to do
some pass-bys during the day,
keep our eye on things,
all right?
Now, I've lived around here
for a long time.
I know most of these people
around here are good people,
but, you know, we don't
blame you 'cause you've got
some you-know-whats
in your country,
so we hope you don't blame us
because we've got our share.
Let me tell you something.
About a million years ago,
I get out of the Academy.
I've got to go on a patrol
with this guy Terry Sikorsky.
He's an old school cop.
He's a veteran,
30 years on the job,
Ukrainian.
We're down in the Tenderloin,
and he busts this guy Winston.
Winston's got a kilo of shit
in his shirt.
Shit?
You know, heroin, dope.
Sikorsky busted him
twice before. He cuffs him.
Winston turns to Sikorsky
and says, "The harm is done."
I don't get it.
We're back at the station,
and I ask Sikorsky,
"What do you mean
'the harm is done'?"
Sikorsky looks at me,
and he says,
"It's what people do to people.
What does it matter
who did it? The harm is done."
So, if I'm you,
I'd stay put and fight.
Tim!
Hey, Tim!
Hang on a second.
What the hell
is going on?
What?
You gave half my shift
to Juanita.
The woman can barely
speak English.
I'm not getting any
complaints about Juanita.
You're getting
complaints about me?
Yeah. Lots.
Okay, okay. Listen.
I've got to have
these shifts.
You took away Wednesday
and Thursday,
and I've got
to have these shifts,
or I'm not going
to be able to make it.
Come on, man.
Help me out.
Look, I know you're going
through some tough times--
Tough times. Tough times.
That's what you call it,
tough times? You have no idea
what the hell
you're talking about.
Lea--
Do you know what
I've been dealing with?
Lea, calm down.
Look, this is serious.
If your work doesn't improve,
I'm going to have to let you go.
You can consider this
your official warning.
This is bullshit!
From the guy down there.
( sobbing )
I can't talk
about this anymore.
We lost our son.
Somebody threw a brick
through our window.
You're losing
your clients.
People will realize
that Walter didn't do it.
And you're sure that's
what they're going to find?
Aren't you?
My son was not a murderer,
but what does that matter?
Things are changing.
People are desperate.
They'll believe anything now!
This is our home, Ali.
We have to defend it.
That is fine for the cops
because they have guns,
and they can protect
themselves.
We are foreigners here
and always will be.
They see a gun
in the hand of a Muslim,
and he's a terrorist.
Kalkowitz can't know
what that feels like.
His son died in Iraq.
That's what I'm saying,
right there.
His son died in Iraq.
What does that tell you?
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Ali and I had a terrible night.
You lied to me.
What?
What are you talking about?
I never lied to you.
Have you been drinking?
Why, you want to drink?
No, you don't do that,
but your son hanging out
with terrorists,
beating up white kids,
that's okay.
Why didn't you tell me
that Walter had been arrested?
Why didn't you tell me that?
What you read or heard
in the news
is just not true.
Walter is innocent.
I trusted you!
I told you my secrets.
I told you about my Eddie,
and all along you knew.
Stop it! Stop it!
You knew!
You of all people
should understand
what I'm going through.
And I thought
you were my friend.
Your friend.
How?
How can I be your friend?
Your son killed Eddie.
That's what I thought.
So a week ago,
this is all bullshit,
and now this kid
is a suicide bomber?
You asked me if I had reason
to suspect him, and now I do.
Are you aware of the fact
that your kid
was being bullied at school?
Eddie was being bullied?
Yeah. We were going
to call you.
Yeah? Where are you
getting this from?
Well, we've got witnesses.
He was standing at
a bus stop on Sullivan,
behind the school.
This bunch of kids
comes up to him,
starts picking on him,
pushing him around. One
of them grabs his knapsack,
throws it out
into the street,
and Eddie says,
"This is the last time
you assholes are going
to do this to me,"
and one of the kids
stops laughing
long enough to say to him,
"Yeah, Eddie. What are you
going to do about it?"
and you know what Eddie says?
No, what?
He said, "Because I'm going
to kill you. All of you."
Bullshit. You're making it up.
That's bullshit?
Yes, it's bullshit!
Don't you think I would know
if my son was being bullied?
He would have told me!
Do you know a kid
named Andrew Hull?
No.
Do you know a kid
named Richie Palmer?
No.
Bobby Mason?
What, are these the boys
that you say were fucking
with my kid?
Yeah!
Then I want to talk to them.
You can't talk to them, Lea,
because two of them are dead,
and one of them is in a coma!
That's a hell of a coincidence,
don't you think?
Huh? You going to
meet me halfway here?
Well, Eddie had nothing
to do with it.
Look, I'm going to get
to the bottom of this,
with or without your help.
( knocking )
Hi.
Hi. I'm glad you called.
Yeah. Come on in.
Just sit down.
Okay.
Do you want something
to drink?
What are you going
to have?
Beer.
Beer sounds good.
I've mellowed with age.
Huh.
Thank you.
So?
The police suspect Eddie.
What?
They're saying
that he threatened
to kill some kids, and then
three of those kids
died in the explosion.
There's no way that Eddie
had anything to do
with this bombing.
I just wanted to tell you
that, you know, I--
I tried. I tried to be
a good mom.
I wanted Eddie
to be a good person,
just like you did.
I tried to love him...
Take good care of him.
Lea, I know. I know.
Don't beat yourself up.
Do you remember when, um--
When he was a baby,
just starting to crawl?
We were living with
your folks in Redding,
and somehow he got outside
into the backyard,
and he started eating
all those daffodils?
One after another, he must have
eaten about 20 of them?
Yeah, and you were convinced
he was going to die.
Yeah, I remember.
I didn't know what to do,
and you were just so calm.
You just picked him up
and drove us straight
to the emergency room.
Remember that?
Yeah. Yeah, I remember.
A lot of good it did.
They didn't do anything,
told us not to worry.
Remember, you almost took
that nurse's head off.
Well, she was a bitch.
( chuckling )
Oh, Lea.
Don't be so tough, Lea.
Let me in.
Let me help you.
Just a little bit.
Okay?
I thought his room
would be messier.
No, I cleaned it.
I mean, he always had...
piles of clothes
everywhere.
He was a good kid.
He had strange taste
in music, though.
I think he got that
from you.
Probably.
You want some juice?
We should think about suing
the police for harassment.
There is no way our son
was involved in that bomb.
You've got some poor,
angry Muslim kid
who was probably raised
by uneducated fanatics
who taught him he could
bomb his way into heaven.
I mean, what is it, 70--
77 virgins? Some shit.
Don't.
What?
Oh, God. I'm supposed to be PC
about people who don't
belong here in the first place?
No way. They get
what they deserve.
Did Eddie get what he deserved?
You know what I meant.
Yeah.
I know what you meant.
You know, I have
a really busy day today.
Yeah.
Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
Ms. Pelletier.
Eleanor. Eleanor.
Was there a woman
asking about me?
Oh, yes.
What did she want?
What do you think?
I don't know.
What did she want?
You can keep it.
Kalkowitz here?
I tried calling, but
I just got his voicemail.
He's in the field today.
How does it feel now?
How do you like
everyone accusing you?
He didn't do it.
That's not
what the papers say.
Come on!
You were right.
Maryam--
No.
We can't be friends.
Your son is a murderer.
( rock music playing )
Hey, it's wild mommy,
from that video.
( laughing )
Gordian Knot time, baby.
Hi, I'm Eddie.
So, my dad's, like,
this religious nut,
but I haven't seen him
for, like, 10 years
'cause he's too busy
praying, or something.
Mom's pretty cool, though.
She takes me to concerts a lot.
Pretty wild mommy, huh?
You know,
to tell you the truth,
I don't really give a shit.
They got the game
stacked out there.
You have to fit
into their little molds
and their
little fucking cliques,
and if you're
anything different,
you're some fucking freak
that they can push around
whenever they feel like it
'cause you're nothing to them.
You're just a thing to them.
You've got to be Quiet Wyatt.
You just sit there and take it,
while they take all the credit,
but it's Gordian Knot time now.
Yeah.
Yes, hello.
Um, I would like
to send flowers
to a patient, and I need
the room number, please?
Uh, Robert Mason?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming over,
Nausheen.
I'm sorry I couldn't
return your calls.
I meant to.
It's just that--
How are you holding up?
Oh God, I miss Walter
so much.
We barely even spoke
the last few months.
We were always so busy.
I hardly saw him.
I know what you mean.
I used to see him and Jawad
all the time,
but I hadn't seen him
in ages.
He ate dinner at your place
the night before the bombing.
No, he didn't.
Yes, he did.
No. I'm positive.
I would've remembered.
I need to talk to you
about something.
When was the last time
you met Walter?
I don't know.
About two months ago.
So, he wasn't supposed
to have dinner with you
the night before
the bombing?
No. We really just weren't
hanging out that much,
you know, for a while.
Since when?
Maybe the last
half a year or so.
Ever since then,
Walter was different.
How so?
Well, he was pissed off.
He didn't talk about it much,
but he was really mad.
Like the fight he had
at the theater?
Yeah.
So if you guys weren't
hanging out, where was he?
I don't know. By himself.
At the mosque.
He even asked me
to come a few times.
At the Logan Street Mosque?
Yeah.
Did you go with him?
Yeah, once or twice.
PA announcer: Dr. Hunton,
4814. Dr. Hunton, 4814.
Aren't you Eddie's mom?
Yeah.
You knew Eddie?
Yeah. We went
to school together.
I'm Robbie's brother.
Oh.
Oh. How is he doing?
Not good.
Why are you here?
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, it's insane,
but they think Eddie
might have had
something to do
with the bombing.
Yeah, I know.
The police think your brother
was bullying him.
Yeah? My brother's
in a coma now.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I didn't, I didn't mean to--
( banging )
What's wrong?
Hey.
Is he going to be
okay?
No. This whole thing
is just so fucked up.
I know.
I mean,
we were just joking.
What do you mean?
The cops were right.
Robbie, the guys,
we were all just
jacking up Eddie.
Why would you do that
to Eddie?
He's a freak!
Do you think he did it?
You think he did it?
We were at the bus stop,
and he says he's
going to kill all of us.
Just because he said it
doesn't mean he did it.
Just because he said things--
People say things all the time.
It doesn't mean he did it.
It wasn't
what he said.
His eyes were dead.
And the bombing?
The bombing
was five days later.
( chanting )
My son Walter--
As-salaamu alaykum.
Wa alaykum as-salam.
I was at Walter's
funeral, Mrs. Munsif.
How are you
getting along?
Was my son coming here
before he died?
Yes, he was.
Wonderful young man.
For how long?
I don't know exactly,
but for some time.
More so recently.
What was he doing here that
he couldn't tell me about?
Nothing.
He was praying,
learning about Islam.
What kind of Islam?
Mrs. Munsif,
Islam is a religion
of peace and charity,
huh?
We are not extremists
or jihadis here.
We are Americans.
We would never teach
anything
that would be violent
or harmful to this country.
Why was he lying to me?
Why didn't he tell me
he was coming here?
I have no idea,
Mrs. Munsif.
Go ask your husband.
My husband knew that
Walter was coming here?
Yes.
He came with him
a number of times.
Excuse me.
When were you
going to tell me?
Tell you what?
About Walter.
What about Walter?
About Walter
going to the mosque.
Stop lying to me, Ali.
I know.
I just spoke to the Imam.
Why didn't you tell me?
I would have,
but he made me promise
not to tell you.
Why?
Because he knew
how you'd react,
that you'd get angry
and try to stop him.
He was lost, Maryam.
I could see it.
He was angry.
He wasn't hanging out
with Jawad and
his friends anymore.
He needed something, Maryam.
What should I have done?
I don't know, but
you should have told me.
How can I ever
trust you again, Ali?
What? What is it?
What happened, Ali?
Well, at first
he studied with the Imam.
He's a good man.
But then he met...
Some of the more radical
people at the mosque.
Why didn't you do something?
Why didn't you stop him?
I tried, Maryam. I tried!
But the more
I told him to stay away,
the more he wanted
to be with them.
Do you think he did it?
He was a good kid, Maryam.
Do you think Walter did it?
I don't know.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm Hank Kalkowitz.
I'm head of the Alameda County
task force on terrorism.
As you know, this past month
we have been investigating
every aspect of the Newmont
shopping mall bombing,
where the two suspects we had
died in the explosion,
and the one eyewitness
was in a coma.
He was in a coma, that is,
up until this morning,
when he died.
( crowd gasping )
Man: Are you saying
you have no more leads?
No, sir. That's not
what I'm saying.
I am not saying that at all.
We are going to follow up
on every lead we get,
but what I am saying is,
at this juncture,
I need to tell you
that this investigation
is going from active to ongoing.
But you know
one of those kids did it!
Aren't you going to do
anything about it?
Don't you owe us
that much?
Well, from my perspective, sir,
what we owe the community
is the truth,
and right now you're going
to have to bear with us
because we don't know
what that truth is.
Thank you.
I'd just like to assure everyone
we are not closing this case.
It is ongoing. What we'd like
to do with the rest of this time
is to answer any questions
that you might have.
( people shouting )
Man: Linda, over here!
Linda!
Linda! Have you had
pressure from the city
to shut down the
investigation because...
Woman: Can I get more
information
on the boy who just died?
( thunder crashing )
( Ali speaking in Urdu )
I thought I might
see you here.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
Do you think we'll ever
know what happened?
Would it change anything?
♪
Go ahead.
No, that's okay.
I'll find another spot.
I don't mind.
All right.
You play?
Yeah. You?
Uh, yeah.
Mostly just
fool around, though.
How long have you
been playing?
About two, two
and a half years or so.
That's cool.
So, what kind of music
do you like to play?
I like Green Day,
Dead Kennedys...
So, like, the easy stuff?
( laughing) Yeah.
Well, what kind
of guitar do you have?
A Fender. You?
♪
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/45z77
Help other users to choose the best subtitles