Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
You're just
having a bad dream.
That's all, baby.
That's all it was.
Bad dreams make
you think you've seen
things that you haven't.
You know what I do
when I have a bad dream?
I close my eyes
and I think of
something nice.
Like being
here with you.
Hurry up, sweetheart.
We're going to be late.
Shit.
Jack?
Did you see someone
ring my doorbell?
No.
Okay, thanks.
I cleaned everything
away, sweetheart.
Everything is exactly
the way it was before.
They're clean
and shiny. Look.
Look. You see?
Okay, all right.
Just close your eyes.
Well, hello, sailor.
Hi!
Permission to
come aboard?
Honey, hold this.
So sorry we couldn't make
it yesterday. Somebody
was working late again.
How're you doing, Sal?
I'm good.
How are you?
I'm all right.
Look at you.
Do you like it?
You look great.
Really? I just
kind of threw it on.
She's had outfits
laid out for a week.
You're such a liar.
You know my husband.
I don't listen
to what he says.
You know that.
I brought my really
good friend, Heather.
She's so nice.
Promise me
you'll be attentive.
How're you doing, man?
She's not
to bring anyone.
You don't like her?
Believe me, she's the best
looking of Sally's friends.
Which it doesn't
say much.
I asked you not to.
You're living on a boat
with an 18-year old boy
and you're saying no girls.
Greg, this is Heather.
She's a very good friend
of mine, and I just thought
you guys should meet.
Hi.
Can you just excuse me
for a moment?
Jess. You okay?
I don't think so.
Hey. What happened?
Hey. What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
You've got nothing
to apologize for.
What is it?
Are you okay?
I'm just tired.
Well, listen, we don't
have to go today if
you don't want to.
No, we do.
I-I want to go.
You sure?
Yeah.
Yeah? Okay, come on.
Come up here.
This is Sally and
her husband, Downey.
This is Heather,
Sally's friend.
You remember Victor.
So let's go sailing!
Okay.
Hey.
You okay?
Is Greg okay?
He's fine.
He's upstairs.
You've been asleep
for a couple of hours.
I had this terrible dream.
What about?
I don't remember.
I wouldn't worry.
Apparently bad dreams
cure you of real
life stress.
As indeed
does champagne.
You want some?
Yeah.
Downey, want to give me
a hand, please?
Actually, Victor, I'm
a guest of the Captain's,
but yes, I will help you.
Victor, what was that
back there at the harbor?
What?
I asked Jess if
she was all right
and you said no.
You told me she was
bringing the little
boy along.
When I was walking
with her in the harbor
I asked where he was.
She couldn't remember.
She stared into space
for like 20 seconds
and then she said
he's at school.
So?
Well, it's Saturday.
Isn’t no school today.
Her son goes to a special
needs school and it's
open every day.
Be nice to her.
All right.
Do you boys
sunbathe together?
Sometimes.
The champagne is not
great but it is cold.
Want some?
No thanks.
Okay, more for me.
Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm sorry, I didn't
realize how tired I was.
You apologize one more
time, and I'm going to
throw you overboard.
Here.
You all right?
Yeah.
He thinks we're
a fishing boat.
He's going to go hungry.
You want to steer?
Nah.
Go on.
Which way
do I am?
You're going to
aim that way.
It's easy, right?
So, she's a waitress
at some diner.
At least there
they talk. They
became friends.
Oh, and she has
an autistic son.
So they're just friends.
Sally!
What do you want me
to say? I'm sorry she
has a retarded son?
Yeah!
Well, I'm sorry.
You know, that's not
Greg's problem, that's hers.
What is it,
is it the shorts?
No! Heather, Greg's
been my friend for
a really long time.
I can't just sit back
and watch him get
shaken down.
She isn't doing that.
Well, I hope not
because Greg is
far too trusting.
I'm kind of
linking the boy.
Uh, no, you're not.
Can you please go up
there and talk to Greg?
I really think
the two of you will
be perfect for each other.
And I really don't like
seeing him with her.
Jess, are you ready?
Yeah, let her go.
Yeah.
Woo!
So, how do you
know everyone?
Victor, he's staying
with me for good.
He got in trouble
at home. He had
to get away.
I found him sleeping
behind the store
at the harbor.
You know, we got talking,
and now he lives here.
Just like that
you let him move in?
Well, I got three rooms.
I can't sleep in them all.
And Downey,
I've known him
since I was a kid.
Sally, his wife,
I know her from
high school.
I dated her
for like four days
in the eighth grade,
so technically
she's my ex.
They seem really nice.
Yeah. Except for the fact
that every year they
feel obliged
to bring me
an eligible girl.
Maybe they think
you're lonely.
Do I give off
lonely to you?
Sometimes.
When I come to see you
at the diner, I'm not
lonely, I'm hungry.
Obviously yesterday
was different.
What happened yesterday?
Yesterday I was
not hungry.
I came in with the sole
purpose of inviting
you sailing.
You did?
I did.
Turn at port side.
We're losing wind.
Let me check it
for just a sec.
So, things are
okay with Tommy?
The same.
Every day is the same.
Tommy likes the things
to be a certain way. Yeah.
If I do one thing
differently, I lose him.
What's the matter?
I've never seen you
like this before.
I don't know. I just, uh,
I just feel guilty when
I'm not with Tommy.
That's because
you're a good mother.
But you can't
be everywhere
all of the times.
Hey, guys. Oh!
How is it going?
We're good.
I was just wondering
if I could steal Jess
away from you.
Sally's dying
to talk to her.
We're kind of in the middle
of something right now.
No, no, it's okay.
I-I should circulate.
Hey, just for the record,
I'm not interested.
You, what the fuck?
Wind's dropped down on us.
It's not dropped,
it's gone.
This is crazy.
You ever seen
this before?
Yeah, yeah. Just not
quite so sudden.
Are we okay to get
home? There is no wind.
Yeah, yeah. We got
an engine. It's not
a problem.
It's just, it's weird.
Greg?
Is that normal?
Okay, I'm fucking
freaked, what the fuck.
Triangle to coast
guard. Over.
Coast guard,
go ahead. Over.
We've just gone from seven
knots to absolute zero. You've
got anything unusual? Over?
Nothing showing up. Over.
It's darkening up pretty
quick out here. Looks like
an electrical storm. Over.
Help me. Please.
Can you hear me?
Help me.
Please, help me.
Killing everyone. They're
dead. They're all dead.
We hear you.
What's your
position? Over.
Distressed caller,
we hear you. What are
your coordinates? Over.
Coast guard, did you hear
a distress call? We're not
getting it anymore. Over.
Distressed caller,
make another transmission.
What is your position?
Greg?
Get below deck now.
Get the life jackets.
Cut it.
Cut the sail.
Vic, get the main
sail down.
Get it down.
Vic!
No!
Get back.
Jess, take my hand.
Grab on.
Heather!
Vic!
Jess.
Are you okay?
All right.
Downey?
Are you guys okay?
Have you seen Heather?
She got lost through
the window.
No. Come on, come on.
Heather!
Greg! Help me!
Sally. Sally.
Just give me
your hand.
Heather!
Are you guys okay?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
Tommy's at school, yeah?
He'll be looked after
until we get back.
He'll be all right.
Thank God. You!
Help us!
Help us. Help.
Help us. Over here.
Oh, God.
Hey. Hey.
Wait. Come on,
over here!
There, there. Over there.
I can see someone.
You, we need some
help down here.
Help us, please!
Hello. We need
some help down here.
Yeah, he's seen us.
He's seen us.
Oh, thank God.
Jump, jump, jump.
Okay. Jess,
come on, come on.
Jess. Come on.
Come on, come on,
take my hand. Okay.
Okay. You okay?
You okay? Yeah?
Hey.
How is it?
See? I told you.
Hello?
Hello!
Do we wait?
No, let's go
to the bridge.
We'll get the captain
to put a call out to
the coast guard.
We'll get a search
for Heather.
Come on.
Do you think Heather
would've made it
on board?
Honey.
There's a chance,
isn't there?
Yeah. Yeah,
there's a chance.
Hello?
Hello!
Somebody please help us?
Hello?
Where the fuck
is everybody?
You don't even now
where we're going.
Well, we're just,
just walking for
the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like
I know this place.
I recognize
this corridor.
Liners, they look
pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
Come check this out.
This is the same ship.
This thing's old.
Jess.
Come on.
1932. It's the same.
Here's where we boarded.
Oh, yeah.
Aeolus.
Aeolus was the Greek
god of the winds and
the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the gods
to the task of pushing a rock
up a mountain
and let it see
roll back down again.
That's a shitty
punishment. What
did he do?
He cheated Death.
No, he made a promise
to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied it but I can't
remember. Can we just
keep on moving, please?
Hello?
Whoever it was
might want to come
back for these.
Let me see?
These are mine.
These are my keys.
What are you
talking about?
They're mine.
Bullshit.
This is, this is
my house key.
This is my, my car key.
This is my son. See?
Wait. So you had them
with you on the yacht?
Yes.
It's got to be Heather.
Come on.
How else did
they get here?
It was Heather dropping
her keys but not bothering
to say, "I didn't drown."
Why not?
Come on.
Heather?
Looks like you get your
welcome party, just
not the welcome.
Heather!
You, Greg, what
time you got?
Eleven thirty.
Heather.
Heather!
Where is everyone?
Sally! Please. Please.
I don't know where
everyone is but the
ship's not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of
us think that it is
but it's not,
so let's just go
to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper
and then we'll go home.
I saw someone.
Fuck.
Wait.
Hello?
Did you see
who it was?
Was it Heather?
I didn't see.
I'm sorry.
Where're you going?
Why don't you
just help me out here?
What?
Just wait for Vic.
It's fine.
Why can't we
go with him?
Let's just do as Greg
says and wait here
for Victor, okay?
Fine.
I think Victor's
in danger.
I'm not worried
about Victor.
I'm sorry I'm acting
weird. It's just I'm
having déjà vu
every time
I turn a corner.
No, no. No.
I know this place.
No, you don't
know this place.
You're just in shock.
That's funny.
What is it?
Is it Tommy?
Is it guilt?
Is that what it is?
Do you feel guilty?
Hello?
Hello.
We're on the third floor.
The bridge is exactly
two floors above us.
Greg, that was blood.
Are you just going to
ignore it?
I know guys that work
on ships like this.
They see us, they get bored.
They're just letting off
some steam.
What? They rescue us
from the sea and then
they just hide for fun?
Yeah.
Well, what's
your theory?
I don't know,
but I'm not,
but I'm not in shock.
I'll be in the ball room.
I'm getting off this ship.
Jess, fuck! Don't you
see that this is all
just in your mind?
Jess! Ships don't
just magically appear
out of nowhere.
They have skippers.
I mean, in your world
right now they don't.
My world is waiting
outside school for his
mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me
about my world.
Jess. Jess, I'm sorry.
Is that blood?
Babe, come on, we're
supposed to meet them
in the theatre.
Heather!
Oh, my God. Shit.
Sally. Sal, come on.
Let's just go
to the theatre.
Downey, I can't see
anymore blood. I don't
think she's in here.
To be honest with you,
I don't think she's
even on the ship.
Okay. So whose
blood was that?
Hello?
Downey? Sally?
Victor. What happened?
Oh, my God.
Stay with me, Greg.
Stay with me, man.
No. No!
You fucking bitch!
You shot him!
What?
He said you shot him.
I didn't!
Fucking liar!
I wasn't even
with Greg!
He's dead!
Look!
God, you're a bitch!
Get your hands off him!
I didn't do it!
I was with Victor.
Someone attacked him.
Someone?
You think I did it?
Why did you tell us
to come to the theatre?
I didn't. l--
Sally, I didn't.
I didn't.
My God, you're
a fucking skit so.
Sally, no.
Sally!
No!
Downey!
Let it go. Let it go.
No!
Don't shoot. Please.
Please, don't
shoot. Please.
I have a son.
Shit.
Who are you?
Tell me!
What the fuck
are you saying?
It's the only way
to get home.
What?
You have to kill them.
Kill them!
{music played on
a scratched record}
Over here.
Come on. Hey!
Help us, please!
Help!
Hey. Hey.
Help us!
Please!
There, there. Over there.
I can see somebody.
Please!
Hello?
Looks like they decided
to scratch the welcome.
Let's go
to the bridge.
We'll get the captain
to put a call out to
the coast guard.
Hello!
Hello?
Where the fuck
is everybody?
Do you even know
where we're going?
Well, we're just,
just walking for
the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like
I know this place.
I recognize
this corridor.
Liners, they look
pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
Jess, come on.
This is the same ship.
This thing's old.
Yeah. 1932.
It is the same.
Here's where we boarded.
Yeah. Aeolus.
Aeolus.
Aeolus was the Greek
god of the winds and
the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the gods
to the task of pushing a rock
up a mountain
only to have it
roll back down again.
That's a shitty
punishment. What
did he do?
He cheated Death.
No, he made a promise
to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied him and I
can't remember. Can we
just keep on moving?
Hello?
Heather?
Hello!
Heather!
Sally. Please. I don't
know where everyone is.
But the ship's
not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of
us think that it is
but it's not,
so let's just go
to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper
and then we go home.
I saw someone.
Hello?
Hello.
Shit. How did you
get here so fast?
Victor, you got, you
got to listen to me. We
don't have much time.
Oh, what's going on?
Where's Greg?
He's dead.
What?
No, I mean,
he was dead.
He's not dead now.
What are you saying?
Downstairs right now
is a copy of myself.
Me, walking and
talking with Greg.
Right.
There.
There's birds.
No, that was
Downey's body.
I just left Downey
back there. How did
you get here so fast?
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
No. Downey was there.
It was Downey's body.
There are bodies
all over this ship.
Your body is on the floor
at the restaurant with
a hole in your head.
Listen, I'm going to do
you a favour, okay?
I'm not going to tell
anyone about this.
It's the truth.
Victor, we got to get
off this ship right now.
You're saying there's
two of you now.
Yes.
And I'm dead
in the restaurant.
You were killed.
Okay. So, I'm dead.
Downey's in the water.
He's dead, too.
Is Sally okay?
See where I'm going
with this, right?
If we are dead and
there's two of you,
how are we all going to
get off this ship?
We should never have
boarded this ship.
I knew something
was wrong.
I should've forced you
to stay on the yacht
and you'd all be alive.
I've got to tell you
I feel pretty alive
right now.
Soon you're going to be dead.
Everything that happened
to you, happened before.
I can't even believe
I'm talking this shit.
You will die and then,
then Downey and Sally
and then Greg.
I didn't do this.
I didn't do it.
We're on the third level.
Greg, that was blood.
You just going to ignore it?
I know guys that work
on ships like this.
They see us, they get bored.
They're just letting off
some steam.
Don't you see that this
is all just in your mind?
Ships don't just
magically appear
out of nowhere.
They have skippers.
I mean, in your world
right now they don't.
My world is waiting
outside school for his
mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me
about my world.
Who are you?
Listen, listen to me.
Please, you have
to listen.
Kill them all.
If they board,
kill them.
Jess. Jess, you
got to kill them.
Please, you have
to listen.
Don't let them board.
No, no. No.
Please, please.
Stop, stop them.
If they board,
kill them.
Jess. Jess, you
got to kill them.
If they board,
kill them.
No, no. No.
Please, please, stop.
If they board, kill them.
Please, please stop.
Jess, Jess, Jess.
Fuck you!
Shit.
Tommy.
Is that blood?
Babe, come on. We're
supposed to meet them
at the theatre.
Victor.
I didn't mean
to hurt you.
You know I didn't mean
to hurt you, right?
Now, I'm going to try
and get us off
this ship, okay?
Sally.
Sally?
Victor?
What happened?
You're not me.
You see?
I'm not crazy.
Victor.
This didn't happen
before. Don't you see?
You tried to
strangle me, remember?
Now, you got to be strong.
I'm going to get the others.
Downey, do something.
Stay with me, man.
Do something.
I don't know
what to do.
Is he dead?
Greg. Greg.
You fucking--
Listen, I'm not going to
hurt you. We don't
have much time.
Don't you point
that thing.
Move!
Go, go, go.
I hit her.
I think I hit her.
What's going on?
Who was that?
It's starting over again.
That's what's going on.
Let's go.
We can't leave
without Greg.
We'll come back
for Greg. I promise.
Let's go, come on!
We can change
the pattern.
Don't you see?
We change the pattern,
we're not trapped. Then
we get off this thing.
She's fucking mad.
You think?
You have to
listen to me.
No, I don't have
to listen to you.
Was it me
that shot you?
I don't know.
Whoa, wait.
Could we just take
a breath for a second?
Okay, Jess, I am prepared
to listen to you
and even to believe
you, but you got to
make some sense.
I'm making perfect sense.
I'm going to get Victor, then
we get off this ship.
Wait here.
And don't trust anyone.
If anyone comes,
you shoot them.
What are you
talking about?
You shoot them.
What?
Victor.
Victor?
I said who is it?
It's me, Jess.
Jesus Christ, what
the fuck happened to you?
A long story.
Where's Victor?
He's dead.
He fell over
the side.
How do we know
you didn't kill him?
You don't.
If you want to live,
you'll follow me.
Downey!
Ignore it.
What's going on?
I said ignore it.
Where are you?
Call out.
No, lama not just
going to ignore it.
What is going on?
Where the fuck
are you?
Call out!
You're in danger.
Who is that?
Not who you think?
So, what are we
doing in here?
Sally!
Wait!
I'm sorry but
I love my son.
Sally?
That wasn't me.
Hello? Hello?
Please, can
you hear me?
Help me.
Please, help me.
She's killing everyone.
They're dead.
They're all dead.
Please--
Sally?
What's your
position? Over.
Sally.
Distressed caller,
we hear you. What are
your coordinates? Over.
Coast guard, did you hear
a distress call? We're not
getting in anymore. Over.
Greg.
Greg, is that you?
Distressed caller, make
another transmission.
What is your position?
Greg, can you
hear me? Greg.
Shit.
Sally?
Oh, my God, what
happened to you?
Get away from me.
It wasn't me, Sally.
I didn't do this to you.
It wasn't me.
Where is Downey?
I don't know
where he is.
You killed him.
What?
No, I didn't.
I didn't kill him.
What?
I swear.
You're crazy.
Why are you
doing this?
Sally, I know it's hard
but you got to trust me.
Got to trust me, okay?
Listen, you
got to hold on.
I think it will
return again.
The yacht, the Triangle,
I think it'll come back.
If it does, we'll escape,
me and you together.
We'll re-board it
and escape.
Please.
Don't hurt me.
Sally, I'm not
going to hurt you.
If you hold on,
you can see
Downey again.
Hey, come on.
Over here.
Hey. Hey. Help.
It returns when
they're dead.
everyone's dead.
Do you think Heather
would’ve made it
on board?
Honey.
There's a chance,
isn't there?
Yeah. Yeah,
there's a chance.
Stop this thing.
Stop this fucking thing.
Please.
I want to go home.
He's dead.
I mean, he
was dead.
He's not dead now.
I was hiding and I saw
this version of myself,
and she had blood
on her face, and
then I killed her.
I killed her on
the front of the ship.
Listen, I'm going to
do you a favour, okay?
I'm not going to tell
anyone about this.
It's the truth.
You got to listen to me.
No, I'm not listening
to another word you say.
You will die, and then
Greg and then Downey.
Don't be scared, Victor.
I can save you.
I know how to save you.
You should try
and eat, babe.
Jess?
Jesus, what
happened to you?
Where's Greg?
Greg told me to tell you
we should meet in
the theatre.
There's a theatre?
Yes, it’s just
that way.
Where are you going?
I'll see you there.
Okay, she's really
starting to freak
me out now.
Don't you see that this
is all just in your mind?
Ships don't just magically
appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers.
In your world
right now maybe
they don't.
My world is waiting
outside school for his
mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me
about my world.
Jess.
Jess, I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Okay.
Take it easy, man.
Just take it easy.
What did we do?
We're not part
of this boat.
We just got here, okay?
We've been walking around.
There's no one on it.
I can go right
now. I will go.
Okay? Just--
Just take it easy.
Take it easy.
Okay?
Jess?
Jess.
Jess, what
are you doing?
What-- what is this?
Why-- what are
you wearing?
I don't want you
to see my face.
Why?
Because this
is not me.
I'm somewhere out there
in the yacht and
you're with me.
And after I kill you,
we'll return.
Is that right?
You know, why-why
don't you just put
down the gun first?
Okay? Come on.
You see, the boat
comes back when
you're all dead.
I've done everything
exactly like before.
But when the boat
comes back, I'll be
ready, I'll be waiting.
I'll be on the landing bay.
I won't let any of them
board, even the other me.
I'll make them all stay
on the upturned yacht.
Okay.
Jess, we'll do
whatever you want.
Okay? Just, just
put down the gun.
Come on.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no!
Greg!
Oh, God!
What happened?
It was Jess.
You fucking bitch!
You shot him. He
said you shot him.
I wasn't even
with Greg!
He's dead!
My God, you're a
fucking skit so.
Downey!
Please.
Don't kill me.
I have a son.
Who are you?
Tell me!
They'll return.
Who are you?
You have to kill them.
It's the only way
to get home.
What the fuck
are you saying?
It's the only way
to save our son.
You have to kill them.
Kill them?
Hurry up, Sweetheart.
We're going to be late.
What's fun in
buying you things
if you're going to leave
them in the fucking garden!
I'm sick of telling
you this, Tommy.
I isn’t buying you anymore
toys if you can't look after
the ones you've got.
Now what?
Oh, I'll just
clean it up, shall I?
Yeah, I'm just cleaning
the fucking mess!
What's the matter
with you, huh? What's
the matter with you?
Just one day off
is all I ask. Just
one fucking day off!
I don't know why you
can't paint a picture
like a normal kid.
You get this
from your father.
He was an asshole, too.
Shit.
Jack?
Did you see anyone
ring my doorbell?
Tommy?
Sweetheart, come here.
Come here.
Come here!
It's okay.
Mommy's fine,
you see?
Mommy's fine.
You're just having
a bad dream. That's
all, baby.
It's all it was.
Bad dreams make you
think you've seen
things that you haven't.
Things are going to be
different now, Tommy.
Mommy won't lose
her temper anymore,
even when you
do things wrong.
And she won't hurt you.
I know she
won't hurt you.
You know how
I know that, Tommy?
Because that woman that
did those things to you
is not Mommy.
This is Mommy.
Mommy's nice.
Shit.
Tommy, stay in the car.
I'm going to
bury it, okay?
We have to go.
We have to get
out of here.
Stop screaming, babe.
Please, Tommy,
it just blood.
Stop screaming!
Tommy, look. See?
There, it's gone.
See? There. It's gone.
Are you all right?
Who are you?
Just a driver.
No point trying
to save the boy.
There's nothing anyone
can do that's going to
bring him back.
Can I give you a ride?
Yes.
Take me to the harbor.
Hey.
I'll leave
the meter running.
You will come
back, won't you?
Yes, I-I promise.
Jess.
Do you know me?
I feel like I do.
Greg talks about
you enough.
Where is Greg?
Where do you think?
Come on, you're late.
You're the one
with the kid, right?
Yeah.
How come you didn't
bring him along?
He's at school.
You sure about that?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I don't think so.
Hey, what's the matter?
What happened?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
What's the matter?
I'm just tired.
Listen, we don't
have to go today if
you don't want to.
No, I do.
I-I want to go.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Yeah? Come,
come here.
This is Sally and
her husband, Downey.
This is Heather,
Sally's friend. You
remember Victor.
Let's go sailing.
Okay.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org