Delicious Vegan Sausages, Cheese
and Burgers - Vegusto.co.uk
This then? This is a not a movie
This is a libel, slander,
defamation of character
A prolonged insult
A godless spit in the face of art
A kick in the pants to God,
man, destiny,
time, love, beauty,
what you will.
I'm going to sing for you
A little off-key, perhaps,
but I will sing
I will sing while you croak
I will dance over
your dirty corpse.
Have you seen Boris?
He's meeting someone who
may rent the apartment
Could you loan me 5 Francs to
take a taxi to Saint Lazare?
Now, you know Mona. If I'm not
there to meet the boat train
she's allowed to turn right
'round and go back
Oh, Henry!
Ok, it's too late already, forget it
Oh, for god's sake, here
She rises up out of a sea of
faces and embraces me
embraces me, passionately
A thousand eyes, noses,
fingers, legs
bottles, windows, purses,
saucers all glaring at us
And we in each other's
arms, oblivious.
I sit down beside her, and she
talks, a flood of talk
Wild, consumptive
notes of hysteria
Perversion, leprosy.
I hear not a word, because she's
beautiful and I love her.
And now I'm happy
and willing to die.
The hotel, where is it?
Can we go to the hotel right now?
Nah, I've gotta find Boris
I thought I'd never get here
When you weren't at the station, I...
Hey! Boris!
Henry, how are you? Nice to see you
Hey, glad to see you!
Here's Mona, my wife
Hello
Oh no
My cheque didn't come, I haven't got it
20 francs?!
It's all I've got, it's
all I got on me, fella!
Here, I'll give you half what I got.
Go on
Come on, Boris
Just...just once?
Ah, alright
Take it
-Thanks
-Yeah
-Really appreciate it.
-Yeah, yeah, sure.
-Thanks a lot!
-Yeah, yeah, sure, swell.
Oh, yeah. A pleasure.
- I see you Boris.
-So long, Henry!
May I take my dress off?
No
Oh, I forgot to tell you
I had a, um...
...reading for a play, just before
I left New York
It was for Charlie Morton's new play
He liked me, he really did
But, of course, they gave the part
to the producer's new girlfriend
They're idiots
Anyway, this...
...you know, she's probably gonna
have to wear a wig
Or if they try to colour that hair
one more time, it'll turn green
I need a Kleenex
You have a Kleenex? No, you don't
have a Kleenex
What do you ask for in French, I don't
know what to ask. Well, I guess Kleenex
They always understand Coca-Cola
-Baby?
-Hm?
-I don't wanna alarm you, but...
-You're covered with bugs
-What!!
You bastard!!
Deux café, s'il vous plaît
It's out of order and it stinks
I must have a bath
I've got to have a bath
It's a little bit cold
Get my clothes hung up
Get 'em pressed. Look at
the state they're in
We look like a couple of tramps
We must find another hotel.
And a clean one
I want to find a good hotel
as soon as they're open.
-What time are they open around
here, anyway? -Seven or eight.
How much money have you got left?
What the hell are you doing? You trying
to get us thrown out of here?
Thank you, tres bien, merci.
Wait, I have to take a bath.
Wait.
-Oh yeah.
-Uh uh! Your bath is running.
Isn't it good to be clean again?
How much money have you got left?
Oh, I've got enough for tonight.
Oh no!
Uh uh, no.
Oh, no.
When I realise that she's gone,
perhaps gone forever
a great void opens up, and I feel that
I'm falling into deep, black space
And this is worse than tears, deeper
than regret, or pain, sorrow
It is the abyss into which Satan
was plunged.
There's no climbing back,
no ray of light
no sound or human voice,
or human touch of hand
How many thousand times walking
through the streets at night
have I wondered if a day would
ever come again
when she would be at my side?
All those yearning looks I bestowed
on the buildings and statues
I'd looked at them so hungrily,
so desperately, that by now
my thoughts must've become a part
of the very buildings and statues.
They must be saturated
with my anguish.
I could not help but reflect, also, that
when we'd walked side by side
through these mournful dingy streets now
saturated with my dream and longing
that she's observed
nothing, felt nothing.
They were like any streets to her, a little
more sordid, perhaps, and that is all.
I became reconciled to this life
without her
and yet if I thought about
her only for a minute
it was enough to pierce the bone and
marrow of my contentment
and shove me back again
into the agonising gutter of
my wretched past.
Somehow...
...the realisation that
nothing was to be hoped for
had a salutary effect on me
And then it occurred
to me, like a flash,
that no-one would refuse a man a meal
if only he had the courage to demand it.
I went immediately to a café and
wrote a dozen letters
"Would you let me have dinner
with you once a week?"
"Tell me what day is most
convenient for you."
It worked like a charm!
I was not only fed, I was feasted.
Every night I went home drunk.
And now I could afford to scratch
off the ones who were a pain the ass.
You see? I calculated your share of
the actual cost of last Tuesday's meal.
Not counting the half bottle of
wine you knocked off the table.
-Won't you be late for class?
-It comes to 12 francs, 63 centimes.
-bringing the total to 1,340.01 exactly.
-We're not asking him to pay us back.
-I know, I know, but it's just very interesting!
Hey!
Hi, come on in!
One by one I fucked myself out
of all those free dinners
The wives turned against me
Or the husbands.
Tania, darling? When's dinner?
I'm just finishing my practise, darling.
We'll have to stop this now,
he's home again.
-Darling, I think the potatoes are burning.
-I'll be there in just a second, darling!
Ah, there we are, darlings
Now, give Henry a large helping,
Sylvester, he's building up
-How was New York?
-Oh, terrible
New York is dreadful, you know that
All those phonies
But we're set for a February opening
And Craig St.Que will direct
It's good. Jolly good
What's next?
Well, there's a work-in-progress,
naturally
I like to call it that
You know, if he finishes a
play in the morning
and there's still an hour or
two before lunch
He puts a new sheet of paper
in the typewriter
and starts right off on a new one
That's how to be a writer
More Henry, or you've had enough?
I think I can take a little more
Give Henry some more, Sylvester
But, you know, he's fantastic!
He never talks about it
But when he sits down to write,
it just rolls out of him
I believe it
You smile at me so confidently,
so calculatingly
I'm flattering the ass off you,
can't you tell?
And I believe...
...this wine is corky
I thought that was only supposed
to happen in the States
While I listen to your crap,
she's got her hand on me
But you don't see that
Yeah, it's in the kichen.
Henry? Why don't you nip out, and bring
in a couple of bottles, huh?
It's on the top...
...shelf
Henry, you fool
So now I'm the only one left who'll
cough up the weekly dinner
Two cognacs, please
Yeah, well, uh...
I didn't know Sylvester was
so hyper-sensitive
Ah, Tania!
It was worth it!
-So, what're you gonna do now?
-Jeez, I don't know
Yeah, that's Fillmore
-Maybe he's got a spare bed
-Doesn't look like it tonight
Princess, princess, don't be mad
I won't move my hips anymore
You speak too much. Too loud
And you speak nonsense!
My nervous, my nervous!
Please give me some champagne
It's the only thing for my temperament
A champagne, please
Oh, hi Joe, hi Joe
-Hi Joe
-Fellas?
I want you to meet the Princess Macha
She's royal, you know
Fillmore? Can I use your sofa tonight?
No, you cannot use the sofa tonight
What are you whispering for?
You want me not to hear?
Why should your friend not sleep
at your apartment tonight?
The poor fellow
You think he gets me there
to make love?
I don't blame you
You should see me when
I'm undressed
I'm very beautiful
But a princess of the blood royale
is not to be bought
for a few miserable bottles
of champagne
-And the caviar
-Oh la la
It's, uh...the royal temperament, huh?
But you won't enjoy it
I warn you
Oh, Princess
You let me be the judge of that, huh?
Alright
Princess
Did I tell you I have the clap?
The clap?!
And what are you making
a fuss for?
It's only gonorrhoea
-Only gonorrhoea?!
Oh, Americans
They have no manners at all!
What's that?
It's me, Henry
Joe from the bar
These blankets are no good.
I'm so cold
Come here and warm me a little
Right away, your Highness
I wouldn't, if I were you
-You didn't give her a key, did you?
-Yes
-Alright
You poor shy boys
I go to take a little coffee now
So, you can get dressed
Money!
Just a little 10 franc note
I see you later
But...
...what a charming place you have
I'm going to like it here
Bye bye
You grab the door
I'm going to get the lock changed
Peckover! You live around here?
No, I work days, too
Didn't you know?
Dentist office up the street
To pay off this set of teeth
they made for me
Hey, don't you read proof
the paper anymore?
Why? What have you heard?
About what?
Well, I know you're hanging around
with Carl and Van Norden
Did they say anything?
They didn't say anything
That boss of mine
He balls the piss out of me
if I miss a semi-colon
Yeah? Maybe he needs more help
I'm a great semi-colon spotter
Well, uh, is there a list I
can put my name on?
For future consideration
Yeah, put it on there
I'll see it gets on
the applications list
Thanks
Thanks a lot
Well, here...
...take a look at these ads, maybe you'll
find something good on there
If you do, you'll be way ahead
of everybody else in Paris
Hey. How about this one?
American needed for teaching in Dijon
under international exchange agreement
Room and board
What's the salary?
There's no mention of money. It's, uh...
"Your contribution to Franco-
American amity."
It's a roof over the head, and food
Bon Soir, Monsieur. Je suis
le professor American
Entrer
Oh, brother!
Good night, Monsieur Miller
Ah, good night, Monsieur Le Censeur
Pray, consider yourself welcomed
among our walls.
I observe you're astounded,
to be listen of English spoke
It is myself that have 'til now instruct
the pupils in this language
But a man occupied as myself
have no more for such
You, Monsieur Miller, henceforth shall talk
the English conversation to the boys
I, uh, my best will do to follow up
your good work
Monsieur Le Censeur
It is a class in the morning
at eight of the clock
You are speaking French, I hope?
Well, a little. Un tout petit peu
Un tout petit peu
Peu
Excellent
Your predecessor was not gifted
with the tongue
He was not capable to follow my work
Also he did not exercise himself to...
...inform us about his departure
He go, uh...
...over the wall
Couldn't he have just gone
through the door?
The door is locked by key
Each night, at ten
To avoid the infiltration of women
A contingency at all costs
to be avoided
Exactement
Now, back to our businesses
Thus, your personal fire for a week
Also, there is in supplementation
two measures of coal, in bucket
Paper must by yourself be found
I for it will start looking at once
Yes. In times you do not converse with
the boys, you are at liberty
The town of Dijon is yours
Amuse yourself goodly
A tout alors, Monsieur Miller
Your continuing good health,
Monsieur Le Censeur
Oh, Tania...
Where now is that
warm cunt of yours?
Those fat heavy garters,
those soft bulging thighs
There's a bone in my prick,
six inches long
Hell, I'll ream out every wrinkle
in your cunt, Tania
Big with seed, I'll send you home
to your Sylvester
with an ache in your belly and
your womb turned inside out
Your Sylvester, yes he knows
how to build a fire
but I know how to inflame a cunt
Tania, I make your ovaries
incandescent
Sylvester's a little jealous now.
He feels something
He feels the remnants
of my big prick
But I've set the
shores a little wider
Ironed out the wrinkles
After me you can
take on stallions
Bulls, rams, drakes, St. Bernards
You can stuff toads, bats,
lizards up your rectum
You can shit
arpeggios if you like
Or string a zither
across your navel
I am fucking you, Tania, so
that you'll stay fucked
And if you're afraid of being fucked
publicly, I'll fuck you privately
I'll tear off a few
hairs from your cunt
and paste them on Boris's chin
I will bite into your clitoris and
spit out two franc pieces.
Good morning, boys, I'm
your new professor
Good morning, Monsieur Professor
Now what shall we talk about?
Anybody have anything they
want to talk about?
Poor kids!
Our first subject is
the physiology of...
Love
Let's consider how the
elephants make love
Pachyderms
Although they're pretty heavily built
They get pretty spry when a
male gets a bone on
A bone?
Uh, some animals have
bones in their penis
Hence this expression...
A...bone...on.
Now, happily, according to Gourmont
This bony structure is lost in man
Now, think
what would happen if you had
half the human race walking
around with a bone on
-Good morning, boys
-Good morning, Monsieur Professor
Right. Sit down
Today, we agreed, was "question day"
Fire away, ask anything at all
We'll answer all questions,
but one at a time
Yesterday, you was telling us
about the whale
Yeah.
This noble beast
Has a penis two metres long
That's quite true my boy, and
that's only in repose
And the kangaroo have two?
That's quite right.
It's a double penis
It's one for weekdays and
one for Sundays
Music was the least of my worries
I didn't even think of cunt
so dismal, so chill,
so barren, so grey was it all
Un telegram, Monsieur
Paris
Indian pearl merchant wants lowlife
guide to Paris. Stop.
How about it, Fillmore!
When's the next train to Paris?
-Monsieur?
-Le prochain train, oh never mind
Merci, merci
No, he go...over the wall
In the fullness of night he disappeared
Fillmore, my all, my saviour
Get in here and sit down
Well, where's the pearl merchant?
Am I ready to take him to the haunts
of coot, fern, and fornication?
Well, it's not the old merchant himself
It's his only nephew
What's he looking for in Paris?
Well as far as I can tell,
his wants are simple
Don't you worry though, the old boy's
paying for his "education"
For God's sake, Ranjid, you can't
jump them in the street.
Let's wait 'til we get to Miss Hamilton
This is it, let me tell you
this is really a refined,
high-class joint
Hello, baby
Hello?
Take your pick, you get your choice
You'll feel better when
you've had a drink
Ladies?
I'll take this one
You have good taste, Monsieur
I am sure you will be very
happy together
What?
No, you can't, they'll be offended
If you wish.
-Let us have rooms next door, huh?
-If you must
Yes?!
Henry?
The young lady has gone for her toilet
but where can I go?
Quick, quick!
Tell me before she comes back!
Use the bidet, for Christ's sake!
Thank you!
Oh Madam, I do beg of you
Have you no shame?
You are responsible, to bring
a savage to Miss Hamilton!
One of the most distinguished
bordel of Paris
Hey man, what'd you do?
What did he do?!
Honey, I show you what he do.
Come with me!
Voila! Régal your eyes on that!
Oh, brother
You shouldn't have told me to
I didn't know it wouldn't go down
I asked you where to go and
you told me to use that
Come along. Let us get out of here
For the femme de chambre
I would like to get out of here
Would you like to try another place?
Oh, no, no.
For some reason or other, man
looks for the miracle
And to accomplish it he
will wade through blood
He will debauch himself with ideas
he will reduce himself to a shadow
If only for one second of his life
he can close his eyes
to the hideousness of reality
Everything is endured
Disgrace, humiliation
Poverty, war, crime, ennui
And the belief that, overnight
something will occur
A miracle which will render
life tolerable
So I think what a miracle it would
be if at the last moment
when the banquet table is set,
and the cymbals clash
there should appear, suddenly,
and wholly without warning
a silver platter, on which even
the blind could see
that there's nothing more
and nothing less
than two enormous lumps of shit
When I look down into this
fucked-out cunt of a whore
I feel the whole world beneath me
a world tottering and crumbling
A world used up and polished
like a leper's skull
If there were a man who dared to say
all that he thought of this world
There would not be left him a square
foot of ground to stand on
When a man appears
the world bears down on him
and breaks his back
There are always too many rotten
pillars left standing
for man to bloom
The superstructure is a lie
And the foundation is a
huge, quaking fear
And if at intervals of centuries
there does appear a man with a
desperate, hungry look in his eyes
A man who would turn the
world upside down
in order to create a new race
The love that he brings to the
world is turned to bile.
Wait, wait! I found them,
I found them!
What the hell are you doing?
What's going on?
Stupid bastards wouldn't stop. Look.
Poor old Peckover fell down
the elevator shaft
Eight storeys
They found him crawling around,
crying, looking for these
He couldn't think about anything else
He hasn't finished paying for them yet
And they're quarrelling about who's
going to write the obituary
I think you're next in line for his job!
Hey hey, get up here!
-What's all this? -Don't worry,
my dear, they're friends of mine
First paycheck in four months
Here's to Peckover, he'd
have liked this
Thanks to us, he died
with his teeth in
To Peckover
Now, let's have another bottle of wine!
Oh no! Look at my dress, you stupid
Now you know not to laugh
at French women!
Spirited girl
Yeah
I'd better follow her
But why?
Because I gave her the key
to my place, that's why
And if I don't apologise
she'll be waiting with a broken bottle
See you later, Joe
You know what I love most about Fillmore?
His absolute refusal
to learn from experience
Llona, now, she had a cunt
I know because she sent us
some hairs from down below
Llona
a wild ass snuffing pleasure
out of the wind
On every high hill, she
played the harlot
And sometimes in telephone
booths, and toilets
She used candles
Roman candles and doorknobs
Not a prick in the land big enough
for her, not one
Men went inside her and curled up
She wanted extension pricks,
self-exploding rockets...
...hot boiling oil made of wax
and creosote
She'd cut off your prick and
keep it inside her forever...
...if you gave her permission
One cunt out of a million
Llona
All cunt, and a glass ass
in which you could read the
history of the Middle Ages
How lucky you are to be able to
afford the good things of life
All the bad things happen to me
First, my little baby...
...and now my mother is at home,
very ill
And there's a doctor to pay,
medicines to be bought
I'm always in difficulties for money
Why don't you come over to my hotel,
and you can tell me all about it
Oh, I couldn't do that. I have to
look after my mother
You could come home with me
I have an apartment to myself
It will be peaceful
Ok, let's go
I gotta warn you, I only got 50 francs
50 francs! Come on, you're
surely joking with me
Bye. I made a mistake
You certainly have made a mistake
Ecouter cherie
Be reasonable
Ok. I'll be nice to you, you'll see
You were lying to me, then
Yeah, I was just lying to you
Taxi!
My god, this place is in such a state,
this mother...has been sick
I can't find anything when I want it
No, don't sit there
Come over here, cherie
Oh, this dress. The zip always sticks
Can you?
Never mind. I've done it myself
Now, what are you waiting there for?
Hurry up and get undressed
Have you seen my diploma on the wall?
First-class honours. Mama
had it framed for me
Come on, get undressed, I think you
should hurry, you know
Where's my...mother disappeared to?
I must go to see mother, just a moment
You can have a bath, if you like,
I'll be back in a few minutes
She's going to die! She's going to die!
Oh dear, dear!
If only I had the money for the doctor
Oh yeah, the money
Will you please take this for
your mother? -You're very kind
But...the doctor is very expensive
-Yes, things are rough all over
-Ah, you're right
Come on, move over
Oh, darling!
I'm dying for you
I warn you
Yes, again, it's so beautiful
-Will you slow down? Where's the fire?
-Here, here!
Take it easy
Where's your mother?
Is she downstairs?
I must go and see mother!
Germaine was different
There was nothing to tell me so
from her appearance
But I'd noticed her
verging toward me
with that curious trot-about
air of a whore
and the run-down heels
cheap jewelry and
the pasty look of their kind
In a few minutes, we were in a 5 franc
room on the Rue Amelot
the curtains drawn and the
covers thrown back
But she didn’t rush things,
Germaine
She sat on the bidet
soaping herself and talked to me
pleasantly about this and that
As she stood up to dry herself
still talking to me pleasantly
suddenly, she dropped her towel
and advancing toward me leisurely
she commenced rubbing her
pussy affectionately
stroking it with her two hands,
caressing it, patting it
There was something about her
eloquence at that moment
in the way she thrust that
rosebush under my nose
which remains unforgettable
she spoke of it as if it were
some extraneous object
which she had
acquired at great cost
an object whose value had
increased with time
and which now she prized above
everything in the world
Her words imbued it with a
peculiar fragrance
It was no longer just her private
organ, but a treasure
a magic, potent treasure,
a God-given thing
and none the less so because
she traded it
day in, day out, for a few
pieces of silver
As she flung herself on the bed,
with legs spread wide apart
she cupped it with her hands
and stroked it some more
murmuring all the while in that
hoarse, cracked voice of hers
that it was good
Beautiful
A treasure, a little treasure
And it was good, that little
pussy of hers
That Sunday afternoon, with its poisonous
breath of spring in the air
everything clicked again
As we stepped out of the hotel
I looked her over again in
the harsh light of day
and I saw clearly what a
whore she was
the gold teeth, the rundown heels,
etc., etc.
Even the fact that she had wormed
a dinner out of me...
...and cigarettes and taxi hadn’t the
least disturbing effect upon me
I encouraged it, in fact
I liked her so well
that after dinner we went back
to the hotel again
and took another shot at it
“For love,” this time
And again that big, bushy
thing of hers
worked its bloom and magic
It began to have an independent
existence – for me, too
There was Germaine...
...and there was
that rosebush of hers
I liked them separately
and I liked them together
I don't think this earthy stuff is going
over too well with Irene
I think she's kind of an ethereal cunt
Ethereal or not she's rich,
she should be
worth a little effort at letter writing
Go on, now, where were we?
Rabelais...
"You send me golden apples,
Irene, dear..."
"...and gifts of shaggy chestnuts, too"
She hasn't given you
anything, has she?
No
But I like that word: "shaggy"
"But if you follow them..."
"...the choicest gift you brought
would be just you"
You know, you say that like
you mean it?
Let's hit her with a little
dash of Keats
"Irene! Peerless nymph!"
"Why fear such tenderness as mine?"
Now, wait a minute, this
is the real clincher
"Oh, let me have thee whole,
all, all be mine..."
"...those hands, those eyes,
divine..."
"...that warm, white, lucent,
million-pleasured breast."
Jesus, that'll do it!
Let's pepper it up a bit
No, no, that's too morbid
"Breathes there, man..."
"...with soul so dead..."
"...who to himself hath never said..."
"...when I see Irene, I think of bed."
Oh, it's not the same class!
Besides, it's too pushy
We've got to bring this to
a delicate conclusion
Well, not too delicate, it's about
getting laid, you know
If the lady's any good at all
it's never far from her mind
All you have to do
is let her know
that you know what
she's thinking about
Did you pay your rent?
It's from her
It's from Irene
Well?
A rendezvous
Christ, you think she's watching us?
Come on, Carl, she's not
gonna eat you
Wish you hadn't said that.
Crude bastard
I can't go in yet! What's the time?
I'm two minutes early!
Alright, alright, let's take a
walk around the block
Press button '2'
"The rescue team's been working
throughout the night..."
"...in an effort to reach the 12 miners
trapped since last Tuesday..."
"...in the Alsatian mining disaster."
"Investigation in the cause of disaster
has revealed..."
"...that the collapse was due to faulty...
tit props?"
"...Pit props."
"Messages of consolation have
arrived from the government..."
I'll bet
Yeah
Henry, it's Carl
Look, Henry...Fill in for me
at the office, will you?
Tell the bastard I'm...anything
Tell him I'm dying!
Ok, Carl
-What's happening?
-Hello?
Are you Henry Miller?
How are you?
You sound so nice
Hello, Joe? She likes you
I told her all about you
How we call each other "Joe"
She wants us to call her "Joe" too
Talk to you later, Henry
Ah, you...
...son of a bitch
Help me read through these stock prices
What happened to Carl?
He says he's dying
Oh, so he's dying, is he,
the little prick?
Come on, give me the low-down
on this whole thing, huh?
He went to visit his rich cunt
He actually went to call her?
Where's she live?
Come on, you seem like a decent guy.
Let me in on this racket!
-It's not a racket
-What do you mean?
A little prick like that slips off to
lay a rich, beautiful
hungry cunt, and you
say there's no racket?
Come on, come on!
Will you calm down, I'll tell you
everything
as soon as Carl gives
me the details, ok?
I like Van Norden but I don't agree
with his opinion of himself
He's not a writer, he's just
cunt-struck, that's all
Come on, Carl, you're hanging me
up. Don't torture me, do it later
Now, tell me, was it good or was it bad?
Wait. I'm gonna tell you everything
That means it was a failure
No. It wasn't a failure
And it wasn't a success, either
You know? It's pretty strange
To think of all those letters
we wrote her
And then to find that...
Well...she was in her dressing gown
There was a bottle of champagne
on the dresser
The room was pretty dark
Curtains drawn, not much light
But her voice was lovely
I know that, go on!
It must've been 9 o'clock...
...because I remember I looked at
my watch to check
Well, the next time I looked at
my watch it was 10 o'clock
She was lying on the divan with
her boobies in her hands
At 11 o'clock it was all settled
We were going to run away, to Borneo!
Didn't she have a husband or something?
Ah, fuck the husband, she
never loved him anyway
She never would've
written that first letter
if the husband hadn't
been old and passionless
And when she says to me...
"...but listen dear"
"How do I know you won't
grow tired of me?"
Ah, what'd you say?
-What do you expect me to say?
"How could anyone ever grow
tired of you?"
Carl, you're the cutest,
what happened then?
I don't know...
Oh, I kissed her breasts a lot,
she seemed to go for that
But then I got sort of tired of them
staring me in the face
So I stuffed them back in her corsage,
or whatever they call those things
Wasn't that a step backwards?
No!
They get hotter if they think
you're cooling off
So, then we had another
coupe of champagne
Ah, there I was, all the time
sitting with my semi-colons wondering
whether I could...
...afford to go the can for five minutes
And I'm dying to take a leak!
I had one hard-on
But it faded out
I grab hold of her hand
I pull her to her feet, and I start
walking her to the door
I tell her I love her, I adore her
I'll go anywhere she says, Istanbul,
Singapore, you name it
...only just now I must go,
it's getting late
Carl, you didn't even tell me
whether she's beautiful
A woman with a voice like that?
When I talked to her on the
phone, I was stunned
I wanted to say one true thing to
her, no matter how silly
after all that crap we wrote her
Was she beautiful?
She had a streak of grey hair
across her forehead
I remember that
You see, I'd almost forgotten it
But it was her arms
They were thin
They were thin, and...
...brittle
If she wrote me ten years younger,
I might overlook the streak of grey hair
And even the brittle arms
But she's too old
You see...
...with a cunt like that
every year counts now
She won't just be one year
older next year
she'll be ten years older
In another year, she'll be
twenty years older
I'll be getting younger looking
all the time
At least for another five years
How did it end?
That's just it, it didn't end
I promised to meet her Tuesday
Oh, and that's not all
I promised to write her a letter
in the meantime
How am I going to write her a letter now?
I haven't got anything to say
Oh, shit
If she were only ten years younger
Listen...
Do you think I ought to go with her?
To Borneo, or wherever it is
she wants to take me?
I don't know how to shoot
I'm afraid of guns and all
that sort of thing
Besides, she'll want me to fuck
her night and day
Nothing but humping and
fucking all the time
I can't do it!
She said she was turning forty
That means fifty
Or sixty
It'd be like fucking your own mother
Well, she must've had something, you were
kissing her breasts, for Christ's sake
Kissing her breasts, what's that?
Besides it was dark, I'm telling you
Look at that. It's coming apart,
the goddamn suit
I'm coming apart
Irene is certainly coming apart
You can forgive a young cunt anything
She doesn't have to have any brains
They're better off without any brains
But an old cunt...
See, an old cunt,
even if she's brilliant
Even if she's the most charming woman
in the world
nothing makes any difference
A young cunt is an investment
An old cunt is a dead loss
All they can do for you is
buy you things
With you, it's different
You don't have to lay her, you can
afford to like her
Maybe you would like her!
Listen, if she's rich I'll like her,
I don't care how old she is
As long as she's not a hag
She's not a hag
What are you talking about?
If that's how it is, I'll fuck her
Ah, if you don't want to. Tell her that.
You be subtle about it, though
Perhaps...
We'll go to Borneo together
I don't know how to shoot either,
that doesn't matter, we'll-
We'll drive, we'll hunt,
wear nice things
You know if we go to Borneo
I won't have hemorrhoids anymore
Maybe I'll develop something else
Something worse
Cholera, do you think?
Ah listen, it's better to die of a good
disease like that, than to
piss your life away on a newspaper,
with grapes up your ass
and buttons falling off your pants
What would you rather do? Be a cripple
all your life or have a job?
Or marry a rich cunt?
Ah, you'd rather marry a rich
cunt, I can see that
Supposing you married her
and then you couldn't get a
hard-on anymore?
Oh, that happens sometimes!
What would you do then?
No, the best thing would be to marry her
and then get a good disease right away
You wouldn't have to worry
about laying her
and you wouldn't have to worry
about the rent either!
That's the best solution for a writer
Listen...
All I want is a good wheelchair
and three meals a day
Then I'd give them something to
read, those pricks
Well. What happened to you?
You should've stayed around for a Pernod
Carl talked about that dame,
Irene, for two solid hours
I could use a Pernod now
I was out looking for Fillmore
Fillmore's been taken to a funny
farm outside Paris
I wonder if that guy's putting us on?
That girlfriend of his gave me
the address
It's around somewhere
But Carl now
That guy's an artist
He described every detail, minutely
He gave it to me with such accuracy
I know the whole goddamn
thing is a lie
But I can't get it out of my mind
You know how my mind works
He told you the whole story,
didn't he?
What do you think, you
think he made it up?
I think he invented the
whole thing just to torture me
I don't care about that
I don't care if the whole thing
is a lie from start to finish
it's the images that get me
I didn't sleep a wink for
thinking of it. -No?
Yeah
Just like that guy to tell me he put
it to her six or seven times
Yeah, well that's a lot of shit
The way he tells me, that she rented a
carriage and drove him to the Bois
and used her husband's fur
coat for a blanket?
That's too much!
I suppose he told you about
the chauffeur
how the chauffeur waited patiently?
And, listen...
...did he tell about how the
motor purred all the time?
He's such a cute little liar, you
can't walk away from him
You know, I don't understand how
a guy writes letters like that
I don't get the mentality behind it
I think it's a kind of masturbation,
what do you think?
I suppose he told you the whole
thing, huh?
Did he tell you about, how he stood
in the moonlight on the balcony
and he kissed her?
-Yeah
-But the way that boy described it
I can just see that little prick standing
there with his arms around a woman
And already he's writing her
another one of those letters
About the rooftops and all that crap
he steals from his French authors
That guy never said a thing
that's original, I found that out
But you have to get a clue
to whom he's been reading lately
And that's damn hard to do
because he's so damn secretive
It's the way he tells it to me
You know how he embroiders things
After that scene on the balcony,
you know
he sort of gives me that like
an hors d'ouvres
Well, after that scene on the balcony
so he says, they went inside and he
unbuttoned her pyjamas
What're you smiling for, was
he shitting me about that?
No, he told me just the
same way you're telling me
Oh. Well, after that, he says
She sitting in a chair, with her
legs up, not a stitch on
He's down on the floor looking up at her
and telling her how beautiful she is
Did he tell you how she looked
like a Matisse?
What I'm getting at, is that moment
when he said he was down on his knees
and with his two skinny little fingers
he spreads her cunt open. Remember that?
He said she was sitting
there in the chair
with her legs dangling over the edge
when he suddenly gets this inspiration
You know, that's after he's already
given her a couple of lays
and given her a little spiel about
the Matisse, but
now, get this
with these two fingers, just
the tips of them, mind you
he spread the little petals open
Squish, squish
Just like that, a little sticky
sound, almost inaudible
Squish, squish
Jesus, I've been hearing it all day
And then, if that wasn't enough for me,
he said he buried his head in her muff
And then, by Christ, if she doesn't
swing her legs around his neck!
When he told me that, oh boy,
that finished me
Can you imagine?
A fine sensitive woman like that swinging
her legs around his neck
It's poisonous!
It's so fantastic it's almost believable
Sounds pretty incredible
Still, you never can tell with
a little prick like that
I suppose anything can happen
Maybe he didn't fuck her at all
Maybe she just let him diddle her?
Well, you never can tell with
these rich cunts
you know, what they might
expect you to do
Well, I better go see Fillmore
It's all over, Joe
They say I'm crazy
Fuck 'em
They say I may have syphilis too
They say I've got delusions of grandeur
What did they put me in this
expensive room for, huh?
Why don't they put me in the ward?
Or in the bughouse!
I can't afford this
I'm down to my last 500 dollars
That's why they got you here, pal
When you run out of dough, they'll
move you out of here quick enough,
don't worry about it
Here, hold onto these for me
They'll rob me of everything I've got
I know
I know you think I'm crazy, but
I want to atone for what I did
I want to get married
I didn't know I had the clap!
See, I gave her the clap, and
I knocked her up
I don't care what happens, but
I'm going to marry her first
He keeps telling me to wait
until I get better
But I'm not going to get
better, Joe, this is the end
Come on, Joe
I'm dying, Joe
And Ginette?
Who's gonna take care of her?
Who's gonna take care of her
after I'm gone?
After you're gone?
You can take care of her
You're healthy
Joe? Would you take care of her?
Ah, easy boy, easy
Would you? For me
Where does she live?
You're a good guy, Joe
That's right, I am.
Where's she living?
Somewhere in the sixth floor
Everyone in Paris lives on the
sixth or seventh floor
so by the time you get up
there, you're incapable
They're all in on it
Yeah
Sixth floor. Where?
365 Rue La Bos
Ok, look
I'll find the girl, hold her hand,
explain everything
Now don't worry about anything.
just lay back, eat your oranges
you know they might be charging
you rent for them
Ginette?
Sit down, please
And you think he keeps his position
when he leaves hospital?
Oh, his job you mean. I suppose so
You speak good English, Ginette
We were pulled together by
common tongues
That must've been nice
But I beg of you, tell me what you think
Jo-Jo want to marry me, he say that
But if he does not...
...you know, a young
girl, in a delicate condition
And with the other thing, besides
If he leaves me, what I'm going to do?
There
Fillmore is a perfect gentleman
He's thinking about you all the time
I'm certain he's gonna stand by you
I'll be the godfather to
the child, how's that?
Oh, you are so good
All the same...
...are you certain you want this child?
If you have this condition you spoke
of, it might be born blind
Don't say such things!
It doesn't make any difference to me
I want a child of my Jo-Jo
Are you alright?
Oh yes
I was thinking of
Jo-Jo and me in the bed
How we did fight
You know, he likes to fight with me
He was a brute!
Oh, do you want some cheese?
Here is my friend, Yvette
-Monsieur Henry, the friend of Jo-Jo
-Enchanté, monsieur
Yvette makes a job
of national importance
She is a spy for the police
Oh god
Come on, what does she actually do?
I regulate the inspection of the ladies
Sounds like pretty essential work
I take you to work in taxi
I just change my robe, and I
come with you
Ginette is a whore
And she has no baby, neither
Maybe she has the clap,
yes, but she isn't pregnant
Well why the hell does she want to
marry him? Does she love him?
She wants someone to take care of her
No frenchman would marry
her, she has a long police record
But if she can marry a rich American...!
Henry? You write your address
and leave it on the table
I'm with you in a moment
There's the address. I've got
a bed at Boris's
Good morning
Who are you?
Hands off, Joe. Elsa's staying a few
days to lend tone to the business
She's gonna show people in when
they come to see the apartment
You want some breakfast?
I have some hot croissant and jam
Now, don't give him breakfast,
it'll encourage him to stay
He's been here long enough
Why don't you move in with
Fillmore again?
I hear they let him out of the nut-hatch
Fillmore will probably be
living with Ginette
and I wouldn't want to disturb
a happy couple
That hasn't worried you up 'til now
Straighten the place up a little
Artistic disorder is ok but
this is ridiculous
He needs a woman
"My..."
"...dear..."
"...Walter"
"Today..."
"...my heart..."
"...is filled..."
"...with sorrow"
Lieber Got!
What's happened to the world?
Aw, let me help
I have no luck, no luck never
I try to write to my lover,
so far away
and what's happened?
The typewriter jams
Oh, poor girl, poor Elsa
I am so sad. So sad
Ah, the Germans!
They take you all
over like an omnibus
They give you indigestion
In the same night, one cannot
visit the morgue, the infirmary...
...the zoo, the signs
of the zodiac...
...the limbos of philosophy,
the caves of epistemology...
...the arcana of
Freud and Stekel.
On the merry-go-round
one doesn't get anywhere...
...whereas with the Germans,
one can go from Vega to Lope de Vega
all in one night and come
away as foolish as Parsifal.
Always the same
Always
Men use me...
...and cast me aside
You know, if you can play
the piano like this
you should have better sense than
to let yourself be tripped up
by every guy with a big putz who just
happened to come along
But what can I do?
I like it
And this is the living room
I can see that
Henry
Hey Fillmore, you old nut!
They let him out, huh?
-Yeah, I'm fine now
-He looks good now, eh, my fiance?
I see you're on the move again, huh?
Yeah, Boris kicked me out
I've gotta find a hotel tonight
You know, unless I can find
someplace to stay
Ginette, why don't you go do some
shopping. Yeah, it'll be alright
We'll be right there at the cafe, ok?
Come on
Have another, I don't care
It's her father's money
My job's gone and we're supposed to get
married in a month or so
Oh, once they get me properly
in their clutches
I'll be nothing but a slave
Ok
First you get married,
then you get divorced
Meanwhile she'll be dropping the kid
Who's gonna take care of it, huh?
Hey fella, some girls are naturally
fat around the middle
Yvette told me that Ginette's
not pregnant
What do you mean?
I know she's gonna have a kid alright,
I felt it kicking around inside of her
That Yvette's a dirty little slut
You see, Joe, I didn't want to
admit this to you, but...
...before I went to the hospital,
I was putting out for Yvette too
Then when the crack up came I couldn't
I mean, I felt like I'd done enough
for both of them, right?
No, no, that Yvette's just...
sore at me, that's all
Boy, I wish it were true
I could get out of this more easily
They've got me by the balls now
God, here she comes again
That's ok, honey
We're just having a little drink
on your father
Drink, my father?
My father never drink!
No honey, that's...
He's trying to explain that the fact is
your old man's paying for these drinks
So, now I'm not understanding
English, eh?
Is that incredible? -Pal, how do you
work yourself into these situations?
You're laughing
You make fun of me
You mock at your fiancée with strangers
-Ginette, don't be stupid
-How I stupid?!
Ginette. I want you to just-
Yeah, that'll teach you how to behave
Come on
Fuck you!
Go home!
Why?
Today I awoke from a sound sleep
with curses of joy on my lips
with gibberish on my tongue,
repeating to myself like a litany
“Fay ce que vouldras!”
Do anything, but
let it produce joy
let it yield ecstasy
So much crowds into my head
when I say this to myself
Images, gay ones,
terrible ones, maddening ones
The wolf and the goat
Syphilis with her
wings outstretched
and the door of the womb
always on the latch
Always open, ready, like the tomb
Lust, crime, holiness
The lives of my adored ones
The failures of my adored ones,
the words they left behind them
The words they left unfinished
But...above all...
...the ecstasy
Hey!
What's the matter with you?
I have a half hour to go to
the bank, and no more
She keeps tabs on me
Come on, let's have a drink. Come on.
I just don't know what to do anymore
You're gonna have to do something
for me, Henry, I'm helpless
She won't let me out of her sight!
The French
You know, I used to rave about them,
but that was all literature
I know what they're really like
They're cruel, and mercenary, and mean
There's no sympathy, no friendship
The most selfish people on earth
They think of nothing but
money, money, money
And so goddamn respectable and
bourgouis, that's what drives me nuts
Oh sure, I hate those puritanical
bastards back home
I hate them as much as you do, but
I'm one of them myself
I don't belong here
I'm sick of it
Look here, Fillmore
What is it you really wanna do?
I'd like to be home with my people
I'd like to hear English spoken
Listen, if that's what you really
want to do, why don't you do it?
Why don't you go?
I'd go today
Yes, by Jesus, I'd go today without
even saying goodbye to her
That money at the bank...
Is that her Father's money or
is it yours? -That's mine
My mother sent it to me
I don't want any of her goddamn money
Suppose we hop in a cab, we
go right down there
you check out every last cent
This afternoon you hop a train to London
In London, you catch the
first boat for America
You can't go back and get any of
your things
Let her keep them
See, in that French mind of hers
she'll never suspect you scooted
off without bag or baggage
No Frenchman would ever dream
of doing a thing like that
unless he's as cracked as you are
Here. That's every bit of it
The closer you get to New York the more
this'll seem just like a bad dream
What are you gonna tell her?
Don't worry about what I'm gonna
tell her. I'm gonna tell her
The important thing is, how much
you wanna give her?
All of it
Why give her anything?
-Oh Joe
-Ok, let's give her this French money
That should hold her for a while
How much is it?
She has two or three thousand francs
there, that's more than she deserves
Christ, will you don't say that,
Joe, please!
I mean, it's a lousy, rotten deal
I'm giving her, you know
She'll never be able to go back
to her parents
Give it all to her, give her the whole
damn thing, I don't care what it is
Stop!
Hey, you can't do that, it's too late
You know what, you're gonna
go get on that train
You can't go back there now.
It's settled
I just don't want her to kill
herself, that's all
Kill herself?! Not her
As far as the money's concerned,
don't worry
Though I hate to give it to her, I'll go right
to the Post Office and I'll telegraph it
Here, send her a postcard,
tell her you're sailing
Tell her you love her, go on
I'll see her tonight, don't worry,
it's gonna be great, you'll see
Hurry up, the train's leaving, let's go
Henry! Bye, Henry!
Bye!
Cab!
Suddenly it occurs to me that, if I
want, I can go to America myself
It's the first time the opportunity's
ever presented itself
My thoughts drift out toward the
sea, toward the other side
where, taking a last look back, I had
seen the skyscrapers
fading out in a
flurry of snowflakes
I see them looming up again, in the
same ghostly way as when I left
see the lights creeping
through their ribs
I see the whole city spread
out, from Harlem to the Battery
The streets choked with ants,
the theatres empty
I wonder, in a vague way, whatever
happened to my wife
After everything quietly sifted
through my head
a great peace came over me
Here, where the river gently winds
through the girdle of the hills
lies a soil so
saturated with the past
That however far back the mind roams,
one can never detach it
from its human background
Christ
Before my eyes, there shimmers
such a golden peace
that only a neurotic could dream
of turning his head away
So quietly flows the Seine, that one
hardly notices its presence
It is always there,
quiet and unobtrusive
like a great artery running through
the human body
In the wonderful peace that
falls over me
it seems as if I'd climbed to the
top of a high mountain
For a little while I will be able to
look around me
to take in the meaning
of the landscape
Human beings make a
strange fauna and flora
From a distance, they
appear negligible
Close up, they're apt to appear
ugly and malicious
More than anything they need to be
surrounded with sufficient space
Space even more than time
The sun is setting
I feel this river
flowing through me
Its past, its ancient soil
The changing climate
The hills gently girdle it about
Its course is fixed.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org